<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="eZ8kvS8Sd98" uploader="Tourist to Local" channel="Tourist to Local" likes="1785" title="48 HOURS in Madrid (Spain's GORGEOUS Capital!) 🇪🇸 Things to Do + Eat!" year="2025" month="5" day="6" date="20250506" is_ac="true">
  <u t="3840">Madrid, the center of Spain,</u>
  <u t="6200">geographically, politically, culturally.</u>
  <u t="9360">This week, we want to learn about what</u>
  <u t="10800">it really means to be a Madrileno. We</u>
  <u t="13440">want to experience the palaces, the</u>
  <u t="15679">plazas, the football, the hone. This is</u>
  <u t="19520">eating good. This is sitting good. Thank</u>
  <u t="21840">you, Madrid. But Madrid is not a new</u>
  <u t="24080">place for me. The last time I came here,</u>
  <u t="25840">it was 2007 on a family vacation. My</u>
  <u t="28400">hair was bigger and my suitcase was half</u>
  <u t="31760">Albert Comry polos. And I have never</u>
  <u t="34079">been to a Spanish-sp speakaking country</u>
  <u t="35920">outside of my home country of Mexico.</u>
  <u t="38000">And this place surprised me in the way</u>
  <u t="39840">it felt like home, but also slightly</u>
  <u t="42160">different in the weirdest ways. The</u>
  <u t="44480">different words they use like botros,</u>
  <u t="46480">the food, and how delicious it all was.</u>
  <u t="48879">I was hooked. Now I'm back years later</u>
  <u t="51280">and I've got a big question on my mind.</u>
  <u t="53440">Has Madrid changed?</u>
  <u t="59840">Good morning, travelers. We made it to</u>
  <u t="62559">Spain. You guys have been asking for</u>
  <u t="64720">this series for I don't even know how</u>
  <u t="66880">long. I know it's early. Madrid is</u>
  <u t="69520">waking up and we're also waking up and</u>
  <u t="71920">we're going to start this journey over</u>
  <u t="73360">here in Plaza Dol. This is supposed to</u>
  <u t="75840">be a 72-hour guide to Madrid. But</u>
  <u t="78240">yesterday we had some flight</u>
  <u t="79600">complications and now we have to do</u>
  <u t="81520">everything we want to see here in 48</u>
  <u t="83680">hours. So, high plaza and by plaza</u>
  <u t="87360">because I have some churros I'm</u>
  <u t="89600">desperately wanting to eat right now.</u>
  <u t="91280">Let's go to get some Madrid breakfast</u>
  <u t="94640">[Music]</u>
  <u t="105720">priorities.</u>
  <u t="109000">Okay.</u>
  <u t="112360">Any day that we can start with churros</u>
  <u t="115040">is going to be a good day. This has been</u>
  <u t="117200">the meal I've been most excited for in</u>
  <u t="119840">our nine-part series here in Europe. The</u>
  <u t="122719">smell in this place is incredible. A lot</u>
  <u t="125119">of people come to Madrid and they do</u>
  <u t="126479">churros and chocolate elsewhere at a</u>
  <u t="129200">very popular place. But this place is</u>
  <u t="131680">super underrated. It's been familyowned</u>
  <u t="134800">generations. This chocolate looks like</u>
  <u t="137760">they've just taken a chocolate bar and</u>
  <u t="140400">just melted it and served it to me. I'm</u>
  <u t="142640">so excited to try this. And according to</u>
  <u t="144640">Martine, you can dip them. So, no, you</u>
  <u t="148480">must you must dip them. I've never done</u>
  <u t="150720">that with a churro, so I'm very</u>
  <u t="152760">excited. Wo!</u>
  <u t="156720">That is some thick</u>
  <u t="160360">chocolate. Holy Toledo. This is amazing.</u>
  <u t="164560">Do we have breakfast plans tomorrow?</u>
  <u t="167290">[Music]</u>
  <u t="168560">We do. Ah, dang it. I want to come back</u>
  <u t="171280">here. Maybe before we leave, before we</u>
  <u t="173200">go on the plane. It's so good. We needed</u>
  <u t="175760">to order more, guys, because that's too</u>
  <u t="178160">little for great chocolate. And we</u>
  <u t="181280">ordered these ones. These ones, they</u>
  <u t="182560">don't call it churro. They call it</u>
  <u t="183920">pores. It's fine to me. It's like a</u>
  <u t="186800">churot churote churote.</u>
  <u t="190730">[Music]</u>
  <u t="196239">Which ones are better? Really? Dang it.</u>
  <u t="200800">I ate almost that whole plate. This</u>
  <u t="202640">one's because I think the chocolate</u>
  <u t="204480">tastes more over there and it's less</u>
  <u t="206560">crunching, but it's good for the</u>
  <u t="208000">chocolate. Oh, interesting. Mhm. It's</u>
  <u t="209760">safe to say that Cheria Chocolaria 1902</u>
  <u t="212799">is definitely underrated. But our next</u>
  <u t="215280">stop, well, no one's missing it. This is</u>
  <u t="217599">where Madrid puts its biggest moments on</u>
  <u t="219680">display. This one, this plaza right now</u>
  <u t="221680">it's called Plaza Mayor, but it has been</u>
  <u t="223840">called different names. Plaza de la</u>
  <u t="225440">Raal, Plaza realal, Plaza de la</u>
  <u t="228239">Constitution, Plaza de la Republica. So</u>
  <u t="231599">many, many names. So this is nice</u>
  <u t="233519">because normally there's a lot of people</u>
  <u t="234959">sitting over here so you cannot see</u>
  <u t="236319">this, but it tells you the story about</u>
  <u t="238640">this place. It used to be bull fighting</u>
  <u t="240959">over here. Also, they tell you the story</u>
  <u t="243920">about the different fires in this in</u>
  <u t="246000">this plaza. This one for instance is in</u>
  <u t="249319">1790. Uh the name of the</u>
  <u t="252599">architecta and there was also trials</u>
  <u t="256560">over here but also carnivals. So it's a</u>
  <u t="260239">very important plaza for the history of</u>
  <u t="261680">Madrid. It's very good that we have to</u>
  <u t="263759">see this before it's completely full of</u>
  <u t="265840">people. There is something I was always</u>
  <u t="267680">curious about in Madrid. I heard rumors</u>
  <u t="269840">about cookies made from nuns in a 17th</u>
  <u t="273040">century monastery called Monasterio the</u>
  <u t="275440">corpos Christi. So, of course, we have</u>
  <u t="277680">to find it out if it was real.</u>
  <u t="281520">Where are you taking us?</u>
  <u t="284720">Get some candies. Julina had questions.</u>
  <u t="287440">Fair ones because yeah, there's no one</u>
  <u t="290240">else over here. And telling her I saw on</u>
  <u t="292560">the internet we can buy sweets in this</u>
  <u t="294880">completely empty monastery does sounds</u>
  <u t="297280">like a good plot for a horror movie. But</u>
  <u t="299759">you need to trust me here. This is so</u>
  <u t="303919">strange.</u>
  <u t="306890">[Music]</u>
  <u t="308440">What? You can buy this here in this</u>
  <u t="310960">church? Definitely. There's no one</u>
  <u t="313120">working here.</u>
  <u t="315900">[Music]</u>
  <u t="324199">What? Today, we'll be buying the cookies</u>
  <u t="326800">without being face to face with anyone.</u>
  <u t="329199">Instead, we'll use this wooden turn</u>
  <u t="331039">style to buy what they call gayas de</u>
  <u t="333280">conventto.</u>
  <u t="337680">That has to be the craziest way I've</u>
  <u t="340320">ever bought cookies in my life. Martin,</u>
  <u t="342800">and look at that. We got the whole box</u>
  <u t="344800">to take home with us. What kind do we</u>
  <u t="346639">even get? I was so swept up in the</u>
  <u t="348080">moment. It's almond. Oh my gosh, that's</u>
  <u t="349759">going to be so good. We're going to try</u>
  <u t="351520">these. But the thing is is we're</u>
  <u t="353759">cramming 3 days worth of eating into</u>
  <u t="355919">two. So, I think we're just going to</u>
  <u t="357600">take it home as a souvenir. Definitely.</u>
  <u t="359680">But that was a great experience. Yeah,</u>
  <u t="361919">super cool. Across town is our next</u>
  <u t="364080">spot. So, we hop the metro and head to</u>
  <u t="366319">Park Delverro. Once a royal playground</u>
  <u t="368720">for King Philip IV, now it's one of the</u>
  <u t="370800">few places where Madrid actually slows</u>
  <u t="373039">down. There's 15,000 trees, 350 acres,</u>
  <u t="377120">and these cute little boats and ducks</u>
  <u t="378800">that made us forget for a minute that</u>
  <u t="380319">we're in the middle of a capital city.</u>
  <u t="383590">[Music]</u>
  <u t="393199">When we were planning Madrid, this was</u>
  <u t="395759">over there in our plans. But then when</u>
  <u t="397840">we knew we needed to shorten to 48</u>
  <u t="400560">hours, we said, "Ah, we cannot put</u>
  <u t="402639">this." Yeah. So, we weren't supposed to</u>
  <u t="405039">be here. But guess what? When you have a</u>
  <u t="407039">fire under your butt to get things</u>
  <u t="408800">moving, sometimes you end up doing</u>
  <u t="410800">things faster than you expected. So, we</u>
  <u t="413039">had a little spot because we can't keep</u>
  <u t="415280">eating food. We We're still full from</u>
  <u t="417120">the churros and we're very glad we're</u>
  <u t="418880">here because it looks amazing. Even</u>
  <u t="420639">though I think the biggest attraction of</u>
  <u t="423360">this park that is the Crystal Palace is</u>
  <u t="425919">closed, still is a beautiful place to</u>
  <u t="428000">be. The cemetery, the people on their</u>
  <u t="430400">little boats and the ducks and the</u>
  <u t="432639">little pond over here, the school kids</u>
  <u t="435280">walking by. Yeah. People walking their</u>
  <u t="437280">dogs. It's a beautiful, beautiful</u>
  <u t="439440">morning. And I'm very grateful I'm alive</u>
  <u t="443039">to see this beautiful park. That was</u>
  <u t="445199">really sweet, honey. It's a It's a I</u>
  <u t="447599">think it's a nice time to be alive over</u>
  <u t="449280">here in Madrid in a morning like this.</u>
  <u t="451120">It is. I agree. Okay, enough being</u>
  <u t="454160">sentimental. We're hungry again. And</u>
  <u t="456080">when lunchtime hits in Madrid, there's</u>
  <u t="458240">only one place you got to go. Marcado</u>
  <u t="460880">San Miguel. This place has been around</u>
  <u t="462639">for over a century, but it wasn't like</u>
  <u t="464960">this last time I was here. For a while,</u>
  <u t="467360">it was falling apart and was almost</u>
  <u t="469280">demolished entirely. But in 2009, it</u>
  <u t="472319">came back to life, and now it's one of</u>
  <u t="474160">the best examples of Madrid's revival</u>
  <u t="476400">and a good place to eat. Oh my god, that</u>
  <u t="478720">looks like something I want. Oh my god,</u>
  <u t="480400">it smells so good in here. And we're</u>
  <u t="482319">hungry, so that's the perfect</u>
  <u t="483360">combination. Oh my gosh, we're like 5 ft</u>
  <u t="486479">in and we already have three places on</u>
  <u t="488960">our definitely want that list. I know.</u>
  <u t="492000">Probably we're going to find more.</u>
  <u t="498720">We get a lot of things here like this</u>
  <u t="500960">sampler of various tortillas from a</u>
  <u t="502879">stand called Picolisto and this monster</u>
  <u t="505199">of a tapa at mozzarella bar. This place</u>
  <u t="507280">is the epitome of girl dinner and I love</u>
  <u t="511039">it. Lots of just little things to snack</u>
  <u t="513680">on. But I am eyeing this bad</u>
  <u t="516760">boy. Look at all this baratha cheese.</u>
  <u t="520399">When I saw this, I knew immediately I</u>
  <u t="522719">was going to inhale this in about 15</u>
  <u t="524320">seconds flat. It looks so good. It's my</u>
  <u t="526560">favorite. This one, it's called the</u>
  <u t="528320">Martin because it has it's not called</u>
  <u t="530959">like that, but I name it like that</u>
  <u t="532560">because it has everything that Martin</u>
  <u t="534000">likes. Olive, dried tomato, cheese,</u>
  <u t="536959">pickle. Come on. I'm going to start</u>
  <u t="539040">doing this whenever I watching football</u>
  <u t="540480">at home. Yeah. Honestly, I don't even</u>
  <u t="542240">know how to eat this. Oh, it's going to</u>
  <u t="544000">fall. Okay.</u>
  <u t="546800">Oh my god. There's like this sweet</u>
  <u t="549519">tomato jam on top and so much bara. They</u>
  <u t="552959">know me. This is like an entire bara</u>
  <u t="555360">portion in one bite. So good. I'm going</u>
  <u t="558240">to try this. And for a Mexican like</u>
  <u t="560080">myself, I have to tell you the tortilla</u>
  <u t="562640">here is very different because it's made</u>
  <u t="564399">of potato and eggs like the one at</u>
  <u t="568760">home. The bread is toasted and then the</u>
  <u t="572240">tortilla patata is not well done, which</u>
  <u t="574560">I like. And you don't mean not well done</u>
  <u t="576560">like bad. You mean not like super</u>
  <u t="578640">completely cooked. Exactly. That's the</u>
  <u t="580399">way it has to be. And also on top it was</u>
  <u t="582240">like a little sauce. I thought it was</u>
  <u t="583760">tomato, but no, it was a little spicy,</u>
  <u t="586560">which I love. Now, don't tell the other</u>
  <u t="588800">countries or the other cities. But for</u>
  <u t="590800">me personally, Madrid is in the top five</u>
  <u t="593440">cities in the entire world where you eat</u>
  <u t="595600">the best. It's amazing. It's amazing.</u>
  <u t="597920">It's amazing. You know what I'm saying?</u>
  <u t="598880">And I'm enjoying I'm in heaven right</u>
  <u t="600720">now. Now, one of the biggest things we</u>
  <u t="602640">were warned about before coming to Spain</u>
  <u t="604480">was pickpocketing, especially in Madrid</u>
  <u t="606560">and Barcelona. Every local we met had a</u>
  <u t="609279">story. And once you've been in a crowded</u>
  <u t="611120">market like this, you get it. So, some</u>
  <u t="613200">tips we always tell our viewers. Keep</u>
  <u t="614720">your phone in zip pockets. Use cross</u>
  <u t="616880">body bags and keep them on you at all</u>
  <u t="618959">times. And turn your backpacks to the</u>
  <u t="620959">front in busy areas. But here's</u>
  <u t="622720">something nobody talks about. Digital</u>
  <u t="625760">pick pocketing. Today's video is brought</u>
  <u t="627600">to you by NordVPN, who keeps us safe</u>
  <u t="629839">online while we travel. Because just</u>
  <u t="631680">like someone can reach into your pocket</u>
  <u t="633040">in real life, someone can reach into</u>
  <u t="634800">your device on an open network and grab</u>
  <u t="637200">your passwords, banking details, even</u>
  <u t="639519">your location. We've been guilty of</u>
  <u t="641279">clicking any free Wi-Fi we find. But</u>
  <u t="643360">sometimes that Wi-Fi is a little too</u>
  <u t="645279">free. But it's not just cafes. Even</u>
  <u t="647680">hotel Wi-Fi or airport networks can be</u>
  <u t="649920">risky, especially whenever you're</u>
  <u t="652000">booking flights or checking your bank</u>
  <u t="653760">account. that data is just floating</u>
  <u t="655920">around for anybody to grab it if you're</u>
  <u t="658160">not protected. That's why we never log</u>
  <u t="660079">into public Wi-Fi anymore without a VPN.</u>
  <u t="662320">We use NordVPN because it keeps</u>
  <u t="664160">everything encrypted, even if the Wi-Fi</u>
  <u t="666399">isn't. And it's not just about safety.</u>
  <u t="668560">When we're abroad, websites sometimes</u>
  <u t="670480">block access just because we're not in</u>
  <u t="672240">our home country, like airline sites</u>
  <u t="674160">showing different prices or even our</u>
  <u t="676000">favorite streaming networks not working.</u>
  <u t="677839">With NordVPN, we can switch our location</u>
  <u t="679920">and use the internet like we're back</u>
  <u t="681519">home. So, yeah, if you're traveling,</u>
  <u t="683760">we're remote, stream content, or you</u>
  <u t="685760">want peace of mind when you hop online,</u>
  <u t="687519">NordVPN is what you need. Go to</u>
  <u t="690680">nordvpn.com/local for a 2-year plan,</u>
  <u t="692880">plus four extra months at a huge</u>
  <u t="694880">discount risk-free with Nord's 30-day</u>
  <u t="697279">guarantee. Madrid is a funny city</u>
  <u t="699680">because there's a lot of little details</u>
  <u t="701920">that you can find on top of the doors,</u>
  <u t="704959">on top of the buildings, you know,</u>
  <u t="706640">there's there's certain things. You</u>
  <u t="708399">really have to look it up for those</u>
  <u t="710079">those kind of details that makes this</u>
  <u t="712959">city special. For example, over on Grand</u>
  <u t="715600">Via, Madrid's central hub for shopping</u>
  <u t="717760">and Broadway shows, you'll find some</u>
  <u t="719440">pretty crazy details if you just look</u>
  <u t="721200">up, like this statue of a Roman goddess</u>
  <u t="723440">shooting down a phoenix on the other</u>
  <u t="724959">side of the street. And if you look</u>
  <u t="726639">down, the pavement below actually has a</u>
  <u t="729120">print of the arrows, too. It's fun stuff</u>
  <u t="731519">like these that made me love this place</u>
  <u t="733200">whenever I first visited. And speaking</u>
  <u t="735040">of fun, I know a neighborhood for that.</u>
  <u t="737600">We decided to move over to Lacha. This</u>
  <u t="740560">is a neighborhood you want to party. Let</u>
  <u t="742560">me tell you that we are not very party</u>
  <u t="745000">people. At least not anymore.</u>
  <u t="748959">So, we are here just exploring and</u>
  <u t="751200">finding a place to</u>
  <u t="753550">[Music]</u>
  <u t="766279">eat. I remember when I came here with my</u>
  <u t="768959">family a lot of years ago, this</u>
  <u t="771360">neighborhood, it looked so different. It</u>
  <u t="773680">had a lot of personality and definitely</u>
  <u t="775680">it changed through the years. Yeah.</u>
  <u t="777720">Unfortunately, you know, I think this</u>
  <u t="779600">neighborhood is for someone. It just</u>
  <u t="782000">maybe isn't for us anymore. And that</u>
  <u t="783839">could be largely due to the fact that we</u>
  <u t="785760">have traveled to a lot of neighborhoods</u>
  <u t="787519">like this recently through our travels.</u>
  <u t="789680">You know, the gentrified neighborhood of</u>
  <u t="791760">the city. There's lots of coffee shops</u>
  <u t="794079">here and lots of cute bars. So, it's</u>
  <u t="795839">definitely a good place to pass by those</u>
  <u t="797680">hours before dinner. But other than</u>
  <u t="800399">that, is it worth going out of your way</u>
  <u t="802079">to go through here? I don't necessarily</u>
  <u t="803760">think so. H Yeah, exactly. As you said,</u>
  <u t="806160">Mamor, it's only to have a drink with</u>
  <u t="808480">someone of your friends or like hang</u>
  <u t="810480">around a little bit. And speaking of</u>
  <u t="812160">drinks with your friends, there's a cool</u>
  <u t="813680">bar on the other side of the city that</u>
  <u t="815360">is well different than anything we'd</u>
  <u t="817680">find in Lewa. And one thing you need to</u>
  <u t="819760">know about us is that we personally are</u>
  <u t="821839">suckers for any kind of themed</u>
  <u t="827320">bar. We're at this place that is called</u>
  <u t="829519">La Peria. That means the hardware store.</u>
  <u t="832000">And we wanted to eat something over</u>
  <u t="833440">here, but we didn't know that the</u>
  <u t="835360">kitchen is closed certain hours. And we</u>
  <u t="838480">walk so far to get over here. But well,</u>
  <u t="841440">at least we're having a drink and we're</u>
  <u t="843120">admiring this place because it's</u>
  <u t="845040">something else. Along all the wall,</u>
  <u t="847519">there's certain things that you will buy</u>
  <u t="849600">in a place like this, you know. We're</u>
  <u t="852079">not regretting it, but still, we need</u>
  <u t="854240">something to eat. I did the research.</u>
  <u t="856000">This place supposed to have a very good</u>
  <u t="858000">food, but well, the kitchen is closed.</u>
  <u t="860399">What we can do? We decide to wander a</u>
  <u t="862399">bit when we come across a place that</u>
  <u t="864000">doesn't look like much from outside, but</u>
  <u t="865839">inside it's packed with locals fresh out</u>
  <u t="868399">of work eating some delicious and</u>
  <u t="870160">affordable tapas. This looks like our</u>
  <u t="872320">type of place. We really wanted to live</u>
  <u t="874079">the experience of tapas and we found the</u>
  <u t="875839">right place to do it. This place is</u>
  <u t="877519">called Los. The menu is extensive and I</u>
  <u t="880560">knew this was going to be a good spot</u>
  <u t="881839">because when we sat down, they threw</u>
  <u t="883839">these delicious sausages in front of us,</u>
  <u t="887040">like smoked. So so smoky and melt in</u>
  <u t="891920">your mouth. They were so good. I I want</u>
  <u t="894880">to figure out what they were and was</u>
  <u t="896720">without asking. It was like welcome, you</u>
  <u t="899199">know. It was amazing. So in front of us</u>
  <u t="901440">we have several tapas, but we're going</u>
  <u t="903199">to just keep ordering more and more and</u>
  <u t="905279">more. These look delicious. I'm so glad</u>
  <u t="908079">we're here. Yeah. No frills, no lines,</u>
  <u t="910240">just locals having tapas. And that's</u>
  <u t="912079">exactly what we wanted here in</u>
  <u t="914839">Madrid.</u>
  <u t="918670">[Music]</u>
  <u t="927480">Another day in Madrid. I'm excited for</u>
  <u t="930560">day two. I think it's going to be a very</u>
  <u t="933279">different day that it was yesterday. We</u>
  <u t="935120">have a lot of fun things to do today.</u>
  <u t="936880">Yeah. We're starting off here in Plaza</u>
  <u t="938800">de Espa. What a gorgeous place. And uh</u>
  <u t="941760">what do you say we take a look through</u>
  <u t="943600">here before we head to our next stop,</u>
  <u t="945839">which is a museo. A museum, which is a</u>
  <u t="949600">museo. A museum like you've never seen</u>
  <u t="952240">before.</u>
  <u t="953759">Sorry. What? A museum. A museum.</u>
  <u t="958320">Shut up. You know, we make these videos</u>
  <u t="960720">in English and Spanish. I get a little</u>
  <u t="963600">stuck sometimes. I love it. I love it.</u>
  <u t="965839">Anyway, let's go to the</u>
  <u t="969399">mo a mus. Okay, here's a here's a tip</u>
  <u t="974160">for you. Don't learn English from me.</u>
  <u t="976079">Okay, today we aren't visiting a museum</u>
  <u t="978320">with ancient sculptures or dusty oil</u>
  <u t="980720">paintings. This is a temple of taste, a</u>
  <u t="984000">monument to the noble pig. Welcome to</u>
  <u t="986959">Elmo del Hammon. Inside, legs of ham</u>
  <u t="990399">dangle from the ceiling like holy</u>
  <u t="992320">relics. And the energy is part Delhi,</u>
  <u t="995040">part fever</u>
  <u t="1002120">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1007320">dream. we're talking about and it has a</u>
  <u t="1009759">very special place in my heart over here</u>
  <u t="1011839">because every single day when we were in</u>
  <u t="1013519">Madrid with my family that is the best</u>
  <u t="1016160">that I remember with them. We always</u>
  <u t="1018160">wanted to have a breakfast over here but</u>
  <u t="1019759">it was this juice a sandwich and a</u>
  <u t="1022880">coffee every single day before we start</u>
  <u t="1024880">exploring beautiful Madrid. We're having</u>
  <u t="1026880">this and right now it's hard being over</u>
  <u t="1029839">here without them because I live now in</u>
  <u t="1032799">the US. So, it's difficult for me to see</u>
  <u t="1035439">them or it's difficult for me to have a</u>
  <u t="1037360">trip with them, especially a great one</u>
  <u t="1039679">like it was in Madrid. So, it just</u>
  <u t="1042319">brings me back. This reminds me. So, the</u>
  <u t="1045679">first thing that it was in my plans</u>
  <u t="1047559">whenever we knew we're coming over here</u>
  <u t="1050240">to Madrid was having this breakfast. And</u>
  <u t="1053840">I don't want to cry whenever I have the</u>
  <u t="1055679">first bite, but probably I will. It's</u>
  <u t="1059160">it's this is this is very important for</u>
  <u t="1061679">me. and I will send a picture of course</u>
  <u t="1063360">to my family. I love you guys.</u>
  <u t="1068320">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1074000">As good as I remember, I meet my family.</u>
  <u t="1077760">Guys, what are you doing down there?</u>
  <u t="1079120">Come here with us. We're in the Royal</u>
  <u t="1081280">Palace of Madrid. This is the What did</u>
  <u t="1083840">you say? Largest palace in accidental</u>
  <u t="1086720">Europe. Is that correct? That's correct.</u>
  <u t="1088320">almost doubles the size of Versailles</u>
  <u t="1090400">and also Buckingham Palace. And if</u>
  <u t="1092799">you're planning to come over here, book</u>
  <u t="1094559">your tickets in advance because the line</u>
  <u t="1097200">is quite shorter if you do that. Yeah,</u>
  <u t="1099120">for sure. Let me go take a look inside.</u>
  <u t="1100720">Let's go. Technically, this palace is</u>
  <u t="1102640">the official residence of the Spanish</u>
  <u t="1104559">royal family. But no one is actually</u>
  <u t="1106799">living here these days. It's just used</u>
  <u t="1108960">for state ceremonies. And this place is</u>
  <u t="1111360">massive. There's over 3,400 rooms across</u>
  <u t="1114960">135,000 square m. It cost €14 to enter</u>
  <u t="1118960">here. And even though it's crowded, it's</u>
  <u t="1121840">one of the spots we think it's worth</u>
  <u t="1125620">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1139960">it. I mean, this is palace elegana</u>
  <u t="1143640">extravaganza to the max. Everything is</u>
  <u t="1146400">so ornate. It's breathtaking. And</u>
  <u t="1148960">Martinez was just telling me something</u>
  <u t="1150160">funny that I can definitely relate to.</u>
  <u t="1151840">Um he was saying that when he visited</u>
  <u t="1153120">here with his family, he did not</u>
  <u t="1154559">appreciate this place as a 17-year-old.</u>
  <u t="1156960">And that's the funny thing about travel</u>
  <u t="1158559">is you could go to a place at a</u>
  <u t="1160080">different period of your life and have a</u>
  <u t="1161840">different takeaway of it. This place is</u>
  <u t="1164080">really cool. And I'm realizing that</u>
  <u t="1166480">maybe we need to redecorate our</u>
  <u t="1167840">apartment. Honey,</u>
  <u t="1170480">we need a bigger budget. See? Very, very</u>
  <u t="1173200">nice to live over here. It's beautiful.</u>
  <u t="1175440">The only con it will be like you're in</u>
  <u t="1178559">one side and it's like, "Oh my god, I</u>
  <u t="1180080">forgot my cell phone in the other. You</u>
  <u t="1182160">have to walk all the way over there." So</u>
  <u t="1184320">now I'm good in my I think that I think</u>
  <u t="1186880">that people who live here um they have</u>
  <u t="1189600">they have people for those types of</u>
  <u t="1191120">tasks. That's true. Time for lunch. And</u>
  <u t="1193919">we're not going to lie, we tried to come</u>
  <u t="1195679">to this place yesterday, but we</u>
  <u t="1197600">couldn't. So if you try to come to this</u>
  <u t="1199520">place, please make a reservation. So,</u>
  <u t="1202320">this place is called La Rosaria and it</u>
  <u t="1204960">specialized on rices. So, I bet it's</u>
  <u t="1207840">going to be a very good</u>
  <u t="1210190">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1219000">lunch. This is eating good. This is</u>
  <u t="1222640">sitting good. Thank you, Mad.</u>
  <u t="1228010">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1229440">This is creeping hot because it's quite</u>
  <u t="1231440">literally just come out of the kitchen.</u>
  <u t="1234159">They warn you when you order this that</u>
  <u t="1235760">it's going to take 30 minutes for it to</u>
  <u t="1237280">come out. That's how I knew this was a</u>
  <u t="1238960">good spot because everything is fresh.</u>
  <u t="1240880">Now, this is not paella. Okay? I know a</u>
  <u t="1245440">lot of tourists will see this and say,</u>
  <u t="1246880">"Oh, it's paella." Not everything with</u>
  <u t="1248799">rice is paella. Do they serve a really</u>
  <u t="1251919">good paella here? Yes. Probably the best</u>
  <u t="1254960">in the city. But what we ordered today</u>
  <u t="1257440">was one of their famous rice dishes.</u>
  <u t="1259840">This is packed with all sorts of meat,</u>
  <u t="1261840">an entire clove of garlic. And I kid you</u>
  <u t="1265280">not, even just the rice itself is so</u>
  <u t="1268120">flavorful. And what's fun is that this</u>
  <u t="1270240">is big enough to share for two people.</u>
  <u t="1271919">So, we are enjoying this lunch Madrid</u>
  <u t="1275280">style.</u>
  <u t="1277280">You guys didn't think we're going to be</u>
  <u t="1279200">in Madrid and not seeing the Santiago</u>
  <u t="1280880">Vabo, right? Is there anyone who's</u>
  <u t="1282960">surprised that we're here right now?</u>
  <u t="1284240">because I am not. Martin is a</u>
  <u t="1286799">notoriously huge football fan. So, of</u>
  <u t="1289520">course, we needed to do a stadium tour</u>
  <u t="1291120">of where Real Madrid plays. For €35</u>
  <u t="1293760">each, we got to walk through this huge</u>
  <u t="1295440">museum and we learned all about the</u>
  <u t="1297120">stadium itself and got to see all the</u>
  <u t="1299200">trophies. It's very rare that I, someone</u>
  <u t="1301600">who does not watch sports, gets very</u>
  <u t="1303520">impressed with the stadium. But check</u>
  <u t="1304880">this out, guys. They can actually flip</u>
  <u t="1307280">the field that's in the middle. That's</u>
  <u t="1309919">really cool. I mean, it's amazing.</u>
  <u t="1312799">People are going absolutely nuts over</u>
  <u t="1315120">all of this stuff. I'm excited for them.</u>
  <u t="1317200">Even though I don't know much about</u>
  <u t="1318559">football, I'm trying. What's that?</u>
  <u t="1320559">Martinez is indoctrinating me into the</u>
  <u t="1322400">football world. So, slowly I'm learning.</u>
  <u t="1324400">And, you know, everybody's just so happy</u>
  <u t="1325840">to be here. Yeah. Especially in this</u>
  <u t="1327840">room because there's the 15 Champions</u>
  <u t="1330480">League of Real Madrid, which is it's a</u>
  <u t="1332320">big deal. I I don't know much about</u>
  <u t="1333919">football, but I do know that that's a</u>
  <u t="1335120">lot. Yeah, definitely. I'm glad I got to</u>
  <u t="1337600">see the stadium, but also I really want</u>
  <u t="1340320">to be real with you. We have done much</u>
  <u t="1342080">better stadium tours in other places</u>
  <u t="1344240">where we have a guide and it cost much</u>
  <u t="1346640">lower. Super fans of Real Madrid will</u>
  <u t="1348799">still love this experience, but it's</u>
  <u t="1350480">probably worth skipping if seeing the</u>
  <u t="1352400">stadium isn't a huge goal of yours. But</u>
  <u t="1354720">I will say I was happy that at the end</u>
  <u t="1357280">we have as much time as we wanted to</u>
  <u t="1359600">take pictures inside of the stadium.</u>
  <u t="1361679">There's something else. Definitely</u>
  <u t="1363440">something else. And yes, of course, I'm</u>
  <u t="1365200">wearing my Puma jersey because Sanchez,</u>
  <u t="1367919">you know, I came back to Madrid</u>
  <u t="1370000">expecting change, and there has been</u>
  <u t="1371840">some. I noticed more tourists, trendier</u>
  <u t="1374880">bars, and a few new corners I didn't</u>
  <u t="1377039">know. But what's wild is how much it</u>
  <u t="1379760">hasn't changed at all. The buildings</u>
  <u t="1381600">there are still grand, the Hamon, the</u>
  <u t="1384320">still salty. Actually, Madrid didn't</u>
  <u t="1386960">change much. I did. Back then, I didn't</u>
  <u t="1390080">know how rare it was to travel with your</u>
  <u t="1392000">whole family. I didn't realize how</u>
  <u t="1394159">precious time was. I wonder where I will</u>
  <u t="1396880">be in life next time I'm in Madrid. All</u>
  <u t="1399200">right, enough of that. We have one last</u>
  <u t="1401600">meal over here. Well, we did it more. We</u>
  <u t="1403919">made it to our last spot. Hey,</u>
  <u t="1405600">definitely, but I don't want to leave. I</u>
  <u t="1407440">don't want to leave. I don't either. We</u>
  <u t="1409120">really liked Madrid. These last two</u>
  <u t="1410880">days, it was a great experience over</u>
  <u t="1412400">here in the capital of Spain, and</u>
  <u t="1414720">definitely it's a place that I will come</u>
  <u t="1416559">back. Now, this video focused a lot on</u>
  <u t="1418960">tradition, you know, seeing seeing the</u>
  <u t="1422320">real Madrid. Yeah. The culture of</u>
  <u t="1424159">Madrid. But there's one spot, as we</u>
  <u t="1426640">said, our flight got delayed. So, the</u>
  <u t="1429440">first day we arrived over here very</u>
  <u t="1431280">late. So, we just walk over here, the</u>
  <u t="1433520">Gambia, and we were looking for some</u>
  <u t="1435679">dinner and we found this spot. Yeah,</u>
  <u t="1438240">this was not even supposed to make it</u>
  <u t="1439679">into the itinerary, you guys. It's</u>
  <u t="1441600">totally different from something we</u>
  <u t="1442799">would normally show in our videos</u>
  <u t="1444080">because this is a very popular spot on</u>
  <u t="1445919">social media, right? But guess what? It</u>
  <u t="1448640">deserves a spot in this video because it</u>
  <u t="1450480">was that good. We've been dreaming about</u>
  <u t="1452840">returning. So unlike us, but we're going</u>
  <u t="1455600">to show you guys what is it. It's a</u>
  <u t="1457200">pasta place. It's amazing. And we're</u>
  <u t="1460240">going to have dinner over here. A good</u>
  <u t="1462000">dinner. We're probably going to order</u>
  <u t="1463200">the exact same thing we did the other</u>
  <u t="1464640">night. Definitely. This is Bea Pasta.</u>
  <u t="1467039">The inside looks like a spaceship. And</u>
  <u t="1469520">you can look through the spaceship</u>
  <u t="1470880">windows to watch them making the fresh</u>
  <u t="1472799">pasta. It's not like any Italian</u>
  <u t="1475039">restaurant we've ever seen before.</u>
  <u t="1476720">Martin loves the Tartufo Fest, which is</u>
  <u t="1479120">like Kacowi Pepe, but served straight</u>
  <u t="1481360">from a cheese wheel. And I went for the</u>
  <u t="1483360">candy me, which is actually barata</u>
  <u t="1485279">stuffed pasta in a pecarino cream and</u>
  <u t="1487440">tomato sauce. That is life-changing.</u>
  <u t="1492400">And that's the reason why I suggesting</u>
  <u t="1494559">this place. Not only because they have</u>
  <u t="1497200">freshmade pasta every single day. Also</u>
  <u t="1500320">because they serve it in such fun ways.</u>
  <u t="1503679">You see how they serve my pasta? And</u>
  <u t="1505440">also Juliana is made like a little</u>
  <u t="1507440">candies. Not only it's fun how they make</u>
  <u t="1510400">it, it tastes delicious. Delicious,</u>
  <u t="1512880">guys. It's one of the best pastas we</u>
  <u t="1514559">have. And what I really wanted to come</u>
  <u t="1516480">back for was their incredible I think</u>
  <u t="1519120">it's called the habibi cake dessert. It</u>
  <u t="1521440">is Dubai chocolate which I had never had</u>
  <u t="1524080">before coming here. And you guys need to</u>
  <u t="1525600">hear the crunch on this thing.</u>
  <u t="1530559">So good. It's like I don't even know</u>
  <u t="1533279">what's in this. I know there's pistachio</u>
  <u t="1535039">and chocolate and so much whipped cream</u>
  <u t="1537200">as you guys can see. There's magic. So</u>
  <u t="1539840">good. Next week we're headed to Sevilla.</u>
  <u t="1542000">We cannot wait to share that video with</u>
  <u t="1543520">you guys. But in the meantime, we're</u>
  <u t="1545039">going to leave you one video so you can</u>
  <u t="1546640">watch our adventures. So long, travel</u>
  <u t="1548480">well. Make the world your neighborhood.</u>
  <u t="1549600">See you guys next time.</u>
  </text>
