<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="AZ1ddyRrRzk" uploader="Project Happiness " channel="Project Happiness " likes="42972" title="ALBANIA SEGRETA - Tatuatori in bunker antiatomici e spie comuniste" year="2023" month="7" day="12" date="20230712" is_ac="false">
  <u t="6640">[Giuseppe] Do we dare?</u>
  <u t="8357">[music]</u>
  <u t="15143">This may be the most secret Bunker in all of Albania.</u>
  <u t="28057">Hey, you motherf***er!</u>
  <u t="31186">It's going to be a long day...</u>
  <u t="35800">I asked if he could give me a tattoo,</u>
  <u t="37814">and now he's picking one.</u>
  <u t="45300">My name is Giuseppe and I have a mission:</u>
  <u t="47391">to travel the world,</u>
  <u t="48966">to meet the most extraordinary people of the planet</u>
  <u t="51657">and to ask them a simple question:</u>
  <u t="53714">"What does happiness mean to you?"</u>
  <u t="55671">Welcome to Progetto Happiness.</u>
  <u t="62714">[music]</u>
  <u t="79057">Incredible!</u>
  <u t="80086">I'm inside the biggest, securest bunker in the world.</u>
  <u t="83429">I'm 300 feet below Tirana, Albania's capital.</u>
  <u t="87515">Albania holds a saddening record:</u>
  <u t="89600">it has more bunkers than any other country.</u>
  <u t="92143">In the 70s, the paranoia of Albania's communist former dictator Enver Hoxha</u>
  <u t="95871">resulted in the nationwide construction of more than 170,000 bunkers.</u>
  <u t="100200">Hoxha was one of the worst despots of the East.</u>
  <u t="103029">For 40 years he led the country with an iron fist,</u>
  <u t="105787">isolated Albania from the rest of the world,</u>
  <u t="108071">making it into a kind of North Korea.</u>
  <u t="111071">He enacted extremist communist policies,</u>
  <u t="113429">doing away with private property, freedom of speech and religion,</u>
  <u t="116814">condemning the Albanians to live inside an open-air prison</u>
  <u t="120114">without any window to the outside world.</u>
  <u t="122271">From the post-war period to the 1990s,</u>
  <u t="124382">Albanians lived in terror of the Sigurimi, a frightening secret police,</u>
  <u t="128300">and bunkers were the result of Hoxha's manic obsession</u>
  <u t="131744">with an unlikely enemy attack.</u>
  <u t="134730">After the fall of the communist regime in the '90s,</u>
  <u t="138014">many bunkers were destroyed to forget that sad moment.</u>
  <u t="141457">But others remained to commemorate</u>
  <u t="143587">the resilience of the Albanian people.</u>
  <u t="145571">We'll go around all of Albania to find the most iconic bunkers,</u>
  <u t="149314">meet someone who experienced firsthand</u>
  <u t="151460">the dictatorship of the communist regime,</u>
  <u t="153491">and understand what it means today to be happy in Albania.</u>
  <u t="156600">It's my first time in Albania. I've never been.</u>
  <u t="159186">I was surprised to find out *only* 3 million people live here.</u>
  <u t="163500">A fairly small number,</u>
  <u t="166100">but Albanian pride is immeasurable.</u>
  <u t="169429">They're very proud of their nation, their ethnicity...</u>
  <u t="173187">And they don't call themselves "Albanians",</u>
  <u t="175772">but rather "Shqiptarë",</u>
  <u t="177468">which means "Children of the Eagles".</u>
  <u t="179429">and in turn, Albania is the "Nest of the Eagles".</u>
  <u t="182829">This is also apparent in the national flag:</u>
  <u t="187472">a red background and a two-headed eagle.</u>
  <u t="190791">Very proud.</u>
  <u t="193186">We see it everywhere, in all houses</u>
  <u t="195586">there's always the flag waving.</u>
  <u t="197586">[music]</u>
  <u t="202571">A bunker!</u>
  <u t="203543">Usually bunkers are found in the countryside.</u>
  <u t="207071">Do we dare?</u>
  <u t="210357">There it is.</u>
  <u t="218543">This definitely is someone's land. It's been cultivated.</u>
  <u t="221611">Usually bunkers this big are only found on private property.</u>
  <u t="225771">Public ones have been dismantled since the regime's fall</u>
  <u t="230030">to recover the iron and sell it.</u>
  <u t="233014">And inside such big bunkers there's a ton of iron.</u>
  <u t="235900">But this one's still standing.</u>
  <u t="237630">Let's go look.</u>
  <u t="239157">Many Albanians hate this symbol of the regime,</u>
  <u t="243690">while others have left them standing as a momento,</u>
  <u t="248814">as a reminder to those who did not live through it</u>
  <u t="254400">that there was a very dark period of Albanian history.</u>
  <u t="258300">Interesting...</u>
  <u t="260129">Now everything is destroyed, abandoned.</u>
  <u t="264100">Nothing but a fig plant.</u>
  <u t="267000">The dome-shaped structure...</u>
  <u t="269844">to protect against "potential" enemy attacks</u>
  <u t="273814">which never actually occurred.</u>
  <u t="276872">Many of my Albanian friends told me</u>
  <u t="279614">that nowadays the bunkers are used,</u>
  <u t="282157">or were used, once the regime fell,</u>
  <u t="285357">as public toilets, if you get my point,</u>
  <u t="288043">or for a roll in the hay.</u>
  <u t="290957">A safe, protected place to bring girls...</u>
  <u t="295914">And make love.</u>
  <u t="304500">Holy cow!</u>
  <u t="305700">These are much bigger than what we just saw.</u>
  <u t="318686">It's like a post-apocalyptic scene.</u>
  <u t="320614">As if we were the last to survive on Earth...</u>
  <u t="323258">and these bunkers saved our lives.</u>
  <u t="325887">But no, these were bunkers they believed necessary</u>
  <u t="329100">in case of a potential attack, probably from the Adriatic Sea.</u>
  <u t="332286">They were strategically positioned, in front of the sea</u>
  <u t="336514">to look out for the arrival of possible enemy ships...</u>
  <u t="340414">But they never arrived.</u>
  <u t="343414">[music]</u>
  <u t="368514">Albania is so beautiful!</u>
  <u t="380880">During the communist era, Enver Hoxha declared Albania</u>
  <u t="384244">the first atheist state in the world.</u>
  <u t="386657">Indeed, the only religion allowed was "Albanianism",</u>
  <u t="389487">the cult of the fatherland.</u>
  <u t="391029">Secret police closed down all places of worship</u>
  <u t="393754">and began to persecute believers of every religion.</u>
  <u t="396571">But one policeman, whose very job</u>
  <u t="398737">was to spy on others, did something extraordinary.</u>
  <u t="402100">We are going to meet him.</u>
  <u t="405000">As we prepared for the war, we were ready to defend ourselves</u>
  <u t="409843">from the imperialists, the Americans,</u>
  <u t="413310">the Russians, Germans, British... everyone.</u>
  <u t="416929">And all our preparation was in how to intercept signals</u>
  <u t="421957">to understand what was happening,</u>
  <u t="423631">whether enemies were attacking us or not.</u>
  <u t="425843">And coincedentally, in those years,</u>
  <u t="428658">I was listening to a transmission from Monte Carlo in Albanian.</u>
  <u t="431387">It caught my attention.</u>
  <u t="433286">It was on shortwave signals and talked about someone named Jesus.</u>
  <u t="439457">And they said he was a savior,</u>
  <u t="442115">that by believing in him, your life will be saved,</u>
  <u t="445257">and he will give you a new life, a life of plenty.</u>
  <u t="449815">After several messages, I decided to listen to it again,</u>
  <u t="454815">in the next transmission and going forward.</u>
  <u t="458672">The problem is that it was very dangerous for me</u>
  <u t="462771">listening to it regularly while working in the military.</u>
  <u t="467086">I couldn't listen because it was illegal,</u>
  <u t="470572">and I would have wound up either losing my job,</u>
  <u t="473558">being persecuted, or put in prison.</u>
  <u t="476243">In the time of communism, we were taught about only one person.</u>
  <u t="480514">We only knew the dictator Enver Hoxha.</u>
  <u t="483300">He was a God to us, the only one who could save us.</u>
  <u t="487700">We have been raised from childhood to praise him,</u>
  <u t="491172">saying "Glory to Hoxha", all of that kind of thing.</u>
  <u t="493829">This made me very curious about the word of Jesus.</u>
  <u t="498357">Learning of another hero whose name I'd never heard,</u>
  <u t="502914">who we didn't grow up with and couldn't even imagine.</u>
  <u t="506130">We might have heard the name "God", but not "Jesus".</u>
  <u t="509057">These short messages on the radio were very clear,</u>
  <u t="513401">very simple and understandable for us.</u>
  <u t="517557">And that got me started on listening every day,</u>
  <u t="521126">writing, and learning to find out who this savior is.</u>
  <u t="525457">Not that he would have saved me then,</u>
  <u t="528330">but I wanted to compare him to the one we lived for, Jesus.</u>
  <u t="532429">God says: "I will open the eyes of the blind."</u>
  <u t="535630">I understood what real life was, thank God.</u>
  <u t="539100">Maybe my friends were uncomfortable,</u>
  <u t="542532">some close friends have renounced me,</u>
  <u t="546372">and they asked me what I was doing, but I was very happy.</u>
  <u t="550358">My happiness is different.</u>
  <u t="553400">What we need to understand is that I am no longer the old Berti.</u>
  <u t="557587">I've changed, my life has changed, now it makes sense.</u>
  <u t="561372">and my happiness is that I no longer have love of this world,</u>
  <u t="565801">but I have the love of Christ, and I'm glad that not just me,</u>
  <u t="569571">but many others have heard the message,</u>
  <u t="572994">and I continue to serve them.</u>
  <u t="575271">Because we know how lost we were.</u>
  <u t="578329">But now we are happy, we will be together with Christ,</u>
  <u t="581287">with Jesus today, and for eternity.</u>
  <u t="584080">Half a century of ideological madness which denied the rights of God</u>
  <u t="587987">and systematically denying human rights</u>
  <u t="590658">did not manage to eliminate the hope of the Albanians,</u>
  <u t="593630">who, as in the case of Berti, clung to their faith.</u>
  <u t="607129">This may be the most secret Bunker in all of Albania.</u>
  <u t="610214">It was reserved for the high ranks of the Albanian army.</u>
  <u t="613471">Nobody knew it existed apart from the Army.</u>
  <u t="616514">When the communist regime fell, it was discovered by chance:</u>
  <u t="622043">a lady bought this land, built a hotel on it</u>
  <u t="625168">and one day she found a secret tunnel</u>
  <u t="628074">leading to the other side of the hill.</u>
  <u t="634214">[music]</u>
  <u t="642229">There are bats here. See?</u>
  <u t="644800">- No. - Look...</u>
  <u t="647257">-I can't see. -Ooh!</u>
  <u t="649286">Here it is, here it is...</u>
  <u t="652271">[bats squeaking]</u>
  <u t="657357">It touched me...</u>
  <u t="660086">[laughs]</u>
  <u t="661543">-Did you see it? -Yes!</u>
  <u t="666171">It's a huge bunker.</u>
  <u t="667814">Hundreds of soldiers could barricade here,</u>
  <u t="670472">and leaders who would command from here.</u>
  <u t="673730">These rooms were used both as bedrooms and offices.</u>
  <u t="680257">Where they would send communications to the troops.</u>
  <u t="687643">The doors were also made of reinforced concrete</u>
  <u t="692143">to not allow radiation to enter in case of nuclear attack.</u>
  <u t="697415">In this way, whoever was hiding here</u>
  <u t="700226">would have survived even an atomic bomb.</u>
  <u t="705057">The owner was very kind.</u>
  <u t="707668">She doesn't let anyone in this place.</u>
  <u t="711386">And she just showed me the tunnel</u>
  <u t="713958">that connected the district headquarters to the bunker.</u>
  <u t="719557">From here the soldiers could hide in case of attack.</u>
  <u t="723844">And now it's a hotel, and she is the owner.</u>
  <u t="727857">She was very kind.</u>
  <u t="729488">What incredible luck.</u>
  <u t="731686">Small interruption from Future Giuseppe.</u>
  <u t="733957">Right now I am in Skopje, Macedonia.</u>
  <u t="737086">I'm here to tell you an amazing story:</u>
  <u t="739122">the city of the Romani people.</u>
  <u t="740729">Where the mayor, newspapers, and even the television is all Roma.</u>
  <u t="744557">But in September I'll tell you everything.</u>
  <u t="747429">I come from the future to tell you a secret,</u>
  <u t="749915">one of my travel secrets.</u>
  <u t="751711">I drink when I'm thirsty.</u>
  <u t="754040">I know, amazing.</u>
  <u t="755446">But you must ask yourself:</u>
  <u t="757571">*what* do I drink?</u>
  <u t="758772">I drink AirUp.</u>
  <u t="760643">This water bottle is brilliant.</u>
  <u t="762458">Thanks to these pods with different natural flavors,</u>
  <u t="765543">while I drink, I breathe through my nose</u>
  <u t="767540">and the aroma of the pod travels from my throat to my nose,</u>
  <u t="770686">making me feel like I'm drinking water flavored with wild berries,</u>
  <u t="775129">when really it's just plain water.</u>
  <u t="777543">This way I have more desire to drink during the day,</u>
  <u t="780643">especially now that it's summer,</u>
  <u t="782895">I avoid sugary drinks and, above all,</u>
  <u t="785271">I don't waste plastic bottles during my travels.</u>
  <u t="788229">Now that I've revealed one of my most amazing secrets,</u>
  <u t="791286">I'll leave a link below to try AirUp.</u>
  <u t="793798">Now back to Albania for an interest factoid for us Italians.</u>
  <u t="798657">One of the most curious consequences</u>
  <u t="800604">of the communist era and its insane censorship</u>
  <u t="802930">is that in Albania 70% of people speak Italian.</u>
  <u t="807786">I know it sounds absurd, but until 1991,</u>
  <u t="810288">year of the fall of the regime,</u>
  <u t="812453">the only way for them to have news from the world</u>
  <u t="815022">was to turn their antennas towards our country,</u>
  <u t="817430">to tune in secretly to Italian radio and TV.</u>
  <u t="821330">We were their only window to the world.</u>
  <u t="824730">That's what I was told by a construction worker</u>
  <u t="827943">who I met by chance, and bought me a coffee.</u>
  <u t="830814">Italy. "Do you speak Italian too?"</u>
  <u t="832970">Even the cats speak Italian here!</u>
  <u t="841200">Good?</u>
  <u t="842971">It's not Lavazza...</u>
  <u t="845571">How did you feel when you watched</u>
  <u t="847870">the world outside Albania through Italian television?</u>
  <u t="851472">Secretly, we watch Rai 1 and Rai 2...</u>
  <u t="857257">Secretly.</u>
  <u t="859030">Because the Sigurimi…</u>
  <u t="862343">-Yes, the secret police... -Secret police.</u>
  <u t="865215">They roamed all over the city, in all neighborhoods...</u>
  <u t="868714">And in all the alleys to see if our antennas were facing Italy.</u>
  <u t="873957">My God!</u>
  <u t="876386">It hurts me, the memory...</u>
  <u t="879071">Their faces, always like this.</u>
  <u t="882143">It was a nightmare!</u>
  <u t="883721">- A nightmare? - Yes!</u>
  <u t="885031">I said: "But why was all this necessary?"</u>
  <u t="888301">The whole world lives free.</u>
  <u t="890139">Back then, no.</u>
  <u t="891114">"Don't look over there, don't watch TV,"</u>
  <u t="893429">"Do not go..." All closed off.</u>
  <u t="896320">The regime did not allow us to read anything</u>
  <u t="899588">apart from the history the Russians wrote.</u>
  <u t="904614">We didn't like it, we wanted the West.</u>
  <u t="908143">And who better than Italy?</u>
  <u t="912471">Here, in front of us.</u>
  <u t="914015">So... Fashion, literature,</u>
  <u t="917372">the poetry, the songs...</u>
  <u t="920210">Culture...</u>
  <u t="921457">Italy has a lot to give to humanity.</u>
  <u t="929143">Hearing Beznic speak about my home country</u>
  <u t="932140">with so much admiration affects me deeply,</u>
  <u t="935041">because I've never seen Italy with those eyes.</u>
  <u t="937930">I probably always have taken it for granted.</u>
  <u t="940758">And before saying goodbye I have to thank him</u>
  <u t="943529">for reminding me of the luck I have</u>
  <u t="945917">in being able to call it "home".</u>
  <u t="948571">We are about to get to the most amazing bunker of all</u>
  <u t="951886">it is absurd what they managed to create</u>
  <u t="954262">inside a fallout bunker!</u>
  <u t="956029">It's a tattoo studio!</u>
  <u t="958771">In there a person, a character,</u>
  <u t="961347">who's now a local legend,</u>
  <u t="963057">created a studio in which he tattoos people,</u>
  <u t="965757">his name is Keq Mark, and it's a name that tells a story</u>
  <u t="969065">because Keq means "Bad".</u>
  <u t="971686">He has a somewhat murky past,</u>
  <u t="974453">because he spent 9 years in jail in New York</u>
  <u t="977829">and then he was deported here to Albania.</u>
  <u t="979501">Oh, we're here!</u>
  <u t="981760">Okay, so: from now on</u>
  <u t="983880">really anything can happen.</u>
  <u t="985929">He's very...</u>
  <u t="987879">histrionic, I've already been told.</u>
  <u t="990114">It could be good or bad...</u>
  <u t="992243">Just think that he decides whether to tattoo his clients or not,</u>
  <u t="995644">and if he doesn't like you you can go back home...</u>
  <u t="998271">And he also decides what to tattoo.</u>
  <u t="1001430">So...</u>
  <u t="1002770">Fingers crossed and let's go get Keq.</u>
  <u t="1007570">Nice to meet you, Giuseppe.</u>
  <u t="1009730">They call me Peter, but my nickname is Keq.</u>
  <u t="1013429">With square haircut and a cold and motionless gaze,</u>
  <u t="1016315">Keq looks like a Soviet villain from an American movie.</u>
  <u t="1020387">But really it only takes a few seconds to reveal his welcoming nature.</u>
  <u t="1024787">He wants to show me his famous bunker right away,</u>
  <u t="1028558">furnished with his art: apocalyptic,</u>
  <u t="1030703">provocative and somehow spiritual.</u>
  <u t="1033529">[music]</u>
  <u t="1046300">Would you prefer me to call you Keq or Peter?</u>
  <u t="1048543">Keq.</u>
  <u t="1049758">Because Keq is something bad.</u>
  <u t="1051800">How did you manage to escape and go to the United States?</u>
  <u t="1055450">I went to Yugoslavia,</u>
  <u t="1057600">I applied for a visa with the American Embassy,</u>
  <u t="1060630">and I went to America.</u>
  <u t="1062040">And what did you do in America?</u>
  <u t="1064280">How did you live?</u>
  <u t="1066329">I used to work as a pizza maker.</u>
  <u t="1068440">I was paid well, but then…</u>
  <u t="1071030">Yeah, I happened to meet other three guys</u>
  <u t="1074443">who used to stay in Belgrade in Yugoslavia with me</u>
  <u t="1078486">and they had no place to stay so I took them in.</u>
  <u t="1082320">And the landlord told me</u>
  <u t="1084515">that I couldn't bring anyone so I told the guys:</u>
  <u t="1087029">"When you walk down the stairs don't f*****g make noise."</u>
  <u t="1090530">And they listened to me for a day or two</u>
  <u t="1093360">then they forgot and they kicked me out.</u>
  <u t="1095960">I lost my job and everything and I ended up on the street.</u>
  <u t="1099000">And I got locked up for armed robbery.</u>
  <u t="1101600">Tell me the truth, did you like it? Was it exciting?</u>
  <u t="1106320">Yes, it was like an addiction.</u>
  <u t="1108858">Like adrenaline.</u>
  <u t="1112071">You know, I mean...</u>
  <u t="1114772">I was not afraid when they called me to work.</u>
  <u t="1119215">They'd say, "Hey man, we have a job. Come over."</u>
  <u t="1123981">I didn't care if I had to be the lookout, go in, or... whatever.</u>
  <u t="1128830">So many times...</u>
  <u t="1130044">I was seconds away from death.</u>
  <u t="1134450">How did you end up here with this bunker?</u>
  <u t="1137280">When I got married I bought this land.</u>
  <u t="1141130">The bunker happened to be here,</u>
  <u t="1143310">so I decided to use it for something.</u>
  <u t="1146714">I started tattooing as a hobby,</u>
  <u t="1151490">people started liking it and we are close to the main road.</u>
  <u t="1155771">So many people from different nations</u>
  <u t="1158079">stopped by to take pictures.</u>
  <u t="1160286">I got to talking with them,</u>
  <u t="1162107">So I said, "F**k it, I have to do something with that."</u>
  <u t="1165029">So now I'm making a living out of that.</u>
  <u t="1167214">In addition to tattoos, Keq's main passion is guns.</u>
  <u t="1171286">He wants to try one out with me which he assembled himself.</u>
  <u t="1180843">Holy s**t!</u>
  <u t="1188840">Go this way, turn back.</u>
  <u t="1191970">So I have to go a little bit...</u>
  <u t="1194450">Yes, keep going.</u>
  <u t="1197800">He's fucking drunk.</u>
  <u t="1200055">He is my barber!</u>
  <u t="1201729">Hey, you motherf***er!</u>
  <u t="1206040">Johnny!</u>
  <u t="1206960">You guys wanna have a drink here?</u>
  <u t="1209120">Why not.</u>
  <u t="1210043">Come on.</u>
  <u t="1211371">I don't know what's going on.</u>
  <u t="1212942">We are going to have a drink with him,</u>
  <u t="1215171">I think he's already had a lot...</u>
  <u t="1218600">Yes.</u>
  <u t="1222729">He is Keq's friend.</u>
  <u t="1225360">Keq's friend!</u>
  <u t="1230871">It's going to be a long day, I think...</u>
  <u t="1234320">Beer?</u>
  <u t="1235530">Beer.</u>
  <u t="1236300">At 11 in the morning...</u>
  <u t="1244240">Thank you very much.</u>
  <u t="1248943">He's drunk too.</u>
  <u t="1250172">Another one.</u>
  <u t="1251700">I like the Italian language...</u>
  <u t="1253558">Do you speak Italian, a little?</u>
  <u t="1256686">No.</u>
  <u t="1259843">What a sight!</u>
  <u t="1261043">He was very drunk too...</u>
  <u t="1263500">He's in the middle of the street. I'm worried about him.</u>
  <u t="1269280">Albania is the best country in the Balkans.</u>
  <u t="1275080">Why?</u>
  <u t="1276544">We have the best nature, the best lakes,</u>
  <u t="1281100">the best oceans, beaches. You understand?</u>
  <u t="1286960">Keq is taking me to the lookout point</u>
  <u t="1289532">from which Enver Hoxha, back in the days of communism,</u>
  <u t="1292257">admired what he believed to be his empire.</u>
  <u t="1297880">He would stop here to smoke for 10-15 minutes.</u>
  <u t="1302181">And check this view, always.</u>
  <u t="1304414">Imagine what he was thinking. "Everything is mine."</u>
  <u t="1307450">Yes.</u>
  <u t="1308514">They were so poor but ready to die for the country.</u>
  <u t="1313715">Ready to die.</u>
  <u t="1316120">Would you?</u>
  <u t="1317201">Well... probably yes, even now I would die for my country.</u>
  <u t="1323770">When you talk about jail , it seems almost..</u>
  <u t="1330015">not fun, but something that is ok.</u>
  <u t="1333557">Yeah, 'cause you get used to that shit, man.</u>
  <u t="1337014">Yeah.</u>
  <u t="1337958">You get used to it.</u>
  <u t="1339636">You know what the hardest part is...</u>
  <u t="1342315">When are you get arrested, for example?</u>
  <u t="1345490">The hardest part is when you get sentenced</u>
  <u t="1348501">and the judge with the hammer "5 years, 6 years, 10 years..."</u>
  <u t="1354186">Then you have to settle down because you have nothing.</u>
  <u t="1358529">You can't change anything, you gotta f*****g do the time.</u>
  <u t="1362490">Forget about it.</u>
  <u t="1363690">Work out, keep busy, draw, do something.</u>
  <u t="1368901">You understand?</u>
  <u t="1370320">How many jails did you "visit"?</u>
  <u t="1374830">I've probably been to 20 jails.</u>
  <u t="1377786">20 jails?</u>
  <u t="1378701">Yes.</u>
  <u t="1379929">I was in Auburn one time, the oldest prison in America.</u>
  <u t="1386200">I was in maximum security.</u>
  <u t="1388320">And one time I remember I had two days left in my sentence.</u>
  <u t="1393410">And there was this black guy who was in prison for life.</u>
  <u t="1396840">I was listening to my Walkman</u>
  <u t="1399751">and he asks me if he can use it for a couple of hours</u>
  <u t="1404601">I knew he would never give it back to me.</u>
  <u t="1407572">But I felt that if I didn't give it to him,</u>
  <u t="1410797">I would have been a f*****g weakling.</u>
  <u t="1413272">So I gave it to him, but then…</u>
  <u t="1416914">I had a fight with him. Two days left on my sentence.</u>
  <u t="1422050">We fought knife to knife.</u>
  <u t="1425210">How did you get the knife?</u>
  <u t="1427286">You can take a piece of steel, sharpen it...</u>
  <u t="1430589">you make a knife with anything.</u>
  <u t="1432889">Because when your mind works like this,</u>
  <u t="1435452">you can always make something out of that,</u>
  <u t="1437695">you understand?</u>
  <u t="1438810">And you always knew you'd have to defend yourself.</u>
  <u t="1441600">Yes, but...</u>
  <u t="1442604">Even though I was two days away fom finishing my sentence</u>
  <u t="1446572">they guy's got a life sentence,</u>
  <u t="1448686">I won't lend you my f*****g Walkman, I'd rather fight.</u>
  <u t="1452630">I swear to God, I'm not lying.</u>
  <u t="1457560">Keq, can I see your tattoos?</u>
  <u t="1462720">Yes why not?</u>
  <u t="1463701">Do you like the idea?</u>
  <u t="1467329">I have a total of 80... 89/90.</u>
  <u t="1476343">All by yourself?</u>
  <u t="1477787">Yes, with the left hand, with the right.</u>
  <u t="1480644">My son did my back.</u>
  <u t="1483770">- Your son did it? - Yeah.</u>
  <u t="1485129">It says "Apocalypse".</u>
  <u t="1487400">Which is your favorite?</u>
  <u t="1490120">I have some on my legs.</u>
  <u t="1491930">Let me see if I have underwear on, sometimes I don't wear 'em.</u>
  <u t="1497080">This is the devil in a glass. The woman holding the glass.</u>
  <u t="1501560">The only part you didn't do was your back.</u>
  <u t="1504071">That's right, I couldn't do it. You know what I thought?</u>
  <u t="1507300">I swear to God, I won't lie to you.</u>
  <u t="1509429">I had the tattoo gun and I thought of hanging it on the wall...</u>
  <u t="1514015">No...</u>
  <u t="1515044">Stick it to the wall, let the engine run</u>
  <u t="1518550">and take a mirror like this...</u>
  <u t="1522170">But you didn't do it.</u>
  <u t="1523286">No, I didn't do it, because...</u>
  <u t="1525357">That would have been funny, though.</u>
  <u t="1527371">But either way, you know...</u>
  <u t="1529587">This is my property, I can do whatever the f*** I want.</u>
  <u t="1533557">I don't want hi-tech tattoos.</u>
  <u t="1537170">I did these in prison, so I don't care.</u>
  <u t="1539674">I like them the way they are.</u>
  <u t="1541986">They're a little bad, but I got them in prison.</u>
  <u t="1544640">They have a history behind them.</u>
  <u t="1547570">I asked Keq if he could give me a tattoo</u>
  <u t="1550300">I waited for his reply for a few seconds...</u>
  <u t="1553215">I wanted to understand whether he wanted to or not.</u>
  <u t="1555901">Finally he said yes, and now he's choosing it.</u>
  <u t="1560186">Let's hope for the best.</u>
  <u t="1573457">It will definitely be a traditional Albanian symbol...</u>
  <u t="1576558">I think he's got it.</u>
  <u t="1582914">Beautiful.</u>
  <u t="1615720">Beautiful job, man.</u>
  <u t="1617169">I'm very happy to have a tattoo from you.</u>
  <u t="1620114">There is always a question that I ask to everyone around the world</u>
  <u t="1623901">to understand how happiness can change.</u>
  <u t="1627040">I would like to understand what happiness is for you,</u>
  <u t="1630553">after everything you've been through.</u>
  <u t="1633290">This is a big question...</u>
  <u t="1635320">Yeah...</u>
  <u t="1636215">A nice question...</u>
  <u t="1638320">Family is a big happiness.</u>
  <u t="1642900">Until getting married, having children,</u>
  <u t="1646301">you always think happiness is something else.</u>
  <u t="1650530">It can be prostitutes, football, drugs, alcohol...</u>
  <u t="1654215">Because you are not married.</u>
  <u t="1656010">Once you're married it's the happiest thing in your life.</u>
  <u t="1659500">It was nice meeting you guys.</u>
  <u t="1663372">Anytime you pass by you are welcome to stop by.</u>
  <u t="1669360">If you don't find me here, don't look for me,</u>
  <u t="1671869">because I'll be gone for good.</u>
  <u t="1673886">Either Heaven or Hell.</u>
  <u t="1675682">Most likely... People say this is Heaven</u>
  <u t="1678457">but when I go, I'll try Hell.</u>
  <u t="1682829">Because I've been to Heaven before, if that's it.</u>
  <u t="1686490">I wonder if Keq is aware of what he created.</u>
  <u t="1689386">Transforming a fallout bunker,</u>
  <u t="1691275">a symbol of oppression and fear,</u>
  <u t="1692960">into a welcoming place full of art, creativity and openness.</u>
  <u t="1697760">It's amazing how the Albanian people,</u>
  <u t="1700407">in such a dark time, were able to recognize</u>
  <u t="1702922">in art, in religion, and in a simple book,</u>
  <u t="1705833">the ways out and the seeds</u>
  <u t="1707660">to make a different reality blossom.</u>
  <u t="1709714">In these days I've learned to admire a nation</u>
  <u t="1712443">that I knew, but didn't understand.</u>
  <u t="1715301">Where high mountains protect from all sides</u>
  <u t="1718643">the traditions of a land among the proudest in the world.</u>
  <u t="1721629">I got the impression that Albanians had different eyes,</u>
  <u t="1725343">as if they had the innate ability</u>
  <u t="1727501">to find opportunities for happiness often invisible.</u>
  <u t="1731443">The emblem of Albanian happiness</u>
  <u t="1733960">I found in Beznic's words, which I leave you with:</u>
  <u t="1737358">If you don't love others, you don't love life.</u>
  <u t="1740187">How can you not be happy,</u>
  <u t="1742368">with all of this happiness that surrounds you?</u>
  <u t="1746130">There are rivers that flow, the mountains,</u>
  <u t="1750570">the sea, the clouds, the blue...</u>
  <u t="1753601">there are songs that remind you of all this...</u>
  <u t="1757058">My God...</u>
  <u t="1758559">Life is worth living!</u>
  <u t="1763357">ENGLISH SUBTITLES: Kayla Baker</u>
  </text>
