<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="kdWjQXVCHh4" uploader="in Viaggio col Tubo" channel="in Viaggio col Tubo" likes="4863" title="BERLINO in un WEEKEND! - Guida di viaggio [ENG subs]" year="2017" month="01" day="15" is_ac="false">
  <u t="26760">Hi everybody! Welcome back to "In Viaggio col Tubo"!</u>
  <u t="28840">This is our travel guide for a weekend in Berlin!</u>
  <u t="54540">Actually, instead of a weekend it's more like 3 days,</u>
  <u t="57240">arriving on Friday around lunch time.</u>
  <u t="59380">So, the first thing to do is LUNCH!</u>
  <u t="61420">We go to "Suzette", a French Crêperie</u>
  <u t="64060">yes, French in Berlin!</u>
  <u t="65480">that makes huge sweet and savoury crêpes, and even gluten-free.</u>
  <u t="69120">But now let's go back to the "Grandeburg" Gate...</u>
  <u t="71400">Grandeburg..big ravine! (In italian Grande=big, Burg sounds like "burrone"=ravine)</u>
  <u t="73800">But now let's go back to "Grand.." Gate..I keep saying "Grandeburg"!</u>
  <u t="76980">But now let's go back to Brandenburg Gate,</u>
  <u t="79000">a must-see monument in Berlin,</u>
  <u t="82420">free to watch, here outside.</u>
  <u t="84040">There're also some museums about the "Grandeburg" Gate..</u>
  <u t="87060">Don't say it again! You made it once, it's ok! Don't tempt fate!</u>
  <u t="92040">So, after the Brandenburg Gate, with the B,</u>
  <u t="94660">we walk South to see the famous Memorial to the Murdered Jews of Europe.</u>
  <u t="99400">It consists of 2.711 steles of varying heights on an uneven terrain,</u>
  <u t="104060">Even though it's arranged in orthogonal grids,</u>
  <u t="106420">walking through the installation, you feel lost in a gray maze.</u>
  <u t="109480">This symbolizes how, even in a supposedly ordered system,</u>
  <u t="113140">people can feel swallowed up by a world without soul.</u>
  <u t="116800">And to stay on the topic, there is a curiosity that we want to tell you about the streets in Berlin.</u>
  <u t="121000">Around the city there're these brass plates</u>
  <u t="123700">that have been placed where some people were deported.</u>
  <u t="128380">For example, this Max was deported on 19th February 1939.</u>
  <u t="134320">But now, it's time to go to the Reichstag, to visit the spectacular dome of the German Parliament.</u>
  <u t="139520">The entrance is free but you've to book it in advance, so set the date first.</u>
  <u t="143040">*link in the description</u>
  <u t="144060">It's veeeery beautiful!</u>
  <u t="145100">There's this walkway that goes up all around the dome.</u>
  <u t="147840">But be careful 'cause</u>
  <u t="149460">even if this seems to be the most Italian city in Germany,</u>
  <u t="153280">you're still in Germany! So there's</u>
  <u t="154780">a walkway to go up and one to go down.</u>
  <u t="156980">Don't go on the wrong one!</u>
  <u t="158660">After a scenic walk, we have a coffee with Nicole,</u>
  <u t="161680">that tell us how to discover a less known Berlin.</u>
  <u t="165840">* Italian subs*</u>
  <u t="194840">Nicole made us want to discover a hidden Berlin,</u>
  <u t="198260">but we'll see tomorrow morning.</u>
  <u t="199860">Now it's time for dinner and we try something typical.</u>
  <u t="202740">We're in this restaurant, I don't exactly remember its name,</u>
  <u t="206440">I mean, I know its name 'cause it's also written on the plate, but I can't pronunce it</u>
  <u t="209340">let's say "Treffpunk" (*it's "Treffpunkt")</u>
  <u t="211560">I'm having a curry wurstel,</u>
  <u t="213560">a wurstel with curry,</u>
  <u t="215740">that seems to be pretty typical of Berlin.</u>
  <u t="220200">Good?</u>
  <u t="223140">Good!</u>
  <u t="224380">It's the only place I know where they make it gluten-free</u>
  <u t="227560">It's essentially a wurstel with curry ketchup.</u>
  <u t="231640">If you don't need it to be gluten-free, you can find it everywhere!</u>
  <u t="234760">I, instead, I'm having a light meal with a single Berlin-style meatball,</u>
  <u t="239660">It seems like a normal meatball!</u>
  <u t="246000">It's quite tasteless!</u>
  <u t="248360">I'm a bit embarassed 'cause the people at our table,</u>
  <u t="250460">since we're at this table with other 4 people that we don't know,</u>
  <u t="254140">they're looking at us..</u>
  <u t="256000">but it's ok!</u>
  <u t="257060">YouTuber's life! :)</u>
  <u t="269640">*Leave a Like for our Berliner cameraman*</u>
  <u t="271920">Our first day ends here.</u>
  <u t="273920">Tomorrow'll be another big and long day,</u>
  <u t="276440">see you tomorrow!</u>
  <u t="277360">Saturday morning we wake up early to explore the city.</u>
  <u t="280500">We get off at this unpronounceable stop</u>
  <u t="282920">to meet Stefano of "Ciao Berlin!"</u>
  <u t="284900">that helps us discover the North area of Neukölln</u>
  <u t="287560">and its micro neighbourhoods called Kiez.</u>
  <u t="290160">The micro neighbourhood</u>
  <u t="291820">in the districts where there's a high level of socialisation,</u>
  <u t="296320">be it crossroads, squares or stretches of road,</u>
  <u t="301280">where people don't just pass by,</u>
  <u t="305460">'cause they're focused on their job, on their stuff,</u>
  <u t="307780">but they sit, read the paper, have a coffee, chat etc.</u>
  <u t="312140">This is an area with a rising charm,</u>
  <u t="313860">chosen by the creators both for its low rent</u>
  <u t="316220">and because, as Nicole told us yesterday,</u>
  <u t="318260">to be successful in Berlin you have to not show off.</u>
  <u t="321380">*Italian subs*</u>
  <u t="348260">You may not find anything without a guide since there're no monuments.</u>
  <u t="351920">The places of interest are, in fact, unique restaurants or small shops</u>
  <u t="355800">like this kimono shop.</u>
  <u t="356920">Ok, we were walking around this neighbourhood in Neukölln,</u>
  <u t="359600">and we walked into this vintage kimonos shop,</u>
  <u t="362980">and now I'm gonna try one on 'cause they're too beautiful!</u>
  <u t="366900">*Italian subs*</u>
  <u t="400480">But now it's time for lunch</u>
  <u t="402060">so we go in a typical restaurant of this area, a vegeterian one,</u>
  <u t="406080">"Holy Flat".</u>
  <u t="407080">Where I have a vegan dish with, boh, everything</u>
  <u t="409920">while Martina..?</u>
  <u t="410880">I'm having the soup of the day which is sweet potatoes and coconut,</u>
  <u t="415040">and this bowl of salad, avocado, cheese and..</u>
  <u t="419500">wow!</u>
  <u t="420040">After lunch, we say goodbye to Stefano and we go back to the famous Berlin with its Museum Island.</u>
  <u t="425060">There're, of course, many museum and we can't see them all.</u>
  <u t="428260">So we visit the Pergamon, that,</u>
  <u t="429980">despite the several halls closed for major renovation works,</u>
  <u t="433620">offers some spectacular looks on the past.</u>
  <u t="436440">Unfortunately even the main hall containing the Pergamon Altar is closed,</u>
  <u t="439640">but many pieces are open to the public: the colourful Gate of Babylon,</u>
  <u t="445900">and the huge Market Gate of Mileto,</u>
  <u t="451460">in addition to many finds.</u>
  <u t="463700">The admission is 12€,</u>
  <u t="465780">but if you plan to visit more than 2 museums,</u>
  <u t="467980">we recommend the Museum Pass</u>
  <u t="469680">that for 24 € guarantees admission in more than 50 museums on three consecutive days.</u>
  <u t="474860">Since we have the pass, why not use it?!</u>
  <u t="477560">But before reaching the next destination outside the island,</u>
  <u t="480300">we go to the Hackesche Höfe.</u>
  <u t="490440">They are eight courtyards of the former Jewish district in the early 1900s,</u>
  <u t="494180">all interconnected.</u>
  <u t="495500">And</u>
  <u t="496300">they're a bit difficult to find.</u>
  <u t="498200">This is the entrance</u>
  <u t="513540">We keep going until we arrive at the Naturkunde, the Museum of Natural History,</u>
  <u t="517360">with its ancient and giant inhabitants.</u>
  <u t="520440">Behind us there's the largest mounted dinosaur skeleton (he adds "ever mounted"),</u>
  <u t="526360">I've messed up this sentence!</u>
  <u t="528000">in Europe..</u>
  <u t="529220">in the world!</u>
  <u t="530580">"Mounted" doesn't mean that it's fake, but that they remounted real fossils.</u>
  <u t="535540">It's 13 metres tall!</u>
  <u t="538020">Weren't they herbivore? Why are their teeth so sharp?!</u>
  <u t="552600">Price 8€ per person</u>
  <u t="559540">There aren't only dinosaurs, of course, but also</u>
  <u t="562420">more or less rare animals, some VERY rare :P from all over the world.</u>
  <u t="565800">And then there's a dragon's head.</u>
  <u t="569600">If you don't like museum so much, we've got something else for you!</u>
  <u t="572660">40 minutes from the centre, there's the famous stadium where Italy won the 2006 World Cup.</u>
  <u t="577740">So if you're a football fan as much as we are, it's a must!</u>
  <u t="583180">Joking apart, this stadium is full of history:</u>
  <u t="585860">it hosted the 1936 Olympics, the first with television transmission;</u>
  <u t="590540">and here Bolt broke the 100m world record.</u>
  <u t="594140">But it's now Martina's favourite moment of the day, dinner!</u>
  <u t="597120">After a quick look around Alexanderplatz, we go to "The Pub",</u>
  <u t="600460">a pub with generous helpings and a beer tap in the middle of the table.</u>
  <u t="605080">And after a good sleep, we start our last day in Berlin with..</u>
  <u t="609120">the must-see East Side Gallery, famous and iconic in Berlin,</u>
  <u t="613100">that is none other than the Berlin Wall.</u>
  <u t="614940">That's right! We don't need to add anything else 'cause it's world-famous.</u>
  <u t="618080">It's worth the visit!</u>
  <u t="620080">One thing we noticed is that in many parts</u>
  <u t="623620">there's a metal fence to avoid people's scribblings.</u>
  <u t="627420">And you may say "Is it necessary?" Yes, it is!</u>
  <u t="630160">That's how it is where there's no fence:</u>
  <u t="632280">So, maybe, it's better with the fence.</u>
  <u t="634740">In 2009 all the artists were called back to repaint the wall.</u>
  <u t="639120">That's how it was in 2009..</u>
  <u t="642400">the drawing were almost unrecognizable.</u>
  <u t="644620">This is the only part of the wall that was left like this,</u>
  <u t="647760">'cause it's the icon of</u>
  <u t="649600">the ban "no destroy or damage the wall",</u>
  <u t="654620">'cause it's an important symbol for the city.</u>
  <u t="657740">Of course, they also called this artist,</u>
  <u t="659740">and this one on this side is the part of his painting that he restored.</u>
  <u t="664700">But they left this part here like this.</u>
  <u t="666660">We walk along the wall up to Oberbaumbrücke,</u>
  <u t="670100">this beautiful red bridge, symbol of the Berlin ruled by the East Germany.</u>
  <u t="674200">Here we take the tram up to Mauerpark.</u>
  <u t="676820">a must-see on Sunday and famous for its colourful flea market.</u>
  <u t="680540">There are some flea markets where you can find more or less interesting things.</u>
  <u t="685200">Yes, it's a matter of taste, at the end!</u>
  <u t="686920">And there's some street food!</u>
  <u t="695200">OK</u>
  <u t="696440">Waffel</u>
  <u t="697200">Official tasting of the dark chocolate waffle</u>
  <u t="705120">Really good!</u>
  <u t="706140">It's spilling!</u>
  <u t="707840">It's spilling, but the dough is not sweet.</u>
  <u t="710240">I mean, only the chocolate is sweet,</u>
  <u t="711900">not the dough.</u>
  <u t="713160">How sad!</u>
  <u t="714180">So it's..</u>
  <u t="715300">good, but not a 10 out of 10.</u>
  <u t="717960">I'm having a "catira" with everything in</u>
  <u t="720300">It's this little sandwich of corn flour</u>
  <u t="723720">with everything inside.</u>
  <u t="728460">It's similar to the tacos we used to prepare in Australia.</u>
  <u t="731400">You've something on your nose!</u>
  <u t="750620">It's about to burst!</u>
  <u t="774040">There're also street artists who do pretty much everything, but especially singers.</u>
  <u t="778400">There should also be karaoke in summer,</u>
  <u t="780400">but in winter the sun sets at 3.30pm, so..</u>
  <u t="784480">When they finished playing, we've also asked a couple of questions to the Riders Connection</u>
  <u t="788120">like " if they come here to play every Sunday".</u>
  <u t="791800">* Italian subs*</u>
  <u t="817260">Byeee! ("Arrivederci" in Italian)</u>
  <u t="819340">After this quick lunch in Mauerpark,</u>
  <u t="821380">we head to another place, symbol of the East-West division:</u>
  <u t="824420">Checkpoint Charlie!</u>
  <u t="826480">It was one of the border crossing between East and West Berlin,</u>
  <u t="830100">guarded by American soldiers,</u>
  <u t="833220">and now, instead, there're these guys that you've to pay to get a photo with.</u>
  <u t="838500">So, it's kind of a tourist trap,</u>
  <u t="840500">but if you just pass by and look from afar, it's ok.</u>
  <u t="843900">Judging by the fact that this little booth is now in a triangle</u>
  <u t="847460">formed by McDonald, Starbucks and KFC,</u>
  <u t="850000">we can say that the West has won hands down!</u>
  <u t="852120">There's still one last stop we've to make before leaving,</u>
  <u t="855920">but first..</u>
  <u t="856840">One of the most beautiful things in Berlin,</u>
  <u t="859680">that you can see for free all around the city,</u>
  <u t="863440">are these pieces of street art,</u>
  <u t="866020">that are humongous, amazing,</u>
  <u t="868260">well-kept, also because they're financed by the city itself.</u>
  <u t="873580">They're scattered all over the city, even far from each other,</u>
  <u t="876760">so go check out our website 'cause</u>
  <u t="879280">there's a map of the finest paintings we've found,</u>
  <u t="882620">in this way you can have your own map</u>
  <u t="884840">and look for them.</u>
  <u t="886520">Maybe you're in a tourist spot and you know that</u>
  <u t="890080">"200m away from here, there's something like this, and it's worth the visit!"</u>
  <u t="894400">Finally here we are at the last stop of our 3-days trip in Berlin:</u>
  <u t="897660">Jewish Museum Berlin.</u>
  <u t="898940">There're of course exhibition rooms with any kind of relicts about this culture,</u>
  <u t="903020">but they particularly recommended this museum because of the three axes,</u>
  <u t="906640">hallways that symbolize the different fates of the Jewish people.</u>
  <u t="910020">There aren't many show-pieces here,</u>
  <u t="911780">it's more a sensory experience created by the architecture.</u>
  <u t="915060">The first axis is the Holocaust,</u>
  <u t="917300">that ends in a cold and dark tower.</u>
  <u t="925020">The second axis is the Exile that ends in a open space.</u>
  <u t="928700">This is The Garden of Exile,</u>
  <u t="930700">on the top there's the Promised Land,</u>
  <u t="932480">but people have to walk down here,</u>
  <u t="934820">the Promise Land is unreachable</u>
  <u t="937180">and</u>
  <u t="938000">since the floor is tilted and with all these stone,</u>
  <u t="942580">it's difficult to walk</u>
  <u t="944380">It seems many people lose their bearings,</u>
  <u t="948200">they feel dizzy.</u>
  <u t="949680">It represents</u>
  <u t="951360">the feelings that people have when they're force to emigrate</u>
  <u t="955020">to escape from a bit complicated situations.</u>
  <u t="974160">The first two axes are connected by the Axis of Continuity</u>
  <u t="977580">that ends with the actual entrance to the museum.</u>
  <u t="980080">Probably the most interesting installation in the museum is "Fallen Leaves",</u>
  <u t="984280">dedicated to all the victims of wars.</u>
  <u t="1005440">Ok, we've started this video here</u>
  <u t="1007540">and we end it here at Brandenburg Gate,</u>
  <u t="1009600">in the evening this time.</u>
  <u t="1010940">We're ready to go back home and take the plane.</u>
  <u t="1013560">Go check out our website www.inviaggiocoltubo.com</u>
  <u t="1016660">'cause you can find a map with everything we saw.</u>
  <u t="1020100">You can download it and use it.</u>
  <u t="1022400">Now, it's your time!</u>
  <u t="1024020">Let us know in a comment what are your must-see in Berlin,</u>
  <u t="1028060">if you've already been here, how much you like this city,</u>
  <u t="1030240">if you like this city..</u>
  <u t="1031640">so let us know in a comment.</u>
  <u t="1034280">Thanks for watching!</u>
  <u t="1035600">See you in the next video!</u>
  <u t="1037280">Bye! :D</u>
  <u t="1038520">Please give this video a thumbs up and subscribe!:D</u>
  </text>
