<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="69O1FyBcnR8" uploader="Project Happiness " channel="Project Happiness " likes="162518" title="COME ENTRARE IN COREA DEL NORD DA SOLI 🇰🇵 (episodio 1)" year="2020" month="1" day="22" date="20200122" is_ac="false">
  <u t="4100">Ok, The time has come to tell you everything about my avventure in North Korea.</u>
  <u t="9420">Very particural things happened during my trip,</u>
  <u t="11700">which probably my dear friend Kim would not I tell you about</u>
  <u t="16560">But I thought about it, a lot.</u>
  <u t="18800">And I wondered,</u>
  <u t="20280">If I were a real repoter.. what should I do?</u>
  <u t="22660">And the answer was obvious.</u>
  <u t="24280">Tell the truth! Tell the truth about a country we know nothing,</u>
  <u t="27060">because of its dictatoriship which scares journalists and reporters.</u>
  <u t="31920">I'm neither one nor the other,</u>
  <u t="34460">but in my own little I want to tell you what I saw in North Korea.</u>
  <u t="38000">Having said that in my videos I filmed and interviewed people who still live there.</u>
  <u t="41220">So, I leave the interpretation to you of the answers they gave me</u>
  <u t="45540">and I'll refrain from commenting, because I don't want to put them in difficult situation.</u>
  <u t="50160">Remeber that, in North Korea there are 28 million people.</u>
  <u t="53860">For 70 years, the population is oppressed by authoritarian regime</u>
  <u t="57260">let by the Kim dinasty,</u>
  <u t="59100">which deny all basic human rights:</u>
  <u t="62120">press, press freedom,</u>
  <u t="63500">freedom of expression and religious association.</u>
  <u t="65840">It's the most dangerous and isolated country in the world.</u>
  <u t="68780">A open prison, in which no citizen can go out,</u>
  <u t="71980">except by running the risk of being captured and killed.</u>
  <u t="77820">North Korea is a surreal world,</u>
  <u t="80120">which I want tell you about.</u>
  <u t="82260">Uff...Ready?</u>
  <u t="84360">Let's start from the very first day! From Beijing,</u>
  <u t="87380">where the train departs from and it takes 25 hours to Pyongyang, the capital of North Korea.</u>
  <u t="92900">There, I met with a representative of the agency</u>
  <u t="95845">who helped me to get my North Korea visa.</u>
  <u t="99520">This is your korean visa.</u>
  <u t="101340">ok</u>
  <u t="102460">yeah, so important!</u>
  <u t="103920">Because, actually, entering in North Korea it's not difficult..</u>
  <u t="106600">Unless you are a journalist or reporter,</u>
  <u t="109520">but you need an agency.</u>
  <u t="111620">it's impossible for a turist to get in without a travel agency.</u>
  <u t="115740">Basically, the agency is an intermediary between the North Korean government and you,</u>
  <u t="118880">because actually, it can only offer you two kinds of tours:</u>
  <u t="121200">the first one is a group tour,</u>
  <u t="122760">in which you can travel together with other tourists</u>
  <u t="125020">and it's the cheapest one, the most affordable;</u>
  <u t="127320">While the second one is a private tour,</u>
  <u t="129580">thanks to you could travel "alone".</u>
  <u t="131520">And I said "alone"..Because you're constantly,</u>
  <u t="134520">continuously</u>
  <u t="135740">accompanied by two guides</u>
  <u t="138100">who control every single step you take.</u>
  <u t="142020">Which I would call more guards,</u>
  <u t="143260">they are guides-guards.</u>
  <u t="144580">Let's call them GUIRDS, if you want, from now on.</u>
  <u t="146720">Obviously, the private tour costs a little more,</u>
  <u t="148920">but I chose that one because, in my mind I had a plan.</u>
  <u t="153960">I'll tell you about it later.</u>
  <u t="154860">If you are wondering how much a private tour costs..</u>
  <u t="156820">I paid for three nights almost 1000 euros.</u>
  <u t="161500">1000 euro...!</u>
  <u t="163000">How many arancini I'd could buy with 1000 euros!</u>
  <u t="165520">Well, I have to said however, the cost of package includes everything:</u>
  <u t="168000">all meals, therefore all the restaurants,</u>
  <u t="169360">all nights in the hotel all museums, all transfers..</u>
  <u t="173220">Ah, pay attention! One Thing.. To be clear.. You can''t choose the hotel.</u>
  <u t="177180">You can't't choose the reastaurants.</u>
  <u t="178580">Everything is already arranged by the North Korean government.</u>
  <u t="182420">eheh</u>
  <u t="183100">I have to laugh to tell you this part of the story,</u>
  <u t="185220">even if actually there's nothing to laugh.</u>
  <u t="187000">During the brefing, the intermediary repeated to me</u>
  <u t="189380">over and over things not to do absolutley in North Korea.</u>
  <u t="193400">And I assure you I was well-intentioned,</u>
  <u t="195680">I listened him, I took notes,</u>
  <u t="197760">I asked questions to try not to risk anything.</u>
  <u t="200980">Now, I'm going to make you a list of all these rules.</u>
  <u t="203740">And, don't ask me how..</u>
  <u t="205800">During 3 days I've been there I was able to break ..all of them.</u>
  <u t="209660">However.. I left the country without being arrested</u>
  <u t="212940">and with all my videos.</u>
  <u t="214940">Very first rule:</u>
  <u t="215780">it's forbidden to criticize the regime.</u>
  <u t="217980">Clear!</u>
  <u t="219000">Stupid question:</u>
  <u t="220360">Is it possible to meet the leader?</u>
  <u t="223400">It's forbidden to film and photograph soldiers</u>
  <u t="226540">or buildings under construction,</u>
  <u t="229440">it's also forbidden to film or photograph from the train windows</u>
  <u t="233080">or from the car windows which will take you around.</u>
  <u t="236480">Pay attention to this! because it's very interesting:</u>
  <u t="238520">it's very forbidden to take photos of only parts of monuments</u>
  <u t="241660">or paintings which representing leaders.</u>
  <u t="244500">For them it's a very serious affront.</u>
  <u t="247040">In fact, every time I filmed or I was taking photos</u>
  <u t="249360">one of the Guirds was always behind me..</u>
  <u t="253240">checking what I was doing.</u>
  <u t="255080">This is even more rich!</u>
  <u t="256220">It's forbidden to fold the newspaper</u>
  <u t="258360">in the part where there is the supreme leader's photo, Kim Jong-un.</u>
  <u t="262300">It's strictly forbidden to speak about religion.</u>
  <u t="264760">In North Korea, there is no a religion?</u>
  <u t="267560">or to introduce sacred texts in the country</u>
  <u t="270520">Because, in reality, the unique God fro them is their leader.</u>
  <u t="274920">This is good!</u>
  <u t="275880">Forbidden to named the country, North Korea.</u>
  <u t="278760">What's the tipical, the most famous dish in North Korea?</u>
  <u t="282440">Because yes.. for them, the country doesn't called North Korea, it's Korea.</u>
  <u t="286180">Or otherwise</u>
  <u t="287700">D. P. R. K.</u>
  <u t="288560">It means Democratic People's Republic Of Korea.</u>
  <u t="295740">Disobedience, non-compliance and transgression of these rules</u>
  <u t="298520">directly implies to deportation from the country or to be arrest.</u>
  <u t="303460">eeeh!?</u>
  <u t="304700">Ah, I forgot..The cherry on the cake. Just a little detail.</u>
  <u t="307340">In North Korea, internet doesn't work</u>
  <u t="309360">and you cannot make calls, so our mobile phones don't work.</u>
  <u t="312820">Therefore you are in the country with the most ferocious dictatorship in the world</u>
  <u t="316160">and if something ever happens to you nobody will know it.</u>
  <u t="320800">it's good, isn't it?</u>
  <u t="321900">After receiving the long list of explanation..I got on the train</u>
  <u t="324400">and after passing the baggage check by North Korean sodierls..</u>
  <u t="328520">Finally.. I got into North Korea.</u>
  <u t="332120">A magical land, lush and unspoil**..</u>
  <u t="334200">no!...From the beginning the landscape is barren, gloomy and foggy.</u>
  <u t="340180">And trying to glimpse what there was behind the 50's buildings..</u>
  <u t="344060">I had the impression that the best buildings,</u>
  <u t="347020">the most modern ones,</u>
  <u t="348480">are in the front trying to cover everything behind them.</u>
  <u t="356940">Even the freight trains seem somehow being covered,</u>
  <u t="360700">to not show what they are carrying.</u>
  <u t="363680">It also started to snow.</u>
  <u t="365220">I took the advantage to film the last video before entering the capital, Pyongyang.</u>
  <u t="382460">Uff! OK, I'm alraedy on the North Korean train. And I arrive to Pyounyang tonight, in the capital.</u>
  <u t="386280">And probabily this is the last time, I'm able to speak</u>
  <u t="388680">without risking to be listened to somebody.</u>
  <u t="391040">Let's start officialy Happines Project in North Korea.</u>
  <u t="393540">I have to be able to make my ten question about happinnes to North korean.</u>
  <u t="397480">If they'll be my guides or they'll be passersby.</u>
  <u t="399760">I have to be able to involved the formula recipe of happiness.</u>
  <u t="402780">What's the problem?</u>
  <u t="404400">It's illegal to make any kind of interview,</u>
  <u t="406020">and so I should make my ten question in any casual conversations.</u>
  <u t="409720">What a wonderful day, very darling Dong.</u>
  <u t="413340">But, listen!</u>
  <u t="414200">What is, in your opinion, that thing always makes you smile?</u>
  <u t="417900">Eh! Lol, eh!</u>
  <u t="419900">Something like this!</u>
  <u t="421340">To give less attention, I'll try to film everything with my phone</u>
  <u t="424400">Eh, guys! This is the mission!..</u>
  <u t="426540">... e anche...not be arrested.. That would not be bad!</u>
  <u t="433040">Everybody is exceited because we've just arrived in Pyoungyang!</u>
  <u t="438540">We couldn't see anything because there are very few lights turned on.</u>
  <u t="444240">very few and even more it's raining!</u>
  <u t="457520">North Korea!</u>
  <u t="459880">Waiting for me out of the station there were already my two guirds and car driver</u>
  <u t="463460">Surprise, surprise!</u>
  <u t="465260">They are two girls of my age.</u>
  <u t="466800">I just met two guides:</u>
  <u t="469320">TChoe and Kim.</u>
  <u t="471340">I immediately try to film with my phone, to test how the react.</u>
  <u t="475500">Nice to meet you!</u>
  <u t="476460">Two ladies! I didn't expected that!</u>
  <u t="478160">Really?Yeah!</u>
  <u t="478660">So, we're gonna spend the next three days toghether.</u>
  <u t="481500">yeah!</u>
  <u t="482420">We all three! Like you too and the driver</u>
  <u t="486060">Wow! I'm so spoilt! Three people just for me.</u>
  <u t="489360">Yeah!</u>
  <u t="490360">Wow! The hotel is not bad!</u>
  <u t="494040">For the next three days my new guird friends</u>
  <u t="497040">will sleep in the same hotel</u>
  <u t="498200">And I can't put a foot out of here without them</u>
  <u t="502480">The hotel looks very luxurious</u>
  <u t="506020">and very very too much quiet.</u>
  <u t="508620">This is the same hotet where a few years ago</u>
  <u t="511600">an American boy named Otto Warmbier</u>
  <u t="513440">It'd seem to have stolen a stupid poster</u>
  <u t="515940">and he was sentenced to 15 years of forced labor</u>
  <u t="520100">to end up mysteriously killed.</u>
  <u t="524840">It's beautiful! I didn't expected like that!</u>
  <u t="527840">Yeah!</u>
  <u t="528920">Ehm..In our country hotels are divided ehm..in classes:</u>
  <u t="534780">special class, first class and second class.</u>
  <u t="538500">This is the special class hotel.</u>
  <u t="540400">Wow!</u>
  <u t="541880">This is your room card.</u>
  <u t="547900">Surreal!</u>
  <u t="550100">Cameras!</u>
  <u t="553160">Wow!</u>
  <u t="567060">I'm so exceited!</u>
  <u t="568660">Room number 20 on 37th floor.</u>
  <u t="573180">Et voilà!</u>
  <u t="574440">Pay attention...the room card</u>
  <u t="578660">Ahhhh! So..</u>
  <u t="580460">Wow! Look at here!</u>
  <u t="582160">I expected it much more modest,</u>
  <u t="583980">instead I have two beds, so I could sleep</u>
  <u t="587420">for half night in one and half night in the other.</u>
  <u t="591320">TV already on, on an channel..</u>
  <u t="594180">on a French channel. This is interesting!</u>
  <u t="597460">French channel..</u>
  <u t="598760">Let's see the view! Because I'm on the 37th floor.</u>
  <u t="601720">So.. perfect! I see absolutely nothing.</u>
  <u t="606340">Because...In North Korea the evening is completley dark,</u>
  <u t="610620">completely dark. I've yet to find out why.</u>
  <u t="613540">There is also a mini-bar</u>
  <u t="615120">Let's see what my mini-bar has to offer</u>
  <u t="617880">Magnificent! Delicacies from all over the world!</u>
  <u t="622500">The bathroom! I'm curious to see the bathroom.</u>
  <u t="625480">Ahhh..</u>
  <u t="626720">The bathroom is absolutely 50s.</u>
  <u t="630420">Marble! it looks fake! Perfect!</u>
  <u t="634600">curtain!... of shower,</u>
  <u t="637320">which sticks to you like a second skin when you take a shower.</u>
  <u t="641800">Toilet! And..</u>
  <u t="643340">perfect, there's also an inevitable phone for endless sessions</u>
  <u t="646760">on the toilet.</u>
  <u t="649600">Here there is a gas mask.</u>
  <u t="652500">Clearly, This is very important,</u>
  <u t="654540">especially for when you go to the toilet</u>
  <u t="657220">in a ..</u>
  <u t="658680">heavy way.</u>
  <u t="660900">Guys!..</u>
  <u t="662000">Let's find out what this special hotel hast to offer.</u>
  <u t="665240">Oh my..! There is everything!</u>
  <u t="668260">Barber, bowling, billiards</u>
  <u t="670660">ping-pong, karaoke, massages, sauna, pool</u>
  <u t="677100">I'm suprised about the hotel.</u>
  <u t="678600">I had very low expectations! and instead it's ..</u>
  <u t="682860">a classic Grand Hotel of the 50s</u>
  <u t="686740">I had seen many at the time,</u>
  <u t="689260">in the 50s. I had been in many hotels.</u>
  <u t="693020">However.. there are more than 500 rooms</u>
  <u t="697020">47 floors</u>
  <u t="698960">And I'm.. the only one in the hotel</u>
  <u t="701680">I haven't yet met anyone other than the employees.</u>
  <u t="708680">ok.</u>
  <u t="710960">Here We find every kind of things.</u>
  <u t="722240">I'm really curious to see all the extra activities</u>
  <u t="725180">on this -1 floor</u>
  <u t="727700">They told me I can't film anything inside,</u>
  <u t="730820">except table tannis, they mean ping-pong.</u>
  <u t="733920">So, let's see what I can.. This is ping-pong.</u>
  <u t="737900">Hi!</u>
  <u t="740720">Ehi! How you doing?</u>
  <u t="742220">Play ping pong?</u>
  <u t="743020">Do you wanna play with me?</u>
  <u t="744320">You? Me and you?</u>
  <u t="746020">Really?</u>
  <u t="747620">Let's go!</u>
  <u t="749140">Yeah! you good?</u>
  <u t="751520">I'm ok! lol</u>
  <u t="754280">Let's see what a figure of shit I'm going to do.</u>
  <u t="757560">She's a champion, for sure.</u>
  <u t="760880">Lol.</u>
  <u t="762880">She gave me the busted-up one, eh?!</u>
  <u t="764860">Damn!</u>
  <u t="765800">Guys, I haven't played in a lifetime.</u>
  <u t="768200">I'll try to do the best I can, but..</u>
  <u t="794640">Nooo!</u>
  <u t="813580">I'll explan this one, later!</u>
  <u t="820280">Yesss!</u>
  <u t="822500">I won!</u>
  <u t="823360">You won!</u>
  <u t="827220">Thank you very much!</u>
  <u t="828360">Thank you!</u>
  <u t="829340">And Italy win!</u>
  <u t="830700">North Korea against Italy</u>
  <u t="833260">North Korea against Italy.. unfortunally</u>
  <u t="836640">Lol!</u>
  <u t="838060">I won!</u>
  <u t="841200">Bye!</u>
  <u t="843800">It's starts with a bang!</u>
  <u t="845220">A great international challenge immediately:</u>
  <u t="847820">Italia - North Korea, deservedly won by</u>
  <u t="850860">athlete ..Giuseppe Bertuccio D'Angelo</u>
  <u t="855880">She was playing in heels.</u>
  <u t="858140">Luckly, otherwise she'd killed me.</u>
  <u t="862560">Being alone i such a big hotel</u>
  <u t="866020">It's a bit dismal.</u>
  <u t="867600">it scares me.</u>
  <u t="871320">Because you can't thing:</u>
  <u t="872580">I can do what I want, no!</u>
  <u t="873920">You know that as soon as you get wrong</u>
  <u t="876920">It's a good mess.</u>
  <u t="878300">Let's see what there is down stairs</u>
  <u t="883640">Here there is biliards.</u>
  <u t="885200">Hi!</u>
  <u t="885805">Hi! Hello!</u>
  <u t="889560">Can I enter?</u>
  <u t="891080">Biliardo?!</u>
  <u t="891820">Yeah! just to see..</u>
  <u t="895000">no?</u>
  <u t="895580">NO!</u>
  <u t="897160">ok, ok! Bye Bye!</u>
  <u t="899775">I'm alone, I'm alone inside here.</u>
  <u t="902565">Bowling.</u>
  <u t="908035">Hi!</u>
  <u t="909640">Can I see?</u>
  <u t="910420">Yes!</u>
  <u t="910940">Thank you!</u>
  <u t="916840">There's nobady!</u>
  <u t="918300">it's a little bit scary</u>
  <u t="920600">Noo</u>
  <u t="922315">No? You don't want?</u>
  <u t="924805">It looks closed, but actually it's Saturday night,</u>
  <u t="928700">ok that..</u>
  <u t="930680">..It's low season but</u>
  <u t="932600">It should be the karaoke.</u>
  <u t="943240">Tonight, it's Saturday night</u>
  <u t="945500">so this is the most you could expect.</u>
  <u t="948680">HI!</u>
  <u t="950300">Hi, Bye bye!</u>
  <u t="952460">ok, so kareoke is faild!</u>
  <u t="961015">Here there are the..</u>
  <u t="962945">pool, massages, sauna..</u>
  <u t="965915">Hello!</u>
  <u t="966665">Hello!</u>
  <u t="968020">Hi, nice to meet you!</u>
  <u t="970140">Can I?</u>
  <u t="971400">Massages..</u>
  <u t="976360">Sauna?</u>
  <u t="977240">Sauna, How much?</u>
  <u t="979440">How much it?</u>
  <u t="981160">Massages?</u>
  <u t="982060">Yeah!</u>
  <u t="983060">Massages?</u>
  <u t="985280">3,5 euros</u>
  <u t="987940">ok..</u>
  <u t="989200">ok this is..</u>
  <u t="990340">no? ok no!</u>
  <u t="992200">And I thought there.. but you know what?</u>
  <u t="994080">Let's try the massage north korean</u>
  <u t="995360">because.. Go out, I can't go out</u>
  <u t="997480">So.. let's try everything:</u>
  <u t="999880">Thank you! Bye bye!</u>
  <u t="1001880">Thank you for having beat me up for half an hour.</u>
  <u t="1005600">I paid to be..to be beaten for half an hour.</u>
  <u t="1009780">A 60-year-old lady.</u>
  <u t="1012340">She hung on hooks on the roof and she started to step on me.</u>
  <u t="1016940">I mean to step on me with her feet for half an hour.</u>
  <u t="1021100">I fell.. light</u>
  <u t="1024720">without her on me.</u>
  <u t="1026925">I think tour of the hotel</u>
  <u t="1030955">is enough for today, that's ok.</u>
  <u t="1061620">This is the light.</u>
  <u t="1072040">What the hell</u>
  <u t="1074160">It come off</u>
  <u t="1078880">Wait, wait, wait..</u>
  <u t="1083220">Let's see.. I find out something..</u>
  <u t="1088940">What's this?</u>
  <u t="1095920">You know what?</u>
  <u t="1098395">Let's do as I don't see anything</u>
  <u t="1102855">Before taking, I'd to check if there were cameras.</u>
  <u t="1106440">hidden bugs, but</u>
  <u t="1108820">apart from this strange bedside table, I didn't find anything</u>
  <u t="1114280">strange, so</u>
  <u t="1116380">I'm absolutely surprised</u>
  <u t="1118320">I thought they're going to controlled me every single step.</u>
  <u t="1121160">in every movement I did, instead</u>
  <u t="1122760">Everyone is very friendly, everyone is very kind.</u>
  <u t="1126980">I'm surprised, I'm surpreised..I didn't expect</u>
  <u t="1130040">a North Korea like this.</u>
  <u t="1131980">The only thing I can't do....... is leave the hotel alone.</u>
  <u t="1137040">it's not allowed to leave the hotel without my guides.</u>
  <u t="1141960">But...</u>
  <u t="1142680">I had good time tonight, so no problmes.</u>
  <u t="1146540">And I'm so lucky because my guides are my age</u>
  <u t="1149140">They are very young, super nice</u>
  <u t="1151720">and also super curious because they've never seen an Italian.</u>
  <u t="1154640">I'm the first Italian they met</u>
  <u t="1156640">so they've been asked me a billion questions about our country.</u>
  <u t="1159280">And it's wonderful to tell them how many beautiful things we have</u>
  <u t="1162200">and see the reaction in their eyes because</u>
  <u t="1164600">it's as if they were visiting our country throught my words.</u>
  <u t="1167940">So it's a beautiful feeling</u>
  <u t="1170940">But then there is another part of me</u>
  <u t="1173340">who would like to tell them a lot a mess of bullshit.</u>
  <u t="1175920">Like, our president is Topogigio.</u>
  <u t="1178000">to see if they're gonna belive it or not</u>
  <u t="1180380">but I'll hold back.. I won't do it, I promise.</u>
  <u t="1183380">I want to get in good to ask them</u>
  <u t="1186140">many questions as possible and to have more answers about their country, about happiness</u>
  <u t="1191100">I hope, hopefully they could answers.</u>
  <u t="1194575">Anyway I'm tired now, tomorrow I wake up at 6:30 h .</u>
  <u t="1197625">First day of visits.</u>
  <u t="1199905">Maybe I'd better go to bed now.</u>
  <u t="1202360">Goodnight!</u>
  <u t="1205920">In the next episode</u>
  <u t="1210120">It's..The situation isn't..</u>
  <u t="1215540">of the best.</u>
  <u t="1219740">And I think the guy is dead, I think is dead.</u>
  </text>
