<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="LkZzGX5uBVc" uploader="Project Happiness " channel="Project Happiness " likes="58025" title="DENTRO LA CITTÀ PIÙ RAZZISTA AL MONDO 🇿🇦" year="2025" month="11" day="12" date="20251112" is_ac="false">
  <u t="3966">Our policy is what in Afrikaans is called "apartheid".</u>
  <u t="10866">And I am afraid it has very often been misunderstood.</u>
  <u t="14266">It could just as easily, and perhaps much better, be described as a policy of good neighborliness.</u>
  <u t="27133">We are the descendants of those earlier generations of politicians and people who implemented apartheid,</u>
  <u t="36333">who dominated South Africa, who governed it rather well.</u>
  <u t="43066">This is an Afrikaner town, that is what we want to call it one day.</u>
  <u t="46566">A place where Afrikaners can come and feel at home.</u>
  <u t="49066">To feel that we belong to this place.</u>
  <u t="51100">This is our place.</u>
  <u t="53000">When you get permanent residence,</u>
  <u t="56366">you give us the right to call you at any time of the day or night to subject you to a drug test.</u>
  <u t="62433">Here we let the children play in the street without the fear that someone will take them away or run over them with a car.</u>
  <u t="69966">I do not have to look over my shoulder to see who will grab my bag when I go shopping.</u>
  <u t="76166">Here we are safe and we are really happy.</u>
  <u t="93299">My name is Giuseppe and I have a mission:</u>
  <u t="96633">to explore the most remote corners of the planet</u>
  <u t="99833">to meet guardians of ancient secrets,</u>
  <u t="102599">women and men with extraordinary stories</u>
  <u t="105900">and lives able to inspire us and make us see the world with different eyes.</u>
  <u t="111000">And to each of them I will ask the most important question of all:</u>
  <u t="115033">"What does happiness mean to you?"</u>
  <u t="117700">A question so powerful that it reveals the deepest essence of humanity.</u>
  <u t="125700">Welcome to "PROJECT HAPPINESS".</u>
  <u t="141233">This is the most racist town in the world.</u>
  <u t="143633">Or rather, that is the nickname given to Orania, a village of 3,000 strictly white Christian inhabitants.</u>
  <u t="149933">For some it is even the last stronghold of apartheid,</u>
  <u t="152599">while for others it is an example of cultural self determination.</u>
  <u t="156366">And we do not want to limit ourselves to judging, we want to see, talk, understand.</u>
  <u t="160866">Because the real question is: can you really live by creating a border with everything that is different?</u>
  <u t="165566">And what makes a person believe that this is the road to happiness?</u>
  <u t="169433">Well, we will find out together because today a great "Project Happiness" adventure is about to begin.</u>
  <u t="175433">Orania is right here, in the middle of nowhere, in the heart of South Africa.</u>
  <u t="179933">It was born in 1991, when the apartheid regime was collapsing.</u>
  <u t="184533">Apartheid, an Afrikaans word that means separation, was a political and social system of racial segregation,</u>
  <u t="191300">that ruled South Africa for almost 50 years.</u>
  <u t="194233">Imagine a country where whites and blacks lived separated in everything.</u>
  <u t="197766">Schools, transport, hospitals, beaches, even benches.</u>
  <u t="202099">But it was not just about separation.</u>
  <u t="204199">It was systemic inequality.</u>
  <u t="206033">Laws that guaranteed rights only to one part of the population.</u>
  <u t="209566">While the other was excluded from everything.</u>
  <u t="211866">At the end of the 1980s, however, under international pressure and internal uprisings,</u>
  <u t="216433">the white government understood that it could no longer hold on.</u>
  <u t="219333">But not everyone was ready for this change.</u>
  <u t="221666">Some Afrikaners, that is the minority that designed apartheid,</u>
  <u t="224733">feared that with the end of white supremacy they would lose not only power but also their identity.</u>
  <u t="230800">And so, a group of families bought an old abandoned construction site on the banks of the Orange River</u>
  <u t="235533">and began to build a town from zero.</u>
  <u t="237866">That is how Orania was born, an exclusively Afrikaner community.</u>
  <u t="241733">Not only white, but culturally Afrikaans.</u>
  <u t="244933">Here in fact they speak only Afrikaans.</u>
  <u t="247033">They study Afrikaner history and they practice the Calvinist religion just like a century ago.</u>
  <u t="251966">Orania is not just a place.</u>
  <u t="253733">It is an idea.</u>
  <u t="254533">An idea that you can defend your culture by creating your own world that is separate, closed and protected.</u>
  <u t="260100">There is something in this place that attracts you and pushes you away at the same time.</u>
  <u t="264633">In the street everything seems still.</u>
  <u t="266733">There is no one.</u>
  <u t="267833">But in reality there are eyes that are following us.</u>
  <u t="270366">And a simple friendly greeting is enough for us to be welcomed by one of the first inhabitants of Orania.</u>
  <u t="275466">Here we are safe and we are really happy.</u>
  <u t="279866">We want to stay among our Afrikaans people, where we can speak Afrikaans,</u>
  <u t="287033">where we can live our religion, our religious culture.</u>
  <u t="294300">And beyond that, be safe and protected.</u>
  <u t="301233">I do not have to look over my shoulder to see who will grab my bag when I go shopping.</u>
  <u t="307366">Or be anxious about what could happen to us while we sleep at night.</u>
  <u t="313899">And that is why we came to Orania.</u>
  <u t="317899">And among the 2,500 inhabitants who live here permanently,</u>
  <u t="321100">we also meet those who have just arrived with the goal of protecting their child's future.</u>
  <u t="326066">Here we let the children play in the street without the fear that someone will take them away or run over them with a car.</u>
  <u t="332766">Here he will definitely have opportunities to grow as a person and to learn our culture in his mother tongue.</u>
  <u t="342633">And he will be able to use it outside too, if he decides to.</u>
  <u t="348033">And he will also be a farmer!</u>
  <u t="349399">And he will also be a farmer!</u>
  <u t="353433">And then there are also those who think that the only road is to separate from those who are different.</u>
  <u t="357699">Do you feel more Oranian or South African?</u>
  <u t="361533">I see myself as an Oranian.</u>
  <u t="364000">My loyalty starts in Orania and then, partly, also outside.</u>
  <u t="368300">We do not necessarily see a future for us, culturally, outside Orania.</u>
  <u t="373866">For that we are in fact South Africans.</u>
  <u t="378100">We live in South Africa and we have ties all over the country with places that are dear to us.</u>
  <u t="383666">But first of all we are Oranians</u>
  <u t="386366">because it is here that we actively take part in the protection and preservation of our heritage.</u>
  <u t="392500">There are people who would not want us to exist.</u>
  <u t="396899">What do you think are the main misunderstandings?</u>
  <u t="399133">The main misunderstanding is that Orania is an organization or a town that is racist, based on race.</u>
  <u t="407466">Here in Orania, defending your identity does not only mean preserving it, but literally building it.</u>
  <u t="416533">It is really surprising to walk through the streets of Orania because it really looks like a construction site.</u>
  <u t="421899">The town is expanding a lot, there are workers, buildings on every corner of the street.</u>
  <u t="426899">And as you can see here it is full of bricks, they are very special bricks that the workers use here,</u>
  <u t="432000">they are insulating bricks because here the thermal difference between night and day is very strong.</u>
  <u t="438166">Especially also between winter and summer, when in winter it goes down to minus 5 degrees and in summer it goes up to plus 45 degrees.</u>
  <u t="444166">So these workers have to build houses that are habitable, livable for all the people who will arrive.</u>
  <u t="450833">They are more or less 3,000 people, but the goal is to welcome about 50,000 people in the next years.</u>
  <u t="455600">So imagine how this little town will change.</u>
  <u t="458433">And then there is also a very important detail that makes you understand the peculiarity of this little town.</u>
  <u t="462933">That is that all the structures must be lower than the trees.</u>
  <u t="466033">Because here the goal, the urban plan is to create a rural town.</u>
  <u t="470266">Not a town, a megalopolis like Cape Town or like Johannesburg, from which the Afrikaners are running away.</u>
  <u t="476566">Here the town has to be welcoming, human sized.</u>
  <u t="482800">We meet one of the engineers who has been given the most ambitious mission.</u>
  <u t="486833">To transform Orania from a small community into a great nation.</u>
  <u t="492800">Can you explain why Orania chooses not to employ black labor here?</u>
  <u t="497000">The reason is that we do not consider it morally acceptable</u>
  <u t="501800">to exploit the labor of other cultures for our own economic benefit.</u>
  <u t="508333">We have seen that it did not work.</u>
  <u t="509666">It does not work.</u>
  <u t="510933">It is not morally acceptable.</u>
  <u t="512700">And we had to change that.</u>
  <u t="516299">Furthermore we boost the economy because we economically empower our own people.</u>
  <u t="522899">This is an Afrikaner town.</u>
  <u t="524799">That is what we want to call it one day.</u>
  <u t="526700">A place where Afrikaners can come and feel at home.</u>
  <u t="529200">To feel that this is our place.</u>
  <u t="531200">This is our place.</u>
  <u t="532799">In Afrikaans we say: "Bou die stad, bou die toekoms."</u>
  <u t="536200">So build a town to build a future.</u>
  <u t="539100">This is my mission in Orania.</u>
  <u t="545533">Now it is clearer to me, for Orania to exist it needs many new citizens.</u>
  <u t="550333">Afrikaners scattered all over the continent who will answer the call to join this mission.</u>
  <u t="555433">But it is not enough just to want to live in Orania.</u>
  <u t="557633">To enter you have to pass a very strict selection by a committee based on three fundamental criteria.</u>
  <u t="564866">The person is an Afrikaner who speaks Afrikaans fluently.</u>
  <u t="569866">They are a person who is able to provide for themselves.</u>
  <u t="572766">We do not have a big government that supports people economically,</u>
  <u t="576366">so you have to be able to find a job or start a business or have enough savings, and so on.</u>
  <u t="581933">We check whether they have a criminal record and a drug record.</u>
  <u t="585366">Is the person coming here to harm our large population of children that we have in Orania?</u>
  <u t="590466">Or will they be safe from things like drugs, abuse and violence?</u>
  <u t="598266">And finally, also the cultural aspect.</u>
  <u t="602966">Do they profess our beliefs? Do they share our Christian faith? And so on.</u>
  <u t="606866">Even if this could give the impression that it is a very, very strict set of guidelines.</u>
  <u t="611600">In reality it is a very basic set of guidelines.</u>
  <u t="614166">And if you want to enter this community, this space for Afrikaners, these are some of the principles that we keep here.</u>
  <u t="621166">I was imagining the scenario in which I was an Afrikaner who lives in Orania,</u>
  <u t="629366">but then, while studying abroad, I fell in love with a Xhosa woman, a black woman.</u>
  <u t="637266">We get married and we come back to Orania.</u>
  <u t="641066">Can I live in Orania with my wife?</u>
  <u t="643966">That person therefore is not an Afrikaner person.</u>
  <u t="647266">All right, well, remember that Orania is a place for Afrikaners.</u>
  <u t="650466">Many people in these cases would choose a more multicultural town.</u>
  <u t="652866">Anyone can apply, but then they should convince the council.</u>
  <u t="658466">What do you think is the main motivation that pushes people to move to Orania?</u>
  <u t="662833">Is it fear?</u>
  <u t="664299">Is it anger?</u>
  <u t="666000">Or is it the fact of living in a complicated country where they no longer feel safe?</u>
  <u t="672200">Even if these are all reasons why people move to Orania.</u>
  <u t="675600">The incredible corruption.</u>
  <u t="677500">The blatant failure of services in South Africa.</u>
  <u t="680666">The terrible farm murders.</u>
  <u t="682399">They are definitely all contributing factors and we classify them as push factors.</u>
  <u t="686899">But I hope and believe that for many the pull factors are more important.</u>
  <u t="691333">I would like to see a perfect South Africa where there are no potholes in the roads,</u>
  <u t="696266">where there is no crime, where there is nothing wrong and people still choose Orania.</u>
  <u t="702366">And before saying goodbye to Joost, we exchange a few euros with the Ora, Orania’s local currency.</u>
  <u t="707766">It has absolutely no legal value outside here, nor can it in any way replace the South African Rand,</u>
  <u t="713333">but inside the community it is accepted everywhere.</u>
  <u t="716166">In practice it is a voucher system created to keep the money inside the community and strengthen self sufficiency.</u>
  <u t="723866">There is no doubt that safety is one of the reasons why so many choose Orania.</u>
  <u t="728433">Here there are absolutely no thefts, assaults or organized crime.</u>
  <u t="732233">But that does not mean there is no one protecting the town.</u>
  <u t="735600">Police?</u>
  <u t="736466">Present.</u>
  <u t="737433">Firefighters?</u>
  <u t="738500">Also.</u>
  <u t="739466">Ambulance?</u>
  <u t="740433">Sure.</u>
  <u t="741333">But there is just one tiny detail.</u>
  <u t="743799">It is always the same person answering.</u>
  <u t="749033">We are the security department.</u>
  <u t="751833">We are the police.</u>
  <u t="753100">We are the firefighters.</u>
  <u t="754333">We are the water department.</u>
  <u t="756166">Basically, everything that concerns law and order in town, we do it.</u>
  <u t="761333">I imagine you do not have much work to do because Orania is a very safe place.</u>
  <u t="765766">Orania is very safe, but we have to make sure it is safe just outside the borders too.</u>
  <u t="771966">We do not have jurisdiction outside, but it works like a target.</u>
  <u t="776766">In the center there is Orania.</u>
  <u t="778966">If Orania is safe, then it will also be safe outside.</u>
  <u t="783466">That is why we have measures in place.</u>
  <u t="785633">If you want to come and live here, besides everything else you have to do, we take fingerprints.</u>
  <u t="790733">And that way we can see whether you have a criminal record or not.</u>
  <u t="796200">Unfortunately drugs also get here in town, so we do random drug tests.</u>
  <u t="800766">And when you stay here, when you get permanent residence, you sign it.</u>
  <u t="807600">And by signing, you authorize us, as law enforcement</u>
  <u t="813533">to call you at any time of the day or night to subject you to a drug test.</u>
  <u t="819433">And to move from a social experiment to a real town, there are various stages.</u>
  <u t="822966">One of these is to build schools, colleges, universities like the one you see behind me,</u>
  <u t="828166">which however is unique in its kind, because inside there are no desks, there are no books,</u>
  <u t="832566">but there are small building sites where young people come here to study to become the next electricians,</u>
  <u t="838299">the next plumbers, the next bricklayers who will build the great Afrikaner city.</u>
  <u t="844399">I am here and I am here to build.</u>
  <u t="847366">We are in the middle of the building phase to make Orania better and stronger.</u>
  <u t="852799">Right now it is an extraordinary time and place to be a citizen of Orania.</u>
  <u t="857299">It is the most exciting, the most demanding and difficult part of a project and of the community’s and the country’s progress.</u>
  <u t="867533">And to be part of it, it is a great honor to be part of it now.</u>
  <u t="872533">I am proud to be Afrikaner and I love our culture.</u>
  <u t="875299">Certain things happen in South Africa.</u>
  <u t="876566">I cannot study in my language, for me it is difficult.</u>
  <u t="879700">That is what makes Orania beautiful.</u>
  <u t="881299">Here I can study, I can feel comfortable.</u>
  <u t="883466">I do not want to go to campus and hear some group chanting to kill my culture,</u>
  <u t="888566">to kill the people who belong to my culture.</u>
  <u t="890533">If the roles were reversed and I said, "Listen, let us kill this kind of people."</u>
  <u t="893566">If I sang that song at college and things like that,</u>
  <u t="895666">they would arrest me very quickly.</u>
  <u t="897399">So there is a bit of discrimination going on.</u>
  <u t="913000">Napo, where are you from?</u>
  <u t="915266">I am Peruvian.</u>
  <u t="916466">Near Orania?</u>
  <u t="917633">More or less.</u>
  <u t="918299">More or less, right!?</u>
  <u t="919466">Well, Napoleon and I are building the new "Project Happiness" house,</u>
  <u t="923666">but there is one thing that cannot be missing, and that is protection.</u>
  <u t="926799">And you already know with what!</u>
  <u t="928200">With "NordVPN" which protects everything we do online.</u>
  <u t="931533">It connects you securely, encrypts your data and lets you browse as if you were in another country.</u>
  <u t="936166">It also blocks viruses, annoying ads and warns you if your credentials end up on the Dark Web.</u>
  <u t="941366">And the most important thing is that with just one subscription you can protect up to 10 devices,</u>
  <u t="945500">so the whole team, which is not here now, will be protected.</u>
  <u t="949399">How long is this broom?</u>
  <u t="950700">And then it is perfect if you travel or work remotely or you simply want to browse without risks.</u>
  <u t="955566">It is like having a digital alarm system always on wherever you are.</u>
  <u t="959766">And as always by scanning this QR code or clicking the link in the description</u>
  <u t="963166">you can try "NordVPN" with a special offer.</u>
  <u t="965666">And if you are not satisfied you will have 30 days to change your mind, satisfied or refunded.</u>
  <u t="969533">And now let us go back to Orania.</u>
  <u t="977500">There is no doubt that here every citizen is truly proud</u>
  <u t="981299">to be part of this community, to live in Orania.</u>
  <u t="983833">In fact you can see it from all the flags that are displayed outside the houses,</u>
  <u t="987933">outside the buildings, like this one.</u>
  <u t="989966">And the flag however is very symbolic because it recalls the colors of the former South African flag</u>
  <u t="994933">of 1984, before the end of apartheid.</u>
  <u t="998166">There is blue, white, yellow, but this one has a special symbol,</u>
  <u t="1002833">it has a man rolling up his sleeves to get to work, to get down to it.</u>
  <u t="1007133">And it is actually a very direct message because here in Orania they want to remind everyone</u>
  <u t="1011500">that this community was built with effort, piece by piece, without external help.</u>
  <u t="1016700">And it is in fact a source of pride for them to be self sufficient and do everything by themselves,</u>
  <u t="1020766">even if it means staying closed off from the rest of the world.</u>
  <u t="1023933">And by looking closely at this flag you understand a lot about Orania,</u>
  <u t="1027133">this need to build walls, literally and symbolically, to defend their identity.</u>
  <u t="1035133">But there is just one man who can really help us understand what Orania is.</u>
  <u t="1039066">His name is Carel Boshoff, none other than the grandson of Hendrik Verwoerd, the father of apartheid.</u>
  <u t="1045500">But above all, the son of the man who founded Orania in the 1990s, while the old South Africa was collapsing.</u>
  <u t="1052433">In a sense, Carel is a man suspended between two worlds,</u>
  <u t="1055866">the world of imposed separation and the world of chosen separation.</u>
  <u t="1061033">I think people might be surprised by the books you have here.</u>
  <u t="1067933">Some might be surprised by them.</u>
  <u t="1069433">Yes, yes, yes, yes.</u>
  <u t="1070633">No, it is... it is interesting.</u>
  <u t="1075233">Mr. Mandela, who visited Orania, was in a certain sense... how could we call it?</u>
  <u t="1083766">He almost became a family friend.</u>
  <u t="1086766">Really?</u>
  <u t="1088266">Well, I am obviously emphasizing it, but yes.</u>
  <u t="1092566">And what did Mandela think of Orania?</u>
  <u t="1097166">I think he believed it was a passing phenomenon.</u>
  <u t="1102833">He did not think it would last?</u>
  <u t="1104033">He did not think it would last.</u>
  <u t="1105533">No, he thought: "All right, if they have to adapt, let them adapt."</u>
  <u t="1110066">He was never, um, destructively hostile towards Orania.</u>
  <u t="1115566">So, for that we are glad.</u>
  <u t="1118633">The first question might sound a bit harsh.</u>
  <u t="1122400">People outside Orania believe this is one of the most racist towns in the world.</u>
  <u t="1129900">What do you think of this label?</u>
  <u t="1134066">Seen from the outside, you only see a group of white people living together,</u>
  <u t="1139033">who are creating a new community by living together.</u>
  <u t="1142366">From our point of view, it is not about being white.</u>
  <u t="1146200">It is about language and culture and about those bonds</u>
  <u t="1151900">that hold people together in a community, even in a wider social community.</u>
  <u t="1157799">We are the descendants of those earlier generations of politicians and people who implemented apartheid,</u>
  <u t="1166733">who dominated South Africa, who governed it rather well.</u>
  <u t="1172299">We are their descendants physically, but also, in some ways, intellectually.</u>
  <u t="1179133">We are not categorically rejecting where we come from, but we are reinventing that way of thinking.</u>
  <u t="1186166">South Africa, for reasons that are not hard to understand, even from our point of view, does not look kindly on us.</u>
  <u t="1196366">In the past we were too dominant.</u>
  <u t="1201766">We were perhaps a bit overbearing with our values and our ways of operating.</u>
  <u t="1210933">The effect, unfortunately, is that even our language, or perhaps precisely our language, is not liked</u>
  <u t="1219266">and it is represented as the language of the oppressor.</u>
  <u t="1223099">We are discriminated against, but that is not the biggest problem...</u>
  <u t="1229599">Bigger than that is that we are being killed.</u>
  <u t="1233766">Our people are being killed.</u>
  <u t="1235433">Right now South Africa is a violent country.</u>
  <u t="1240200">Every day someone of ours is killed on the farms or in the cities, everywhere.</u>
  <u t="1246366">And we are a small people.</u>
  <u t="1247633">It cannot go on like this.</u>
  <u t="1249166">We cannot live like this.</u>
  <u t="1250133">Like this we will not survive.</u>
  <u t="1252066">And that is why, besides other perhaps more idealistic reasons,</u>
  <u t="1257666">we concretely need a safe harbor and a national home for our people.</u>
  <u t="1262666">How do you see the future of Orania?</u>
  <u t="1265366">Western civilization is entering a very demanding phase.</u>
  <u t="1270333">So our best future is to be part of the next phase, the postcolonial phase of Western civilization.</u>
  <u t="1282966">And I pray, hope and work so that Orania will have this role in the future.</u>
  <u t="1291966">What I wonder though is, can a culture survive if it never meets the other?</u>
  <u t="1296599">Or does it simply become a castle built on the idea that everything that is different is a threat?</u>
  <u t="1302733">I go looking for answers with Joost, at the highest and most symbolic point in Orania.</u>
  <u t="1307233">Monument Hill.</u>
  <u t="1308633">And while we chat, as if framing us all around,</u>
  <u t="1311633">there are the busts of the founding fathers of apartheid and of this town.</u>
  <u t="1315666">And there, with the sun setting over the community that he himself is selecting one by one,</u>
  <u t="1320466">I ask him a question that has been bouncing around in my head since I arrived in Orania.</u>
  <u t="1325633">Do you ever feel here that you are disconnected from the rest of the world?</u>
  <u t="1329700">It does not mean we do not see what is happening in the world, both the good and the bad.</u>
  <u t="1332866">It does not mean we do not know people from other places and other tribes and other nations who do things differently from us.</u>
  <u t="1339400">We are aware, we are connected in that sense.</u>
  <u t="1342433">But we are also connected to ourselves, to our people, to our, to our religion.</u>
  <u t="1347966">And we work precisely for this, to have even more connection in this sense.</u>
  <u t="1351466">That is what we dream of.</u>
  <u t="1352599">What do you think your mission here in Orania is?</u>
  <u t="1356033">To be part of Orania’s bigger mission.</u>
  <u t="1358400">And that is to create a home.</u>
  <u t="1360333">We all know it... instinctively we know we need a home.</u>
  <u t="1363099">A home is protection from the elements, it is a safe place, it is a place where you can be yourself.</u>
  <u t="1369866">And that is what Orania has to be, a home for the people.</u>
  <u t="1373000">What does happiness mean here in Orania?</u>
  <u t="1376400">I think that for the people of Orania, happiness means...</u>
  <u t="1380966">having the possibility to have an impact on the future.</u>
  <u t="1384166">To be builders of the future.</u>
  <u t="1385333">Not being extremely worried about the future because you are busy building it.</u>
  <u t="1392200">If the future worries you, create it.</u>
  <u t="1395733">You have to create the future.</u>
  <u t="1397266">And that is why Orania’s symbol is a young man rolling up his sleeves to work.</u>
  <u t="1402000">And... if the tragedy is to have no influence on the future,</u>
  <u t="1406900">happiness is to have at least a little.</u>
  <u t="1412400">For Joost and his citizens, Orania is a dream.</u>
  <u t="1415333">A dream born from the fear of disappearing, from the will to stay the same while everything around is changing.</u>
  <u t="1421666">It is the dream of those who want to protect a language, a faith, a past and write their own future without interference though.</u>
  <u t="1428766">But it is a fragile dream, because it stands on a border drawn to keep the other out.</u>
  <u t="1433866">The other who is different, distant, often difficult to understand.</u>
  <u t="1438733">And yet we are in South Africa.</u>
  <u t="1440299">A country where diversity is everywhere.</u>
  <u t="1442833">Where cultures mix and right there they find strength.</u>
  <u t="1446366">Maybe I did not understand everything and maybe some things escape me because I do not have their history.</u>
  <u t="1451466">I do not speak their language, but if in order to exist you have to exclude</u>
  <u t="1454666">and if to defend a culture every door to the world is shut,</u>
  <u t="1457766">well, then I do not know if this is a community or a fortress.</u>
  <u t="1462066">Because after all our travels around the world, I have understood that identity, if it is alive,</u>
  <u t="1466966">is not afraid of encounters.</u>
  <u t="1468866">It evolves, it transforms and it grows.</u>
  <u t="1471433">And maybe the only way not to get lost is to change.</u>
  <u t="1475433">But without ever stopping recognizing yourself.</u>
  </text>
