<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="s6j35KUQusc" uploader="Sammy and Tommy" channel="Sammy and Tommy" likes="2257" title="FIRST TIME in AMSTERDAM, NETHERLANDS...it was more chaotic than we expected" year="2025" month="7" day="5" date="20250705" date_ts="1751720505" is_ac="true">
  <u t="2000">Good morning from Amsterdam, you guys. I</u>
  <u t="4000">am super stoked to be here. This city</u>
  <u t="5520">has been on my bucket list for such a</u>
  <u t="7120">long time. Today we are me. Look who's</u>
  <u t="10080">behind you. What?</u>
  <u t="12719">Oh, mom and dad. Hey. Hey. Hello.</u>
  <u t="16960">Welcome.</u>
  <u t="18720">Come on in here. Oh, that was so cute.</u>
  <u t="20880">Hi, guys. Come on over here. All right.</u>
  <u t="23600">So, we are very excited for the next</u>
  <u t="25199">several days. We're traveling with my</u>
  <u t="26720">parents, Tom and Jackie. Some of you</u>
  <u t="28640">guys probably know him as well. And no</u>
  <u t="30480">better way to start than here in the</u>
  <u t="32239">unique city of Amsterdam.</u>
  <u t="34559">Oh,</u>
  <u t="36900">[Music]</u>
  <u t="51120">thank you so much. I appreciate that. No</u>
  <u t="52399">worries. Have a good holiday.</u>
  <u t="57120">So, we arrived here yesterday from Paris</u>
  <u t="59520">on the Euro Star. We used our Euro</u>
  <u t="61440">passes, so that was quick and easy. I</u>
  <u t="63760">love taking the fast trains. And Tom and</u>
  <u t="66080">Jackie arrived here from Spain. They've</u>
  <u t="68000">also been exploring a bit of Europe,</u>
  <u t="69840">doing their own thing, and now we're all</u>
  <u t="71280">together here in Amsterdam. We're</u>
  <u t="72960">actually staying a little bit outside of</u>
  <u t="74400">Amsterdam in the cutest lodging and more</u>
  <u t="77119">affordable. So, we can show you guys</u>
  <u t="78560">that a little bit later on in the video.</u>
  <u t="80479">One of my favorite things about being</u>
  <u t="81920">here in Europe is that yesterday we were</u>
  <u t="84640">just surrounded by people speaking</u>
  <u t="86560">French, French architecture, baguettes,</u>
  <u t="88560">macarons, you know, all the French</u>
  <u t="90640">things. And then we've traveled just</u>
  <u t="92000">like a few hours over and everything is</u>
  <u t="95360">so Dutch, all the architecture, the</u>
  <u t="97759">windmills, the canals, the tulips, and</u>
  <u t="100960">yeah, we're just really excited to be</u>
  <u t="102640">here together as a family and getting</u>
  <u t="104640">our first impressions of the city.</u>
  <u t="107920">Heat. Heat.</u>
  <u t="110580">[Music]</u>
  <u t="118660">[Music]</u>
  <u t="130419">[Music]</u>
  <u t="135599">Oh, what did you got? Got us a treat.</u>
  <u t="137920">These are called chest mini Dutch</u>
  <u t="140640">pancakes. And we got the original with</u>
  <u t="142800">butter and sugar. And I got two forks</u>
  <u t="145440">just for me and you, Jackie. All right.</u>
  <u t="146800">No sharing. No sharing.</u>
  <u t="151440">Crispy on the outside. Buttery and</u>
  <u t="153120">sugar. Has really good flavor. Yeah, I</u>
  <u t="154959">like it. And we came to a coffee shop,</u>
  <u t="156480">so we're going to have our pancakes and</u>
  <u t="157599">coffee. Cheers. It was funny when I was</u>
  <u t="159680">asking the guys at the pancake shop. I</u>
  <u t="161280">was like, "Oh, is there a restaurant</u>
  <u t="162319">nearby?" And he's recommended this cafe.</u>
  <u t="163920">It's called Momento. And he's like, "But</u>
  <u t="165680">make sure it's a coffee store or a cafe,</u>
  <u t="168080">not a coffee shop." Cuz that is very</u>
  <u t="170480">different.</u>
  <u t="172080">[Music]</u>
  <u t="175360">What's your name? Yura. Yura. Yeah.</u>
  <u t="177360">That's a cool name, man. That's unique.</u>
  <u t="178720">Where you from? Here. Are you? Yeah.</u>
  <u t="180720">Yeah. You must love it. Such a beautiful</u>
  <u t="182400">city. It's a nice city. What were you</u>
  <u t="184959">telling me about the wall? But it's it's</u>
  <u t="186720">the original 1680s 1680s one. So that's</u>
  <u t="190319">interesting. Like you can see here the</u>
  <u t="192319">the wood.</u>
  <u t="194640">Oh yeah.</u>
  <u t="197360">That's awesome. And thanks for nice to</u>
  <u t="199040">meet you.</u>
  <u t="205680">So as we're walking by all these canals,</u>
  <u t="207120">you you'll notice the houses are super</u>
  <u t="209280">narrow, like super skinny and tall.</u>
  <u t="211680">That's because back in the 17th century,</u>
  <u t="213760">the houses were taxed based on the width</u>
  <u t="216159">of the houses. So the less wide, the</u>
  <u t="219599">more tax breaks they got, the more money</u>
  <u t="221120">they saved.</u>
  <u t="223680">[Music]</u>
  <u t="230400">What do you think so far, man? Is it</u>
  <u t="231599">living up to the hype? This is better</u>
  <u t="233680">than anything I expected. True. I expect</u>
  <u t="237120">the beautiful canal and the you know the</u>
  <u t="239920">old buildings but the atmosphere is</u>
  <u t="243599">overwhelming for me. It's beautiful.</u>
  <u t="246239">It's casual. Just feels good. It is very</u>
  <u t="249200">relaxed.</u>
  <u t="255870">[Music]</u>
  <u t="261260">[Music]</u>
  <u t="264080">This is an Frank's house. Obviously, as</u>
  <u t="266960">you can tell by the line, it is one of</u>
  <u t="269199">the biggest tourist draws in Amsterdam.</u>
  <u t="271680">Have to probably buy your tickets a</u>
  <u t="273199">couple weeks in advance. Uh we weren't</u>
  <u t="275199">able to get in for a tour, but kind of</u>
  <u t="278320">glad we didn't because it looks like</u>
  <u t="279919">there's a lot of renovations going on.</u>
  <u t="281680">It's hard to get a feel of what the</u>
  <u t="283600">house really looks like from the</u>
  <u t="285040">outside. Yeah.</u>
  <u t="287910">[Music]</u>
  <u t="290720">He's</u>
  <u t="293410">[Music]</u>
  <u t="304479">a beautiful.</u>
  <u t="318240">I went off script. I saw the cutest</u>
  <u t="320400">little shop. So, I had to pop in and I</u>
  <u t="323280">bought the cutest ring. Another ring.</u>
  <u t="326160">And I didn't even tell you guys. I</u>
  <u t="327759">picked up these other two little rings</u>
  <u t="329199">in Paris and some earrings. That's my</u>
  <u t="332080">favorite little souvenir because I can</u>
  <u t="334000">just put it on and travel with it. It</u>
  <u t="335440">doesn't take up any space in my luggage.</u>
  <u t="337039">So,</u>
  <u t="339150">[Music]</u>
  <u t="350800">[Music]</u>
  <u t="352639">So, this city is obviously known for its</u>
  <u t="354479">canal system, which stretches over 100</u>
  <u t="356160">km long, and they have over 1,300</u>
  <u t="358639">bridges, which is three times the amount</u>
  <u t="360960">that Venice has. It's hard not to</u>
  <u t="363120">compare the city with Venice. Me and dad</u>
  <u t="365120">were already talking about it. Just so</u>
  <u t="366880">much more relaxed, so much more room to</u>
  <u t="368479">get around.</u>
  <u t="370080">I want to cry but love you till I die.</u>
  <u t="378080">The guy we met at the coffee shop</u>
  <u t="379440">earlier was so sweet. He directed us to</u>
  <u t="381680">this cute little place which is a</u>
  <u t="383199">traditional Dutch diner since 1945. And</u>
  <u t="386479">he told us what to order. Some little</u>
  <u t="389120">roast beef sandwiches. Tommy got a</u>
  <u t="390880">salted beef sandwich. And I think</u>
  <u t="392800">classically you're supposed to get it</u>
  <u t="393919">with milk. Tommy came back with a glass</u>
  <u t="395759">of chocolate milk. He went rogue. I</u>
  <u t="398160">don't think it's the same, but it looks</u>
  <u t="399840">yummy. It's on the menu. Has to be good.</u>
  <u t="401600">Mom said it was on the menu. So,</u>
  <u t="403440">chocolate milk. And we also got a order</u>
  <u t="405680">of bitter ball.</u>
  <u t="410080">That's a great recommendation. Love the</u>
  <u t="411600">vibe of this place. It's super busy.</u>
  <u t="413120">Looks like a ton of locals. People are</u>
  <u t="414720">just sitting up at the bar and the</u>
  <u t="416720">workers are uh humorous. Humorous. It's</u>
  <u t="420240">good work for it. Cheers, you guys. Look</u>
  <u t="422240">how delicious that looks. They they</u>
  <u t="424479">serve it to you like right away. Sam's</u>
  <u t="426960">making fun of me. How good does that</u>
  <u t="428479">look? I haven't had chocolate milk since</u>
  <u t="429919">like the second grade.</u>
  <u t="434000">So simple, but oh so good. Good. That's</u>
  <u t="438000">good beef. And not only that, the</u>
  <u t="441199">mustard's amazing for some reason, isn't</u>
  <u t="443039">it?</u>
  <u t="444639">Obviously, I think the the salted one is</u>
  <u t="447440">better. Look, it's his almost gone</u>
  <u t="449440">already.</u>
  <u t="451520">The bitter ball are like a Dutch snack</u>
  <u t="454240">food. They're like ve or ragu meatballs</u>
  <u t="458800">I think in the sauce and then deep</u>
  <u t="460720">fried. So I think it's a little bit</u>
  <u t="462400">misleading this crispy exterior. I think</u>
  <u t="464639">they're going to be not so crispy on the</u>
  <u t="466560">inside. And you dip them in mustard</u>
  <u t="470260">[Music]</u>
  <u t="474960">crispy.</u>
  <u t="476960">That is so good. It's like a like a</u>
  <u t="480800">stew. A deep fried stew ball.</u>
  <u t="483039">Interesting. Why does Sammy get to go</u>
  <u t="485360">first all the time? You can tell I came</u>
  <u t="487759">from a family with a lot of siblings. I</u>
  <u t="490639">kind of feel like I'm in Willy Wonka</u>
  <u t="492319">land. You know, when you bite into it,</u>
  <u t="494319">it's a full meal. Roast beef, potatoes,</u>
  <u t="496960">and gravy. It's so true.</u>
  <u t="500080">Hey, the second course is coming up.</u>
  <u t="502240">Roast beef and a baked potato.</u>
  <u t="506800">That cafe was felt so authentic. The</u>
  <u t="509360">ladies were so sweet working there, too.</u>
  <u t="511360">And the food was so good. So good. We</u>
  <u t="513279">had to go back for seconds.</u>
  <u t="515130">[Music]</u>
  <u t="520320">What do you think of the alternate</u>
  <u t="521519">thinker? Well, I think that I just saw</u>
  <u t="523760">the original in Paris 2 days ago.</u>
  <u t="526920">[Music]</u>
  <u t="530160">So, after all that salted beef, we're a</u>
  <u t="532320">little thirsty. So, it's time for some</u>
  <u t="534720">beers. We wouldn't be hanging out</u>
  <u t="536720">together. It wouldn't feel right if we</u>
  <u t="537839">didn't have some beers now, right? Back</u>
  <u t="539839">with the crew. And I was going to take</u>
  <u t="541440">him to a sweet treat and Jackie was</u>
  <u t="542880">like, "I think I'm filling a drink on a</u>
  <u t="544480">terrace." I was like, "That sounds</u>
  <u t="546480">pretty good, too." Thank you.</u>
  <u t="550660">[Music]</u>
  <u t="553200">Cheers, you guys. Amsterdam. Amsterdam.</u>
  <u t="579600">One of the things I was most excited for</u>
  <u t="580959">about coming to Amsterdam is or Holland</u>
  <u t="584000">in general is their shroop waffles. This</u>
  <u t="586800">is like I love having these back at</u>
  <u t="588800">home, but this is fresh, so I'm super</u>
  <u t="590720">stoked about that. Look like mom got a</u>
  <u t="592959">fancy one. Chocolate and raspberries.</u>
  <u t="595440">Amazing. Let's dig in. I feel like</u>
  <u t="598399">mine's not as good as the ones I bought</u>
  <u t="599839">from the store. The raspberry is</u>
  <u t="602000">amazing.</u>
  <u t="604399">I know that's not what I'm supposed to</u>
  <u t="606000">be commenting on, but yeah.</u>
  <u t="622060">[Music]</u>
  <u t="632000">We've just come to walk through Vondo</u>
  <u t="633600">Park. It's so nice during sunset hour</u>
  <u t="635839">right now. It is busy. You got to very</u>
  <u t="638640">much stay vigilant with the bicycles and</u>
  <u t="640560">the runners, etc. But it's so nice</u>
  <u t="642640">because I love like the river with the</u>
  <u t="644160">tulip beds and the parakeetses in the</u>
  <u t="646640">trees. Yeah, great way to spend the</u>
  <u t="648640">evening. I don't ever think I've seen a</u>
  <u t="650399">river that has like floating flower beds</u>
  <u t="653519">in it. And this river just has like</u>
  <u t="655519">floating tullet beds. It's like the most</u>
  <u t="657279">unique, beautiful, colorful thing. It's</u>
  <u t="659920">so adorable, right? Very unique. It's</u>
  <u t="662640">very cool. Yeah.</u>
  <u t="664500">[Music]</u>
  <u t="685070">[Music]</u>
  <u t="690880">Nice size boat.</u>
  <u t="694079">So, we're ending our day. We rented our</u>
  <u t="695839">own boat. It was only €80 a couple,</u>
  <u t="697680">which is really nice. We looked in a lot</u>
  <u t="698959">of the group tours, but they look busy.</u>
  <u t="701440">It's just nice having our own boat to</u>
  <u t="703519">explore all the canals we want. We</u>
  <u t="705120">bought some snack seed as well. Now</u>
  <u t="707760">we're just relaxing. We're going to wait</u>
  <u t="709200">until the lights come on, too, to see</u>
  <u t="710720">all the reflective lights and Amsterdam</u>
  <u t="712959">at night. So, I think we timed it</u>
  <u t="714480">perfectly. How you feeling, Capitan?</u>
  <u t="717519">Feeling good. Okay,</u>
  <u t="721279">we went to the grocery store and picked</u>
  <u t="723040">up some drinks.</u>
  <u t="725120">Little gin and tonic and a can. It's our</u>
  <u t="727360">favorite. And tang, too. Cheers. Tanker</u>
  <u t="730800">should sponsor us. That's terrible. I</u>
  <u t="733360">didn't say that. No, they should. That'd</u>
  <u t="734880">be amazing. So, we also picked up some</u>
  <u t="736320">snacks. Some nuts, salami, olives, and</u>
  <u t="739040">cheese. Perfect. And some chips and</u>
  <u t="740720">things like that. So, yeah. Cheers.</u>
  <u t="753820">[Music]</u>
  <u t="768160">So Sammy wasn't very happy with me that</u>
  <u t="769760">I booked a boat cruise so late and she</u>
  <u t="772399">didn't want to get her own boat. But</u>
  <u t="774320">aren't you glad we did now? Yes. Only</u>
  <u t="776480">because of the price. I was like €80 a</u>
  <u t="778560">couple only. It was 60 a piece to go on</u>
  <u t="780560">a group tour with a bunch of other</u>
  <u t="782560">people. But we saw the ones that you</u>
  <u t="784000">could pay 30 or 40 and it's it's worth</u>
  <u t="787040">the extra money. Oh man, so nice. The</u>
  <u t="789440">timing too is spectacular. The lighting</u>
  <u t="791120">is so nice. I love snacks on a boat. I</u>
  <u t="794480">just it's just so just love it. Snacks</u>
  <u t="797519">on a boat. Can't beat it.</u>
  <u t="809610">[Music]</u>
  <u t="813839">This is the life. Yeah. Great move.</u>
  <u t="816880">Perfect. Hey, is there a better way to</u>
  <u t="818720">see Amsterdam than this? I don't think</u>
  <u t="820399">so. No.</u>
  <u t="826160">Second Stroop Waffle today. The store</u>
  <u t="828320">brand. I like these better.</u>
  <u t="832450">[Music]</u>
  <u t="835600">All right. Lights are coming on.</u>
  <u t="842080">[Music]</u>
  <u t="848180">[Music]</u>
  <u t="852560">It's so pretty. Oh, it's so nice.</u>
  <u t="863440">I am</u>
  <u t="866930">[Music]</u>
  <u t="872320">without the night.</u>
  <u t="875300">[Music]</u>
  <u t="884560">We're back. It was great. So fun, right?</u>
  <u t="886399">Everybody enjoyed it. Fabulous.</u>
  <u t="888079">Beautiful and really nice. Okay, now the</u>
  <u t="891360">big question. Do we want to walk through</u>
  <u t="892480">the red light district?</u>
  <u t="894959">Red light district. I mean, you seem</u>
  <u t="898639">hankering for it. I just want to see it.</u>
  <u t="901040">She can't go to Amsterdam without going</u>
  <u t="902720">to the red light district. And nobody</u>
  <u t="905440">else I'd rather go with than my parents</u>
  <u t="907040">and my wife.</u>
  <u t="909040">[Music]</u>
  <u t="915279">everything.</u>
  <u t="928240">Okay, we just walked through the</u>
  <u t="929519">district. Many pretty ladies, right?</u>
  <u t="932399">Yeah, just a bunch of pretty ladies and</u>
  <u t="933680">windows and lots of lights. Lots of</u>
  <u t="935440">street food, actually, too. Such a great</u>
  <u t="936959">day here in Amsterdam. We'll see you</u>
  <u t="938720">guys tomorrow. We're going to explore,</u>
  <u t="940000">show you guys where we're staying at,</u>
  <u t="941680">and go to Cooking Hall. Yeah. See some</u>
  <u t="944480">of the flowers. Good night, guys.</u>
  <u t="947840">[Music]</u>
  <u t="951279">We can be</u>
  <u t="953839">anything.</u>
  <u t="956079">We can be</u>
  <u t="958639">anything.</u>
  <u t="960100">[Music]</u>
  <u t="966079">Good morning from our beautiful place in</u>
  <u t="967920">Hiligum. Hillome. Hillome. So, we're</u>
  <u t="970959">staying about 45 minutes outside of</u>
  <u t="972639">Amsterdam. It takes us two trains to get</u>
  <u t="974959">in, which is what we did yesterday. We</u>
  <u t="976399">explored all over Amsterdam. And then</u>
  <u t="978959">today, we are going to Kenhoff. We're</u>
  <u t="981839">going to go see all the tulips. But this</u>
  <u t="983680">is our beautiful place. We're right on a</u>
  <u t="985680">canal. We have these beautiful tulip</u>
  <u t="987759">fields that are covered by plastic cuz I</u>
  <u t="990160">think they're trying to save the bulbs</u>
  <u t="991440">for the parade next week is what our</u>
  <u t="993199">host told us. But some of the fields</u>
  <u t="995040">over there are just absolutely vibrant.</u>
  <u t="996800">And we have canoes here that we can put</u>
  <u t="998959">in the canal and go like canoeing around</u>
  <u t="1000880">if we wanted to get up close with the</u>
  <u t="1002480">tulips. And look, there's ducks and</u>
  <u t="1004480">birds. And there's swans here. It's so</u>
  <u t="1007199">peaceful and relaxing. And the Airbnb is</u>
  <u t="1010720">massive for four people. So that's</u>
  <u t="1012320">really comfortable for us. And the price</u>
  <u t="1014480">was so good. I think it was $500 a</u>
  <u t="1017360">couple for four nights. So for</u>
  <u t="1020320">Amsterdam, that's a pretty good deal. I</u>
  <u t="1022959">think we're outside Amsterdam. We're</u>
  <u t="1024400">outside of Amsterdam. It's a pretty good</u>
  <u t="1026480">deal. And the place also comes with</u>
  <u t="1028400">bikes. And today we're going to be</u>
  <u t="1030319">biking into Kukenhoff. Yay. So, they</u>
  <u t="1032959">only had three bikes at our Airbnb, so I</u>
  <u t="1034880">rented an electric bike here. It was €20</u>
  <u t="1037039">for the day. And the guy who was working</u>
  <u t="1038880">there recommended another bike path you</u>
  <u t="1040640">can go on. There's like a tulip barn you</u>
  <u t="1042319">can go check out, a museum as well. So,</u>
  <u t="1044400">we'll see how much we explore today</u>
  <u t="1045679">around our spot here in Hong Kong.</u>
  <u t="1050559">Yeah. La.</u>
  <u t="1056160">So nice being in a place where it's so</u>
  <u t="1057600">bike friendly.</u>
  <u t="1064640">I feel right around. Wow, look how</u>
  <u t="1067440">pretty. So lucky to be here this time of</u>
  <u t="1069919">year, right? Perfect timing.</u>
  <u t="1073360">No, it really worked out perfectly. The</u>
  <u t="1075039">flowers are still in bloom and the last</u>
  <u t="1076640">two days have been warm, so they're</u>
  <u t="1078080">extra blooming.</u>
  <u t="1080160">Ooh la la. I like how beautiful.</u>
  <u t="1084880">I like the things you do. I like it when</u>
  <u t="1087840">I'm with you.</u>
  <u t="1097360">I did it. You're so dramatic. Good job,</u>
  <u t="1099600">though. I was so scared. The biggest</u>
  <u t="1102160">white team.</u>
  <u t="1104240">TMI.</u>
  <u t="1107120">I don't like biking.</u>
  <u t="1109310">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1111760">I can't believe the cars coming in here</u>
  <u t="1113600">and all the bikes. It is so packed with</u>
  <u t="1116160">people. People love their tulips</u>
  <u t="1118559">apparently.</u>
  <u t="1121440">I'm super glad we actually bike though</u>
  <u t="1122880">cuz the traffic so backed up a long</u>
  <u t="1125440">ways.</u>
  <u t="1132240">I like it when you</u>
  <u t="1136160">do. I like it when you got my first</u>
  <u t="1139280">picture.</u>
  <u t="1141120">Snap it.</u>
  <u t="1147840">I like it when I'm with you.</u>
  <u t="1152000">La.</u>
  <u t="1159460">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1162799">So, really nice of ladies. Not really</u>
  <u t="1164400">our thing. Very pretty. Yeah, but I did</u>
  <u t="1166400">see someone carrying a beer around as</u>
  <u t="1168160">they're looking at flowers. Okay,</u>
  <u t="1169280">there's hope yet. So, there might be</u>
  <u t="1171440">might be our next destination.</u>
  <u t="1174110">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1190160">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1196320">So, I am blown away by the crowd. So, I</u>
  <u t="1198080">had to show you guys and get it up high.</u>
  <u t="1202630">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1210320">I feel tricked. I know Tommy does. He He</u>
  <u t="1213280">looked at me earlier. He was like, I</u>
  <u t="1214480">feel like you tricked me cuz I told him</u>
  <u t="1216480">we're coming to a place with beautiful</u>
  <u t="1217679">flowers, but he didn't know like how</u>
  <u t="1219280">like viral Disneyland. He didn't know</u>
  <u t="1220960">how viral this place was. So, it is</u>
  <u t="1223600">very, very crowded here. I don't get it.</u>
  <u t="1226400">It's beautiful. The flowers are so</u>
  <u t="1228080">pretty. Everything's so The weather's</u>
  <u t="1230720">perfect around the river. The like it's</u>
  <u t="1232880">just a great atmosphere. But there are</u>
  <u t="1235280">shoulderto-shoulder people here. So,</u>
  <u t="1241039">bars are looking better.</u>
  <u t="1246159">Heat.</u>
  <u t="1250030">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1262559">Heat.</u>
  <u t="1269200">Did</u>
  <u t="1275620">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1277600">you have a good time? I did. I enjoyed</u>
  <u t="1279440">all the beautiful flowers. My favorites</u>
  <u t="1281120">are the ones that are mixed and you can</u>
  <u t="1282640">see all the different ones together. Me,</u>
  <u t="1284240">too. Rather than just the rows of one</u>
  <u t="1286000">solid color. Yeah, it's a bit crowded</u>
  <u t="1288000">for us. Short and sweet visit. We're</u>
  <u t="1289679">going to hop back on our bikes.</u>
  <u t="1292320">Any takeaways, Mom? Oh, everything was</u>
  <u t="1294720">stunning. And it's just imagine you can</u>
  <u t="1296960">come back in two more weeks and get a</u>
  <u t="1299039">different type of viewing, which is</u>
  <u t="1300320">crazy. Yeah, that's awesome. Okay, we're</u>
  <u t="1302240">here for a little over an hour. Too</u>
  <u t="1305600">long. Way too crowded. All right, time</u>
  <u t="1308559">to get out of here. Over there on the</u>
  <u t="1310000">right. Yep. This way.</u>
  <u t="1315320">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1320159">You see all the cars lined up.</u>
  <u t="1323679">So, the guy I rented my bike from</u>
  <u t="1325120">recommended this castle, which we're</u>
  <u t="1326640">walking up to now. I think it's €10 to</u>
  <u t="1328880">get inside, but we just want to look at</u>
  <u t="1330720">the grounds and see the outside of it.</u>
  <u t="1333280">Looks very cool.</u>
  <u t="1339720">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1350880">Very</u>
  <u t="1358159">pretty, but chaotic, right? So chaotic.</u>
  <u t="1361360">So many cars, not big enough roads.</u>
  <u t="1363520">Definitely not for a weak biker as well.</u>
  <u t="1366480">You guys want to bail on it? Pretty</u>
  <u t="1368559">busy, right? I want to bail. Okay.</u>
  <u t="1380000">We've come to Zor, a nice local cafe</u>
  <u t="1382960">here. The whole place is rented out for</u>
  <u t="1384960">a birthday party. So, we have the little</u>
  <u t="1386640">back back table in the corner. We just</u>
  <u t="1388640">met the owner. His name's Nigel. Very</u>
  <u t="1390400">sweet man. And he recommended a IPA.</u>
  <u t="1393600">Actually, it's called Insomnia. Has like</u>
  <u t="1395039">a textured can. Look how cool that</u>
  <u t="1396559">looks. That's nice. He was very excited</u>
  <u t="1398240">to share it with us. So, me and dad are</u>
  <u t="1400960">excited to try it. Cheers. Cheers.</u>
  <u t="1403120">Cheers. Cheers. Cheers.</u>
  <u t="1407360">Yeah, that's fantastic. Isn't that good?</u>
  <u t="1410080">So fruity, but cheesy. Definitely a</u>
  <u t="1413760">hazy. Yeah, hazy, which is our favorite</u>
  <u t="1417200">citrus. How did he know? Super citrusy.</u>
  <u t="1419760">Okay, thank you, Nigel.</u>
  <u t="1425360">I got the meat platter. Looks like we</u>
  <u t="1427440">have some steak, some pork ribs, and</u>
  <u t="1429360">some chicken saté. Oh, yeah. With fries.</u>
  <u t="1432080">With fries and a salad, which are both</u>
  <u t="1433760">refillable. Sammy got a big spicy burger</u>
  <u t="1436480">with some fries. I love that the salad</u>
  <u t="1438640">is refillable.</u>
  <u t="1441360">Okay, ended our day with some ice cream.</u>
  <u t="1443760">I got the peanut and dark chocolate 70%.</u>
  <u t="1447840">Dark chocolate and cherry. Cherry was</u>
  <u t="1449760">her favorite. Cherry's the best.</u>
  <u t="1450880">Peanut's really good, too. And the dark</u>
  <u t="1452480">chocolate, they're all amazing. Such a</u>
  <u t="1454080">great first time here in Amsterdam and</u>
  <u t="1455679">our little town here. Um, tomorrow we're</u>
  <u t="1457679">actually going to do a food tour as</u>
  <u t="1458720">well. So, we'll see you guys then. Thank</u>
  <u t="1460159">you for watching. Cheers. Cheers. Heat.</u>
  <u t="1463900">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1466170">[Applause]</u>
  <u t="1469440">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1476320">Heat.</u>
  <u t="1480150">[Music]</u>
  </text>
