<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="TPnQVzFTAR8" uploader="Kate Brock" channel="Kate Brock" likes="2441" title="Five days in Paris" year="2026" month="3" day="1" date="20260301" date_ts="1772377251" is_ac="true">
  <u t="3280">Wow,</u>
  <u t="5359">Paris.</u>
  <u t="9170">[music]</u>
  <u t="22240">So, we were supposed to fly to Paris</u>
  <u t="23439">tonight, but it's a little snowy. Snow</u>
  <u t="25680">kind of made the plans a little</u>
  <u t="26880">difficult. Now, we're just venturing out</u>
  <u t="28320">and we're going for dinner.</u>
  <u t="42640">After a few calls with the airline, we</u>
  <u t="44640">were finally able to rebook our flight</u>
  <u t="46800">for the [music] next day. So, we set off</u>
  <u t="48960">on the adventure. We had about a 2-hour</u>
  <u t="51440">stop in Montreal and then [music] we</u>
  <u t="53520">just got on our flight straight to</u>
  <u t="55360">Paris.</u>
  <u t="66479">Okay. How do you open this?</u>
  <u t="68880">&gt;&gt; Oh, I opened it. Welcome. We're in</u>
  <u t="72479">Paris. Welcome to my home. So, we have</u>
  <u t="76960">all of our bags here.</u>
  <u t="79600">Got some umbrellas because it's raining.</u>
  <u t="82000">Look at this view.</u>
  <u t="89360">Wow.</u>
  <u t="91200">Paris. Next. Is this a bedroom?</u>
  <u t="94560">Yes. Look at this bedroom. Oh my</u>
  <u t="97840">goodness. Beautiful bed. Look at this</u>
  <u t="100079">shower.</u>
  <u t="101200">&gt;&gt; Oh, that's cool.</u>
  <u t="102079">&gt;&gt; And this little nightstand. [music]</u>
  <u t="103920">Okay, next up,</u>
  <u t="112560">another bedroom. This is our parents</u>
  <u t="114399">bedroom. Oh, mommy. Look at this</u>
  <u t="117040">beautiful space.</u>
  <u t="120479">Gorgina.</u>
  <u t="123680">Wow. And then in the bathroom.</u>
  <u t="128479">&gt;&gt; Wow. Gorge.</u>
  <u t="134080">&gt;&gt; Okay, so we just arrived in Paris and I</u>
  <u t="137360">am going to take a shower and then we're</u>
  <u t="139760">going to go and get a coffee and walk</u>
  <u t="141360">around. try not to go to sleep because</u>
  <u t="144239">then I will be completely off of the</u>
  <u t="146720">schedule. So, going to shower and we're</u>
  <u t="148400">just going to like get out of the house</u>
  <u t="149599">and start walking around. My sister and</u>
  <u t="151440">I are obviously very tired. Neither of</u>
  <u t="153120">us slept last night. I can't sleep on a</u>
  <u t="155280">plane. My sister can't sleep on a plane.</u>
  <u t="156879">It's how it goes. So, we're both</u>
  <u t="158239">obviously very tired. It's like 8:00</u>
  <u t="160560">a.m. in Toronto and I just like</u>
  <u t="162480">essentially just pulled an all nighter.</u>
  <u t="164080">But, we're just going to walk around for</u>
  <u t="165360">a bit and explore and just like try and</u>
  <u t="168319">stay awake. We're probably going to go</u>
  <u t="169599">for dinner or something, but just like</u>
  <u t="171440">go and explore. I really love Paris and</u>
  <u t="173920">it's also just like so fun to be able to</u>
  <u t="176319">use my French even though my French is</u>
  <u t="177920">like kind of really bad and out of</u>
  <u t="179519">practice, but I'm excited to be here and</u>
  <u t="182319">you know, it's a bit rainy, but it's</u>
  <u t="184159">such a cool city and so very excited to</u>
  <u t="186959">explore. I'm just brushing out the</u>
  <u t="188319">eyebrows right now. I'm using the</u>
  <u t="189760">Glossier Boy Brow. I've been using this</u>
  <u t="191519">a lot lately and I really honestly like</u>
  <u t="193519">it quite a lot. It fills in my eyebrows</u>
  <u t="195360">really nicely and subtly. But yeah, I'm</u>
  <u t="197200">going to finish up doing my makeup. get</u>
  <u t="198720">dressed and then we're going to head out</u>
  <u t="200640">and go on a little adventure. I'm so</u>
  <u t="202640">excited.</u>
  <u t="208480">We're just venturing out right now into</u>
  <u t="211040">the into the city.</u>
  <u t="220082">[music]</u>
  <u t="228597">&gt;&gt; [music]</u>
  <u t="232640">&gt;&gt; Taste test. So, we're trying</u>
  <u t="236239">Cafe New, which is like over there. Cafe</u>
  <u t="240560">Paris.</u>
  <u t="244959">It's good.</u>
  <u t="251522">&gt;&gt; [music]</u>
  <u t="265278">[bell]</u>
  <u t="271759">&gt;&gt; Hello everyone. So, first monument of</u>
  <u t="274160">the trip. We're at Noam.</u>
  <u t="279120">Oh, this dog.</u>
  <u t="281199">Hello.</u>
  <u t="289520">&gt;&gt; Wow.</u>
  <u t="301040">Come on.</u>
  <u t="305888">[music]</u>
  <u t="315759">Going to go to bed. I will see you all</u>
  <u t="317520">tomorrow morning and good night.</u>
  <u t="339360">Good morning everyone. It is</u>
  <u t="342560">Wednesday [music]</u>
  <u t="344240">and I just woke up. I'm having a little</u>
  <u t="346479">bit of coffee that there's someone like</u>
  <u t="348400">literally like drilling something</u>
  <u t="350160">outside and it's so loud it woke me up</u>
  <u t="352160">this morning. But I had a really good</u>
  <u t="353759">sleep last night. I slept like all</u>
  <u t="355039">through the night and I actually feel</u>
  <u t="356320">like normal today instead of completely</u>
  <u t="359039">delusional and exhausted. So that's</u>
  <u t="361199">always a plus. So yeah.</u>
  <u t="368769">[music]</u>
  <u t="373354">[music]</u>
  <u t="389840">All right, just got back from season.</u>
  <u t="394080">So, I'll do a little haul of the things</u>
  <u t="396800">that I got and then we're going to go</u>
  <u t="398479">out for the rest of the day. Okay,</u>
  <u t="400000">lovely people. Let me give you a haul. I</u>
  <u t="403039">got this literal beautiful jacket. It's</u>
  <u t="406880">such a fun little like spring jacket. I</u>
  <u t="410479">feel even though it's like really cold</u>
  <u t="413039">still in Toronto, I'm definitely going</u>
  <u t="414720">to be able to wear this in the spring.</u>
  <u t="416639">It's such a beautiful cut and I love it.</u>
  <u t="418720">It's a little cropped trench. I [music]</u>
  <u t="421360">think it's genuinely so cute. Love it.</u>
  <u t="423919">And then the next thing I got is just</u>
  <u t="425599">this like oversized button-up, which I'm</u>
  <u t="427520">really excited about. But it's like it's</u>
  <u t="429199">oversized, but it's like not too big.</u>
  <u t="431680">And I feel like [music] it's really</u>
  <u t="433199">cute. And I love how like the white is</u>
  <u t="435039">kind of it's like off-white. It's not</u>
  <u t="436800">just like stark white. Cute.</u>
  <u t="440720">Cute. And you can like obviously</u>
  <u t="442319">unbutton it, button it up. And I love</u>
  <u t="444000">the sleeves. They're like longer. So</u>
  <u t="447360">cute.</u>
  <u t="452800">Then we were back out on the town. We</u>
  <u t="454880">decided to go to this place [music] for</u>
  <u t="456080">lunch. They had like mostly gluten-free</u>
  <u t="457759">and like health food stuff, but it's</u>
  <u t="459039">actually really good. And then we walked</u>
  <u t="460639">around more. I love all of like the</u>
  <u t="462240">little things that you see when you walk</u>
  <u t="464000">out. Just like all of the stands with</u>
  <u t="466000">the art, the bakeries, [music] just so</u>
  <u t="467919">many cute little shops and everything.</u>
  <u t="469680">Just walking around is literally the</u>
  <u t="471039">best cuz you just get to see everything.</u>
  <u t="472560">And then we went into Noam, which</u>
  <u t="474225">[music] was also just so so beautiful.</u>
  <u t="476879">Walked around even more and then headed</u>
  <u t="478560">home.</u>
  <u t="480639">Okay, I just got home. It was a very fun</u>
  <u t="482879">day. It's currently 6:30 and now we're</u>
  <u t="485680">just going to go get dressed to go for</u>
  <u t="487199">dinner. We're going around like 7, so</u>
  <u t="490240">got to start getting dressed for that.</u>
  <u t="492560">For dinner, we headed to La and they</u>
  <u t="495520">specialized in soulets. [music] For</u>
  <u t="497120">dinner, we got this mushroom spinach</u>
  <u t="499039">sule. And then the desserts were</u>
  <u t="500560">honestly so so good. They actually had</u>
  <u t="502479">gluten-free options. So, we got this one</u>
  <u t="504639">pistachio and chocolate sule. So, so, so</u>
  <u t="508240">good. And then the other one we got was</u>
  <u t="510479">almond and caramel. [music] Definitely</u>
  <u t="512399">recommend. So good. And then we headed</u>
  <u t="515279">back and then I had a peppermint tea</u>
  <u t="517680">when I got back.</u>
  <u t="522000">I was up pretty late working on one of</u>
  <u t="524080">my assignments. And so now I'm finally</u>
  <u t="526959">going to go to bed. So I'll see you all</u>
  <u t="529440">tomorrow morning. Bye.</u>
  <u t="545680">Today we are going to Muse de laerie and</u>
  <u t="550399">then I think we also want to go to the</u>
  <u t="552640">Dior Museum. I think is putting on some</u>
  <u t="555440">sort of museum maybe. I think it's like</u>
  <u t="558880">maybe archive fashion like I'm not</u>
  <u t="560720">really sure what it is but it seems</u>
  <u t="562320">really cool. So, going to try and get</u>
  <u t="563839">into that, but it's all sold out. So,</u>
  <u t="565839">they sell tickets at the door, so we're</u>
  <u t="567279">going to try and get some of those.</u>
  <u t="568320">Right now, I'm just getting ready for</u>
  <u t="569440">that. Okay, so here's the outfit today.</u>
  <u t="570959">These shoes I got in London. These jeans</u>
  <u t="573040">are Reformation bag is Marge Sherwood.</u>
  <u t="576080">This thrifted and then this coat is my</u>
  <u t="578320">sisters. And then this necklace, Monica</u>
  <u t="580560">Viner, rings me. And these are from my</u>
  <u t="584560">mom.</u>
  <u t="586320">I genuinely loved this art gallery. My</u>
  <u t="589200">mom said that when she lived here in the</u>
  <u t="591360">'9s, she would always come here and</u>
  <u t="592781">[music] just stare at the paintings for</u>
  <u t="594560">hours because it was just such a</u>
  <u t="596399">peaceful environment and it was never</u>
  <u t="598160">really that busy. And I thought that</u>
  <u t="600160">that was really cool to experience that</u>
  <u t="601920">again with her. And then we saw the rest</u>
  <u t="604160">of the gallery. And I [music] just love</u>
  <u t="605839">smaller galleries because I feel like</u>
  <u t="607440">you can really truly appreciate all the</u>
  <u t="609519">art that is there.</u>
  <u t="623839">Hello everyone.</u>
  <u t="625680">Currently back from the day. We went to</u>
  <u t="628959">the museum the laie. Did a lot of</u>
  <u t="632560">walking around, had some lunch, and now</u>
  <u t="634800">we're back. I could probably sleep for</u>
  <u t="637279">15 hours at this point. Could go to bed</u>
  <u t="640000">and I wouldn't wake up for 15 hours. But</u>
  <u t="644079">in 45 minutes, we're going to dinner.</u>
  <u t="646320">And then after dinner, we have this gala</u>
  <u t="648480">and it's like 1920s themed, which is</u>
  <u t="651680">like really cool. I'm very excited to go</u>
  <u t="654560">to that. I bought a little dress for</u>
  <u t="656320">that. So, that should be really fun. I</u>
  <u t="658560">just finished a discussion post that</u>
  <u t="660240">literally took me like 2 weeks for no</u>
  <u t="662399">apparent reason. And I'm going to start</u>
  <u t="664720">doing my makeup and getting ready for</u>
  <u t="666240">dinner. So, that is what's going on.</u>
  <u t="669200">This blanket is so warm and I just want</u>
  <u t="670959">to sit here forever, I think.</u>
  <u t="675312">&gt;&gt; [music]</u>
  <u t="680959">&gt;&gt; We just got back from dinner. I've done</u>
  <u t="682800">my makeup and done my hair. What I'm</u>
  <u t="685120">doing for my hair is I'm doing like a</u>
  <u t="686480">sort of like headband. I think I'm going</u>
  <u t="687600">to do something like this.</u>
  <u t="692000">I don't know.</u>
  <u t="693839">Okay, so this is the dress that I'll be</u>
  <u t="697839">wearing tonight. It actually looked like</u>
  <u t="699680">this on both sides, but then I des</u>
  <u t="701519">sequined the front because I was like,</u>
  <u t="703040">this shiny is a little bit chewy. I</u>
  <u t="706079">don't know. Is it chewy to say the word</u>
  <u t="707600">chewy? I don't know, guys. Um, but this</u>
  <u t="709360">is the dress I'm wearing. Gorgina. Okay,</u>
  <u t="711680">we're going to put this on. Here's the</u>
  <u t="714000">dress.</u>
  <u t="717888">[music]</u>
  <u t="726399">Okay, everyone. Let's go to the party.</u>
  <u t="730480">I need to check out check.</u>
  <u t="734480">&gt;&gt; Oh, there's a bike there.</u>
  <u t="741468">[music]</u>
  <u t="744480">&gt;&gt; Good morning. Um, didn't go to bed until</u>
  <u t="747760">like 2:00 a.m. and had to wake up at</u>
  <u t="750560">9:30 this morning. Trying to wake up and</u>
  <u t="755200">get some stuff done.</u>
  <u t="762320">I'm actually so tired,</u>
  <u t="764720">but I'm [clears throat] excited for the</u>
  <u t="765760">day.</u>
  <u t="768880">Okay, my makeup is done and now I need</u>
  <u t="770240">to pick out an outfit, which I'm a</u>
  <u t="772160">little bit stressed about because I have</u>
  <u t="773440">no idea what to wear. That's what I'm</u>
  <u t="774959">wearing.</u>
  <u t="780079">I got to go.</u>
  <u t="783519">Okay, currently home. did a little</u>
  <u t="785519">outfit check. I mean, did a lot of</u>
  <u t="787920">change. I also changed rooms because my</u>
  <u t="790480">cousin and her boyfriend are coming to</u>
  <u t="793120">stay with us because they live in</u>
  <u t="794480">London. So, they just took the train.</u>
  <u t="795680">So, now my sister and I sharing a room.</u>
  <u t="798160">Nice. And um yeah, we're headed to</u>
  <u t="801440">Truckado right now, which is like the</u>
  <u t="803440">view of the So, we can have a view of</u>
  <u t="804959">the Eiffel Tower. So, we're going to go</u>
  <u t="806720">and do that, which is exciting.</u>
  <u t="819680">Afterwards, I decided that it [music]</u>
  <u t="821519">was time to go vintage shopping. The</u>
  <u t="823440">first place that I went was Bobby, and I</u>
  <u t="825200">had seen a lot of like Tik Toks and</u>
  <u t="826880">posts about it, so I really wanted to</u>
  <u t="828320">check it out. [music] They had really</u>
  <u t="829200">cute stuff, but it was a little bit more</u>
  <u t="830480">on the expensive range. And then next, I</u>
  <u t="832639">checked out Shea Snow Bunny, which</u>
  <u t="834720">genuinely such beautiful stuff, but it</u>
  <u t="836399">was all mostly [music] vintage designer.</u>
  <u t="838240">And so, I mean, the pieces were great,</u>
  <u t="839600">but I didn't really get anything. The</u>
  <u t="841040">next place I checked out was Fa Vintage.</u>
  <u t="843360">There was genuinely such a great [music]</u>
  <u t="845040">selection. So many beautiful pieces and</u>
  <u t="847040">it was also a little bit more affordable</u>
  <u t="848800">than the other two. Okay, just got back</u>
  <u t="851279">from</u>
  <u t="853040">Eiffel Tower and then did some vintage</u>
  <u t="855120">shopping. I went to this place called</u>
  <u t="858320">Vintage and I got the most beautiful</u>
  <u t="860320">jacket. Okay, it looks literally very</u>
  <u t="864000">similar to this one, but it is so</u>
  <u t="866639">beautiful. It is so soft and it's also a</u>
  <u t="869600">lot longer. Look at this. She is</u>
  <u t="872959">stunning. I'm actually obsessed with</u>
  <u t="875360">that. Okay, let me should probably do a</u>
  <u t="877440">try on. Like genuinely gorge. And it</u>
  <u t="880800">also has this like this so I can just</u>
  <u t="883440">tie it up too, which I love. I love like</u>
  <u t="886480">that kind of vibe as well. And it also</u>
  <u t="889680">has like buttons as well, so I can just</u>
  <u t="892240">like button it up, which I think is</u>
  <u t="893920">awesome. It's also just super warm.</u>
  <u t="896959">Stunning.</u>
  <u t="900720">It is now time to shower and nap because</u>
  <u t="903920">I had like 6 hours of sleep last night.</u>
  <u t="908639">I'm actually not going to shower. I'm</u>
  <u t="910560">simply going to wash my face and take a</u>
  <u t="913279">nap. Time for a 1-hour nap.</u>
  <u t="917440">Out for dinner. This is what I'm</u>
  <u t="918800">wearing.</u>
  <u t="921595">&gt;&gt; [music]</u>
  <u t="928160">&gt;&gt; Good morning. I was finally able to have</u>
  <u t="930639">like a long sleep last night. It's like</u>
  <u t="932639">11:00. It's the last day in Paris. So,</u>
  <u t="937040">yeah. This is what I'm wearing. Just</u>
  <u t="938959">very simple.</u>
  <u t="941245">[music]</u>
  <u t="953035">&gt;&gt; [music]</u>
  <u t="957621">[music]</u>
  <u t="968756">[music]</u>
  <u t="980480">&gt;&gt; Okay, so it is Sunday, February 1st, and</u>
  <u t="983519">we are now heading home. Unfortunately,</u>
  <u t="986320">it was so fun. I actually genuinely love</u>
  <u t="988880">Paris, so I will be back.</u>
  <u t="1004781">&gt;&gt; [music]</u>
  </text>
