<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="X0QdhFkfG6U" uploader="Joel and Emilia" channel="Joel and Emilia" likes="1366" title="I Spent 1 Month in India and Here's What Happened 🇮🇳" year="2025" month="4" day="29" date="20250429" is_ac="true">
  <u t="1439">We knew it was going to be different</u>
  <u t="3040">from anywhere else we've been. And after</u>
  <u t="5279">traveling all over Asia, it felt like we</u>
  <u t="8000">were missing out on the madness, chaos,</u>
  <u t="10080">and beauty that is</u>
  <u t="12120">India. 13 times bigger than the UK and</u>
  <u t="15200">home to 1.5 billion people. We had just</u>
  <u t="18480">30 days on our visas to see as much as</u>
  <u t="21439">possible. Over the next month, we're</u>
  <u t="23199">traveling from north to south, hoping to</u>
  <u t="25359">experience the incredible variety this</u>
  <u t="27439">vast country has to offer. As most</u>
  <u t="30160">travelers do, we began our first day</u>
  <u t="31840">jumping in a taxi on the way to Old</u>
  <u t="34079">Delhi. Thank you. Because we arrived so</u>
  <u t="38000">early last night. I think Amelia is</u>
  <u t="39760">definitely jetlagged. Obviously, I came</u>
  <u t="41040">from Bangladesh, so I'm feeling a little</u>
  <u t="43360">bit better than you. I'm so tired. You</u>
  <u t="46160">know, when jet lagged just makes you</u>
  <u t="47360">feel odd. I think we're about to enter</u>
  <u t="49120">the chaos. People everywhere. There's</u>
  <u t="50879">cars everywhere. There's honking. How</u>
  <u t="52399">are you? Hello, I'm good, thank you. How</u>
  <u t="53760">are you? Nice to meet you. What's your</u>
  <u t="56000">name? My name is Oves Ansari. Oh,</u>
  <u t="60399">actually the streets of Old Delhi is not</u>
  <u t="62559">that wide. So the car cannot enter.</u>
  <u t="64879">Yeah. Oh, very small.</u>
  <u t="68720">So busy.</u>
  <u t="70560">So many homes.</u>
  <u t="73280">Navigating through the narrow streets,</u>
  <u t="74960">we arrived at Jama Masid, the largest</u>
  <u t="77439">mosque in the city.</u>
  <u t="81040">Oh wow.</u>
  <u t="82880">For the females to enter the mosque, you</u>
  <u t="84799">have to wear a gown. This was 50 rupees.</u>
  <u t="87680">that matches my trousers. So, I'm happy</u>
  <u t="89439">with that. It looks great on you.</u>
  <u t="91280">Already when we've entered here, a few</u>
  <u t="93040">people have come up to us and asked for</u>
  <u t="94320">photos. We've said no so far, but I</u>
  <u t="96799">think we're we're going to get pulled in</u>
  <u t="98159">at some point. So, what we've heard is</u>
  <u t="101680">in India, you get so many people asking</u>
  <u t="103680">for photos, and if you say yes to one,</u>
  <u t="106159">you're going to have a line. You're</u>
  <u t="107439">going to have a queue. The best thing,</u>
  <u t="108960">especially in Delhi, is to just say no.</u>
  <u t="111520">It's Joel's turn for a photo now. What's</u>
  <u t="114320">your name? Okay, cool.</u>
  <u t="119280">Okay, one. I'm sacked in again. Number</u>
  <u t="122479">two photo of of the whole of India. This</u>
  <u t="125840">mosque is so beautiful and different</u>
  <u t="127280">from anything else we've really seen.</u>
  <u t="128959">The architecture is amazing. It's made</u>
  <u t="131120">out of sandstone which makes it this</u>
  <u t="132959">ready color. It was built 450 years ago,</u>
  <u t="135520">the same time as the Taj Mahal was</u>
  <u t="137200">built. And it was built by like the same</u>
  <u t="139120">people. Another photo time. Oh dear. I</u>
  <u t="143040">think people are gathering. Oh no.</u>
  <u t="145680">Amelia, run. No, they're coming. There's</u>
  <u t="148800">a group behind you. Here we go. I'm</u>
  <u t="151520">going to lose my girlfriend in a minute.</u>
  <u t="153040">Yeah,</u>
  <u t="154879">why do they want selfie?</u>
  <u t="158160">Why? They like upload on their WhatsApp</u>
  <u t="160480">stages. It's like an Instagram story.</u>
  <u t="162400">Exactly. Okay.</u>
  <u t="164879">I don't know why I'm holding that kid's</u>
  <u t="166720">hand, but she seemed cute.</u>
  <u t="170519">Okay. Let's do a photo.</u>
  <u t="173519">Yeah. Group photo. Where you from?</u>
  <u t="176239">China. Not you.</u>
  <u t="179519">Delhi. Okay.</u>
  <u t="182319">Okay.</u>
  <u t="184480">Very good. Thank you. Where are you</u>
  <u t="186080">from? Where you from? Delhi.</u>
  <u t="189840">Okay.</u>
  <u t="192319">Thank you, brother. This guy's come to</u>
  <u t="194080">help the staff. That's nice of him.</u>
  <u t="202720">We have just arrived in the spice and</u>
  <u t="206239">market area. So this area is very busy.</u>
  <u t="209040">It feels so old here. I think the city</u>
  <u t="211680">of old Delhi is like 750 years old. And</u>
  <u t="214640">you can really feel that here. This is</u>
  <u t="217720">wild. There's so many like sounds, so</u>
  <u t="220480">many smells, so much going on. Oh, I</u>
  <u t="223360">lost you.</u>
  <u t="226000">I can barely like keep next to you</u>
  <u t="227680">because there's so many people. Also, I</u>
  <u t="229920">think I've learned my lesson about the</u>
  <u t="231280">photo taking that if someone asked for a</u>
  <u t="233040">photo, I say no. Now,</u>
  <u t="236000">oh, look at these streets.</u>
  <u t="238480">Wearing brand new white trainers was not</u>
  <u t="240239">a good idea. Not in Old Delhi. Oh my</u>
  <u t="242959">gosh. This is definitely a bit of a</u>
  <u t="244879">culture shock coming straight from the</u>
  <u t="246480">UK, but it's kind of enjoyable chaos is</u>
  <u t="249920">the best way to put it.</u>
  <u t="253020">[Music]</u>
  <u t="254959">This looks like it could be 700 years</u>
  <u t="256959">old, doesn't it?</u>
  <u t="259280">Look, you just got random wires coming</u>
  <u t="261199">out the ceiling. I don't really want to</u>
  <u t="262560">touch that. This is wild.</u>
  <u t="265840">There's so much cooler in here as well.</u>
  <u t="269120">I feel like if I had to describe what it</u>
  <u t="270880">feels like to be over stimulated, I</u>
  <u t="272560">would put you in this street. There is</u>
  <u t="274160">so much going on. Like everywhere I</u>
  <u t="275840">look, 100 different stories are</u>
  <u t="277759">happening. And the wires are stressing</u>
  <u t="280639">me out. They're just on another level.</u>
  <u t="282160">Like, what is that?</u>
  <u t="286639">I am caught in the traffic. Amelia's</u>
  <u t="289759">lost.</u>
  <u t="292080">You're right.</u>
  <u t="293919">I got stuck between a rickshaw and a van</u>
  <u t="297120">and I was like, I only just fit through.</u>
  <u t="299199">If I was any bigger, wouldn't have</u>
  <u t="300880">happened. Oh, this guy's coming through.</u>
  <u t="305520">It's crazy, isn't it? It's wild out</u>
  <u t="308680">here.</u>
  <u t="310919">Feel like I'm going to go death in a bit</u>
  <u t="314080">with all this honking.</u>
  <u t="318240">Apparently, we have to cross this road.</u>
  <u t="320639">Good luck with that. I'm not so sure</u>
  <u t="323280">about this.</u>
  <u t="337120">We have just finished our crazy</u>
  <u t="338880">whirlwind of a tour and we've come to</u>
  <u t="340880">one of the most famous spots here in</u>
  <u t="342479">Delhi. Behind me is the India Gate. This</u>
  <u t="344960">is a very famous monument here in Delhi</u>
  <u t="347039">and it represents 70,000 people who died</u>
  <u t="349759">in World War I. And apparently all their</u>
  <u t="352800">names actually written on the monument</u>
  <u t="355680">over there. How's your first four hours</u>
  <u t="358080">been on the streets of India? I mean</u>
  <u t="359360">I've come from Bangladesh but compared</u>
  <u t="361440">to the UK this must be something. It is</u>
  <u t="364160">a bit of a culture shock but also I</u>
  <u t="366800">think in my mind I had prepared for the</u>
  <u t="368720">worst because I'd heard so many people's</u>
  <u t="370240">different opinions. Some people were</u>
  <u t="371360">like don't go to Delhi. It's dangerous.</u>
  <u t="373280">It's really bad for girls. And actually</u>
  <u t="375680">like yes, it's been extremely chaotic,</u>
  <u t="378720">but people haven't been like bothering</u>
  <u t="380720">us that much. People haven't been</u>
  <u t="382160">staring like too much that I feel super</u>
  <u t="384960">uncomfortable. I mean, yeah, I'm I'm</u>
  <u t="387680">excited for the next month. Honestly</u>
  <u t="389440">though, the next thing on my mind is</u>
  <u t="391039">food because we accidentally skipped</u>
  <u t="393039">lunch in all the chaos. And while</u>
  <u t="394720">breakfast this morning, mine wasn't even</u>
  <u t="396479">Indian. So, it's time to try some proper</u>
  <u t="398960">Indian food. Let's do it. We found some</u>
  <u t="402000">food court and it says fish fingers with</u>
  <u t="404160">tarta sauce. That is not normal, is it?</u>
  <u t="406720">I wouldn't expect fish fingers in India</u>
  <u t="408720">at the gate of India. So random. Joel is</u>
  <u t="411680">going to book us an Uber now. Are we</u>
  <u t="413039">going for an Uber car or an Uber tuk</u>
  <u t="414960">tuk? I think we can select just</u>
  <u t="417919">Delhi police in the way. I'm pretty sure</u>
  <u t="419759">you can just select like an Uber tuk</u>
  <u t="421520">tuk. So let's see what it's like. It</u>
  <u t="423919">says it's only 80 rupees which is so</u>
  <u t="426000">cheap. Okay, let's get the tuk tuk. It's</u>
  <u t="427840">more fun.</u>
  <u t="429840">Oh no.</u>
  <u t="432080">So, we're in the tuk tuk now. It was a</u>
  <u t="433520">little hard to find because it was</u>
  <u t="434639">across the other side of the road and</u>
  <u t="436240">like every other tuk tuk driver was kind</u>
  <u t="438080">of hassling us. But yeah, we've got it.</u>
  <u t="440160">Pretty smooth process is</u>
  <u t="444560">that was way too close. That was really</u>
  <u t="446400">too close for comfort. We were like just</u>
  <u t="449440">so casual about things. The bike just</u>
  <u t="452080">crashed into the bus and nothing</u>
  <u t="453520">happened and he just sat there and it's</u>
  <u t="455360">like daily life in India. Just carry on.</u>
  <u t="457840">Oh my god. They just crashed and they</u>
  <u t="460400">don't</u>
  <u t="464840">mind. Yep. Thank you.</u>
  <u t="469660">[Music]</u>
  <u t="471599">So, our street actually seems quite</u>
  <u t="473280">lively. We are a little bit out of like</u>
  <u t="476000">the main part of Delhi, but it feels</u>
  <u t="478319">more local, more</u>
  <u t="479879">chilled. Slightly chilled. Hello. Hello,</u>
  <u t="483680">J House.</u>
  <u t="488080">Thank you. That looks amazing. Looks so</u>
  <u t="491280">good. We're currently on the rooftop of</u>
  <u t="493680">our hostel and it's so pretty up here.</u>
  <u t="496000">There's so many plants and pretty lights</u>
  <u t="497759">everywhere. And this is our dinner for</u>
  <u t="500400">this evening. We've got a thie. They ran</u>
  <u t="502639">out of dahl, but we've got I can't</u>
  <u t="505039">remember what these dishes at all</u>
  <u t="506720">called, but we'll put them on the</u>
  <u t="507840">screen. But it looks so good. I love</u>
  <u t="510160">having this mix of different dishes. It</u>
  <u t="512560">feels like I'm having like five dinners</u>
  <u t="514080">in one. You get to try loads of</u>
  <u t="515360">different bits. I've got a bit of</u>
  <u t="516479">papadom here. So, I'm just going to give</u>
  <u t="517680">this a try.</u>
  <u t="520320">M. Is it good? Yeah. The sauce is</u>
  <u t="523440">amazing. Is that paneer? That's with</u>
  <u t="526080">cottage cheese. So, it's like cottage</u>
  <u t="527680">cheese. It's really plain cuz Amelia</u>
  <u t="529920">doesn't like cheese. But the sauce is so</u>
  <u t="532560">good.</u>
  <u t="537440">It is only 900 p.m. and I'm so ready for</u>
  <u t="541040">bed. We are literally ready for bed. I'm</u>
  <u t="543200">in my pajamas. And what time is our</u>
  <u t="544800">flight? We have to get up at 3 a.m.</u>
  <u t="548800">3:00? I thought it was 4:00. No, but we</u>
  <u t="550720">have to get there. We actually have to</u>
  <u t="553040">get up at 3:00 a.m.</u>
  <u t="556000">I'm so tired already that that we'll see</u>
  <u t="559279">you in the morning.</u>
  <u t="565920">Even the airport is crazy and the horns</u>
  <u t="568080">are still going.</u>
  <u t="580080">I've just messaged our taxi service</u>
  <u t="581760">saying we're here and he just said okay.</u>
  <u t="585279">Good confirmation. Mr. Joel friend.</u>
  <u t="591680">Ah, thank</u>
  <u t="596760">you. Here we go. Welcome to Jaipur.</u>
  <u t="604880">We left the airport about 10 minutes ago</u>
  <u t="606880">and already it's so different from</u>
  <u t="609360">Delhi. Like the roads just seems so much</u>
  <u t="612240">quieter. There's not nearly as much</u>
  <u t="613839">honking going on. Just feels like a</u>
  <u t="615920">calmer energy.</u>
  <u t="618959">voice.</u>
  <u t="623880">[Music]</u>
  <u t="627920">Whilst we've been here in India, we've</u>
  <u t="629680">been running into a few problems.</u>
  <u t="631440">Accessing certain websites and accessing</u>
  <u t="634079">Tik Tok as Tik Tok is banned here. As we</u>
  <u t="637040">do social media for a living, this has</u>
  <u t="639040">been a major problem as we literally</u>
  <u t="641040">can't do our job. We can't even post or</u>
  <u t="643519">access the flipping app. However, thanks</u>
  <u t="646079">to ProtonVPN, this has not been a</u>
  <u t="648160">problem for us. By simply switching our</u>
  <u t="650240">virtual location to the UK or other</u>
  <u t="652320">locations in the world, we can now</u>
  <u t="654000">access Tik Tok and we've had no issues.</u>
  <u t="656240">Now, we can keep on scrolling and we've</u>
  <u t="658720">got no issues whatsoever on here. My</u>
  <u t="660720">favorite thing about ProtonVPN is you</u>
  <u t="662560">can watch content online as if you were</u>
  <u t="664800">in your home country in 4K and with no</u>
  <u t="667760">buffering. ProtonVPN will always have a</u>
  <u t="670399">free version with no ads and no logs,</u>
  <u t="672880">but it really shines with the paid</u>
  <u t="674399">version with over 11,000 servers in 110</u>
  <u t="677839">countries, advanced privacy features</u>
  <u t="679680">supporting streaming platforms, and</u>
  <u t="681200">secure court servers to protect yourself</u>
  <u t="683519">from cyber attacks, which we're</u>
  <u t="685120">constantly exposed to. With over 100</u>
  <u t="687760">million users, and freedom to choose</u>
  <u t="689279">from over 110 countries, I highly</u>
  <u t="691519">recommend downloading ProtonVPN's free</u>
  <u t="693839">app today. And if you are looking to</u>
  <u t="695680">protect all your devices, then I'll</u>
  <u t="697200">leave a link in the description. And</u>
  <u t="698880">with that, you'll get a huge 64% off.</u>
  <u t="702720">And there's also a 30-day money back</u>
  <u t="704800">guarantee. So there's no reason why you</u>
  <u t="707040">shouldn't give it a try. Link in the</u>
  <u t="709360">description. We've just had a quick</u>
  <u t="710880">breakfast, jumped into an Uber tuk tuk,</u>
  <u t="712959">and we are on to our first place here in</u>
  <u t="715279">Jaipur. It feels like we're escaping the</u>
  <u t="717600">city a little bit more now. We're</u>
  <u t="718800">actually heading uphill onto the</u>
  <u t="721279">outskirts of the city and we're in the</u>
  <u t="722959">countryside, but it is so dry around</u>
  <u t="725440">here.</u>
  <u t="728639">Thank you.</u>
  <u t="733040">Here behind me is the Amber Palace. This</u>
  <u t="735360">was built in the 16th century, 1727,</u>
  <u t="738560">which is a very long time ago. We are</u>
  <u t="741200">coming across a goat. Oh my word. At the</u>
  <u t="743200">palace. A random goat just around around</u>
  <u t="746480">the palace. Maybe this is his</u>
  <u t="748360">palace. The kids are just chasing the</u>
  <u t="750560">goat. It's running off. Excuse me. I</u>
  <u t="752399">don't want 20. One for 20. I don't But I</u>
  <u t="755839">don't want one. Even free. No. We</u>
  <u t="758240">haven't really filmed any of it cuz it's</u>
  <u t="759760">a little bit hard. But everyone just</u>
  <u t="761920">keeps on coming up to us and selling us</u>
  <u t="764000">loads of random stuff. Lots of</u>
  <u t="765760">umbrellas. Umbrellas. Statues. Statues.</u>
  <u t="768959">Anything that you could want. It feels</u>
  <u t="770480">as though when you hold up the camera,</u>
  <u t="772000">like the hawkers and the people selling</u>
  <u t="774240">stuff kind of move away and they don't</u>
  <u t="775920">really want to be on camera. So, little</u>
  <u t="777519">technique, just hold up a camera,</u>
  <u t="778800">pretend you're vlogging.</u>
  <u t="782160">It's so sad to see these wild, what</u>
  <u t="784880">should be wild elephants covered in</u>
  <u t="787120">paint for tourism just for money. A lot</u>
  <u t="790480">of people think that elephant riding is</u>
  <u t="792399">okay. But unfortunately, if you look up</u>
  <u t="794880">elephant crushing, do your own research</u>
  <u t="797200">and you'll realize the elephants have</u>
  <u t="799279">treated really badly in order to be in</u>
  <u t="801440">that state.</u>
  <u t="803519">The palace itself seemed huge from the</u>
  <u t="805360">outside with tourists everywhere, but to</u>
  <u t="807519">actually get inside, we had to pay 500</u>
  <u t="809360">rupees each. We decided to ignore all</u>
  <u t="811519">the tour guides so that we could explore</u>
  <u t="813120">by ourselves.</u>
  <u t="814880">This place is exactly what I would</u>
  <u t="816320">picture when I think of an Indian</u>
  <u t="817680">palace. And it's weird because we've</u>
  <u t="818959">been moving so quickly the past couple</u>
  <u t="820399">of days. Like I feel like I'm just</u>
  <u t="822000">processing that I'm actually in India</u>
  <u t="823839">right now. Inside the palace was</u>
  <u t="825680">incredibly beautiful with so many</u>
  <u t="827279">intricate details covering the walls. It</u>
  <u t="829760">definitely felt like a completely</u>
  <u t="831279">different version of India to the one we</u>
  <u t="832959">had experienced yesterday. It's so</u>
  <u t="834959">different here from Delhi. Not many</u>
  <u t="836320">people have come up for us for photos.</u>
  <u t="837920">No one really seems to be staring at us</u>
  <u t="839680">or seems interested in us. Just as I was</u>
  <u t="842079">saying, that's quite funny. We got a</u>
  <u t="844959">photo.</u>
  <u t="847839">Thank you. Where are you from? Punjab.</u>
  <u t="850240">Punjab. Punjab. Punjab. Nice. Oh, wow.</u>
  <u t="852560">This place is a little bit of a maze.</u>
  <u t="854399">There's so many different directions and</u>
  <u t="856800">like little alleyways you can go down.</u>
  <u t="860399">Oo, where does this go to? More palace.</u>
  <u t="864480">So, up here behind me is the Chaool</u>
  <u t="866160">Wall. And apparently, I read online that</u>
  <u t="868079">it's the third longest wall in the</u>
  <u t="870079">world, which is pretty crazy. And so, we</u>
  <u t="872240">will be going there either later today</u>
  <u t="874560">or tomorrow. All right, I'm getting a</u>
  <u t="876240">little bit lost now. There is so many</u>
  <u t="877839">different directions. This place is</u>
  <u t="880079">literally massive. I mean, we've</u>
  <u t="881920">probably been walking around for an hour</u>
  <u t="883360">and I still don't know where the exit</u>
  <u t="884880">is. Like, it just keeps on going. We've</u>
  <u t="887120">just seen our first monkeys and they</u>
  <u t="889120">don't look like the ones in Bali which</u>
  <u t="890880">steal all your stuff.</u>
  <u t="893519">There is a bull coming for me right now.</u>
  <u t="895839">Oh my gosh. This is our first wild bull.</u>
  <u t="898560">Like why is there a bull? I get a normal</u>
  <u t="900399">cow, a female cow, but a bull is a</u>
  <u t="902800">little bit too much, right? Yeah. I</u>
  <u t="904399">mean, if that gets angry, I'm gone. But</u>
  <u t="907519">it is supposed to be very normal just to</u>
  <u t="909279">find cows in the middle of the city and</u>
  <u t="911680">every everywhere basically in</u>
  <u t="914279">India. Hello</u>
  <u t="920519">Okay, thank</u>
  <u t="922920">you. We've just arrived in the center of</u>
  <u t="925440">Jaipur and it is a lot more like old</u>
  <u t="927839">Delhi now. There is so much like things</u>
  <u t="930240">going on. Got loads of markets, people</u>
  <u t="932399">carrying crazy stuff like this. It is</u>
  <u t="936079">pretty crazy again. I feel like I'm in</u>
  <u t="937760">everyone's way. Oh my gosh. Look through</u>
  <u t="940560">there. Do you want to go through there?</u>
  <u t="942320">Yeah. Let's go for it.</u>
  <u t="944800">Here we go. Oh my gosh, this is crazy.</u>
  <u t="946959">Hello. Christmas tinsel. We got some</u>
  <u t="949600">locks here.</u>
  <u t="952240">This is a fully coming out. Wow, that is</u>
  <u t="955600">some bright colored cotton candy. It's a</u>
  <u t="958160">little bit off-putting when I see so</u>
  <u t="959680">many people spitting on the street. But</u>
  <u t="962079">it's definitely not normal, is it? Not</u>
  <u t="963759">normal where we're from. She's crossing</u>
  <u t="965199">the</u>
  <u t="966199">road. Amelia's cross without me. Oh</u>
  <u t="972120">dear. Oh.</u>
  <u t="975440">Yeah, we have just arrived on a tour</u>
  <u t="977920">with Get Your Guide where Oh, thank you.</u>
  <u t="981639">Manufacturer more than 20 countries.</u>
  <u t="983839">Okay, there you go. A little business</u>
  <u t="985199">card. Anyway, we're doing a food tour.</u>
  <u t="987519">So, we're going to be trying loads of</u>
  <u t="988880">local Indian street food and in probably</u>
  <u t="991600">the most hygienic way possible because</u>
  <u t="993360">we got a guide who knows all the best</u>
  <u t="995040">spots. Let's begin. Thank you. Got</u>
  <u t="998639">myself a samosa here.</u>
  <u t="1002959">M.</u>
  <u t="1004560">Very good. I'm guessing it's vegetable</u>
  <u t="1006079">or something. But the pastry is amazing.</u>
  <u t="1007920">It like flakes away like proper pastry.</u>
  <u t="1010160">Really good. Is it quite spicy?</u>
  <u t="1013279">It's like nice flavor. Not too spicy so</u>
  <u t="1016000">far. Unless I've just not got the spicy</u>
  <u t="1017839">bit yet. M. Is it good? M. Really good.</u>
  <u t="1021839">What is this called again? Jamboli.</u>
  <u t="1024160">Jellybee. Jellybee. So it's flour with</u>
  <u t="1026640">batter and then it's got sugar over the</u>
  <u t="1029039">top.</u>
  <u t="1032319">M. That's good. It kind of like pops in</u>
  <u t="1034640">the middle and it's really sweet. It's</u>
  <u t="1037199">my first Indian dessert, but it's very</u>
  <u t="1039120">good. M. Oh wow, that's really good. I</u>
  <u t="1041520">can't even describe what it tastes like,</u>
  <u t="1043439">but it's just like a very sweet kind of</u>
  <u t="1045640">crunchy crunchy dessert. So they boil</u>
  <u t="1048960">the carrot with the milk and then it</u>
  <u t="1050880">will be like this. Is this like the end</u>
  <u t="1053039">product? Yeah. Like</u>
  <u t="1056640">this is like milk mixed with carrot.</u>
  <u t="1059520">Yeah. Yeah. Milk mixed with carrot.</u>
  <u t="1063120">Let's give this a go.</u>
  <u t="1066400">Oh, this is only for winter. Winter</u>
  <u t="1069039">time. It's a winter kind of food. It's</u>
  <u t="1071840">very sweet. I didn't even know it was</u>
  <u t="1073520">going to be like a dessert kind of</u>
  <u t="1074880">thing. It kind of hit me with sugar. I</u>
  <u t="1076480">was like, "Wo,</u>
  <u t="1078960">it's like an unusual texture to think of</u>
  <u t="1081440">carrot and milk." Yeah. I almost</u>
  <u t="1082960">wouldn't think it was carrot unless No,</u>
  <u t="1084880">that doesn't. Of course, we couldn't do</u>
  <u t="1087360">a food tour without trying some proper</u>
  <u t="1089120">Indian chai.</u>
  <u t="1091520">Oh, that's so good. Is it? Yeah. Not too</u>
  <u t="1093919">sweet. Just like a really nice flavor.</u>
  <u t="1097440">So, in this chai, you have masala spice.</u>
  <u t="1100240">You've got cardamon. You've got what</u>
  <u t="1102320">else was there? Sugar, cinnamon,</u>
  <u t="1104400">cinnamon, ginger, all mixed into this</u>
  <u t="1106960">tea. Like, it's not just a tea bag like</u>
  <u t="1108480">we have in the UK. There is so much</u>
  <u t="1110240">which goes into just this one cup. And</u>
  <u t="1112640">we're definitely going to be having more</u>
  <u t="1113760">of this as we travel around India cuz it</u>
  <u t="1115440">is so good. Cheers. Cheers.</u>
  <u t="1118799">Let's pop our used chai things here.</u>
  <u t="1121120">Very good. That's good. Got a system.</u>
  <u t="1122960">Keep it clean.</u>
  <u t="1126160">All right, we got a professional to help</u>
  <u t="1127520">us cross the street now. Easily done. He</u>
  <u t="1130160">stopped the car with his powers to</u>
  <u t="1132400">prepare some chapati. Just you can see.</u>
  <u t="1134960">And the people are having is during the</u>
  <u t="1137520">lunch time. This bread looks so good.</u>
  <u t="1140160">Yeah. So, we've got some of this grains</u>
  <u t="1142720">which are going to put on top of the</u>
  <u t="1145360">chapati.</u>
  <u t="1150160">Oh, wow. It's really flavorful.</u>
  <u t="1152559">Basically got onions and grains and</u>
  <u t="1154559">stuff on top and it's quite spicy but</u>
  <u t="1158000">like not too spicy. How's the chapati?</u>
  <u t="1160320">The chapati is so good cuz it's just</u>
  <u t="1161840">been, you know, fried on there. The</u>
  <u t="1163600">bread in India is always just so</u>
  <u t="1168440">good. M.</u>
  <u t="1170559">It's everything is so full of flavor,</u>
  <u t="1172400">isn't it? So good. I love Indian food.</u>
  <u t="1175039">Wow. Look.</u>
  <u t="1178720">Thank you. Thank you. He's taking the</u>
  <u t="1180640">juice of sugar cat. Yeah. He's my best</u>
  <u t="1184320">friend. He is now in Buddhist. Oh, so</u>
  <u t="1187120">good. It's so like smooth.</u>
  <u t="1190320">Yeah. In the summer, that's when</u>
  <u t="1192400">sugarcane juice is very, very popular</u>
  <u t="1194240">because it gets really hot. So, if we're</u>
  <u t="1196480">in the summer right now, this whole room</u>
  <u t="1198320">would be completely full of people. But</u>
  <u t="1200960">because it's winter, a bit cooler, it's</u>
  <u t="1203039">not too busy. Indian street food has a</u>
  <u t="1205760">bad reputation and is known for not</u>
  <u t="1207760">being the cleanest. We felt confident</u>
  <u t="1209520">with our guide as he only allowed us to</u>
  <u t="1210960">eat at specific stalls and some were</u>
  <u t="1213120">even government approved by the tourism</u>
  <u t="1214880">board. So, this food store behind me is</u>
  <u t="1217600">one of the most famous samosa stalls in</u>
  <u t="1219919">all of India. And apparently it's been</u>
  <u t="1221840">open since</u>
  <u t="1223480">17 very loud since 1727. So it's almost</u>
  <u t="1227120">been open 300 years which is crazy.</u>
  <u t="1231919">Chocolate chocolate.</u>
  <u t="1236880">What's the name? Burfy. Burfy. Burfy.</u>
  <u t="1239520">This is a popular dessert here in India.</u>
  <u t="1241840">And I think this is a chocolate one. So</u>
  <u t="1243440">it's like milk and sugar and things and</u>
  <u t="1245760">cardamon. And cardamon.</u>
  <u t="1248720">It just tastes super sugary. just like</u>
  <u t="1251120">full of sugar. We've just come across</u>
  <u t="1253200">these pink carrots in the pink city of</u>
  <u t="1255360">Jaipur. It just goes so well. But I've</u>
  <u t="1257440">never seen that kind of carrot before.</u>
  <u t="1258960">That's good.</u>
  <u t="1261000">No, no, thank you. It's okay. Thank you.</u>
  <u t="1264559">Mia's grabbing some oranges. Get some</u>
  <u t="1266799">fruit while I can. I feel like orange is</u>
  <u t="1268480">a good choice because they skin on it.</u>
  <u t="1270960">Yeah. How much? 20 rupees. Two piece.</u>
  <u t="1273760">Okay. 20. Hello cow.</u>
  <u t="1281600">I'm a bit worried about the cow. I think</u>
  <u t="1284000">this cow has just eaten some street</u>
  <u t="1285919">food. Oh, it's got another cow sniffing</u>
  <u t="1287440">its bum. Look, it's got like batter</u>
  <u t="1289919">coming from its mouth. This is why you</u>
  <u t="1292159">have to eat at the right places.</u>
  <u t="1293840">Otherwise, you'll get cow spit in you.</u>
  <u t="1296000">Oh, maybe it's the leftovers.</u>
  <u t="1300330">[Applause]</u>
  <u t="1302159">I don't want it, but it's really good.</u>
  <u t="1304000">Sounds good, but it won't fit in my bag.</u>
  <u t="1306400">This This one bag, man. No, no, no, no.</u>
  <u t="1309919">I don't have one in the back. Thank good</u>
  <u t="1311919">price, my friend. Buy No, no, no. Don't</u>
  <u t="1313679">need, don't need. Very cheap. Okay.</u>
  <u t="1315760">Without even realizing it, we came</u>
  <u t="1317440">across one of the most iconic buildings</u>
  <u t="1319120">of Jaipur, the Howa Mahal. Although it's</u>
  <u t="1322159">located on a busy road, it really shows</u>
  <u t="1324240">why they refer to Jaipur as the pink</u>
  <u t="1326480">city. As we walked further through the</u>
  <u t="1328240">city gates, everything turned from pink</u>
  <u t="1330159">to yellow and the streets became flooded</u>
  <u t="1332240">with pigeons.</u>
  <u t="1338240">I just got pooed on by a pigeon. There's</u>
  <u t="1340880">loads of pigeons here. A Isn't this a</u>
  <u t="1343200">good girlfriend? Get yourself a</u>
  <u t="1344720">girlfriend who wipe pigeon poo off you.</u>
  <u t="1347679">Ew. You're actually doing it for me?</u>
  <u t="1349360">This is lovely. Ew. Ew. Ew. We need to</u>
  <u t="1351280">get out of here, though. Ew. Cuz Why is</u>
  <u t="1353440">it green? It's green. I can't see it. Is</u>
  <u t="1356320">it still on me? Yeah. Oh, for goodness</u>
  <u t="1358720">sake. Thank you. You're welcome. I owe</u>
  <u t="1361200">you. It's good luck. Okay, the skies</u>
  <u t="1363600">tell me it's good luck. This will be</u>
  <u t="1366000">going in the wash. Now, I don't think</u>
  <u t="1367600">these ancient walls were built for</u>
  <u t="1369600">massive coaches full of tourists. Look,</u>
  <u t="1372000">it I don't How did it even fit through</u>
  <u t="1373919">there? I think we are now in like the</u>
  <u t="1375760">walled city of Jaipur cuz we've just</u>
  <u t="1377919">come through this gate and I think</u>
  <u t="1379760">there's seven gates in all of Jaipur,</u>
  <u t="1381280">which is how you get into like this ward</u>
  <u t="1383200">area of the city. How pretty do they</u>
  <u t="1385440">look though? This one's so pretty. I</u>
  <u t="1387360">quite like the yellow color. Obviously,</u>
  <u t="1389039">Jaipur is famous for the pink, but this</u>
  <u t="1390799">color is really nice in the golden sun.</u>
  <u t="1393520">Jaipur is called the pink city because</u>
  <u t="1395200">it's all painted terracotta pink, apart</u>
  <u t="1397360">from this bit behind me, which happens</u>
  <u t="1398720">to be yellow. But that is because in</u>
  <u t="1400960">1876, the Prince of Wales visited Jaipur</u>
  <u t="1403840">and they decided to paint it pink</u>
  <u t="1405440">because that color means hospitality.</u>
  <u t="1407280">So, it was kind of to welcome him here</u>
  <u t="1409120">in Jaipur. Hello.</u>
  <u t="1412320">Noto.</u>
  <u t="1414320">There's more pigeons above us. Joel is</u>
  <u t="1416240">traumatized. I'm Dr. I hate pigeons. I</u>
  <u t="1418559">don't know why I like liked them a</u>
  <u t="1420480">minute ago. You were having so much fun</u>
  <u t="1421760">a minute ago and now the pigeons have</u>
  <u t="1423440">ruined it. Look, even this little brick</u>
  <u t="1426000">shaw, whatever that is, is pink. As the</u>
  <u t="1428480">day came to an end, we headed towards</u>
  <u t="1430159">the famous Jaipur wall, hoping to catch</u>
  <u t="1432400">a glimpse of the</u>
  <u t="1434679">sunset. We've just begun the hike up to</u>
  <u t="1436960">the sunset spot, and hopefully we'll get</u>
  <u t="1438880">there in time because we didn't realize</u>
  <u t="1440400">how much of a actual walk it is up to</u>
  <u t="1443120">the top. But look at this. Already we</u>
  <u t="1446480">can see how good the view is up here.</u>
  <u t="1449440">There's so many kites in the sky. Like</u>
  <u t="1451279">some of them are so high and literally</u>
  <u t="1453279">in the trees. Apparently they had a kite</u>
  <u t="1455200">festival about a month ago and you can</u>
  <u t="1456960">see how many kites there are everywhere.</u>
  <u t="1458480">Like so many must have got stuck. Oh,</u>
  <u t="1462080">look. There's some more kids about to</u>
  <u t="1463760">fly some kites. Hi. Hello. Money. Money.</u>
  <u t="1469200">Oh, no money.</u>
  <u t="1472880">This is what we walked up. pretty pretty</u>
  <u t="1475120">actually high, aren't we? We are. It</u>
  <u t="1477440">didn't feel too bad cuz it's not like</u>
  <u t="1478960">stairs. It's just like a gradual</u>
  <u t="1480520">incline. But I am saying that I'm quite</u>
  <u t="1483520">out of breath. I think we have reached</u>
  <u t="1486240">the top. We've just arrived at the</u>
  <u t="1488400">Jaipore wall, but there's not really a</u>
  <u t="1491039">viewpoint at this bit, is there? No, I</u>
  <u t="1492799">think there's a wall in the way. Like,</u>
  <u t="1494320">we need to see Oh, maybe we can see</u>
  <u t="1496880">through this gap. Anyway, we want to try</u>
  <u t="1499360">and get down there. Maybe we need to go</u>
  <u t="1500960">back down the stairs. Yeah, I don't</u>
  <u t="1502320">think this is getting us anywhere.</u>
  <u t="1507039">I think we've actually got a view now.</u>
  <u t="1509760">Look at this. Wow. It's actually amazing</u>
  <u t="1513200">how big the city is, isn't it? It's</u>
  <u t="1516039">huge. Such a nice view.</u>
  <u t="1519520">Jaipur wall is actually the third</u>
  <u t="1521440">longest wall in the world. And it does</u>
  <u t="1524080">feel very long. I don't think we're</u>
  <u t="1525120">going to be walking the whole length</u>
  <u t="1526320">right now. We've actually reached a</u>
  <u t="1528000">point we can see now. And it is so big.</u>
  <u t="1530720">Like this city, you cannot get a</u>
  <u t="1532799">perspective of how big it is until you</u>
  <u t="1534320">get up here. Like look at this place. I</u>
  <u t="1537679">just have a little look. I'm being safe.</u>
  <u t="1540720">Think we can get on top? Oh,</u>
  <u t="1545000">definitely. Seems a very sturdy wall.</u>
  <u t="1547440">All right. Be careful. I can't get my</u>
  <u t="1550320">leg up.</u>
  <u t="1552320">Oh, there you go. The yoga flexibility</u>
  <u t="1554480">has come out. It's quite nice up here,</u>
  <u t="1556159">isn't it? Hi,</u>
  <u t="1561770">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1570480">What do you think? It's pretty cool,</u>
  <u t="1572320">isn't it? Yeah. All the lights are</u>
  <u t="1574080">starting to come up as well. Yeah, it</u>
  <u t="1576000">looks even cooler, I would say, like</u>
  <u t="1577919">right now with a bit of pink. Yeah. But</u>
  <u t="1580159">then like sparkling lights coming on.</u>
  <u t="1582640">Pink sky and a pink city. So peaceful,</u>
  <u t="1585039">actually. It's so peaceful considering</u>
  <u t="1586960">how crazy this city is. Yeah,</u>
  <u t="1591360">I've had such a crazy two days. Like</u>
  <u t="1593600">obviously there's been so many good</u>
  <u t="1595360">moments, but I think there's also been</u>
  <u t="1596880">some shocking moments as well, just</u>
  <u t="1598880">getting used to like all the traffic,</u>
  <u t="1600480">the beeping. Even though we've traveled</u>
  <u t="1602400">a lot, I feel like things in India are</u>
  <u t="1604080">still such a completely different</u>
  <u t="1605600">experience.</u>
  <u t="1607200">After visiting the crazy cities of Delhi</u>
  <u t="1609200">and Jaipur, it was time to head to a</u>
  <u t="1611039">place less traveled and one of the big</u>
  <u t="1613200">reasons I wanted to visit India. We had</u>
  <u t="1615760">a 4-hour journey to the town of Godan, a</u>
  <u t="1618000">key pilgrimage center in India, but also</u>
  <u t="1620240">where my uncle has been living for over</u>
  <u t="1622320">20</u>
  <u t="1624440">years. Good morning from rural India. We</u>
  <u t="1627440">are in one of the most spiritual holy</u>
  <u t="1629120">places in the whole country and we are</u>
  <u t="1631679">here to see my uncle. Now, we've</u>
  <u t="1633760">actually been here a couple of days</u>
  <u t="1635440">already, and it's been just a very eye</u>
  <u t="1639039">opening, different experience than we've</u>
  <u t="1641200">ever had before, right? We've never</u>
  <u t="1643120">really done anything quite like this,</u>
  <u t="1645120">but it's definitely a really cool</u>
  <u t="1647840">experience. Yes.</u>
  <u t="1650799">As we here visiting my uncle, I'm also</u>
  <u t="1652880">joined with my mom and grandpa, the</u>
  <u t="1655919">person who gave birth to my uncle,</u>
  <u t="1657600">obviously. Yes, that's true. You're</u>
  <u t="1660159">learning. You're learning.</u>
  <u t="1662240">We are currently walking to my uncle's</u>
  <u t="1664159">temple where he's been living for the</u>
  <u t="1666320">last 21</u>
  <u t="1672120">years. We are about to feed monkeys with</u>
  <u t="1674960">like hundreds of bananas and apparently</u>
  <u t="1676799">it's just chaos. So</u>
  <u t="1680000">this guy's got all the bananas.</u>
  <u t="1686880">Lots of the other monkeys are coming</u>
  <u t="1688480">now. They all almost look like me cats</u>
  <u t="1690720">when they stand. Yeah. Look how many</u>
  <u t="1693120">monkeys there are. What? Whoa. Joel,</u>
  <u t="1696320">look at what? Look, they're all coming</u>
  <u t="1698399">from over there.</u>
  <u t="1705640">Wa.</u>
  <u t="1709720">What? Oh, they're coming this way. Yeah,</u>
  <u t="1712240">it's a little bit scary, isn't it? This</u>
  <u t="1714559">whole group is just 100 to 120 monkeys.</u>
  <u t="1717840">But honestly, I just can't believe how</u>
  <u t="1719919">many there are. Oh, is this one going to</u>
  <u t="1722320">snatch snatch from his friend? This</u>
  <u t="1724880">morning for breakfast, I have porridge</u>
  <u t="1726720">with a bit of sugar on and some fresh</u>
  <u t="1728880">guava, papaya, and some grapes. And</u>
  <u t="1731760">Joel's got some kit, which I think is a</u>
  <u t="1734480">blend of like lentils, rice, and</u>
  <u t="1736320">vegetables. It looks very good. Very</u>
  <u t="1738559">healthy way to start the morning. The</u>
  <u t="1740320">kit is actually really good. I kind of</u>
  <u t="1742000">prefer it to the porridge I had</u>
  <u t="1743520">yesterday. And it's basically like just</u>
  <u t="1745520">some spices mixed in. So it's like just</u>
  <u t="1747840">all mixed in. I quite like I mean I like</u>
  <u t="1749760">it but like sus I don't don't pass it</u>
  <u t="1752960">for breakfast. Not for breakfast. I can</u>
  <u t="1755120">eat anything for breakfast but some</u>
  <u t="1756720">people are a bit more fussy like Amelia.</u>
  <u t="1759360">Hey</u>
  <u t="1761360">after breakfast we decided to walk a</u>
  <u t="1763200">section of the pilgrimage here in</u>
  <u t="1764799">Govadan which is 23 km in total.</u>
  <u t="1768880">This area has spiritual importance as</u>
  <u t="1770799">it's where Krishna was born and Govidan</u>
  <u t="1773039">hill fame came from a story where</u>
  <u t="1774799">Krishna lifted the entire hill with one</u>
  <u t="1777279">finger to protect the villages from</u>
  <u t="1779200">torrential rains. Over the next couple</u>
  <u t="1781360">of days I was able to understand more</u>
  <u t="1782960">about my uncle's life here in India and</u>
  <u t="1784880">how different it is from the UK.</u>
  <u t="1786799">Visiting the local temples and learning</u>
  <u t="1788559">more about the Harry Krishna movement.</u>
  <u t="1790559">We said goodbye to my family and headed</u>
  <u t="1792480">to one of the most famous points in the</u>
  <u t="1795159">country. Good morning. So it is</u>
  <u t="1798279">currently 5 6 and we are heading to the</u>
  <u t="1801919">Taj Mahal for sunrise. Although it feels</u>
  <u t="1804720">very dark right now, doesn't it? Doesn't</u>
  <u t="1806559">feel like the sun is going to rise</u>
  <u t="1807840">anytime soon right now. I have to be</u>
  <u t="1809600">honest, it's actually very peaceful</u>
  <u t="1811279">right now. I feel like usually India's</u>
  <u t="1813440">crazy and chaotic, but now I feel like</u>
  <u t="1815440">we're on the streets by ourselves. Are</u>
  <u t="1817440">we early? Are we early? Are we Are we at</u>
  <u t="1819600">the wrong time or something? No one's</u>
  <u t="1821440">hassling me and we're literally 2</u>
  <u t="1823600">minutes away from the Taj Mahal.</u>
  <u t="1828559">We have got through security, given them</u>
  <u t="1830240">our tickets, and I think we're in the</u>
  <u t="1832000">Taj Mahal now. Oh, actually. Oh, wow.</u>
  <u t="1834640">Look,</u>
  <u t="1837919">I don't think this this is not the Taj</u>
  <u t="1839679">Mahal itself. Maybe the the gardens. I</u>
  <u t="1842080">think it's the gates, like the gates</u>
  <u t="1844080">through to it. It looks incredible. As</u>
  <u t="1848159">you can see, it's kind of cloudy this</u>
  <u t="1849760">morning, so I'm not sure how good the</u>
  <u t="1851520">sunrise is going to be. I think it even</u>
  <u t="1853039">rained last night. Like yeah like the</u>
  <u t="1854960">floor is so wet. I mean I didn't even</u>
  <u t="1857440">know it could rain in this part of India</u>
  <u t="1858880">at the moment because it's been so dry.</u>
  <u t="1863679">It looks insane. It looks huge. It looks</u>
  <u t="1866720">massive.</u>
  <u t="1870270">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1878840">What? How beautiful does it look right</u>
  <u t="1881360">now? Like everything's going orange. It</u>
  <u t="1883279">looks insane because it's so cloudy. The</u>
  <u t="1885520">sky is kind of got this orangey pink hue</u>
  <u t="1888000">and it looks so pretty. Look at it. Look</u>
  <u t="1890720">at the sky. Like what is going on right</u>
  <u t="1894640">now? And somehow we've got this entire</u>
  <u t="1896480">little patch to ourselves. Probably not</u>
  <u t="1898159">for long, but considering how many</u>
  <u t="1900159">people are, that's quite impressive.</u>
  <u t="1902090">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1904880">There was just lightning. You didn't see</u>
  <u t="1906559">it. Where am I looking? Literally just</u>
  <u t="1909039">over here. Okay, that would be cool.</u>
  <u t="1911840">It's behind the car. That would be</u>
  <u t="1913760">awesome.</u>
  <u t="1915590">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1918559">That doesn't sound good. It's actually</u>
  <u t="1921519">started raining here. Like I don't know</u>
  <u t="1923519">what the chances are, but it there are</u>
  <u t="1926080">raindrops falling from the sky and we've</u>
  <u t="1928480">seen lightning. Like what are the</u>
  <u t="1929679">chances of that? Probably very very slim</u>
  <u t="1931679">because it is just so dry, especially</u>
  <u t="1934080">because we are here in February. There's</u>
  <u t="1936159">another flash of lightning. Did you see</u>
  <u t="1937679">that? Yes. This always happens to us</u>
  <u t="1939840">somehow. We always managed to bring a</u>
  <u t="1941519">storm with us. So many different places</u>
  <u t="1943360">we've been caught. Everyone is clearing</u>
  <u t="1945440">out and we've got this whole like</u>
  <u t="1947120">walkway bit mostly to ourselves. The</u>
  <u t="1949919">only downfall is we're very wet. Yeah,</u>
  <u t="1952000">we are wet and we do have cameras on us</u>
  <u t="1953760">so it's not the smartest. But when are</u>
  <u t="1955919">you going to be at the Taj Mahal in the</u>
  <u t="1957360">rain again? Exactly. Not many people get</u>
  <u t="1959760">to do this. This is unique.</u>
  <u t="1964640">It was easy to see why it's named one of</u>
  <u t="1966559">the seven wonders of the world. It's</u>
  <u t="1968480">genuinely one of the most beautiful</u>
  <u t="1970240">buildings we have ever</u>
  <u t="1972120">seen. Our time in Agra was short, but we</u>
  <u t="1974880">decided to visit again that afternoon to</u>
  <u t="1976960">see it in the sunlight, which made it</u>
  <u t="1978960">even more beautiful. We spent the</u>
  <u t="1980960">evening relaxing on the rooftop of our</u>
  <u t="1982559">hostel. And at 10 p.m., we got a tuk tuk</u>
  <u t="1984960">heading to the bus stop for our first</u>
  <u t="1986880">overnight</u>
  <u t="1989480">bus. Only in India would this random</u>
  <u t="1993039">side of the road be a bus station.</u>
  <u t="1996559">Where are we? What's going on? Where is</u>
  <u t="1998880">this bus? I don't know. We are lost. We</u>
  <u t="2002240">would be doomed without this tuk tuk</u>
  <u t="2003919">driver. We would literally be stranded</u>
  <u t="2005360">on the side of the road. And if this bus</u>
  <u t="2006960">doesn't turn up, I don't know what we're</u>
  <u t="2008480">going to do.</u>
  <u t="2010559">After an hour of waiting at the side of</u>
  <u t="2012320">the road, the bus finally arrived.</u>
  <u t="2024000">We've been on this bus a few hours now</u>
  <u t="2026720">and it is so bumpy. Especially because</u>
  <u t="2028960">we're at the back. It's very very hard</u>
  <u t="2031919">to sleep for any longer than like 5 10</u>
  <u t="2034480">minutes because the roads are just so</u>
  <u t="2037440">like bumpy. Hopefully we stop for a</u>
  <u t="2040240">toilet soon. The good thing is though,</u>
  <u t="2042240">we do have our own private cabin which</u>
  <u t="2044080">can shut completely. And I'll show you</u>
  <u t="2046399">in a few hours time when it's lighter in</u>
  <u t="2049440">this room.</u>
  <u t="2059839">This driver is actually crazy. Like why</u>
  <u t="2062320">are you rocking so much? I've never</u>
  <u t="2064879">experienced it. What was</u>
  <u t="2068440">that? Oh my god.</u>
  <u t="2076079">We are not faking this. This is not</u>
  <u t="2078679">fake. This is what it's like. This is</u>
  <u t="2081760">the space we've got and we can actually</u>
  <u t="2083359">shut the door properly so we can shut</u>
  <u t="2085599">everyone else out on this</u>
  <u t="2087800">bus. Honestly, I'm so glad we've got</u>
  <u t="2090560">this space. Otherwise, I don't know what</u>
  <u t="2092800">we'd be doing. The rest of</u>
  <u t="2096440">the someone's having a horn beeping</u>
  <u t="2099119">competition.</u>
  <u t="2103359">After that</u>
  <u t="2104760">incredible, eventful, horrible bus</u>
  <u t="2108800">journey, we've arrived at Vinasi and</u>
  <u t="2111280">we've just checked in to our guest house</u>
  <u t="2113920">for the next three nights. I have to be</u>
  <u t="2116079">honest, the side of my body is hurting.</u>
  <u t="2118320">I think I might be bruised from just the</u>
  <u t="2120720">bouncing because it was constant like</u>
  <u t="2123359">all the bumping on the bus. I mean, at</u>
  <u t="2126320">one point we both got thrown really</u>
  <u t="2128320">high, like really high like big air</u>
  <u t="2130400">time. So yeah, a very interesting</u>
  <u t="2133839">journey. One which makes me never want</u>
  <u t="2135839">to take an Indian bus ever again. I</u>
  <u t="2138800">think today we need a recovery day and</u>
  <u t="2141200">then tomorrow we're going to explore</u>
  <u t="2143280">this city. Can't</u>
  <u t="2148359">click. There it is. Our first view of</u>
  <u t="2151599">the river Ganges, the Ganga River. Look</u>
  <u t="2154560">how many people have gathered to bathe</u>
  <u t="2156000">in the Ganges this early in the morning.</u>
  <u t="2158320">Do you actually think they're all going</u>
  <u t="2159440">in? I I assume so. That's like the</u>
  <u t="2161440">ritual I think they do. We've only been</u>
  <u t="2163520">here like 20 seconds on the river and it</u>
  <u t="2165839">just feels like somewhere completely</u>
  <u t="2167440">different to anywhere else we've been in</u>
  <u t="2169119">India.</u>
  <u t="2170960">The best way to see the city this time</u>
  <u t="2172800">of the day is from the water. We hopped</u>
  <u t="2174800">on a boat that would take us down the</u>
  <u t="2176400">infamous Ganges, a river so polluted by</u>
  <u t="2179119">human industrial waste that is confirmed</u>
  <u t="2181680">biologically dead. But Hindus believe no</u>
  <u t="2184079">matter how dirty the water may seem,</u>
  <u t="2186000">it's spiritually clean and those who</u>
  <u t="2187760">bathe in it will have their sins washed</u>
  <u t="2189680">away. At all times throughout the day,</u>
  <u t="2191839">you will see hundreds of people lining</u>
  <u t="2193440">the gats and entering the water. The</u>
  <u t="2196480">sand has started to rise and one thing</u>
  <u t="2198720">about India is you always get like a</u>
  <u t="2200480">beautiful orange ball of fire. It's just</u>
  <u t="2202960">amazing. Every sunrise is good. That</u>
  <u t="2205200">boat journey was definitely really cool</u>
  <u t="2207440">experience. But I thought as we walk</u>
  <u t="2209040">along like the gaps and along the river,</u>
  <u t="2211119">we're going to actually see more up</u>
  <u t="2212320">close what is going on in this city.</u>
  <u t="2217839">I definitely wasn't expecting to see</u>
  <u t="2219440">that this morning. There's this guy kind</u>
  <u t="2221200">of covered in ash in powder. Um but he</u>
  <u t="2224160">is completely naked. Like completely</u>
  <u t="2226240">naked. Completely naked. Still something</u>
  <u t="2228240">I didn't want to see. So I think these</u>
  <u t="2230480">people who are covered in ash are called</u>
  <u t="2232560">sados. And apparently they've given up</u>
  <u t="2234800">all their material possessions and they</u>
  <u t="2237040">want to live in a world of ash. Very</u>
  <u t="2239599">different way of life. But that's what</u>
  <u t="2242160">you get here in Veronasi. Maybe it gets</u>
  <u t="2244320">worse once you go downstream. But I was</u>
  <u t="2246320">expecting the river Ganes to be a lot</u>
  <u t="2248480">more dirty. It didn't look as bad as I</u>
  <u t="2250480">was expecting. I think I just had this</u>
  <u t="2252560">bad image in my mind. We're going to go</u>
  <u t="2254240">back and grab some breakfast and then</u>
  <u t="2255599">we're going to come out and explore more</u>
  <u t="2256880">of this city later because towards the</u>
  <u t="2259599">evening is when it really starts to</u>
  <u t="2262000">build up. And apparently it gets pretty</u>
  <u t="2264000">crazy because this city is so old. It's</u>
  <u t="2266240">only little alleys and it feels like</u>
  <u t="2267599">you're just walking back in time. Look</u>
  <u t="2269599">at through here. Look at</u>
  <u t="2272440">this. Mind the poo.</u>
  <u t="2276090">[Music]</u>
  <u t="2281680">We are back out in the chaos now. And</u>
  <u t="2283839">honestly, it feels even busier than</u>
  <u t="2285520">earlier. It is a little bit overwhelming</u>
  <u t="2288079">being here. Dodge the cow. Yeah.</u>
  <u t="2292640">We are now back on the riverfront of the</u>
  <u t="2294400">Ganges and it doesn't seem too busy at</u>
  <u t="2296480">the moment. I think once we walk further</u>
  <u t="2298560">up to the other gats, it could be a bit</u>
  <u t="2300720">crazy. Yeah, I think the busiest area is</u>
  <u t="2303200">in the north and that's basically where</u>
  <u t="2305440">we're going to be going as we walk along</u>
  <u t="2307440">the riverfront. But I have picked up a</u>
  <u t="2309599">bit of a cold. I don't know if it's just</u>
  <u t="2310880">from the dust and the pollution in</u>
  <u t="2312640">India, but yeah. Sorry if my voice</u>
  <u t="2314400">sounds a little bit dodgy. It's so</u>
  <u t="2316160">off-putting when I'm vlogging and people</u>
  <u t="2318079">are staring so intensely into my eyes.</u>
  <u t="2321680">Yeah, there is so much staring in India.</u>
  <u t="2323440">You don't get it many other places as</u>
  <u t="2325440">much, but here they just gaze into you</u>
  <u t="2327440">like genuinely stare at you. Yesterday I</u>
  <u t="2330400">had a competition with this guy who was</u>
  <u t="2332160">just staring at me. He didn't know it</u>
  <u t="2333839">was a competition, but I had an internal</u>
  <u t="2335359">competition and after 10 seconds he was</u>
  <u t="2338320">still staring at me and I was staring at</u>
  <u t="2339920">him. So, I just had to look away cuz I</u>
  <u t="2341599">felt so so uncomfortable. I am actually</u>
  <u t="2344320">in a bit of shock right now because it</u>
  <u t="2346000">feels so peaceful. It actually feels</u>
  <u t="2348320">nice to go on a walk and that is the</u>
  <u t="2350160">first time I've said that in India</u>
  <u t="2351680">because honestly I haven't felt great</u>
  <u t="2354320">walking around places just because it's</u>
  <u t="2355920">so busy and the traffic is the traffic</u>
  <u t="2357680">in Veronasi is terrible. Whereas you</u>
  <u t="2359440">come along here and it's actually quite</u>
  <u t="2361440">nice.</u>
  <u t="2365440">We're walking through this area with a</u>
  <u t="2366640">lot of tents and I think this is where a</u>
  <u t="2368240">lot of the sadus are maybe where they</u>
  <u t="2370720">sleep. Um, and these are the men we told</u>
  <u t="2372880">you about earlier. Some of them are</u>
  <u t="2374160">naked. As we walked past one of the</u>
  <u t="2376000">guys, he was covered in ash. I could</u>
  <u t="2377920">kind of smell it as he walked past me.</u>
  <u t="2379760">Like the ashy smell. Um, which is</u>
  <u t="2382240">slightly</u>
  <u t="2386440">off-putting. There is literally a naked</u>
  <u t="2389760">man walking around in the fire ashes. In</u>
  <u t="2392960">the fire ashes.</u>
  <u t="2394440">Like it's I've never seen anything like</u>
  <u t="2397280">this.</u>
  <u t="2400240">I've just checked on the map and we have</u>
  <u t="2401920">just reached our first burning gat. And</u>
  <u t="2404720">as it kind of says in the name, this is</u>
  <u t="2407440">a a gap where they burn bodies and</u>
  <u t="2409520">they're cremated and then put into the</u>
  <u t="2411119">Ganges. Now, we're actually going to be</u>
  <u t="2412560">heading further north to the largest</u>
  <u t="2414400">burning gap where the most cremations</u>
  <u t="2415920">happen every single</u>
  <u t="2417480">day. So, it's going to get pretty crazy</u>
  <u t="2420320">as we get further on, but we haven't</u>
  <u t="2422880">seen any bodies as of yet. I don't want</u>
  <u t="2425760">to get too much up close shots because</u>
  <u t="2427280">you want to be respectful, but over</u>
  <u t="2428720">there you can see the smoke coming out</u>
  <u t="2430640">and I assume that's a ceremony going on.</u>
  <u t="2433280">It's a massive culture shock for me.</u>
  <u t="2434880">I've never seen kind of dead bodies or</u>
  <u t="2437440">cremation or anything, but here it is</u>
  <u t="2440000">just so normal. That is just what they</u>
  <u t="2441760">do and that's what people come here to</u>
  <u t="2443760">do. They come here to die and they are</u>
  <u t="2446720">happy to do that. So, it's kind of</u>
  <u t="2448800">interesting seeing something that's so</u>
  <u t="2451040">hidden from us be something so public</u>
  <u t="2453520">here. Does kind of make you slightly</u>
  <u t="2455520">uncomfortable, but it's interesting.</u>
  <u t="2457839">Looks like it's about to get a bit</u>
  <u t="2459520">busier up here. There is so many people</u>
  <u t="2461800">around. Look at the look at the foot</u>
  <u t="2464400">traffic we've got coming in. And as we</u>
  <u t="2466720">leave this gap and go over to the next</u>
  <u t="2468319">one. Farasi is actually a very popular</u>
  <u t="2470640">tourist destinations for Indians as</u>
  <u t="2472240">well. I think there's over 5 million</u>
  <u t="2474079">local Indians who come here because</u>
  <u t="2476079">obviously they want to, you know, go in</u>
  <u t="2477920">the Ganges, take a dip because it is</u>
  <u t="2479839">considered very a very sacred river and</u>
  <u t="2482880">because there's so many tourists here,</u>
  <u t="2484079">you obviously get loads of sellers who</u>
  <u t="2486079">are selling all kind of stuff. So all</u>
  <u t="2488079">these beads, all loads of different</u>
  <u t="2490160">stuff all along the banks back there.</u>
  <u t="2493119">Immediately didn't look cuz I told it,</u>
  <u t="2494960">but I just saw something like very</u>
  <u t="2497119">disturbing. You're freaking me out. What</u>
  <u t="2498480">did you see? Basically, I saw the guy's</u>
  <u t="2501280">body part and then there was like</u>
  <u t="2503680">something hanging and swaying from it</u>
  <u t="2505680">like attached to it. What? Honestly,</u>
  <u t="2508079">didn't give it that much of a look. What</u>
  <u t="2509359">was hanging? I don't know. I really</u>
  <u t="2511520">didn't look that much, but it was just a</u>
  <u t="2513200">little Okay. Never seen that. Not on the</u>
  <u t="2516079">streets, not in public. Like, well, I</u>
  <u t="2518319">don't think people do that in private</u>
  <u t="2519440">either, do they? I I don't know. Okay,</u>
  <u t="2521839">I'm going to stop talking.</u>
  <u t="2530800">Mhm. Those female sados, I don't know</u>
  <u t="2532800">the correct term. Um, they were so nice.</u>
  <u t="2535280">They were kind of calling me over and</u>
  <u t="2536800">like shaking my hand. They had me sit</u>
  <u t="2538480">with them. They were saying something to</u>
  <u t="2539920">me. Obviously, I couldn't understand,</u>
  <u t="2541280">but they seemed like they meant well.</u>
  <u t="2543359">And then we gave them like 20 um and</u>
  <u t="2547359">they asked us for 100, which is kind of</u>
  <u t="2550240">crazy considering they give up material</u>
  <u t="2552240">possessions and then they ask for quite</u>
  <u t="2554160">a lot of money. We're into our walking</u>
  <u t="2555760">and our hiking and you know go for</u>
  <u t="2557680">little walks but this walk is like</u>
  <u t="2559359">nothing I've ever done before. Like I've</u>
  <u t="2561040">seen people covered in ash like just</u>
  <u t="2564160">things I've never seen before in the</u>
  <u t="2565920">middle of the city by this river. Like</u>
  <u t="2568000">this place in India is like nowhere</u>
  <u t="2569839">else. And if you want a a crazy</u>
  <u t="2571760">experience or visit somewhere completely</u>
  <u t="2574800">different then Baronasi is the place to</u>
  <u t="2577680">come. We have just come up to have a</u>
  <u t="2580160">little bit of a viewpoint of all the</u>
  <u t="2582079">crowds all around here. We want to be a</u>
  <u t="2584319">little bit honest on what we found out</u>
  <u t="2586480">and what our hotel owner was telling us</u>
  <u t="2588880">about. And a lot of the sadus here, a</u>
  <u t="2590640">lot of the crazy things that they're</u>
  <u t="2591920">doing um is actually fake and they're</u>
  <u t="2594560">not real sados. Apparently, the proper</u>
  <u t="2596079">sadus actually live up near Rishek and</u>
  <u t="2598160">in the Himalayas and live a very</u>
  <u t="2599680">peaceful life and not asking for money.</u>
  <u t="2602240">I almost want to think of it as like</u>
  <u t="2603680">they're more like street performers than</u>
  <u t="2605200">like general sados. I would also say</u>
  <u t="2607359">that here in Veronasi has been the worst</u>
  <u t="2609599">in terms of men staring. I have never</u>
  <u t="2612400">experienced it this badly. Um I feel</u>
  <u t="2615040">quite uncomfortable even just lifting my</u>
  <u t="2616720">head up. I feel like I have look have to</u>
  <u t="2618480">look at the ground most of the time so</u>
  <u t="2620240">that I avoid making eye contact with</u>
  <u t="2622000">anyone and I don't know they just keep</u>
  <u t="2624319">staring. They don't even smile. They're</u>
  <u t="2626079">kind of like staring at you and like</u>
  <u t="2627280">when they want a photo rather than like</u>
  <u t="2628880">asking politely like some people are</u>
  <u t="2630720">like grabbing me.</u>
  <u t="2632720">What have we got here? A dolphin</u>
  <u t="2634400">restaurant. Hello. Hello. Oh, this is</u>
  <u t="2638119">cute. This is away from the chaos. But</u>
  <u t="2640640">we can view the chaos. It's quite nice</u>
  <u t="2642400">to just get out of it for a second. Oh,</u>
  <u t="2644720">wow. Thank you. Wow, that looks good.</u>
  <u t="2649440">Thank you very much. I got I know it's</u>
  <u t="2651839">not very Indian local, but I've got a</u>
  <u t="2654560">Kit Kat milkshake and I'm really happy</u>
  <u t="2656079">about it. It looks really good. This is</u>
  <u t="2659520">my first very first banana lassi ever in</u>
  <u t="2663200">the history of Joel Friend.</u>
  <u t="2668119">M. Oh, wow. That's really good. You</u>
  <u t="2671119">know, like Nesquick, the Nesquick banana</u>
  <u t="2674000">milkshake as you have as a kid. Kind of</u>
  <u t="2676319">like that, but there's actual proper</u>
  <u t="2677920">ingredients like yogurt and milk in it.</u>
  <u t="2680400">I am a lassie lover after that. Back in</u>
  <u t="2683040">the chaos now. Let's head towards the</u>
  <u t="2685839">Burning Gap. Hi.</u>
  <u t="2689040">Hi. It is so busy right now. It is</u>
  <u t="2691760">feeling like the most populated country</u>
  <u t="2693119">on the planet, isn't it? Yeah. I can</u>
  <u t="2694720">smell onion. Onions? Yeah. Really</u>
  <u t="2696640">strong. Oh, yeah. Some street food going</u>
  <u t="2698960">on. Right now it is definitely busier</u>
  <u t="2701359">than usual in Baronasi because of the</u>
  <u t="2702960">Kua. So a lot of people are coming here</u>
  <u t="2705680">because of that festival. Wo, look how</u>
  <u t="2707839">many people there are here. Like it is</u>
  <u t="2709520">insane. And look how many shoes are down</u>
  <u t="2711599">there. All the shoes that have like</u>
  <u t="2713119">washed up. Why is there so many flip</u>
  <u t="2714960">flops? That is crazy. Keep your shoes</u>
  <u t="2717119">on. Almost looks like there's going to</u>
  <u t="2718319">be a big crush here. I feel like we</u>
  <u t="2720319">should stay here until it chills out a</u>
  <u t="2721920">little bit. Let's join this mayhem cube.</u>
  <u t="2725520">See if we can get through.</u>
  <u t="2727200">[Applause]</u>
  <u t="2729680">Which country?</u>
  <u t="2732560">Which country? England.</u>
  <u t="2735920">England. London. London. Yeah.</u>
  <u t="2739839">There we go. Into a little bit of a</u>
  <u t="2742240">crash.</u>
  <u t="2746240">We made it through without too much</u>
  <u t="2748720">chaos.</u>
  <u t="2752160">I don't want to lose you. Make sure you</u>
  <u t="2753599">stay behind me or grab my bag or</u>
  <u t="2755760">something. I've almost got lost a couple</u>
  <u t="2757280">of times. One time I got a bit stuck</u>
  <u t="2758880">behind Joel and then I had a circle of</u>
  <u t="2760720">photo tapers around me. Yeah, I was I</u>
  <u t="2762960">was vlogging. That's why you just I</u>
  <u t="2764960">forgot. I didn't realize you just</u>
  <u t="2766480">disappeared. Forgot about me.</u>
  <u t="2770400">Here we are then. We have reached the</u>
  <u t="2772240">destination that we've been trying to</u>
  <u t="2774000">get to as we've walked along the left</u>
  <u t="2775760">side of the Ganges. We are at the</u>
  <u t="2777359">burning gap, but not any burning gap,</u>
  <u t="2779119">the largest burning gap. And this is</u>
  <u t="2780880">where they cremate over 80 people every</u>
  <u t="2783359">single day here. Oh, wow. Okay. I think</u>
  <u t="2785920">I've just seen someone carrying a body.</u>
  <u t="2787839">I did just see I think a dead body going</u>
  <u t="2791119">into the water. Like not even cremated.</u>
  <u t="2794319">Really? Did you actually see it? No, it</u>
  <u t="2796960">was wrapped wrapped in orange. In this</u>
  <u t="2799599">gap, the fires have said to be burning</u>
  <u t="2801359">continuously for 3,500 years. Here, the</u>
  <u t="2805040">bodies are dipped into the Ganges just</u>
  <u t="2806800">before the bodies are taken to be</u>
  <u t="2808480">cremated. Hindus believe that cremations</u>
  <u t="2810880">on the banks of the Ganges help the soul</u>
  <u t="2812720">attain moxia, meaning the end of cycle</u>
  <u t="2815359">of death and rebirth.</u>
  <u t="2818079">Go this way. Okay, thank you.</u>
  <u t="2820400">Apparently, we should go this way. So, I</u>
  <u t="2822480">assume all this wood here will be used.</u>
  <u t="2824560">There's so much wood will be used to</u>
  <u t="2827040">burn the bodies.</u>
  <u t="2829760">To be cremated here in Veronasi is a</u>
  <u t="2832000">great honor. Strangers are welcome to</u>
  <u t="2833760">watch the cremation rituals and rejoice</u>
  <u t="2835520">with the families that their loved ones</u>
  <u t="2837040">have entered a place of peace and</u>
  <u t="2839119">happiness. As we were watching the</u>
  <u t="2840880">flames, this guy came up to me and he</u>
  <u t="2842480">said that these flames actually burn for</u>
  <u t="2844400">24 hours. So around the clock they are</u>
  <u t="2846960">burning bodies and behind the burning is</u>
  <u t="2849839">actually a hospice and apparently that's</u>
  <u t="2851839">where people wait to die. So people who</u>
  <u t="2854640">are kind of sick and elderly, they wait</u>
  <u t="2856400">there for their turn. Generally I just</u>
  <u t="2858720">feel incredibly overstimulated. There's</u>
  <u t="2860880">so many thoughts in my mind. Like partly</u>
  <u t="2862800">I just feel like I've gone back in time</u>
  <u t="2864560">maybe to like 30 BC. I don't know what</u>
  <u t="2867040">was going on then. But feels old. It</u>
  <u t="2870079">feels crazy. I knew it was going to be</u>
  <u t="2872640">intense coming here. But the things I've</u>
  <u t="2874400">seen and the way it's done in such an</u>
  <u t="2876720">old ancient crazy way is like I'm never</u>
  <u t="2880480">going to forget like this trip, this day</u>
  <u t="2883040">of just being here.</u>
  <u t="2887440">Very shortly there should be a ceremony</u>
  <u t="2889680">here. I'm not too sure what's going to</u>
  <u t="2891760">happen, but it's some sort of ritual</u>
  <u t="2893920">which goes on every evening here in</u>
  <u t="2895839">Baronasi. Okay, I'm going to do one.</u>
  <u t="2900800">Hello. This was a oneie. No, no, no, no.</u>
  <u t="2905920">No, do not grab me.</u>
  <u t="2913839">The problem with the selfies are they</u>
  <u t="2916160">just kind of grab you aggressively and</u>
  <u t="2918319">if we say yes once then honestly like</u>
  <u t="2920640">swarms of people come and kind of chase</u>
  <u t="2922559">us and it's not very nice. The bells</u>
  <u t="2924480">have just started going off. I'm not</u>
  <u t="2926240">100% what what that means but I think it</u>
  <u t="2929599">might be time for the ceremony.</u>
  <u t="2943119">The bell ringing is to ward off the evil</u>
  <u t="2945200">spirits and is an offering of seven</u>
  <u t="2946800">elaborate gifts of light to the</u>
  <u t="2948700">[Applause]</u>
  <u t="2953340">[Music]</u>
  <u t="2955960">river. After that ceremony, everyone's</u>
  <u t="2958400">going in the water and like dipping down</u>
  <u t="2961119">and they're releasing these candles. I</u>
  <u t="2962960">think when you release candles in the</u>
  <u t="2964400">water, it's said to give good karma. So</u>
  <u t="2966240">that's why they've got like the flowers</u>
  <u t="2967599">around them with like a little candle.</u>
  <u t="2969440">It's quite cute. Maybe we should release</u>
  <u t="2971200">one. And that guy is releasing some old</u>
  <u t="2973680">milk or chai into the water. Oh, he is.</u>
  <u t="2975920">He's washing washing his chai. You just</u>
  <u t="2978640">have everything going on at the same</u>
  <u t="2980000">time like a spiritual ceremony next to</u>
  <u t="2981920">just like some guy cleaning his dishes.</u>
  <u t="2988480">So here we are. We just got these two</u>
  <u t="2990160">candles. I gave the guy 50 and he gave</u>
  <u t="2991920">us another one. Yeah. Really nice guy.</u>
  <u t="2994559">But they're so pretty. They are so</u>
  <u t="2996160">pretty. So, we're going to release these</u>
  <u t="2997599">and hopefully we get good karma. Yeah.</u>
  <u t="2999680">Together.</u>
  <u t="3005440">Almost feel like making a wish. I feel</u>
  <u t="3007040">that's what we would do. But</u>
  <u t="3015040">it's just really, really beautiful here</u>
  <u t="3016720">at the front, especially down by the</u>
  <u t="3018720">Ganges here. spirit feels a very calm,</u>
  <u t="3020800">very spiritual. It felt like a cool</u>
  <u t="3023119">little moment lip releasing that on the</u>
  <u t="3024720">river. After a crazy, overwhelming day</u>
  <u t="3027520">in Vonasi, we got up early the next day</u>
  <u t="3030000">for a flight to a completely different</u>
  <u t="3031920">part of the country.</u>
  <u t="3035440">How are you feeling this morning? Not</u>
  <u t="3038240">good. Unfortunately, last night after</u>
  <u t="3041040">our day in Veronasi, I ended up getting</u>
  <u t="3043040">a very bad stomach and was on the toilet</u>
  <u t="3045119">for a while. I've taken a modium. Um,</u>
  <u t="3047920">but my stomach cramps are quite bad. I'm</u>
  <u t="3049920">quite hungry though at the same time.</u>
  <u t="3051599">So, it's not too bad. I haven't vomited</u>
  <u t="3053599">or anything, but not the most</u>
  <u t="3055680">comfortable.</u>
  <u t="3059050">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3071839">How you feeling?</u>
  <u t="3073839">It happened.</u>
  <u t="3075599">We thought we might be okay if we ate at</u>
  <u t="3077680">good restaurants,</u>
  <u t="3079319">but deli belly. Well, very nasty belly</u>
  <u t="3082480">has hit me. Obviously, I've still been</u>
  <u t="3084480">struggling with my upset tummy today and</u>
  <u t="3088400">we've both just been in bed, but we</u>
  <u t="3090000">didn't realize like we probably got ill</u>
  <u t="3092559">just coincidentally from different</u>
  <u t="3094319">places. Like I'm pretty sure mine was</u>
  <u t="3096559">from Vinasi somewhere. I picked up some</u>
  <u t="3098640">kind of bug. I think Joles might even be</u>
  <u t="3101040">from Mumbai airport lounge. It's hard to</u>
  <u t="3103599">know. It's hard to know, but that's the</u>
  <u t="3105280">only thing I've eaten today,</u>
  <u t="3107760">literally. And then a quason. So,</u>
  <u t="3112079">I think we need a good night's</u>
  <u t="3114450">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3120599">sleep. We last talked to you guys a few</u>
  <u t="3123200">nights ago and we were not doing very</u>
  <u t="3125040">well. Since then, we still haven't been</u>
  <u t="3127359">doing very well. Um, we have been in</u>
  <u t="3130319">this bed a lot. I'm just going to check</u>
  <u t="3132480">on Joel. He is here in the bathroom. Can</u>
  <u t="3135599">I come in? Yeah, if you don't want to</u>
  <u t="3138240">smell anything.</u>
  <u t="3140720">How are you doing in here? Little bit of</u>
  <u t="3143119">a struggle. The last few days we've been</u>
  <u t="3145040">on this very toilet and it's seen some</u>
  <u t="3147079">things you no one should see. But we are</u>
  <u t="3150319">feeling a little bit better now.</u>
  <u t="3151839">Definitely not 100%. So, we can start</u>
  <u t="3154160">exploring Goa finally because I'm very</u>
  <u t="3157359">excited to be here. Aren't you? I am. We</u>
  <u t="3159680">haven't seen anything because we've been</u>
  <u t="3161520">stuck in this region.</u>
  <u t="3165040">Good morning from the south of India. We</u>
  <u t="3167520">are finally in Goa and we have escaped</u>
  <u t="3169440">the crazy north of India after 2 weeks</u>
  <u t="3172000">there. We're currently on a very bumpy</u>
  <u t="3174559">dusty road and we are heading to a</u>
  <u t="3177440">beach, an actual beach in India. And</u>
  <u t="3180319">they're supposedly supposed to be</u>
  <u t="3182400">incredibly beautiful.</u>
  <u t="3193090">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3194720">This is cool. It's gone into like a</u>
  <u t="3196160">little jungle forest. A narrow narrow</u>
  <u t="3199599">walk. Oh, there's a cat. Probably a</u>
  <u t="3201760">domesticated cat, not a not a tiger. Oh,</u>
  <u t="3205599">I can hear the sea. This is incredible.</u>
  <u t="3208800">It's actually lovely. It's very small,</u>
  <u t="3211359">though. Boating. Boating. Yeah. Actually</u>
  <u t="3214240">next to this mountain there's one visa.</u>
  <u t="3215839">So we'll take you there. We'll drop you</u>
  <u t="3217520">for like uh 20 minutes. And how much to</u>
  <u t="3220079">go there? Actually we are taking,000 per</u>
  <u t="3222480">person but you have two people. No you</u>
  <u t="3224240">give 1,800 only. That's it. Yeah it's a</u>
  <u t="3226559">lot. Actually I taking that much only</u>
  <u t="3228640">sir. Oh only. Ah for me it sounds a lot</u>
  <u t="3232079">of money. 1,500 for both of you. We'll</u>
  <u t="3234480">give 1,500 for both of you. A private</u>
  <u t="3236400">boat for Okay, let's</u>
  <u t="3237960">do let's go. Hi, what a beautiful way to</u>
  <u t="3242240">start our first proper day here in Goa</u>
  <u t="3244480">after 3 or 4 days of miserable food</u>
  <u t="3247800">poisoning from North India. We're still</u>
  <u t="3250319">not fully recovered by Yeah, if I'm</u>
  <u t="3251839">honest, we're still not fully recovered.</u>
  <u t="3253760">So, at any minute, the toilet at the</u>
  <u t="3256839">moment. It could get</u>
  <u t="3259880">interesting. This is definitely quite</u>
  <u t="3261760">the expensive trip to do. £15 just to go</u>
  <u t="3264960">round to the next beach. Sometimes you</u>
  <u t="3266559">just got to go for it. It's so</u>
  <u t="3268680">overpriced.</u>
  <u t="3270319">It's just there.</u>
  <u t="3274400">So, this is Honeymoon Beach. Ameilia is</u>
  <u t="3276480">going to jump in off the boat.</u>
  <u t="3279839">Here we are on honeymoon. See you here.</u>
  <u t="3282400">On Honeymoon Beach. On Honeymoon Beach.</u>
  <u t="3284480">It's not our honeymoon, by the way.</u>
  <u t="3286160">Yeah, it's on that beach. No rumors,</u>
  <u t="3287839">please. In all honesty, now I know how</u>
  <u t="3290000">far the beach is, which is literally</u>
  <u t="3291680">like just around the corner, just the</u>
  <u t="3293599">other side of that hill. It is very</u>
  <u t="3295599">expensive to get here. I could have swam</u>
  <u t="3297920">here pretty much. Pretty much could have</u>
  <u t="3300240">swam here. But I mean, oh well. At least</u>
  <u t="3303359">we're supporting the locals, you know,</u>
  <u t="3305040">giving them some healthy money. It's not</u>
  <u t="3307280">a bad beach. And the great thing is this</u>
  <u t="3309119">beach won't be nearly as busy as the</u>
  <u t="3311680">butterfly beach where we just arrived</u>
  <u t="3313920">literally 10 minutes</u>
  <u t="3317000">earlier. The water does look quite</u>
  <u t="3319359">impressive. But I wasn't sure what the</u>
  <u t="3320800">beaches were going to be like here in</u>
  <u t="3322400">India. But it's fairly like a green nice</u>
  <u t="3325280">color. You know, not crystal clear</u>
  <u t="3327200">because even though I'm a meter deep, I</u>
  <u t="3328960">can barely see my feet. But I think</u>
  <u t="3331839">later this afternoon, we'll try and head</u>
  <u t="3333359">to another beach which is supposed to be</u>
  <u t="3334880">like more remote and like beautiful like</u>
  <u t="3337920">more white sandy. It's quite peaceful</u>
  <u t="3339760">here, isn't it? It's quite peaceful.</u>
  <u t="3341280">Imagine, you know, few days ago we were</u>
  <u t="3343280">in Veronasi and now you can talk to me</u>
  <u t="3345680">very quietly on this beautiful honeymoon</u>
  <u t="3348000">beach in the same country. Remember this</u>
  <u t="3350480">is the same country. There's no beeping</u>
  <u t="3352000">going on here. It's a huge country. But</u>
  <u t="3355040">like this just feels a million miles</u>
  <u t="3356960">away from Vinasio. Explain. Oh yeah.</u>
  <u t="3359760">Been here about 50 minutes now. And now</u>
  <u t="3361680">we're going to be heading back to the</u>
  <u t="3362880">main beach. It's also only 10:00 a.m.</u>
  <u t="3364880">and it's already getting pretty hot</u>
  <u t="3366480">here. I don't know if the rocks are</u>
  <u t="3367839">making it really warm, but blime me, it</u>
  <u t="3370400">must be so hot here in July and August</u>
  <u t="3372480">cuz it's only March. It's only the 1st</u>
  <u t="3374160">of March.</u>
  <u t="3377280">Here we go. Back on</u>
  <u t="3378850">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3382280">the city. The most amazing thing about</u>
  <u t="3386640">being here in Goa is just how peaceful</u>
  <u t="3389520">it is. Just stop for a minute and take</u>
  <u t="3391040">it</u>
  <u t="3392200">in. This is India, the same country.</u>
  <u t="3398240">So many horns. I think that will blow my</u>
  <u t="3400640">mind for the rest of the trip cuz we are</u>
  <u t="3402720">heading further south to Kerala and I</u>
  <u t="3404960">think in Kerala it should be similar to</u>
  <u t="3408559">this.</u>
  <u t="3418960">This road is terrible.</u>
  <u t="3422880">We've got lots of cows in the way.</u>
  <u t="3424480">Please don't grab me. I'm actually kind</u>
  <u t="3426880">of scared of the balls. Flipping an X.</u>
  <u t="3429440">That's what you got to do when you're</u>
  <u t="3430640">driving in here. Dodger the cows. Have a</u>
  <u t="3433520">little</u>
  <u t="3435359">Don't</u>
  <u t="3437119">I want to talk?</u>
  <u t="3441040">Thank you.</u>
  <u t="3442760">Wow. Here we go.</u>
  <u t="3446160">Cheers. Cheers. So, this is my first</u>
  <u t="3449839">Indian coconut.</u>
  <u t="3454160">Oh, that's good. Right. That's so good.</u>
  <u t="3456319">So good. Only 70 rupees for this.</u>
  <u t="3458799">Coconuts are supposed to have like more</u>
  <u t="3460880">nutritional value. Well, more hydrating</u>
  <u t="3463520">than water. So, get yourself a</u>
  <u t="3469880">coconut. The beaches we went to this</u>
  <u t="3472079">morning were okay, but I don't think</u>
  <u t="3474319">they fully show off how good Goa is. And</u>
  <u t="3476880">so, we've been recommended this one</u>
  <u t="3478319">beach that's supposed to be really nice</u>
  <u t="3479760">and very empty. That is where we're</u>
  <u t="3481920">heading now. But I think we might try</u>
  <u t="3483520">and get some food along the way. Let's</u>
  <u t="3486559">go. You ready for food? I'm so hungry.</u>
  <u t="3492660">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3497839">Just arrived at Zest. Look how fancy</u>
  <u t="3500160">this looks. It looks like we are in</u>
  <u t="3502240">Bali. Well, in a minute it might look</u>
  <u t="3504720">like we're in Bali when we take you into</u>
  <u t="3506240">this little</u>
  <u t="3508280">place. Here we go. Look at</u>
  <u t="3516280">this. This is not a bad thing. I've got</u>
  <u t="3519839">an iced latte which a little bit risky</u>
  <u t="3522559">because of our stomachs, but I can't</u>
  <u t="3525200">complain. This view is incredible. We're</u>
  <u t="3527520">at the very front of this cafe with this</u>
  <u t="3529839">beautiful view. I can't wait to go to</u>
  <u t="3531920">check out this beach after. This place</u>
  <u t="3533839">is insanely beautiful. We were just</u>
  <u t="3535920">saying like if you had to guess where</u>
  <u t="3537359">you were right now, this feels like</u>
  <u t="3539440">Australia. Like they're just big white</u>
  <u t="3541599">beach, blue water. Thank you. Thank you</u>
  <u t="3544400">very much. These look insane. Wo, that</u>
  <u t="3548559">is a lot of fruit. I am very excited.</u>
  <u t="3550799">That is a proper Balan smoothie bowl.</u>
  <u t="3553440">That is This is my passion. It's very</u>
  <u t="3555599">good. It's very good. Very, very great.</u>
  <u t="3558640">This isn't like the only cafe like this.</u>
  <u t="3560480">There are a few like really nice cafes</u>
  <u t="3562240">here in Goa. I just can't believe I'm in</u>
  <u t="3564480">India right now. Like this was not what</u>
  <u t="3567760">you imagine of India at all. We're just</u>
  <u t="3571520">going to quickly jump on the bike and</u>
  <u t="3573040">just head a little bit further down to</u>
  <u t="3574400">the beach because blime me I want to</u>
  <u t="3576640">check out that beach which was in front</u>
  <u t="3578240">of us at Zest. There it is. Ready? Yeah.</u>
  <u t="3589440">Here we go then. This must be one of the</u>
  <u t="3591359">most beautiful beaches in all of Gala.</u>
  <u t="3594240">Now, I have no um evidence to support</u>
  <u t="3596720">that, but look at this flipping beach.</u>
  <u t="3599520">There is no one on it. And we're in a</u>
  <u t="3601599">country with 1.5 billion people on it.</u>
  <u t="3605200">It's huge and it's so empty. Like a</u>
  <u t="3607280">beach like this in the UK would be</u>
  <u t="3609200">packed with people. I just can't believe</u>
  <u t="3611200">this is India. But I don't know about</u>
  <u t="3612960">you, but I kind of want to go in the</u>
  <u t="3614160">water. This sand is burning my feet.</u>
  <u t="3616400">It's so hot. I think we'll settle down</u>
  <u t="3618480">right about here. Kind of surprising</u>
  <u t="3620559">that they actually have a lifeguards</u>
  <u t="3622799">here because this is such an empty</u>
  <u t="3624240">beach. They also have it in the main</u>
  <u t="3625839">beach in PaloMen, which is where we're</u>
  <u t="3627599">staying. We'll show you that area and</u>
  <u t="3628960">that beach later. Flip a neck. It's too</u>
  <u t="3631119">hot on my feet. I just took my</u>
  <u t="3632319">Birkenstocks off. It is so hot here,</u>
  <u t="3634559">even though it is just March. Like, it</u>
  <u t="3636720">must get so hot here in August and July.</u>
  <u t="3639680">Anyway, let's go in the sea.</u>
  <u t="3648400">The sea water here is just so warm. Like</u>
  <u t="3651280">it feels like a farm. Here we go. Some</u>
  <u t="3653680">waves.</u>
  <u t="3655020">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3660480">What a beautiful</u>
  <u t="3671799">beach. It is so peaceful. We've just</u>
  <u t="3674079">come up here sat in the shade cuz it is</u>
  <u t="3676559">so hot in the sun. Especially the sand.</u>
  <u t="3678480">It's so hard to walk on, right? Yeah. It</u>
  <u t="3680240">literally burns my feet. But I guess</u>
  <u t="3681760">they literally haven't had any rain</u>
  <u t="3683839">recently, so all the sand is just hot.</u>
  <u t="3686480">One of the interesting things about Goer</u>
  <u t="3688319">is it's kind of nicknamed the party</u>
  <u t="3690319">place here in India because the it's got</u>
  <u t="3693760">like the lowest tax on alcohol. So you</u>
  <u t="3695839">can actually get like pretty cheap</u>
  <u t="3696960">alcohol compared to like other states. I</u>
  <u t="3698799">think there's actually direct flights</u>
  <u t="3700240">from London to Goa. So there's quite a</u>
  <u t="3702880">few Brits who come here on holiday</u>
  <u t="3704400">because you know you can drink really</u>
  <u t="3706079">cheap alcohol especially compared to the</u>
  <u t="3708079">UK but also it attracts a lot of local</u>
  <u t="3710559">Indians and it's also supposed to be</u>
  <u t="3712160">like one of the safest places for women</u>
  <u t="3713839">in all of India and even like walking</u>
  <u t="3716000">around it's very different from when we</u>
  <u t="3718240">were in Vinasi and we had a lot of eyes</u>
  <u t="3719920">on us like asking for selfies people</u>
  <u t="3721839">like grabbing us and stuff whereas here</u>
  <u t="3724400">people are so relaxed people are very</u>
  <u t="3726079">kind you also don't get hassled for like</u>
  <u t="3728599">anything which is very very different</u>
  <u t="3731040">from where we have been in the north.</u>
  <u t="3732960">So, the bike that we rented is costing</u>
  <u t="3735040">us £500 rupees a day. So, £5 a day,</u>
  <u t="3737920">which I don't think is too bad. I really</u>
  <u t="3740240">don't know why I didn't just park up</u>
  <u t="3741839">there. It would have been so much</u>
  <u t="3742960">easier. But anyway, let's try and get</u>
  <u t="3745040">this thing out.</u>
  <u t="3748839">Right. This</u>
  <u t="3754440">is Joel's going into a ditch.</u>
  <u t="3762640">This feels sketchy. And he's</u>
  <u t="3766280">sliding. It worked somehow. Yay. Wasn't</u>
  <u t="3771359">too bad. Could have been a lot worse.</u>
  <u t="3773920">Could have been. Could have been a lot</u>
  <u t="3776240">easier if I just stopped.</u>
  <u t="3778720">That really could have been avoided, but</u>
  <u t="3781119">that's not Joel.</u>
  <u t="3785260">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3789599">We are back in the town where we're</u>
  <u t="3791359">staying in PaloMen. This is quite a</u>
  <u t="3793440">popular town in the south of Goa. The</u>
  <u t="3795440">weird thing is here you have to walk</u>
  <u t="3796799">through restaurants to get to the beach,</u>
  <u t="3799280">so it feels like you're just</u>
  <u t="3800319">trespassing, but that's just what you</u>
  <u t="3802079">have to</u>
  <u t="3803750">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3808760">do. So, as you can tell, this beach is a</u>
  <u t="3811680">lot more set up for tourists. There's</u>
  <u t="3813760">obviously like daybenches, daybenches,</u>
  <u t="3816880">what they called? Sun lounges all along</u>
  <u t="3818960">the beach. You got the dogs. You got</u>
  <u t="3820960">loads of people on it because it's</u>
  <u t="3822240">coming down to sunset. It's quite nice</u>
  <u t="3824000">because the beach here isn't too built</u>
  <u t="3826000">on. It's not like big like modern</u>
  <u t="3827680">building. It's kind of these shacks. So,</u>
  <u t="3829680">you can actually stay on the beach</u>
  <u t="3830799">front. They were about 60 60 I think a</u>
  <u t="3834079">night, but we're staying somewhere which</u>
  <u t="3835599">is half the price and it's literally a</u>
  <u t="3837359">2-minute walk from the beach. So, we'll</u>
  <u t="3838880">show you that a bit later. Look at all</u>
  <u t="3840720">the palm trees there are all the way</u>
  <u t="3842400">along the beach. And there just little</u>
  <u t="3844400">little beach shacks. This side of the</u>
  <u t="3845920">beach looks a bit like Thailand because</u>
  <u t="3847359">of all the rocks. It reminds me of like</u>
  <u t="3850000">Kottow or like Kosmu Copangyang. It's</u>
  <u t="3853440">really really pretty. I have to be</u>
  <u t="3855359">honest, I do feel like the beaches</u>
  <u t="3856720">actually here in India, well Goa</u>
  <u t="3858799">specifically are much nicer than the</u>
  <u t="3860960">beaches in Sri Lanka cuz they're so</u>
  <u t="3862640">wide. So you can actually like walk</u>
  <u t="3863920">along them really nicely. They feel like</u>
  <u t="3866480">big Australian beaches. We just went for</u>
  <u t="3868720">a little swim and it was very nice. It's</u>
  <u t="3870880">so calm in the water right now, even</u>
  <u t="3872720">though that wave sounded really loud.</u>
  <u t="3874880">But unfortunately, the sun has already</u>
  <u t="3876240">gone down. Look at it. It's already gone</u>
  <u t="3878240">down because there's so much cloud. But</u>
  <u t="3880400">it's a lovely little vibe. People are</u>
  <u t="3881760">playing frisbee. People playing</u>
  <u t="3883640">football. It just feels like quite a</u>
  <u t="3886480">nice atmosphere down here for sunset.</u>
  <u t="3888319">Yeah, I feel like there's a nice amount</u>
  <u t="3890319">going on without it feeling too crowded.</u>
  <u t="3892240">I mean, there's no one sat anywhere near</u>
  <u t="3894559">us, but there's still lots going on.</u>
  <u t="3896480">Aha. We have the sun has just poked out</u>
  <u t="3898799">for like maybe 10 seconds. It's already</u>
  <u t="3902079">going. It's already going, but we're</u>
  <u t="3903440">just going to take that last little</u>
  <u t="3904559">moment in. Amazing. Good sun. Good sun.</u>
  <u t="3907760">Very red. Very red.</u>
  <u t="3915119">We have all packed up and we are about</u>
  <u t="3918160">to take a night train from here in Goa</u>
  <u t="3921359">all the way south 800 km to Kochi. We're</u>
  <u t="3924960">going to Carerala. Everyone's spoken so</u>
  <u t="3927280">much about Carerala, so I am very</u>
  <u t="3929920">excited for this. You ready for the</u>
  <u t="3932000">journey? Packed up. I think so. The taxi</u>
  <u t="3934799">is probably here to take us to the</u>
  <u t="3936520">station. Get my shoes on. Let's go to</u>
  <u t="3939760">Kerala. You got the key. I do and the</u>
  <u t="3942559">padlock.</u>
  <u t="3949039">Here we are then. We have arrived at</u>
  <u t="3950720">Magadon Station. The station here in</u>
  <u t="3952640">Goa. feel like I'm back in India.</u>
  <u t="3954720">Although it's still much calmer. It's</u>
  <u t="3957200">way calmer. This would not be what a</u>
  <u t="3959200">station would be like in Delhi or</u>
  <u t="3961240">Vinasi. This is calm. Said we had to get</u>
  <u t="3964720">here an hour before. Not really sure why</u>
  <u t="3967599">or if that's really true. I think we</u>
  <u t="3970000">have just found our train up here on</u>
  <u t="3971680">platform 6. I think we're in Well, we</u>
  <u t="3974640">are in first class, but I don't know if</u>
  <u t="3976319">it' be the first carriage on the train.</u>
  <u t="3978559">Let's have a look. So far, it feels very</u>
  <u t="3981760">civilized, isn't it? Yeah, it's very</u>
  <u t="3983440">like calm experience. Yeah.</u>
  <u t="3986730">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3989920">I think we must be down the other end</u>
  <u t="3991599">because all the second classes are here.</u>
  <u t="3995920">Must be at the end, maybe. How do you</u>
  <u t="3998160">hear the second class? Cuz it says</u>
  <u t="4000000">second class on it there.</u>
  <u t="4002480">Don't know how I missed that. We've been</u>
  <u t="4004640">walking down this train for like 10</u>
  <u t="4006480">minutes at least. It is humongous. And I</u>
  <u t="4009760">think we're at literally the other end.</u>
  <u t="4011520">I think the first class is at the back.</u>
  <u t="4014319">Here we go. This is ours. We missed</u>
  <u t="4021960">it. Five and six. No way. What? We've</u>
  <u t="4026480">got our own room. Have we actually?</u>
  <u t="4028559">Yeah. Are you serious? Yeah. There's no</u>
  <u t="4030400">one else in here but</u>
  <u t="4031880">us. Oh, this is amazing. I thought we'd</u>
  <u t="4035200">be sharing. Are we going to have a movie</u>
  <u t="4037039">night? Movie. This is going to be</u>
  <u t="4038720">amazing. Yeah, we're moving. We're</u>
  <u t="4041160">cruising. I have to be honest, so far</u>
  <u t="4043599">this Indian railway experience has been</u>
  <u t="4045359">amazing. Like we booked it on 12 go Asia</u>
  <u t="4047280">and I'll leave a link in the</u>
  <u t="4048160">description. So you so you can book</u>
  <u t="4050000">those your like ticket there. But this</u>
  <u t="4052079">is good, isn't it? It's so easy. But</u>
  <u t="4054400">it's kind of weird. Like there's no</u>
  <u t="4056480">place to like scan your tickets before</u>
  <u t="4058079">you get on the train. Literally anyone</u>
  <u t="4059440">can just get on. But it's also very like</u>
  <u t="4062160">clear what train it is and like what</u>
  <u t="4064640">room you're in. So good job India. Good</u>
  <u t="4068240">job on your trains.</u>
  <u t="4074880">I might have spoken a little bit soon</u>
  <u t="4077920">about the Indian railway experience. It</u>
  <u t="4080000">keeps bumping and we're only traveling</u>
  <u t="4082000">about 10 20 km per hour. So, this could</u>
  <u t="4086480">be a bumpy a bumpy night. It's better</u>
  <u t="4088799">than the night bus. Oh, for sure. I</u>
  <u t="4091520">mean, it can't get as bad as the night</u>
  <u t="4093440">bus cuz the night bus was truly truly</u>
  <u t="4096080">something. We just found these little</u>
  <u t="4097920">packages. There's two of them. And</u>
  <u t="4100640">inside we have a small towel and then</u>
  <u t="4106480">some</u>
  <u t="4107640">bedding. I'm not sure if it's like a</u>
  <u t="4110159">sheet or what, but it's nice that they</u>
  <u t="4113040">provide that. So, it is 20 to 10 now and</u>
  <u t="4115600">we're starting to get ready for bed.</u>
  <u t="4116960">Well, I'm not. I'm actually just going</u>
  <u t="4118799">to be editing editing these videos for</u>
  <u t="4121199">you down below for a few hours. Um,</u>
  <u t="4124000">Amelia is looking pretty ready for bed,</u>
  <u t="4125839">aren't you? Well, I took a dozy like</u>
  <u t="4129839">anti anti-sickness tablet for the car</u>
  <u t="4132159">journey because I get car sick, but it</u>
  <u t="4134239">made me sleepy and now all I could think</u>
  <u t="4136000">about is sleeping. So, I'm in bed. But</u>
  <u t="4138799">I've got myself, it came with two</u>
  <u t="4141040">sheets, the packet. So, I put one like</u>
  <u t="4143440">over the bed and like over the pillow</u>
  <u t="4145839">just cuz it felt nice and clean. And</u>
  <u t="4147920">then I've got this sheet and then I've</u>
  <u t="4149359">got a blanket on top. It is so cold in</u>
  <u t="4151679">here, right? It's freezing and I'm right</u>
  <u t="4153839">under the air vents. I actually feel</u>
  <u t="4155520">like nice and cozy and tucked in now.</u>
  <u t="4157440">You look very cozy. Look like you're</u>
  <u t="4160000">praying for an arctic winter or</u>
  <u t="4161759">something. Yeah. Looks very cool though.</u>
  <u t="4164480">I think we can use these lights. Ooh,</u>
  <u t="4167839">mood lighting. It's a bit blue in here,</u>
  <u t="4170400">isn't it? It's very blue. Like it.</u>
  <u t="4173359">Anyway, that can work for me cuz I've</u>
  <u t="4175679">got my little light down here. And</u>
  <u t="4178319">there's also one two plugs. We got two</u>
  <u t="4181199">plugs sockets here as well, which is</u>
  <u t="4183279">pretty good. We can charge our phones up</u>
  <u t="4185520">ready for the morning. The coolest thing</u>
  <u t="4186960">is in the morning we are doing something</u>
  <u t="4189679">very exciting and I just can't wait.</u>
  <u t="4193359">Good</u>
  <u t="4199800">night. Here we go. Let's leave this</u>
  <u t="4202520">train. This pretty decent train to be</u>
  <u t="4204960">fair.</u>
  <u t="4211679">We have arrived in Kerala. Yay! In the</u>
  <u t="4215120">south of India.</u>
  <u t="4221920">90 minutes in the taxi and we arrived in</u>
  <u t="4223920">Aleppy, famous for the Kerala</u>
  <u t="4225679">backwaters. And for the next 24 hours,</u>
  <u t="4228239">we are staying on a private house boat.</u>
  <u t="4231520">We have to go fourth one. Fourth one.</u>
  <u t="4234719">Fourth one. Carefully. Are you okay?</u>
  <u t="4237600">Yeah. How many boats are we climbing</u>
  <u t="4239040">from? We have closed. We've just got</u>
  <u t="4241600">given a welcome drink. This is fresh</u>
  <u t="4243600">lemon. Here's our captain George.</u>
  <u t="4245840">Captain George. He will be driving us</u>
  <u t="4247440">for the next few days. We are just</u>
  <u t="4249199">unraveling the boat and we will be off</u>
  <u t="4251440">any moment now. It is time to start our</u>
  <u t="4253760">cruise around the Kerala backwaters. I</u>
  <u t="4256400">am so excited for this. Should we have a</u>
  <u t="4259120">look up here? Apparently, this is our</u>
  <u t="4261040">cruising platform where we can watch</u>
  <u t="4263360">from the balcony. How is this? Hey, I've</u>
  <u t="4265920">got a bed. You've got a bed. You can</u>
  <u t="4268000">just fall asleep. I might if I'm not</u>
  <u t="4270239">careful, to be honest. This is just</u>
  <u t="4271920">going to be such a relaxing time just</u>
  <u t="4273760">taking in the views on this beautiful</u>
  <u t="4275440">house boat. Did I mention this is all</u>
  <u t="4278320">private just for me and Amelia. How long</u>
  <u t="4281840">have you been the captain? 16 years. 16</u>
  <u t="4284560">years. Wow. We're in good hands. Very</u>
  <u t="4287920">good hands.</u>
  <u t="4291120">Living the life. You look like you've</u>
  <u t="4292719">got like a cops here and you're having a</u>
  <u t="4294960">party on this boat. Yeah, just me and my</u>
  <u t="4297440">private boat with my drink.</u>
  <u t="4306480">So, I think right now we're in like a</u>
  <u t="4308000">big lagoon area and then we'll go</u>
  <u t="4310400">through maybe some more like smaller</u>
  <u t="4312400">narrow river areas. It looks like no</u>
  <u t="4314640">choppy waters today. No choppy waters. A</u>
  <u t="4316960">nice relaxing cruise.</u>
  <u t="4319520">We will be giving you guys a little tour</u>
  <u t="4321360">around our house boat, but for now, I'm</u>
  <u t="4323920">just going to relax here because I I</u>
  <u t="4326480">just can't move. It's too comfy. We are</u>
  <u t="4328560">about to have lunch whilst we've pulled</u>
  <u t="4330560">in here for the next half an hour or so.</u>
  <u t="4333679">So, we've got some rice, some papadoms,</u>
  <u t="4335920">a vegetable curry, beans, cabbage, fresh</u>
  <u t="4339440">fish that was caught in the lakes, and</u>
  <u t="4342239">what was this one? Like I'm not sure,</u>
  <u t="4344239">but I think it's a little bit sweet or</u>
  <u t="4346000">something.</u>
  <u t="4349199">The fish is still Oh, it's incredible.</u>
  <u t="4352239">The vegetable</u>
  <u t="4356040">pirala backwaters which we are on right</u>
  <u t="4358560">now is made up of five big lakes and</u>
  <u t="4361120">they're all conjoined using man-made</u>
  <u t="4362719">canals and also natural rivers. This</u>
  <u t="4364719">whole area is actually attached to the</u>
  <u t="4366719">sea but very very far away. So it's</u>
  <u t="4369120">mostly all fresh water. I wonder if</u>
  <u t="4371520">there's any crocodiles in here. Like can</u>
  <u t="4373600">we swim in it? I don't think there is. I</u>
  <u t="4376400">would like a swim because it's so hot. I</u>
  <u t="4378880">think we've both just gone really</u>
  <u t="4380480">lethargic and relaxed. Although there is</u>
  <u t="4382719">a nice breeze right now. These rice</u>
  <u t="4385120">fields here are so green. Everywhere</u>
  <u t="4387760">else we've been in India so far has just</u>
  <u t="4389679">been so brown and arid. Obviously right</u>
  <u t="4391760">now we're in the bigger canal ways, but</u>
  <u t="4393520">we want to head down to some of the</u>
  <u t="4395040">smaller rivers. And to do that, we</u>
  <u t="4396960">actually need to get a smaller boat. One</u>
  <u t="4399199">has just pulled up next to us. So I</u>
  <u t="4400719">think we're going to pull over and then</u>
  <u t="4402480">transfer over to that boat. Hello.</u>
  <u t="4404640">Hello. Thank you. Hello. On to the next</u>
  <u t="4407600">boat.</u>
  <u t="4409360">Say goodbye to our boat. Bye boat. See</u>
  <u t="4412000">you later. Hopefully that returns. Yeah,</u>
  <u t="4414239">cuz that's got all our stuff on it and</u>
  <u t="4415840">our bed, which I'm looking forward to.</u>
  <u t="4418159">Oh, maybe we're going down these little</u>
  <u t="4419960">waterway. The Kerala backwaters also has</u>
  <u t="4422560">like this nickname called the Venice of</u>
  <u t="4424640">the East. And I can kind of see why here</u>
  <u t="4426239">because there's houses all the way along</u>
  <u t="4427920">and the only way to get around is by</u>
  <u t="4430000">boat. Hi. Hi. Hello. Welcome to Kerala.</u>
  <u t="4434880">Thank you. Thank you. Genuinely, we've</u>
  <u t="4437199">probably only met a few people here, but</u>
  <u t="4438880">everyone's been so like peaceful in the</u>
  <u t="4442080">way they've just said, "Hello, welcome."</u>
  <u t="4445120">Ooh, coconut boat. Coconut. Maybe we get</u>
  <u t="4448800">a coconut.</u>
  <u t="4450640">Three coconuts, please.</u>
  <u t="4456239">You okay?</u>
  <u t="4459040">Thank you. This is the life, isn't it?</u>
  <u t="4462080">This is the life. Just cruising along</u>
  <u t="4463920">the river, fresh coconut in hand. I feel</u>
  <u t="4467120">like this is the most relaxed I've felt</u>
  <u t="4469040">in India. This is the most relaxed I've</u>
  <u t="4471120">felt ever. It's very offputting.</u>
  <u t="4475120">We're going under a bridge. We got to</u>
  <u t="4476640">get right down. He said duck. He said</u>
  <u t="4478800">duck.</u>
  <u t="4482640">Good luck. Oh, it's not too bad.</u>
  <u t="4498480">That's so funny. So, we just saw a boat</u>
  <u t="4501600">full of school children. So, rather than</u>
  <u t="4504159">having a school bus, they have a school</u>
  <u t="4505520">boat here. That's so cute. School boat.</u>
  <u t="4508560">That is how they just go about their</u>
  <u t="4510159">lives here.</u>
  <u t="4511920">Here's our boat. George is waiting for</u>
  <u t="4513920">us with his big smile. Hello. All</u>
  <u t="4517360">beautiful. Yeah, very amazing.</u>
  <u t="4520960">So peaceful out there. Thank you.</u>
  <u t="4526719">It is tea time. And we also have</u>
  <u t="4529280">ourselves some fried banana. I thought</u>
  <u t="4532159">that was like an Indonesian thing, but</u>
  <u t="4533920">clearly it's a thing in south of India,</u>
  <u t="4536320">too. If you're interested in the house</u>
  <u t="4538239">boat we're staying on, I'll leave a link</u>
  <u t="4539520">in the description. We booked it on Get</u>
  <u t="4540880">Your Guide, and so far it's been very</u>
  <u t="4543679">good, hasn't it? Highly recommend.</u>
  <u t="4552640">Looks like they've put this temporary</u>
  <u t="4554000">like boat floating device to get that</u>
  <u t="4556000">truck across. And now it looks like</u>
  <u t="4557920">they're unraveling it over there and</u>
  <u t="4560960">they're going to hopefully let us</u>
  <u t="4562239">through. This does look like a very</u>
  <u t="4564480">small gap, but I know George will have</u>
  <u t="4566159">it under control. He's the best driver</u>
  <u t="4568239">in all of Kerala. It looks very narrow.</u>
  <u t="4573600">I'm not 100% sure, but maybe we're going</u>
  <u t="4575280">to be watching the sunset here. And</u>
  <u t="4576640">maybe this is actually where we're going</u>
  <u t="4577840">to be camping tonight. Well, I say</u>
  <u t="4579840">camping, obviously. We're going to be</u>
  <u t="4580960">sleeping on this house boat. Is this Do</u>
  <u t="4582800">we sleep here? Yeah. Oh, nice. Now, it</u>
  <u t="4586239">is time to give you a tour around our</u>
  <u t="4588640">house boat. And it's not this one. It's</u>
  <u t="4591280">actually this one. All right. Amelia is</u>
  <u t="4592960">going to jump back on and take you</u>
  <u t="4594880">around. You have to walk the plank to</u>
  <u t="4597280">get back on. Yep. Make sure you don't</u>
  <u t="4599520">fall in. You don't want to do that. And</u>
  <u t="4601679">then through here, this is where our</u>
  <u t="4603360">captain George sits. We've got like a</u>
  <u t="4605760">pirate ship wheel thing. This boat can</u>
  <u t="4608560">only fit two people, but there is so</u>
  <u t="4610640">much seating. We've tried to try as many</u>
  <u t="4612800">chairs as we can, but we really don't</u>
  <u t="4614880">need this many. But it's very nice. We</u>
  <u t="4616480">got these ones. And then over here is</u>
  <u t="4619360">our dining table where we had our lunch.</u>
  <u t="4621679">And there's a pineapple that I've been</u>
  <u t="4623360">eyeing up for later because fruit is so</u>
  <u t="4626320">good here. And if you follow me this</u>
  <u t="4628560">way, down the corridor, we have our</u>
  <u t="4631520">bedroom. And down at the end there is</u>
  <u t="4633520">kind of like their quarters where they</u>
  <u t="4635600">have the kitchen and stuff. And through</u>
  <u t="4637920">here is our bedroom. And it's so much</u>
  <u t="4640400">cooler in here because we actually have</u>
  <u t="4642719">AC even though we're floating. We only</u>
  <u t="4645199">have it on in the evening and when they</u>
  <u t="4646960">plug up to like the hookup that's on the</u>
  <u t="4648960">land at the moment. But it's so nice</u>
  <u t="4650960">because it is so hot at this time of</u>
  <u t="4653120">year. And obviously, ooh, this is the</u>
  <u t="4657120">first time I've laid on this bed and you</u>
  <u t="4659520">kind of sink into it. It feels like</u>
  <u t="4661199">memory foam. Is it not hard? No. Oh,</u>
  <u t="4664960">last night we slept on a train and that</u>
  <u t="4667040">was rock hard. So, this is lovely. A</u>
  <u t="4669920">little extra seat because you can never</u>
  <u t="4672000">have enough I guess you could like lay</u>
  <u t="4674080">that out and probably have a third bed.</u>
  <u t="4675920">Oh, that's probably why. But you can</u>
  <u t="4677520">never have enough places to sit on this</u>
  <u t="4679679">boat. And then in here is the bathroom.</u>
  <u t="4682640">I don't know if it's just me, but it</u>
  <u t="4684000">feels slanted. Probably because we're on</u>
  <u t="4686719">the water. Yeah, maybe there's more</u>
  <u t="4688320">things on the right of the boat than the</u>
  <u t="4689760">left, I think. So, um, which is why this</u>
  <u t="4692400">door keeps falling. But we actually have</u>
  <u t="4695440">a proper shower, a sink, and a toilet</u>
  <u t="4699040">with a bum gun and toilet paper. What</u>
  <u t="4701600">more could you need? When we booked</u>
  <u t="4702960">this, we generally weren't sure if Whoa,</u>
  <u t="4704719">you really do sink into this bed. We</u>
  <u t="4706960">really weren't sure whether we'd have</u>
  <u t="4708320">like a shower. Like we thought it might</u>
  <u t="4710000">just be a bucket or something because</u>
  <u t="4711120">obviously we're on the boat, but it is</u>
  <u t="4712880">so nice to have these luxuries in the</u>
  <u t="4715199">middle of Kerala backwaters.</u>
  <u t="4721100">[Music]</u>
  <u t="4725199">Oh, this room is really</u>
  <u t="4727960">swaying. Is it swaying? I think we're</u>
  <u t="4730800">just at an angle. Also, I'm kind of blue</u>
  <u t="4733679">right now because they've got blue light</u>
  <u t="4735280">and sun.</u>
  <u t="4739600">[Music]</u>
  <u t="4746320">How did you sleep on the wonky bum?</u>
  <u t="4748880">Good. I slept a bit wonky. So, every</u>
  <u t="4751199">time I don't know, every time I woke up</u>
  <u t="4753520">in the night, I was like falling further</u>
  <u t="4755199">into jail when I had to climb back up to</u>
  <u t="4757120">the other side of the bed because it was</u>
  <u t="4759040">really on that much of a slump.</u>
  <u t="4763760">We have finally cut open the pineapple</u>
  <u t="4766719">and I am so happy. Look at that. It</u>
  <u t="4769679">looks incredible. Fresh pineapple.</u>
  <u t="4773760">She's dancing. She's happy. She's got</u>
  <u t="4776480">what she's been eyeing up these last 24</u>
  <u t="4779360">hours. So good. Just as we're finishing</u>
  <u t="4782000">our breakfast, unfortunately, it's time</u>
  <u t="4783760">we have to head back to the harbor. So,</u>
  <u t="4786080">let's enjoy this final journey along the</u>
  <u t="4788800">backwaters.</u>
  <u t="4790710">[Music]</u>
  <u t="4801840">I just saw this lady like doing the</u>
  <u t="4803360">laundry, but the way she was doing it</u>
  <u t="4804960">was like whacking it on this rock. I've</u>
  <u t="4807679">never used that technique before, but</u>
  <u t="4809120">maybe Amelia should try it. I might try</u>
  <u t="4811760">that when I do my laundry next to just</u>
  <u t="4814000">whack it on a rock. Maybe it's a drying</u>
  <u t="4816880">method or something. And unfortunately,</u>
  <u t="4818560">I think it's time that we're going to</u>
  <u t="4819840">leave our house boat, but we still have</u>
  <u t="4822400">lots more to do here in Kerala.</u>
  <u t="4826800">And here we are back on the land. Thank</u>
  <u t="4829120">you, babe. Lovely stay. Thank you so</u>
  <u t="4831440">much.</u>
  <u t="4837679">I don't even believe this. We have just</u>
  <u t="4839280">checked in this ocean front little villa</u>
  <u t="4841440">place for only</u>
  <u t="4843880">$25.20 per night. And it is beautiful.</u>
  <u t="4846960">Like the sea is literally what 40 meters</u>
  <u t="4849920">away. So this is our beautiful little</u>
  <u t="4851600">room. This is just the only room they</u>
  <u t="4853440">have here in this place. But let me show</u>
  <u t="4856159">you the sea. Check out this view. We're</u>
  <u t="4860400">literally 40 m away and we are only</u>
  <u t="4862320">spending $25 a night. Like that just</u>
  <u t="4864640">blows me away. Hello. Anyone home?</u>
  <u t="4868080">Hello. Welcome to my beach house. It's</u>
  <u t="4870800">so nice in here. We've got a big bed.</u>
  <u t="4873679">We've got a seat. And it's actually</u>
  <u t="4875199">really spacious. So, we've been able to</u>
  <u t="4877280">spread out all of our stuff. There's all</u>
  <u t="4879600">my stuff on the floor as usual. Yeah,</u>
  <u t="4882080">Joel likes to spread out his clothes.</u>
  <u t="4884400">And we obviously have a nice bathroom.</u>
  <u t="4887360">It feels like everything's brand new in</u>
  <u t="4889760">this place. And the price is just</u>
  <u t="4891760">insane. I can't believe it. Are you</u>
  <u t="4893760">ready for the beach? Always. Always</u>
  <u t="4897199">ready. Always ready for a swim. The sky</u>
  <u t="4900320">is so blue and it just looks so nice</u>
  <u t="4902159">with the sunbeds, the white sand. You</u>
  <u t="4905040">just feel relaxed. The whole thing is</u>
  <u t="4906960">like where is everyone? There's 1.5</u>
  <u t="4908640">billion people, but there's like no one</u>
  <u t="4910640">here. Like look at the beach. It's so</u>
  <u t="4912360">empty. We're going to try and get one of</u>
  <u t="4914320">these sunbeds. Not sure how much they</u>
  <u t="4915840">are, but let's see if someone comes over</u>
  <u t="4918320">if we kind of perch around them. Should</u>
  <u t="4920080">we go for these ones? Yeah, let's go for</u>
  <u t="4922480">the ones at the end. Look, we've got a</u>
  <u t="4924080">nice towel. Oh, here comes the guy. How</u>
  <u t="4926880">much? 1 hour. 200. Okay. How many times?</u>
  <u t="4931040">Uh, maybe just 1 hour. 200. Okay.</u>
  <u t="4935040">Oh,</u>
  <u t="4939040">this is not bad. What a</u>
  <u t="4941800">life. Got my book here which I haven't</u>
  <u t="4945040">started because we've been so busy in</u>
  <u t="4947199">India and it's been so chaotic that I</u>
  <u t="4948880">haven't wanted to read my book. But now</u>
  <u t="4951040">maybe I can take a time to read because</u>
  <u t="4953199">we were so ill when we were in Goa. We</u>
  <u t="4955199">had no time for like doing exactly this.</u>
  <u t="4958400">But this just feels so good. You're</u>
  <u t="4959920">getting your little suntan, aren't you?</u>
  <u t="4962000">Yeah. Get my little turn on in an India.</u>
  <u t="4966159">I've given up breeding. Giving up? Yeah.</u>
  <u t="4969440">I think it's time we probably go in the</u>
  <u t="4970880">sea. Yeah. Yeah. Well, I'm going in. I'm</u>
  <u t="4974639">getting too sitting here doing nothing.</u>
  <u t="4978639">Ready for a swim. I was ready the moment</u>
  <u t="4981120">we sat on those benches. To be</u>
  <u t="4987080">fair, I can't get over how warm the sea</u>
  <u t="4991120">is here. Like it is so</u>
  <u t="4997159">hot. Pound it.</u>
  <u t="5012159">Sand is so hot. Amelia's running. Help</u>
  <u t="5015280">me. She's literally burning my feet.</u>
  <u t="5017120">Let's try this one. Luave Cafe. probably</u>
  <u t="5020239">traditional French food, I assume.</u>
  <u t="5025360">This is a mango fish curry. We weren't</u>
  <u t="5027520">sure what it was going to be like, but</u>
  <u t="5029120">honestly, it's one of the best things</u>
  <u t="5030719">I've ever eaten. It tastes so good. And</u>
  <u t="5032800">the fish is incredibly fresh. It's</u>
  <u t="5035440">almost like a Thai curry, I'd say, cuz</u>
  <u t="5037760">it's quite light, but the fish is just</u>
  <u t="5039520">melts in your mouth. It's so good.</u>
  <u t="5041040">Right. We're going to have to get this</u>
  <u t="5042000">again. It's just</u>
  <u t="5043239">incredible. Oh.</u>
  <u t="5045500">[Music]</u>
  <u t="5060400">drag our suitcases along the sand. The</u>
  <u t="5062800">people here are just so nice. They like</u>
  <u t="5064560">refuse to let us carry our bags. I feel</u>
  <u t="5067440">so bad cuz it's heavy. So, we are about</u>
  <u t="5069840">to jump in a taxi for about quite a</u>
  <u t="5071920">while and head to Manar up into the</u>
  <u t="5074080">mountains of Kerala. I'm so excited.</u>
  <u t="5081760">I don't know what's going on, but we</u>
  <u t="5083440">just stopped in the road. And I think</u>
  <u t="5086239">they're dressed up as Hindu gods, maybe.</u>
  <u t="5089440">It looks like. Wo. Wow. So cool. I don't</u>
  <u t="5094000">know what it's for, but it's beautiful.</u>
  <u t="5095520">She's smiling. I got a smile at me.</u>
  <u t="5099120">So, I don't know if that was correct,</u>
  <u t="5100320">but it sounded like that sword kind of</u>
  <u t="5102239">thing, the metal was going directly</u>
  <u t="5104480">through the cheek and through the</u>
  <u t="5105840">tongue. But for some reason, they don't</u>
  <u t="5107360">feel pain. Maybe someone knows more</u>
  <u t="5109360">information about this than</u>
  <u t="5111950">[Music]</u>
  <u t="5124360">me. Munar feels a lot busier than we</u>
  <u t="5127360">were expecting. and it's kind of hard to</u>
  <u t="5129120">get around. I think we're going to try</u>
  <u t="5130639">and take the public bus. We've got a</u>
  <u t="5132719">written down instructions here from our</u>
  <u t="5134880">hotel manager. We've just got into the</u>
  <u t="5137440">town center of Manar and I think we've</u>
  <u t="5139920">just found the bus stop just in front of</u>
  <u t="5141520">us here. So, we're going to take the</u>
  <u t="5143520">public bus so we can avoid all these</u>
  <u t="5145280">package tours which seem to be sold here</u>
  <u t="5147440">in Munar.</u>
  <u t="5149520">We are getting the bus to Sinny and then</u>
  <u t="5152000">we stop at Lockheart. Nice. Yeah.</u>
  <u t="5156719">I didn't like it. I think this is our</u>
  <u t="5159040">bus tenny.</u>
  <u t="5164960">This is our second Indian bus and this</u>
  <u t="5167679">is a very local one. So, wish us luck</u>
  <u t="5170400">through the mountain roads. Oh, wow.</u>
  <u t="5172880">Starting to see some greenery outside</u>
  <u t="5174639">the town of</u>
  <u t="5177239">Manar. That was a very relaxing bus ride</u>
  <u t="5181120">here in India. I was not expecting that.</u>
  <u t="5183040">I was expecting him to like crash down</u>
  <u t="5185440">the down the road, but it was actually</u>
  <u t="5188320">just a beautiful ride. But</u>
  <u t="5190480">unfortunately, they didn't stop when we</u>
  <u t="5192800">wanted them to stop. I don't know if</u>
  <u t="5194080">they just have to stop at specific</u>
  <u t="5195440">places, but we now have to walk 15</u>
  <u t="5197520">minutes back in the direction we came.</u>
  <u t="5201520">The thing we found here in Kerala is</u>
  <u t="5203600">that it's a lot of package tour</u>
  <u t="5205440">holidays. So, everyone has like their</u>
  <u t="5207440">individual drivers who take them to the</u>
  <u t="5209040">different points, especially here in</u>
  <u t="5210400">Munar. So, it's a lot harder to do on a</u>
  <u t="5212320">budget, especially if you're</u>
  <u t="5213480">backpacking. But we're proving today</u>
  <u t="5216000">that we think it is possible. Just get</u>
  <u t="5218320">the bus. Just get the bus. As soon as we</u>
  <u t="5220719">got out of the town of Muna, it feels so</u>
  <u t="5222719">much more peaceful again. Lockhart Tea</u>
  <u t="5228760">Factory. There's no one at the ticket</u>
  <u t="5230880">counter and I need to pee. Upon entering</u>
  <u t="5234000">the tea factory, we were invited in for</u>
  <u t="5235920">a tour. The facility was established in</u>
  <u t="5238080">1879 when the British began planting the</u>
  <u t="5240480">crops.</u>
  <u t="5244719">To be honest, we couldn't really hear a</u>
  <u t="5246719">lot of it because she had a mic on, but</u>
  <u t="5248639">she was talking quite quietly and it was</u>
  <u t="5250239">a big group of people. We've been told</u>
  <u t="5252719">that if we walk about a kilometer up the</u>
  <u t="5254800">road that we can actually go into the</u>
  <u t="5256880">rice terraces, rice terraces, tea</u>
  <u t="5259199">plantations, and have a little walk</u>
  <u t="5260960">around. So, we want to hopefully have a</u>
  <u t="5263040">little peaceful walk, but we'll see if</u>
  <u t="5264960">we can get in.</u>
  <u t="5266800">We didn't feel like trying the tea there</u>
  <u t="5268400">because they reuse all the spoons and it</u>
  <u t="5270159">just seemed a bit unhygienic. So, we're</u>
  <u t="5272639">going to have some tea at this little</u>
  <u t="5273840">place. This guy's making us tea right</u>
  <u t="5276080">now. Thank you. Thank you very much.</u>
  <u t="5280560">Uh,</u>
  <u t="5284960">it's so sweet. Cheers. Cheers. Nice cup</u>
  <u t="5289120">of</u>
  <u t="5289340">[Music]</u>
  <u t="5292040">tea. Oh, wow.</u>
  <u t="5295360">This is incredible.</u>
  <u t="5298000">So green. It's like a yellowy green.</u>
  <u t="5300560">It's beautiful. What kind of amazes me</u>
  <u t="5302880">is that it's so dry here at the moment.</u>
  <u t="5305520">Like everywhere is so dry. Especially up</u>
  <u t="5307360">in the mountains. It looks so brown. But</u>
  <u t="5309199">then all these tea plantations are just</u>
  <u t="5311840">so flipping green. I don't know how they</u>
  <u t="5314159">do it. They must water it. So tomorrow,</u>
  <u t="5317760">if all goes to plan, we will try and</u>
  <u t="5320080">climb the mountain up there. Is it that</u>
  <u t="5322880">one? I'm pretty sure it's that one. Oh,</u>
  <u t="5326239">yeah. Looks quite high up, doesn't it?</u>
  <u t="5328080">Yeah. Gonna get a freshly cut pineapple.</u>
  <u t="5334719">So, about 100 years ago, the year ago,</u>
  <u t="5337120">105 years ago, 105 years ago, we got</u>
  <u t="5340000">speaking to this lovely man who</u>
  <u t="5341280">explained Munar used to have a railway,</u>
  <u t="5343120">but a huge flood destroyed the rail and</u>
  <u t="5345120">it was never rebuilt.</u>
  <u t="5347280">No chili. That's perfect. Thank you.</u>
  <u t="5350000">Thank you so much. Look at that. Got</u>
  <u t="5352320">some very fresh pineapple. This looks</u>
  <u t="5355280">amazing to me. And they actually grow it</u>
  <u t="5357360">around here as well. Yeah, it's actually</u>
  <u t="5358960">freshly grown.</u>
  <u t="5362960">Thank you very much.</u>
  <u t="5365760">It's so good. The green of the coconut</u>
  <u t="5367920">matches like the beautiful greens</u>
  <u t="5369600">behind. Feels good supporting the local.</u>
  <u t="5372320">If you ever want a little coconut, make</u>
  <u t="5374480">sure you get one because it's your way</u>
  <u t="5376239">of helping the communities who don't</u>
  <u t="5378480">always get all the money from tourism</u>
  <u t="5380719">like the big travel companies on these</u>
  <u t="5382960">big group tours.</u>
  <u t="5388320">We've come into this tea plantation area</u>
  <u t="5390400">which you can actually walk through and</u>
  <u t="5391840">it was 50 rupees each which isn't too</u>
  <u t="5394320">bad. There seems to be a few people</u>
  <u t="5396719">around getting their photo taken but not</u>
  <u t="5399199">too busy. 5 minutes of walking and I'm</u>
  <u t="5402239">pretty sure we've lost everyone else</u>
  <u t="5404719">who's entered this tea plantation. It is</u>
  <u t="5407760">very peaceful around here. It's lovely.</u>
  <u t="5412010">[Music]</u>
  <u t="5425360">A lot of the tea estates here are very</u>
  <u t="5427679">private and so you can't actually walk</u>
  <u t="5429199">on them, but I definitely recommend</u>
  <u t="5431199">coming to this spot because you can</u>
  <u t="5433040">actually walk around pretty much</u>
  <u t="5434560">wherever you want around this area. You</u>
  <u t="5437199">can actually see up there there are some</u>
  <u t="5438719">people working right now. Apparently,</u>
  <u t="5440880">most of the time they do the picking at</u>
  <u t="5442400">like really early in the morning because</u>
  <u t="5443920">of the heat, but maybe because it's</u>
  <u t="5446280">March, they can do it in the middle of</u>
  <u t="5448239">the day cuz at the moment it's only like</u>
  <u t="5450239">24 25° and it's the middle of the day.</u>
  <u t="5454080">So, not too hot. A lot cooler than when</u>
  <u t="5456320">we were in the Kerala backwaters and the</u>
  <u t="5458159">beach</u>
  <u t="5461000">yesterday. I think this is our bus.</u>
  <u t="5464000">Well, we need any bus to Manar.</u>
  <u t="5469000">[Music]</u>
  <u t="5476719">After our walked through the tea</u>
  <u t="5478000">plantations yesterday, I ended up not</u>
  <u t="5479840">feeling very well. I've still got a</u>
  <u t="5481360">stomach bug from Vinasi, which was a few</u>
  <u t="5483760">weeks ago. But Joel is going to do a</u>
  <u t="5486880">hike now without me because I just can't</u>
  <u t="5489440">leave the toilet. You're going to have a</u>
  <u t="5491040">good time. Yeah, I don't think it's too</u>
  <u t="5493760">far a hike. I think it's maybe like an</u>
  <u t="5495600">hour and a half. Right, then let's start</u>
  <u t="5498159">this adventure. I'm going to try and see</u>
  <u t="5500080">if I can get a tuk tuk, but do some</u>
  <u t="5502880">negotiations and see what price we can</u>
  <u t="5504560">get. Otherwise, I'll just take the bus</u>
  <u t="5506000">cuz it's a lot cheaper. I'm going to</u>
  <u t="5508400">Chukamundi, sir. Chukamundi. Chuker</u>
  <u t="5511360">Mundi. Yeah, the the mountain. Okay. I</u>
  <u t="5513440">want How much? Uh took to 400. 400?</u>
  <u t="5517280">Yeah. So, drop off? Yeah, drop off.</u>
  <u t="5519360">Okay, let's go.</u>
  <u t="5521920">Okay. Thank you.</u>
  <u t="5532080">Okay. Yeah, that is all fancy. Perfect.</u>
  <u t="5535040">Thank you. Here we are. We have arrived</u>
  <u t="5537440">at Chukamundi. Now, this is a less busy</u>
  <u t="5539679">track and a less busy viewpoint than the</u>
  <u t="5542159">famous one which everyone goes to and</u>
  <u t="5544320">it's supposed to be super crowded. So,</u>
  <u t="5546239">here we're going for the more hidden</u>
  <u t="5547920">hidden path.</u>
  <u t="5551199">Yeah. You're from England. Yeah, you</u>
  <u t="5554639">only take card. Yeah, only card. Only</u>
  <u t="5556639">card. Yeah. Wow. Very modern. Yeah.</u>
  <u t="5559520">These for me. Bourbon. Included in the</u>
  <u t="5562639">fee. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, okay. Thank</u>
  <u t="5565520">you. That was quite nice. 600 rupees and</u>
  <u t="5567600">it does include a guide, but I was like,</u>
  <u t="5569679">I don't need one. I'm just going to chat</u>
  <u t="5571679">to you guys and kind of follow the path</u>
  <u t="5573280">up cuz apparently shouldn't be too</u>
  <u t="5575199">difficult. So, hopefully we don't get</u>
  <u t="5577080">lost. Yeah. We also got some bourbon</u>
  <u t="5579520">biscuits, some water included as well.</u>
  <u t="5582000">Not too bad. He just told me to be</u>
  <u t="5584639">careful on some of the rocks cuz they're</u>
  <u t="5588040">slippy. Looks like we've got a few</u>
  <u t="5590239">clouds coming in. Hopefully it doesn't</u>
  <u t="5592199">rain. Woo! Look at</u>
  <u t="5595320">this. You can really start to get a</u>
  <u t="5597520">perspective of the tea plantations down</u>
  <u t="5599280">there. Something about looking down on</u>
  <u t="5601280">them just makes them look even better. I</u>
  <u t="5603920">think it's the patterns or the greenery.</u>
  <u t="5606480">What a beautiful view. This section is</u>
  <u t="5608800">just kind of slab of rock. You're going</u>
  <u t="5610880">to have to go up. Not a bad view,</u>
  <u t="5613480">really. It looks as though we've got</u>
  <u t="5616880">ourselves a rain cloud. It does look</u>
  <u t="5619199">pretty</u>
  <u t="5620600">gray. Oh, wow. There's actually cloud.</u>
  <u t="5624480">Look, there's cloud coming off the</u>
  <u t="5626040">mountain. Not sure we even have a view</u>
  <u t="5628159">at the top. Hello.</u>
  <u t="5632920">England. Where are you from? Kerala.</u>
  <u t="5635760">Carerala. Whereabouts? What? From Anar</u>
  <u t="5639440">or Kochi? Yeah. Kochi. Kochi. Oh, nice.</u>
  <u t="5644000">Sorry. Yes. Hello. The is the view</u>
  <u t="5646960">clear? Yeah. Almost. Almost. Maybe. It's</u>
  <u t="5651840">awesome. Yeah. Good. Awesome. Thank you.</u>
  <u t="5654480">Okay. Have a good</u>
  <u t="5656679">trip. Those lovely people said it was</u>
  <u t="5659120">clear at the top. Maybe that will</u>
  <u t="5661199">change. It's not looking great, though.</u>
  <u t="5663440">Look at</u>
  <u t="5664920">this. Just mist coming over. I'm blowing</u>
  <u t="5668400">because we're at altitude. We'll be over</u>
  <u t="5670400">2,000 meters by the time we get to the</u>
  <u t="5671920">top. If you are doing this, it's quite</u>
  <u t="5674000">easy to navigate. You don't really need</u>
  <u t="5675120">a guide as there's little pink ribbons</u>
  <u t="5678000">and like arrows pointing you in the</u>
  <u t="5680239">right</u>
  <u t="5682600">direction. It's so peaceful. I can</u>
  <u t="5685520">literally hear</u>
  <u t="5687960">nothing. And we're still in</u>
  <u t="5694520">India, right? This is turning into quite</u>
  <u t="5696960">the adventurous walk just through all</u>
  <u t="5700239">the undergrowth. Someone's like</u>
  <u t="5701360">macheteed</u>
  <u t="5703960">through. I think I'm just going to sit</u>
  <u t="5706400">here for 2 minutes, maybe three, and</u>
  <u t="5710239">treat myself to a bourbon</u>
  <u t="5715400">biscuit. That's actually really</u>
  <u t="5718600">good. Borbon biscuit. Doesn't get better</u>
  <u t="5722159">than this. Hello. Hello. Is this the</u>
  <u t="5725280">top?</u>
  <u t="5727679">Top view. That's top view further. That</u>
  <u t="5731280">was a fake little top. You know when you</u>
  <u t="5732800">get to the top and you go, "Oh, it's</u>
  <u t="5734800">another next peak." But I think this is</u>
  <u t="5737120">the genuine top just up here. Finally</u>
  <u t="5740560">nearly made</u>
  <u t="5741960">it. And it's closing in. It's</u>
  <u t="5744840">11:24. So that will be Yeah, pretty much</u>
  <u t="5747600">an hour and a half with tripod shots and</u>
  <u t="5749920">drone shots. So I stopped quite a bit.</u>
  <u t="5753600">There we go. The peak. The last little</u>
  <u t="5757400">scramble up the top. And the</u>
  <u t="5761239">view is nowhere to be seen. Of</u>
  <u t="5768199">course. Oh. Well, Chukamundi, we made</u>
  <u t="5771639">it. You made it.</u>
  <u t="5775120">Yeah. Top. Top. Top. Ttop top top. The</u>
  <u t="5777679">top.</u>
  <u t="5779760">Yeah.</u>
  <u t="5784520">Relax.</u>
  <u t="5787800">Hello. These guys asked me to film them</u>
  <u t="5790239">for a video and I have no idea what was</u>
  <u t="5793040">going on. Okay. Okay. Okay.</u>
  <u t="5801719">Okay. Okay. Nice to meet you. Bye-bye.</u>
  <u t="5804880">What friendly people. I have no idea</u>
  <u t="5807840">what they were saying. They said</u>
  <u t="5809360">something about this video. Maybe they</u>
  <u t="5810880">guessed I was a YouTuber or something,</u>
  <u t="5813440">but friendly, smiley, happy</u>
  <u t="5817719">people. Little bit</u>
  <u t="5820360">slippy. All right, this is the place for</u>
  <u t="5824480">the borbon biscuit</u>
  <u t="5831080">eating. I can't tell you how good these</u>
  <u t="5833600">are right now.</u>
  <u t="5840679">And I am practically back. It's</u>
  <u t="5843040">literally like a one minute walk back</u>
  <u t="5845280">down here to the road. Completed it.</u>
  <u t="5848239">It's now half one. So it's taken about 2</u>
  <u t="5850480">and 1/2 hours. So there you go with some</u>
  <u t="5853040">relative</u>
  <u t="5854119">stops. Back to the little hut. I think</u>
  <u t="5857360">I'll just jump on the bus to go back cuz</u>
  <u t="5859199">it will be so cheap and fast. Probably</u>
  <u t="5861600">faster than a tuk tuk.</u>
  <u t="5864320">No.</u>
  <u t="5867600">One out. We're out.</u>
  <u t="5870210">[Music]</u>
  <u t="5874719">That was so fast grabbing a bus.</u>
  <u t="5876320">Literally 2-minute wait and we'll be</u>
  <u t="5878320">back to Manai in no time because these</u>
  <u t="5880880">buses fly down these hills, don't</u>
  <u t="5884280">they? The following day, we headed back</u>
  <u t="5886560">to Kochi, the main city in the state of</u>
  <u t="5890520">Kerala. Good morning from Kochi. We are</u>
  <u t="5893440">about to take a ferry onto the main fort</u>
  <u t="5896080">area of Kochi to have a little look</u>
  <u t="5897679">around this city. I think this is like a</u>
  <u t="5900000">big kind of inward lake, but the best</u>
  <u t="5902000">way to get to the fort area is by ferry</u>
  <u t="5904080">because if you take the road, apparently</u>
  <u t="5906000">it takes like forever to get around and</u>
  <u t="5907840">you get stuck in traffic and stuff. So,</u>
  <u t="5909920">the ferry is the best way and apparently</u>
  <u t="5911760">it's super cheap. It seems so calm and</u>
  <u t="5914320">quiet down this road. I don't know if</u>
  <u t="5915679">it's just cuz it's like 8:00 in the</u>
  <u t="5917600">morning or if this bit's just a bit</u>
  <u t="5919760">calmer. Fort Coochi this go there to go</u>
  <u t="5922960">there. Okay. Thank you.</u>
  <u t="5928719">So that only costs six rupees each and</u>
  <u t="5931360">they literally only sell the tickets</u>
  <u t="5932639">literally as the boat arrived which</u>
  <u t="5933920">makes no sense but that's India for you.</u>
  <u t="5936480">Here we go onto the ferry.</u>
  <u t="5941420">[Music]</u>
  <u t="5947360">We've just arrived in Port Kochi and</u>
  <u t="5949360">we're going to try and take a touk to</u>
  <u t="5951040">the main area. How much to the basilica?</u>
  <u t="5953920">Basilica? 40 rupees. 40 rupees. Okay,</u>
  <u t="5959600">that's good. We just got an honest</u>
  <u t="5960960">price. 40 rupees to the basilica here in</u>
  <u t="5963600">Fort Coochi. Honest tuk tuk driver. I</u>
  <u t="5966719">like</u>
  <u t="5968360">it. It's okay. Thank you. Here we have</u>
  <u t="5973199">arrived at a basilica at the cathedral</u>
  <u t="5975360">and apparently it's like one of the most</u>
  <u t="5976960">famous churches in all of India. It's</u>
  <u t="5979679">pretty big as well. I forget how like</u>
  <u t="5982560">Christian it is here or Catholic. Like</u>
  <u t="5984480">there's so many different religions in</u>
  <u t="5986080">Kerala, but they all seem to get on well</u>
  <u t="5988239">and just like respect each other, which</u>
  <u t="5990000">is so nice. One thing I forgot to</u>
  <u t="5991840">mention is here in Kerala, it's actually</u>
  <u t="5993520">kind of like a communist party which</u>
  <u t="5995280">kind of runs the state. Um, I'm not</u>
  <u t="5997440">sure. Obviously, it's not super</u>
  <u t="5998880">communist, but there was loads of</u>
  <u t="6000400">communist flags when we were up near</u>
  <u t="6001840">Muna. And yeah, just something I had no</u>
  <u t="6004880">idea about before coming to India. It</u>
  <u t="6006880">definitely feels different here. The</u>
  <u t="6008000">streets feel super clean and it just</u>
  <u t="6009920">looks European. I think it has Dutch,</u>
  <u t="6012159">British, and Portuguese influence. So,</u>
  <u t="6014239">that is probably why. But it's honestly</u>
  <u t="6016719">very pretty. Look at this. Oh, it's such</u>
  <u t="6018719">a beautiful little cafe. Wow. Oh, it's</u>
  <u t="6021760">the tourist information. We've just seen</u>
  <u t="6023840">Santa on the streets of Kochi. Didn't</u>
  <u t="6026159">fancy seeing you there. Didn't expect to</u>
  <u t="6028960">see Santa going to the beach in the</u>
  <u t="6033119">city. Can someone explain this to me?</u>
  <u t="6036080">Stick no bills. I've seen it so many</u>
  <u t="6038360">places and I have no idea what it means,</u>
  <u t="6040719">but it's like all on the walls of</u>
  <u t="6042840">things. It's really odd. I just want to</u>
  <u t="6046320">know what it means. Here we go again.</u>
  <u t="6048320">But it's</u>
  <u t="6051880">everywhere. So, we thought we'd come</u>
  <u t="6053920">down to this beach area. And this is</u>
  <u t="6055840">what the beach looks like. There's a</u>
  <u t="6058800">nice dog, but it's just covered in</u>
  <u t="6061080">rubbish. It is just filthy. Look at</u>
  <u t="6064000">that. It's actually crazy. It's not</u>
  <u t="6066239">quite as good as the other beaches we</u>
  <u t="6067600">went to in India, unfortunately. Go kind</u>
  <u t="6069840">of beat this, isn't it? Yeah. Well, even</u>
  <u t="6071920">the beach in Kerala, but no, not here.</u>
  <u t="6075280">Here we go. This bit of the beach is a</u>
  <u t="6076880">little bit nicer. You can see some sand.</u>
  <u t="6079440">You can see some sand. Yeah. Not just</u>
  <u t="6083480">rubbish. Right then guys, we want to</u>
  <u t="6087199">give kind of our debrief on India. This</u>
  <u t="6089440">has been a long video, the longest video</u>
  <u t="6091440">I think we've ever made as well. And</u>
  <u t="6093119">this is literally our last day in India.</u>
  <u t="6095600">Tomorrow we fly somewhere. Secret. It's</u>
  <u t="6098639">Amelia's one of my favorite one of her</u>
  <u t="6101199">favorite countries. If you know Amelia,</u>
  <u t="6103520">I feel like you've got a good idea. So</u>
  <u t="6105600">go down in the description and put what</u>
  <u t="6107760">where you think we're going. Let's start</u>
  <u t="6109360">off with some of the things which we've</u>
  <u t="6110960">really enjoyed about India. Um, where</u>
  <u t="6113360">was your favorite place in India? Oh,</u>
  <u t="6116040">um, I did enjoy Jaipur. I thought that</u>
  <u t="6119199">was cool. I mean, I I love like the</u>
  <u t="6121440">colors of the city, the architecture was</u>
  <u t="6123520">really cool and the wall and everything.</u>
  <u t="6125360">Taj Mahal. You can't just pass that.</u>
  <u t="6127360">Apart from the rain, but that was just</u>
  <u t="6128639">kind of funny to be honest. Added to the</u>
  <u t="6130560">experience, didn't it? Yeah. I mean,</u>
  <u t="6133040">parts of Goa and Carerala have been fun.</u>
  <u t="6135920">Especially like the beaches in Goa.</u>
  <u t="6137840">Like, I was actually blown away by them.</u>
  <u t="6139920">They're so beautiful. One of our</u>
  <u t="6141920">favorite things about India is the food.</u>
  <u t="6143840">Oh, the food is so good. So flavorful.</u>
  <u t="6146639">And you know, coming from the UK, we</u>
  <u t="6148480">have a lot of curry and stuff, but</u>
  <u t="6149920">coming here, I've been like amazed. The</u>
  <u t="6151840">food's so good. It's so good. And</u>
  <u t="6153679">everything that's vegetarian is just</u>
  <u t="6155119">amazing. But one of our favorites is the</u>
  <u t="6156800">mango fish curry, which we had in</u>
  <u t="6158239">Kerala. That is to die for. It's so</u>
  <u t="6161199">good. I don't think we'll ever find it</u>
  <u t="6163119">again, but I just want it. I just want</u>
  <u t="6165440">some of that in my life. Now let's move</u>
  <u t="6167520">on to some of the more maybe negative</u>
  <u t="6170080">opinions and maybe frustrations which</u>
  <u t="6172320">we've had here in India which maybe we</u>
  <u t="6174080">haven't experienced in some other places</u>
  <u t="6175520">before and I think being here a month</u>
  <u t="6177760">has kind of increased and made these</u>
  <u t="6180159">frustrations and little things which</u>
  <u t="6182320">make an experience worse more. Maybe if</u>
  <u t="6184800">we're only here a week it wouldn't have</u>
  <u t="6186159">mattered quite so much. The first thing</u>
  <u t="6188560">for me is the traffic. Like I I knew</u>
  <u t="6191280">coming to India the traffic would be bad</u>
  <u t="6193040">but the honking is so unnecessary. It</u>
  <u t="6195679">feels like people are just being rude to</u>
  <u t="6197840">each other and it hurts my ears so much.</u>
  <u t="6200080">I do have very sensitive ears and I'm</u>
  <u t="6203360">just very sensitive to that kind of</u>
  <u t="6204639">thing. So I did bring like earplugs most</u>
  <u t="6207280">of the time which I wore in the tuk</u>
  <u t="6208480">tuks. But it is like on another level</u>
  <u t="6211199">even compared to like other places we've</u>
  <u t="6212880">been like Indonesia, Sri Lanka, like</u>
  <u t="6215199">Vietnam. One of the big things I want to</u>
  <u t="6217440">make sure we portray is the difference</u>
  <u t="6218880">between the north and the south is big.</u>
  <u t="6220400">And I didn't realize how big a</u>
  <u t="6222239">difference it was in the south.</u>
  <u t="6225360">A lot of these negative opinions are a</u>
  <u t="6227440">lot calmer. Like it's not as busy.</u>
  <u t="6230400">There's a dolphin. I just saw a dolphin.</u>
  <u t="6232960">Are you kidding? No. Are you serious?</u>
  <u t="6235280">Yes, I just saw a dolphin. What? Wo. Wo.</u>
  <u t="6238480">What's it doing?</u>
  <u t="6240480">There's a dolphin.</u>
  <u t="6242800">Oh, wow. Wa. What's it got? Was that in</u>
  <u t="6244400">its mouth? Yeah, it's got a fish in its</u>
  <u t="6246080">mouth. Oh, that's awesome. One of the</u>
  <u t="6247840">things for us as of like adventure</u>
  <u t="6249520">travelers who want like to go off the</u>
  <u t="6251119">beaten path. One of the things we've</u>
  <u t="6252560">really struggled with especially maybe</u>
  <u t="6254159">more here in Kerala and Munar</u>
  <u t="6256320">particularly is everything seems built</u>
  <u t="6258960">for group tourism. Like it's just like</u>
  <u t="6261119">you go to this spot you can't hike in</u>
  <u t="6262719">the rice in the tea plantations. It</u>
  <u t="6265280">feels like you're just in a big group of</u>
  <u t="6267199">people and you have to do all the</u>
  <u t="6268400">tourist spots. Whereas we want to you</u>
  <u t="6270080">know get off the beaten path. That's why</u>
  <u t="6271440">I did that big hike up to that that</u>
  <u t="6273600">peak. But it feels like you can't really</u>
  <u t="6275600">have an adventure here. Maybe we're in</u>
  <u t="6277440">the wrong part of India and this is more</u>
  <u t="6279360">for group tourism. Maybe we need to go</u>
  <u t="6281280">up into the Himalayas or whatever. But</u>
  <u t="6283280">for me that's been frustrating as</u>
  <u t="6285040">someone who likes to adventure. And the</u>
  <u t="6287199">last thing I wanted to mention was how I</u>
  <u t="6289360">felt as a girl traveling India. Now</u>
  <u t="6291199">obviously I'm with Joel so that</u>
  <u t="6293040">immediately unfortunately makes me a lot</u>
  <u t="6294960">safer and I just feel safer. Um but I</u>
  <u t="6298239">think a lot of places if I were alone I</u>
  <u t="6300880">wouldn't feel super safe. And that's not</u>
  <u t="6302960">to say you can't solo travel here</u>
  <u t="6304400">because a lot of women do do it and they</u>
  <u t="6306239">feel totally fine, which is good for</u>
  <u t="6307760">them. But just me personally, maybe I'm</u>
  <u t="6309920">a more anxious person, but I did not</u>
  <u t="6312400">like the way men look me up and down. I</u>
  <u t="6314480">felt quite just uncomfortable. I felt</u>
  <u t="6316400">like I couldn't lift my head up for fear</u>
  <u t="6318560">of making eye contact and having people</u>
  <u t="6320480">stare me down or take photos of me. And</u>
  <u t="6322639">we did have examples even in Goa where</u>
  <u t="6325679">it people looked like they were trying</u>
  <u t="6327199">to sneakily film Amelia. Yeah.</u>
  <u t="6329760">which is just like so disrespectful cuz</u>
  <u t="6332480">they know that it's not right because</u>
  <u t="6334000">they're doing it in such a sneaky way.</u>
  <u t="6335679">Thank you so much for watching this long</u>
  <u t="6337760">documentary kind of experience of our</u>
  <u t="6340080">whole trip here in India. If you did</u>
  <u t="6341440">enjoy it, please hit the like button,</u>
  <u t="6343360">hit the subscribe, and we can continue</u>
  <u t="6344880">to make videos like this. Oh wow,</u>
  <u t="6347679">there's like I This is a great way to</u>
  <u t="6349199">finish India. It's given it a bit of</u>
  <u t="6350960">more of a high. We like that. Anyway,</u>
  <u t="6353360">we'll see you in the next video. by</u>
  </text>
