<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="lwdmULLA3aU" uploader="Joose the Nomad" channel="Joose the Nomad" likes="798" title="I Tried Living in Uluwatu, Bali as a Digital Nomad" year="2025" month="10" day="25" date="20251025" is_ac="true">
  <u t="160">Everybody comes to Uluatu for a holiday,</u>
  <u t="2960">but what if you would actually live</u>
  <u t="4960">here? I decided to find out what life is</u>
  <u t="7600">really like here in Uluatu. Not just the</u>
  <u t="10240">beaches and sunsets, but a proper</u>
  <u t="13120">routine working here and staying healthy</u>
  <u t="16240">and see if it could actually be the best</u>
  <u t="18800">place to live. In this video, I will</u>
  <u t="20640">show you the full experience, the villa,</u>
  <u t="23119">the food, the gym, the traffic, and the</u>
  <u t="25680">overall vibe and lifestyle here. So, by</u>
  <u t="27920">the end, you will know if Uluatu could</u>
  <u t="29760">be the perfect place to live long-term</u>
  <u t="31760">for you.</u>
  <u t="34510">[Music]</u>
  <u t="37680">I came here to Nyangyang Beach to start</u>
  <u t="40079">the video because I thought it would be</u>
  <u t="41520">less touristy, less busy, more raw</u>
  <u t="43840">nature vibe. And I was right. It's so</u>
  <u t="46239">beautiful. Well, look at this. There's</u>
  <u t="48399">no one around. Basically, the whole</u>
  <u t="50480">beach. I just seen some people who</u>
  <u t="52320">clearly live in Uluatu having a morning</u>
  <u t="54239">walk, some local fishermen, but</u>
  <u t="56719">otherwise there's like no one here. I</u>
  <u t="58719">walked all the way to the other side of</u>
  <u t="60320">the beach. Is so nice for morning walks</u>
  <u t="62480">actually. Not so good for running</u>
  <u t="63680">because the sand is quite uh like you</u>
  <u t="65760">will sink into it a little bit, but uh</u>
  <u t="68240">yeah, such a beautiful morning walk</u>
  <u t="69920">spot. There's also someone walking from</u>
  <u t="72000">the hill. You can drive a scooter, but</u>
  <u t="73680">going it by food uh to have a more</u>
  <u t="76560">exercise. So yeah, it's it's beautiful.</u>
  <u t="79280">This is life. It's not even my favorite</u>
  <u t="81360">beach, but it's still super nice. I</u>
  <u t="83600">could get used to this, to be honest.</u>
  <u t="85520">And there's even a couple of guys</u>
  <u t="86799">surfing. It looks incredible. It's not</u>
  <u t="89520">crowded at all. What a beautiful spot to</u>
  <u t="92240">surf.</u>
  <u t="96700">[Music]</u>
  <u t="105390">[Music]</u>
  <u t="108720">I'm back in my villa. I got a proper one</u>
  <u t="111600">this time to see how it is to actually</u>
  <u t="114159">live here if you would have a nice home</u>
  <u t="116640">like this. And yeah, this villa is so</u>
  <u t="119439">beautiful. I will talk more about it</u>
  <u t="121920">later. I'm just going to get some work</u>
  <u t="123759">done. And look how fast the Wi-Fi is.</u>
  <u t="125680">So, it's really not a problem in if</u>
  <u t="127680">you're in a nice place like this.</u>
  <u t="131490">[Music]</u>
  <u t="135840">In Jangu, my daily routine is to order a</u>
  <u t="139040">double protein smoothie. Every single</u>
  <u t="141760">day I do that and it's really important</u>
  <u t="144080">part of my routine kind of. So I wanted</u>
  <u t="146239">to see if I can do the same well here in</u>
  <u t="148959">Uluatu because in Jangu the protein</u>
  <u t="151120">places are just so good. But I found</u>
  <u t="153360">this place that was pretty like it looks</u>
  <u t="156000">really good. The it's huge. It's</u>
  <u t="157840">actually very heavy in my hand. Like</u>
  <u t="159599">that's a lot of protein smoothie. So,</u>
  <u t="161200">let's see how it is. Wow, that's</u>
  <u t="163840">actually insane. That's really good.</u>
  <u t="166239">Just peanut butter, banana, oat with</u>
  <u t="169120">double vanilla protein. And yeah, it was</u>
  <u t="171680">uh on discount, so it's actually pretty</u>
  <u t="173680">affordable. I came to check out the</u>
  <u t="175200">nicest gym they have in Olawat. And it's</u>
  <u t="177120">insane how busy it is here. Like so many</u>
  <u t="179680">people in the cafe. The gym also looks</u>
  <u t="182159">pretty busy. Not that crazy. There's</u>
  <u t="185840">some glass going on.</u>
  <u t="188400">Looks nice though. But what I came to</u>
  <u t="190480">check out and try today is the new</u>
  <u t="192319">recovery area they recently built. It</u>
  <u t="194959">looks so nice here. There are three</u>
  <u t="196640">different temperatures, ice beds, huge</u>
  <u t="200000">jacuzzi, and of course the big pool area</u>
  <u t="203760">which is really beautiful and vibe. It's</u>
  <u t="206480">a proper olato vibe and a big sauna. So</u>
  <u t="211040">that's super super nice. There's even a</u>
  <u t="213280">little jungle gym and yeah, it's a bit</u>
  <u t="216640">pricey. It's $265</u>
  <u t="220000">for the gym and classes and the recovery</u>
  <u t="223120">area for a month. But yeah, it's just</u>
  <u t="226799">super super nice. But I would say it's</u>
  <u t="228560">probably a little more busy here than in</u>
  <u t="230959">the other gyms. There's actually so many</u>
  <u t="233280">options nowadays for gyms and recover in</u>
  <u t="235280">Uluatu. So there's lot to choose from.</u>
  <u t="238000">So it's really nice. Actually, I didn't</u>
  <u t="239760">realize that even in the sauna like</u>
  <u t="241840">there's literally no one. It's just the</u>
  <u t="244000">sun beds that are super busy</u>
  <u t="247040">and the ice beds also not too busy</u>
  <u t="252000">and really nice. Wow. Oh, feels good. I</u>
  <u t="255599">feel like I would be pretty happy to</u>
  <u t="257440">come here like monthly if I live in</u>
  <u t="260560">Ulata. Like it's a really nice place.</u>
  <u t="263040">But it's good to have other options</u>
  <u t="264560">also. Also if this gets too busy can</u>
  <u t="266720">change.</u>
  <u t="270610">[Music]</u>
  <u t="275600">I came to watch sunset in the closest</u>
  <u t="278240">cliff spot from my villa which is this</u>
  <u t="280560">famous cliff with incredible views.</u>
  <u t="283360">Well, I guess this is the money shot</u>
  <u t="287120">nowadays from this cliff. Wow.</u>
  <u t="291360">So beautiful in Luat. So nice to come</u>
  <u t="293840">watch sunset by the cliffs and beaches</u>
  <u t="295919">every day. It's pretty crazy to have</u>
  <u t="298400">this spot like just for myself here.</u>
  <u t="300400">Like what a beautiful place. And by the</u>
  <u t="302720">way, if you're living the normal</u>
  <u t="304240">lifestyle, you know that having a</u>
  <u t="305919">reliable mobile data is nonnegotiable.</u>
  <u t="308720">And what I use for that is today's</u>
  <u t="310400">sponsor, Olafly. And Olafly now has two</u>
  <u t="313039">options. First, their classic eims.</u>
  <u t="316240">Perfect for short trips or holidays. You</u>
  <u t="318800">can set them up before your flight and</u>
  <u t="320720">be online the moment you land in over</u>
  <u t="323120">200 destinations. But if you travel</u>
  <u t="326000">full-time like I do, their new Olafly</u>
  <u t="328960">plans are a total game changer. It's one</u>
  <u t="332080">eim that keeps you connected in 160</u>
  <u t="335360">countries with monthly global data plan</u>
  <u t="338320">and even a regular phone number you can</u>
  <u t="341440">use for verifications and banking. No</u>
  <u t="344320">matter where you're traveling or living,</u>
  <u t="346560">it's the maximum convenience. No SIM</u>
  <u t="348960">card swaps, no roaming fees, no more</u>
  <u t="351360">running out of data. You just choose</u>
  <u t="353199">your plan once, install it, and you are</u>
  <u t="355759">covered everywhere. Honestly, it's the</u>
  <u t="358080">kind of freedom every nomad dreams of. I</u>
  <u t="361039">will leave a link in the description.</u>
  <u t="362960">Trust me, it just makes travel so much</u>
  <u t="364800">more easy. And with my discount code,</u>
  <u t="366800">Yos the Nomad, you will get 5% off and</u>
  <u t="369360">help support my channel.</u>
  <u t="373290">[Music]</u>
  <u t="389919">I came to the cashew tree for lunch.</u>
  <u t="392800">Such a nice vibe and the food also looks</u>
  <u t="395759">very good and healthy. Salad bowl and a</u>
  <u t="399120">protein smoothie. Actually, I have found</u>
  <u t="401199">so many restaurants that have healthy</u>
  <u t="403199">food with enough protein and really</u>
  <u t="405039">good. So, it's really not a problem</u>
  <u t="406800">anymore in Uluatu when it comes to food.</u>
  <u t="409600">It's really good here also. So, yeah,</u>
  <u t="411280">for long-term living, it's all good</u>
  <u t="413280">nowadays. Happy to see. I came to</u>
  <u t="416639">Dreamland Beach to check out the surf as</u>
  <u t="419039">it's definitely something that I would</u>
  <u t="421039">want to do actively if I live in Oluatu</u>
  <u t="423520">as it's famous for one of the best surf</u>
  <u t="425599">scenes in the world. And what I can see</u>
  <u t="427919">that here and all the beginner friendly</u>
  <u t="430000">spots like Padang Padang, it's quite uh</u>
  <u t="432960">crowded. So yeah, it's can be really</u>
  <u t="435840">good place to surf, but there's a lot of</u>
  <u t="437840">people surfing. But you can find those</u>
  <u t="439919">more remote spots if you are more</u>
  <u t="442479">advanced, I guess. But for me, not being</u>
  <u t="445039">so good at surfing, not sure if it would</u>
  <u t="447199">be the best here with the crowds. And I</u>
  <u t="450160">asked the price to rent a board here. So</u>
  <u t="452560">it's $6 per hour. So basically double</u>
  <u t="455520">the price that it would be in Changu.</u>
  <u t="457599">All right. So nice always off the beach</u>
  <u t="459759">or from anywhere. Coming back home to</u>
  <u t="462160">this just so peaceful. My little own</u>
  <u t="466080">oasis here. Oh, this is life. It's</u>
  <u t="469680">really theatu lifestyle. You can by the</u>
  <u t="472319">way stay in this villa also yourself.</u>
  <u t="474639">It's owned by one guy in my community</u>
  <u t="477280">and uh yeah, it's pretty like tactical</u>
  <u t="479280">location. So it's basically next to the</u>
  <u t="481280">golf course road that goes to Dreamland</u>
  <u t="483280">Beach and Bingin. So it's really easy to</u>
  <u t="485280">drive down there. And there's also many</u>
  <u t="487440">restaurants and gym in this area very</u>
  <u t="489680">close by and also you closer to my</u>
  <u t="492000">favorite beach, Melasti Beach, which I</u>
  <u t="494400">will go later. And speaking of my</u>
  <u t="496560">community, the Nomad Tribe, check it out</u>
  <u t="498319">if you come to Bali or Southeast Asia</u>
  <u t="500000">when I live the digital nomad lifestyle</u>
  <u t="501919">or just for a few months. You will get</u>
  <u t="503919">all the resources you would ever need to</u>
  <u t="505840">have the best possible time and avoid</u>
  <u t="507520">any mistakes and meet like-minded people</u>
  <u t="509919">in the community group chat and meetups.</u>
  <u t="512719">So, hope to see you inside. Link in the</u>
  <u t="515120">description for this one also.</u>
  <u t="520270">[Music]</u>
  <u t="529360">I came to Island Paddle for a tournament</u>
  <u t="532320">because it seems like the open games are</u>
  <u t="534320">still a little bit hard to find here,</u>
  <u t="536000">but the tournaments are happening every</u>
  <u t="537680">week and they always fully booked. So,</u>
  <u t="539519">seem like there's good community for the</u>
  <u t="541680">tournaments at least. So, let's see how</u>
  <u t="543040">it goes.</u>
  <u t="545650">[Music]</u>
  <u t="556959">Oh my god, it's so hot. But the</u>
  <u t="558959">tournament was pretty nice. Like, it's</u>
  <u t="561120">crazy that they play this time of the</u>
  <u t="562720">day, midday, so it's extremely hot, a</u>
  <u t="564959">little bit uncomfortable, but it's</u>
  <u t="566320">pretty nice community vibe. Like,</u>
  <u t="567760">there's a lot of people that clearly</u>
  <u t="569040">play here often. And uh yeah, I would</u>
  <u t="571440">say if I live in Ulwatu, it's still hard</u>
  <u t="573440">to find open games, but coming here like</u>
  <u t="576240">every week for the tournaments could be</u>
  <u t="578080">pretty nice. So not as nice as in</u>
  <u t="579519">Changangu, but it's okay. It's nice.</u>
  <u t="581839">Uluatu is not known for working, but I</u>
  <u t="584560">came to check this one co-working cafe.</u>
  <u t="587440">Looks pretty nice here. I got some snack</u>
  <u t="589680">and coconut. The Wi-Fi is not the</u>
  <u t="591360">fastest ever, but uh it's decent. And</u>
  <u t="593839">this sofa is really comfy. No need to</u>
  <u t="597120">pay anything extra. just order food and</u>
  <u t="599440">you can enjoy this nice view and get</u>
  <u t="601839">some work done. There's also this room</u>
  <u t="604399">with AC that is like a proper more</u>
  <u t="607279">proper co-working but it has 250,000</u>
  <u t="610160">minimum spend so you need to spend more</u>
  <u t="613279">to stay full day here. And yeah, about</u>
  <u t="615279">the traffic, it's pretty bad in Olvatu</u>
  <u t="617839">nowadays. Like all the main roads,</u>
  <u t="620079">there's insane amount of traffic. It's</u>
  <u t="622320">really not relaxing to drive the main</u>
  <u t="624720">roads, but at the same time, there's a</u>
  <u t="626800">lot of the smaller roads that are very</u>
  <u t="628880">peaceful, still not much going on. So,</u>
  <u t="631600">it really depends where you go, but I</u>
  <u t="633440">would say that in most cases, you're</u>
  <u t="635600">going to be quite often in these roads</u>
  <u t="638160">that get stuck a little bit and with</u>
  <u t="640240">like crazy traffic jams every day. So,</u>
  <u t="642720">it's definitely not optimal. Like for a</u>
  <u t="644720">short stay, it's pretty manageable. It's</u>
  <u t="647279">okay. But to live here long term, it's a</u>
  <u t="649600">little bit similar than Ubud is that</u>
  <u t="652160">it's a bit too much. Like I'm not sure</u>
  <u t="654160">if I would actually enjoy so much. But I</u>
  <u t="656640">guess if I would live here, I would just</u>
  <u t="658079">avoid certain places and certain ways so</u>
  <u t="660399">I don't need to go to the traffic too</u>
  <u t="662320">often.</u>
  <u t="670640">I came to Melasti Beach for swim and</u>
  <u t="673279">chill. Is so beautiful. Look at this</u>
  <u t="675519">water. It's really feels like Maldives</u>
  <u t="677680">almost. It's incredible. There's no</u>
  <u t="680160">doubts about Olivato being so nice for</u>
  <u t="682640">the beaches. Like it's just so beautiful</u>
  <u t="684959">and relaxing. Like that's something that</u>
  <u t="687040">I definitely miss when I live in</u>
  <u t="688240">Changoo. What a beautiful place to call</u>
  <u t="690560">home. I mean would be a beautiful place</u>
  <u t="692480">to call home. Like the sunsets, the</u>
  <u t="694880">vibe, the beaches are just incredible. I</u>
  <u t="697760">kind of feel bad about not living here</u>
  <u t="699760">when I come here. But at the same time,</u>
  <u t="702000">somehow it just never really feels like</u>
  <u t="704320">home still as Changu does for me. But at</u>
  <u t="707360">the same time, maybe I should give it a</u>
  <u t="708880">chance. But I also noticed that being</u>
  <u t="711120">here alone, it's not really it's kind of</u>
  <u t="713839">feels weird. But being here with a</u>
  <u t="715600">girlfriend, it feels good. So I feel</u>
  <u t="717920">like it's it's a little bit this kind of</u>
  <u t="719279">place that is not as good alone as Jungu</u>
  <u t="721920">is. But if you have a partner, it can be</u>
  <u t="724880">pretty perfect to spend a lot of time</u>
  <u t="726560">here, go to the beach, chilling and</u>
  <u t="728720">going to the restaurants, like it can be</u>
  <u t="730079">really nice. But at the same time, the</u>
  <u t="731360">traffic is a bit too much. So I'm not</u>
  <u t="733920">sure if uh longterm I would feel good</u>
  <u t="736399">here. But yeah, staying in a perfect</u>
  <u t="738320">area, it could be nice. So yeah, I would</u>
  <u t="740959">say if you enjoy this kind of place, I</u>
  <u t="742560">would give it a try. But I'm not fully</u>
  <u t="744880">convinced. So yeah, hope you got value</u>
  <u t="746560">out of the video. Please like the video,</u>
  <u t="748079">subscribe, and hope to see you inside</u>
  <u t="749920">the Nomad tribe.</u>
  </text>
