<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="6PIbdDDtugk" uploader="Drew Binsky" channel="Drew Binsky" likes="72700" title="I Visited Every Country in Europe. Here's My Rankings" year="2025" month="01" day="11" is_ac="true">
  <u t="80">I've been to all 50 countries in Europe.</u>
  <u t="2399">Bonjour.</u>
  <u t="3360">Most of them three or more times. And in</u>
  <u t="5200">this [music] video, I'm going to rank</u>
  <u t="6480">each nation starting from my favorite.</u>
  <u t="8240">It is the best city in Europe, one of</u>
  <u t="10000">the best in the world, all the [music]</u>
  <u t="11280">way down to my least favorite.</u>
  <u t="14240">And yes, right now I am in the beautiful</u>
  <u t="16160">city of Kev, Ukraine.</u>
  <u t="20880">The criteria for my ranking is overall</u>
  <u t="22960">friendliness, cheese, [laughter]</u>
  <u t="25359">affordability, cuisine.</u>
  <u t="27840">That is very good. nightife, natural</u>
  <u t="30320">beauty, historical wonders.</u>
  <u t="32880">I was not expecting to see this in</u>
  <u t="34239">Sicily.</u>
  <u t="35040">And most importantly, the ability to not</u>
  <u t="37280">have to go out of your way to have an</u>
  <u t="39040">authentic cultural experience.</u>
  <u t="41440">Unbelievable.</u>
  <u t="42480">All right, let's begin with my favorite</u>
  <u t="44000">country in Europe and where I am</u>
  <u t="45440">reporting to you right now to kick off</u>
  <u t="47280">this video. Let's go. Number one, the</u>
  <u t="50239">Czech Republic. Here I am in Oldtown</u>
  <u t="52320">Square in Prague. It's literally my</u>
  <u t="53920">favorite place on the planet. Look at</u>
  <u t="55920">this. It is so beautiful. medieval</u>
  <u t="57920">architecture, incredible churches, the</u>
  <u t="60239">oldest functioning astronomical clock</u>
  <u t="62000">tower in the world, and it just doesn't</u>
  <u t="63600">get any better than this. Even though</u>
  <u t="64879">I've spent a year of my life in this</u>
  <u t="66159">city, I still have the goosebumps every</u>
  <u t="67920">time I'm here. I love it. Yes, this is</u>
  <u t="71040">the very city that I studied abroad in</u>
  <u t="72799">in 2012 when I was a junior in college.</u>
  <u t="75280">But I've just fallen in love with this</u>
  <u t="76720">city and this country. And let me tell</u>
  <u t="78479">you why.</u>
  <u t="80240">There are many cities around this</u>
  <u t="81600">country that are stunningly beautiful,</u>
  <u t="83040">like Pilzen where they brew the famous</u>
  <u t="84560">Pilzen Urkel beer. [music]</u>
  <u t="87200">There's a city in the north called</u>
  <u t="88320">Liberets which is near the mountains by</u>
  <u t="90159">the Poland border. There's a town called</u>
  <u t="91680">Olamotz in the east and Boro also in the</u>
  <u t="94640">east. And all the little Czech towns and</u>
  <u t="96479">villages are so cool because you're in</u>
  <u t="98479">Bohemia. That's actually what the region</u>
  <u t="100159">is called like the song Bohemian Rap</u>
  <u t="101600">City by Queen.</u>
  <u t="103920">But what's really cool about Czech</u>
  <u t="105119">Republic is you're right on the border</u>
  <u t="106880">of Eastern Europe and Western Europe. So</u>
  <u t="108720">you still get that Eastern European</u>
  <u t="110159">flare and culture. and and my parents'</u>
  <u t="112079">generation, the ones who grew up in the</u>
  <u t="113600">70s and 80s and even '90s, they grew up</u>
  <u t="116000">in communism. So, they have a different</u>
  <u t="117439">outlook on life and it wasn't so happy</u>
  <u t="119200">golucky for them growing up. And that's</u>
  <u t="120880">maybe why you think Czech people don't</u>
  <u t="122240">smile so much at you on the streets and</u>
  <u t="123680">you think that they're rude, but</u>
  <u t="124640">actually they're super friendly and</u>
  <u t="125840">super cool once you get to know them.</u>
  <u t="127520">Thanks, man.</u>
  <u t="128239">Yeah,</u>
  <u t="128479">but the way the society runs in Prague,</u>
  <u t="130479">it's super safe, super clean. You have</u>
  <u t="132319">that like Western European comfort a</u>
  <u t="134319">little bit here, but they still have the</u>
  <u t="135599">grunge of Eastern Europe. So, there's</u>
  <u t="137280">graffiti on the walls, some of the</u>
  <u t="138480">street signs are ripped off. It's way,</u>
  <u t="140400">way, way more affordable than Western</u>
  <u t="142080">Europe. For example, if you drive an</u>
  <u t="143440">hour from here, you're already in</u>
  <u t="144480">Dresden, Germany. And it's way cheaper</u>
  <u t="146239">in the Czech Republic than it is in</u>
  <u t="147520">Western Europe. Beer is still cheaper</u>
  <u t="149280">than water here, even though it has</u>
  <u t="150800">gotten quite pricey over the last few</u>
  <u t="152239">years. So, we just sat down at a</u>
  <u t="153519">restaurant here in Prague, and I ordered</u>
  <u t="154959">this beer, which was $2 for a half</u>
  <u t="157440">liter, and this tiny little water in a</u>
  <u t="160080">glass can is $3. The Czech Republic is</u>
  <u t="162879">loaded with beautiful parks, cafes,</u>
  <u t="165200">restaurants, bars. It's amazing for</u>
  <u t="167440">night life. This is soing awesome.</u>
  <u t="170160">It's familyfriendly. All the streets</u>
  <u t="172000">have this cobblestone. Like everywhere</u>
  <u t="173680">in Prague, it's so cool. They're like</u>
  <u t="175440">pieces of sand all over [music] the</u>
  <u t="177120">city. It is extremely safe here, way</u>
  <u t="179360">more than other cities I've been to in</u>
  <u t="180879">Europe. Even pickpocketing is pretty</u>
  <u t="182640">minimal if you would ask me compared to</u>
  <u t="184400">a place like Paris or Barcelona. What I</u>
  <u t="186239">love about Prague is, yes, it's the</u>
  <u t="187519">biggest city in Czech Republic, but it's</u>
  <u t="188959">still pretty small. There's about a</u>
  <u t="190239">million people here, but you feel like</u>
  <u t="191519">you can know all the different areas.</u>
  <u t="193360">It's not overwhelmingly big and you can</u>
  <u t="195120">really walk around the entire old town</u>
  <u t="196720">in just a couple hours. It's really</u>
  <u t="198319">great if you like exploring by foot.</u>
  <u t="200959">Public [music] transportation around</u>
  <u t="202080">this country is immaculate. It's</u>
  <u t="203840">perfect. Always on time, easy to get</u>
  <u t="205760">around. You do not need to have a car if</u>
  <u t="207360">you live here. If I'm being honest, the</u>
  <u t="208879">one thing that's not amazing about the</u>
  <u t="210239">Czech Republic is the food. It's very</u>
  <u t="211840">heavy. Meats and potatoes and sauerkraut</u>
  <u t="213840">and cabbage. But you know what? You</u>
  <u t="215280">don't come here for the food. You come</u>
  <u t="216319">here for the fun, the beautiful</u>
  <u t="217599">atmosphere, [music] the relaxing vibes</u>
  <u t="219360">of Czech Republic. Look, they're setting</u>
  <u t="221040">up a farmers market in front of me.</u>
  <u t="222720">There's going to be a beautiful little</u>
  <u t="223840">farmers market here. Also, my favorite</u>
  <u t="225680">small town in Europe is in southern</u>
  <u t="227280">Chuck. It's called Chess Crumblab.</u>
  <u t="229907">[music]</u>
  <u t="231120">It is beautiful and charming just like</u>
  <u t="232879">it is here over the Volultaba River with</u>
  <u t="235680">Charles Bridge in the distance. [music]</u>
  <u t="237439">One of the oldest bridges in the world.</u>
  <u t="239519">I just freaking love this country</u>
  <u t="242720">so much. Number two, Serbia.</u>
  <u t="248720">I cannot tell you how good it feels to</u>
  <u t="250159">be back in Serbia after 7 years. Also</u>
  <u t="252560">staying in Eastern Europe, but this time</u>
  <u t="254400">the capital of the Balkan region and</u>
  <u t="256720">former Yugoslavia. Serbia is amazing.</u>
  <u t="259120">I've been there maybe seven or eight</u>
  <u t="260479">times. I love the people. They're so</u>
  <u t="262400">outgoing in nature. They're friendly.</u>
  <u t="264960">They're kind of like Spanish people.</u>
  <u t="266160">They're very loud, very nationalistic,</u>
  <u t="268400">very proud of their country. Belgrade is</u>
  <u t="270320">amazing. It is not very touristy. So you</u>
  <u t="272560">have these beautiful medieval castles</u>
  <u t="274320">and charming old town streets,</u>
  <u t="276160">restaurants, bars. A lot of them you</u>
  <u t="278000">have to yourself cuz there's just not</u>
  <u t="279360">many tourists there. There's a beautiful</u>
  <u t="280800">fortress in Belgrade right where the</u>
  <u t="282240">Danube and the Sava rivers meet each</u>
  <u t="284000">other. But even getting out of Belgrade,</u>
  <u t="285440">there's a town in the south called Nish,</u>
  <u t="286960">which is beautiful. Up in the north,</u>
  <u t="288400">there's a town called Samborg, which is</u>
  <u t="290000">actually where Yokic is from, the best</u>
  <u t="292160">basketball player in the world right</u>
  <u t="293440">now.</u>
  <u t="295840">There's a town in the north called</u>
  <u t="296960">Novisad where they have an amazing music</u>
  <u t="298639">festival in the summer called Exit,</u>
  <u t="300240">which I really want to go to. And all</u>
  <u t="301840">around Serbia, you really just can feel</u>
  <u t="303520">the energy, the pulse of this country,</u>
  <u t="305440">unlike others. It's so amazing if you</u>
  <u t="307199">want to go out, make some friends, hang</u>
  <u t="309280">out. I mean, play sports. Also,</u>
  <u t="311520">NovakJokovic, the best tennis player of</u>
  <u t="313280">all time, is from Serbia.</u>
  <u t="315713">[cheering]</u>
  <u t="317919">So, it's a tiny country, but has such a</u>
  <u t="319680">big impact on global sports, which is</u>
  <u t="321280">cool if you like sports like I do. The</u>
  <u t="322880">food in Serbia is pretty good. If you</u>
  <u t="324479">like meat, they have chapichi, which are</u>
  <u t="326160">these like thick meatball things. They</u>
  <u t="327840">drink this yogurt thing that they also</u>
  <u t="329440">drink in Turkey. Yeah, if they drink it</u>
  <u t="330800">in Turkey, it's called like Arian there,</u>
  <u t="332960">but the one in Serbia is more it's</u>
  <u t="334800">saltier and it definitely is an acquired</u>
  <u t="336479">taste. I always like to tell people that</u>
  <u t="338080">Belgrade feels like a mini Berlin with</u>
  <u t="339840">graffiti on the walls, which ironically</u>
  <u t="341680">I'm walking on this street in Prague</u>
  <u t="343039">right now feels like the [music] East</u>
  <u t="344160">Gallery wall where the Berlin wall is</u>
  <u t="345680">covered in murals, but Belgrade has that</u>
  <u t="347440">vibe. The music scene is amazing. It's</u>
  <u t="349360">hipster. I don't know how else to</u>
  <u t="350560">explain it. You just got to go there</u>
  <u t="351680">yourself and feel it. It feels different</u>
  <u t="353520">than the rest of Europe. And not to</u>
  <u t="355039">mention, there's beautiful Orthodox</u>
  <u t="356400">churches everywhere. It's really a dream</u>
  <u t="358080">and I always want to be back in Serbia</u>
  <u t="359840">and I hope that if there's one takeaway</u>
  <u t="361199">from this video, it would be to visit</u>
  <u t="363199">Eastern Europe in general. It's just</u>
  <u t="365600">fantastic.</u>
  <u t="367360">Number three, Spain. [music] Spain is</u>
  <u t="370400">just as good as it gets and I freaking</u>
  <u t="373199">love this country. Let me tell you why.</u>
  <u t="376629">[music]</u>
  <u t="377280">So, of course, the big cities of</u>
  <u t="378720">Barcelona, Madrid are amazing and you</u>
  <u t="380880">have to visit and they should not be</u>
  <u t="382400">overlooked.</u>
  <u t="383039">It doesn't get any better than this. But</u>
  <u t="384880">the beauty of Spain for me is the south</u>
  <u t="386880">and the north. The southern region is</u>
  <u t="388160">called Andalucia which is so beautiful.</u>
  <u t="390000">You have towns like Granada, Sevilla,</u>
  <u t="391759">Cordoba. We are out here in southern</u>
  <u t="393600">Spain and and there's this amazing</u>
  <u t="395520">little town of these cave homes carved</u>
  <u t="397520">into the mountain. You guys have to see</u>
  <u t="399199">this to believe it. One of the most</u>
  <u t="400560">beautiful mosques I've ever seen is in</u>
  <u t="401919">Cordoba. There's this Moish architecture</u>
  <u t="403680">which comes from Morocco. It's really</u>
  <u t="405120">close to the border of Morocco. You just</u>
  <u t="406560">have to cross the small sea right there.</u>
  <u t="408160">Right now I'm inside the Mskita in</u>
  <u t="410000">Cordobo, Spain, which is one of the</u>
  <u t="412160">coolest buildings I've ever seen in this</u>
  <u t="413759">architecture.</u>
  <u t="415600">The people of Spain, just like Serbians,</u>
  <u t="417239">[music] are really loud and friendly and</u>
  <u t="419520">passionate.</u>
  <u t="422800">Seriously, like if you've ever met a</u>
  <u t="424080">Spaniard before, you know that they're</u>
  <u t="425520">Spanish because they're just loud. They</u>
  <u t="427280">want to be heard.</u>
  <u t="431680">What is this?</u>
  <u t="432560">As I pass under Charles Bridge, we learn</u>
  <u t="435199">more.</u>
  <u t="436800">I actually took my dad on our annual</u>
  <u t="438560">father-son [music] golf trip in</u>
  <u t="439759">Andalucia. We had an absolute blast.</u>
  <u t="443520">That's right in the hole, Papa. Very</u>
  <u t="445840">good player. Thank you.</u>
  <u t="447199">It is literally every golfer's dream to</u>
  <u t="449360">be down there. The road trip was</u>
  <u t="450800">beautiful. The food was incredible, the</u>
  <u t="452720">kimone, the seafood, the tapas.</u>
  <u t="455840">But then [music] you got to go up north</u>
  <u t="457680">to the northern coast of Spain where I</u>
  <u t="459120">just took my team on an incredible road</u>
  <u t="461120">trip, which I do [music] every year to</u>
  <u t="462479">celebrate the growth of the channel. We</u>
  <u t="464240">started in San Sebastian in the Bass</u>
  <u t="466000">County which was absolutely stunning.</u>
  <u t="467759">The wine, the food, the ocean, the</u>
  <u t="470080">seafood, the views, the cliffs and then</u>
  <u t="471759">we drove the whole northern coast of</u>
  <u t="473840">Spain all the way to a town in Galithia</u>
  <u t="476240">which is on the northwestern part of the</u>
  <u t="477599">country to a town called Vgo which I</u>
  <u t="479759">don't think I've ever seen a more</u>
  <u t="480879">charming town in my life than Vgo,</u>
  <u t="483280">Spain. Put that town on your radar. It</u>
  <u t="485039">will not disappoint. Man, on this walk</u>
  <u t="486800">right now around Prague, I'm finding all</u>
  <u t="488240">these little squares and little</u>
  <u t="490080">alleyways that I've never found before.</u>
  <u t="491255">[music] It's pretty awesome.</u>
  <u t="493440">But Spain has it all. It's a huge</u>
  <u t="495199">country. It has great vibes all around.</u>
  <u t="497120">If you like ocean, you got it. If you</u>
  <u t="498800">want mountains, you got it. If you like</u>
  <u t="500400">to drink, go out and party, you like</u>
  <u t="502160">sangria, the fruity wine that comes from</u>
  <u t="504000">there. It's all in Spain and it's all</u>
  <u t="506479">fantastical.</u>
  <u t="508639">Why am I doing this with my hands all of</u>
  <u t="510160">a sudden? Number four, Iceland.</u>
  <u t="516800">[laughter]</u>
  <u t="517919">We got it. If you like natural beauty,</u>
  <u t="520159">then Iceland is your spot. Wow. Wow.</u>
  <u t="524320">Pretty cool. Holy. It's one of the most</u>
  <u t="526720">beautiful countries in the world and the</u>
  <u t="528240">best to road trip it. Starting in</u>
  <u t="529760">Reikavic, the capital city, which is</u>
  <u t="531519">quite nice. There are a lot of beautiful</u>
  <u t="533120">things to do in that city and is</u>
  <u t="534720">definitely worth visiting like the</u>
  <u t="536160">beautiful church, which looks quite</u>
  <u t="537600">different than this one. The Blue</u>
  <u t="538800">Lagoon, which is a place that you just</u>
  <u t="540480">detox for a while. It's a geothermal hot</u>
  <u t="542800">bath, which there's a lot of those</u>
  <u t="544160">around Iceland. The Blue Lagoon is just</u>
  <u t="545760">the most famous one. Oh, man. That</u>
  <u t="547920">burning sensation of being so hot.</u>
  <u t="550080">Fantastic. Oh, this is so cool, man.</u>
  <u t="552800">Oh my god. I feel like we're going to be</u>
  <u t="554320">here for at least 30 minutes. One of the</u>
  <u t="556320">coolest experiences of my life was</u>
  <u t="557680">playing golf at the northernmost golf</u>
  <u t="559200">course in the world where it was light</u>
  <u t="560480">outside 24/7 in the summer. Let's go.</u>
  <u t="564160">But I recommend you to get in a car and</u>
  <u t="565760">drive south to a little town called Vic</u>
  <u t="567760">on the southern coast. There's black</u>
  <u t="569279">sanded beaches down there. It's a</u>
  <u t="570880">totally different vibe and feel than</u>
  <u t="572320">Reikovic. It's way more remote. And just</u>
  <u t="574399">driving through Iceland, you will see</u>
  <u t="576399">volcanoes. You will see beautiful</u>
  <u t="578480">rolling hills. You will see ocean cliffs</u>
  <u t="580800">and views like you've never seen. And</u>
  <u t="582880">the people of Iceland, there's only a</u>
  <u t="584320">couple hundred thousand of them in the</u>
  <u t="585519">whole country, and they're super</u>
  <u t="586880">friendly.</u>
  <u t="588399">There's a town in the west called Sticky</u>
  <u t="590160">Salmood, which actually went on a cruise</u>
  <u t="592160">ship that continued onwards to</u>
  <u t="593440">Greenland. It was a small town of about</u>
  <u t="595040">3,000 people, but really, really nice.</u>
  <u t="596959">The best salmon I've ever tasted in my</u>
  <u t="598640">life was there. And it's just the</u>
  <u t="599839">epitome of what I love and enjoy about</u>
  <u t="602160">Scandinavia is all found in Iceland. The</u>
  <u t="604720">language is crazy. You won't understand</u>
  <u t="606320">anything. The signs are all like FQZ75.</u>
  <u t="609360">It might as well be in Arabic or in</u>
  <u t="610800">Mandarin because I really have a hard</u>
  <u t="612399">time grasping it.</u>
  <u t="614959">Aenorphinino</u>
  <u t="617360">Gra.</u>
  <u t="619839">But everybody speaks English, so there's</u>
  <u t="621279">no communication barrier. You'll</u>
  <u t="622720">absolutely love your time in Iceland. If</u>
  <u t="625120">you want to try a bizarre food, you</u>
  <u t="626320">could try fermented shark. I thought it</u>
  <u t="627680">was the worst thing I've ever tried in</u>
  <u t="628959">my life. And I've tried almost</u>
  <u t="630160">everything. The smell, I can taste it on</u>
  <u t="632160">my lips right now. Disgusting. But other</u>
  <u t="634720">than that, the cuisine is lovely.</u>
  <u t="636240">Everything is delicate and safe and</u>
  <u t="638160">clean and fancy. It's a very fancy</u>
  <u t="640560">country. It's very eco-friendly to</u>
  <u t="642320">travel there. It's like a minimalistic</u>
  <u t="643839">lifestyle. You just jump in a car, go</u>
  <u t="645600">around. You don't have to bring all</u>
  <u t="646800">these things with you. You just want to</u>
  <u t="647920">go enjoy nature. There are beautiful</u>
  <u t="649519">fjords to check out, which are these</u>
  <u t="651120">like tall little mountain things that</u>
  <u t="652560">come straight out of the water and you</u>
  <u t="653680">can only find them in a [music] few</u>
  <u t="654640">countries in the world. And of course,</u>
  <u t="656079">the Northern Lights. It's one of the</u>
  <u t="657519">best places on Earth to see the Northern</u>
  <u t="659120">Lights. I've [music] sadly failed every</u>
  <u t="660640">time. If you've seen the Northern</u>
  <u t="661600">Lights, let me know in the comments down</u>
  <u t="662720">below where because I'm dying to see</u>
  <u t="664480">them.</u>
  <u t="667440">Number five, Ukraine. Yes, that's right.</u>
  <u t="670399">I'm in Ukraine right now. I'm in the</u>
  <u t="672240">beautiful city of Lviv. I've actually</u>
  <u t="673600">been here for the last week traveling</u>
  <u t="675120">around the country documenting my</u>
  <u t="676640">experiences. I was actually here 9 years</u>
  <u t="678160">ago.</u>
  <u t="678560">How cool is that building? So,</u>
  <u t="680079">this is my second time in Ukraine. It's</u>
  <u t="681519">very different these days with the war,</u>
  <u t="682720">which I'll get into in a little bit. But</u>
  <u t="684880">all I got to say is this country is so</u>
  <u t="687120">charming and beautiful and different</u>
  <u t="688800">than the rest of Europe. First of all,</u>
  <u t="690560">it's massive. It's actually the largest</u>
  <u t="692640">country in Europe. It's like 1500</u>
  <u t="694880">kilometers or something from west to</u>
  <u t="696399">east. The people are amazing. They're</u>
  <u t="698240">beautiful. Things are charming here.</u>
  <u t="699839">Like where I am in the west, it feels</u>
  <u t="701200">like Prague. The city is super unique</u>
  <u t="703040">and beautiful. Cobblestone streets. You</u>
  <u t="704800">have the buildings with the blocks like</u>
  <u t="706720">this. There's little artsy things on</u>
  <u t="708880">every corner. It's just like a freaking</u>
  <u t="710240">dream here. Of course, you have the</u>
  <u t="711760">capital city of Kev, which has the most</u>
  <u t="713600">majestic temples and churches and</u>
  <u t="715519">gardens. Behind me is St. Sophia's</u>
  <u t="717519">Cathedral. It's the oldest cathedral in</u>
  <u t="719200">Eastern Europe. Such a special moment</u>
  <u t="721279">and surreal to actually be back here.</u>
  <u t="723128">[music] Absolutely incredible. It's like</u>
  <u t="725040">a freaking hidden gem there. It's more</u>
  <u t="726560">beautiful than almost any other city</u>
  <u t="728160">I've been to in Eastern Europe. It's</u>
  <u t="729519">also really, really affordable in</u>
  <u t="730959">Ukraine. Not even because of the war. It</u>
  <u t="732720">was actually really cheap when I was</u>
  <u t="733920">here 9 years ago. So, things are</u>
  <u t="735360">extremely affordable if you want to go</u>
  <u t="736720">out to get food, if you want to go out</u>
  <u t="737839">to the bar. And speaking of bars,</u>
  <u t="739200">there's a lot of night life here. And I</u>
  <u t="740480">want to say even during the war,</u>
  <u t="744959">it's been amazing to meet people and see</u>
  <u t="746560">how resilient they are. They've all had</u>
  <u t="748160">friends and family that have lost</u>
  <u t="749328">[music] limbs or lost their lives. But</u>
  <u t="751200">people are really trying to move on and</u>
  <u t="752639">we're really just trying to get past</u>
  <u t="753760">these dark days. And it's been really</u>
  <u t="755200">humbling and emotional to travel Ukraine</u>
  <u t="757120">during these days. And I will have a</u>
  <u t="758560">video coming out soon on my YouTube</u>
  <u t="759839">channel which is going to share real</u>
  <u t="761360">stories as I experience them in real</u>
  <u t="763200">time here in Ukraine. Because it's so</u>
  <u t="764959">big, there's so many different areas to</u>
  <u t="766399">explore. We have the Carpathian</u>
  <u t="767920">Mountains, which is actually the same</u>
  <u t="769200">mountain range that goes through</u>
  <u t="770240">Transennylvania and Romania. And it's</u>
  <u t="771760">also the mountains that originally split</u>
  <u t="773600">Europe and Asia. So there's a lot of</u>
  <u t="775040">culture there. There's a lot of</u>
  <u t="776000">beautiful villages. There's a lot of</u>
  <u t="777200">cool castles which [music] actually we</u>
  <u t="778560">just went to one earlier today. We're</u>
  <u t="780079">here at autumn. So you can see the trees</u>
  <u t="781920">have just started to change colors.</u>
  <u t="783839">Pretty awesome. It's a beautiful little</u>
  <u t="786000">village here. You have people selling</u>
  <u t="788160">homemade stuff that they cook literally</u>
  <u t="789600">in their backyard. And it's a very very</u>
  <u t="791519">nice life out here. The point is all</u>
  <u t="793120">around Ukraine is beautiful nature. You</u>
  <u t="794560">have hikes. You have outdoor sports.</u>
  <u t="796240">Even beaches on the Black Sea. I've</u>
  <u t="797760">never been to Odessa, but I've heard</u>
  <u t="799120">amazing things about it. You have</u>
  <u t="800320">Chernobyl, which is a place I've always</u>
  <u t="801839">wanted to go. Maybe I'll make it there</u>
  <u t="803200">someday. And yeah, Ukraine. It's a very,</u>
  <u t="805040">very special country. I've actually</u>
  <u t="806320">raved about it since I came 9 years ago</u>
  <u t="808800">and uh it's it's really a pleasure to be</u>
  <u t="810959">here again and and I wish and hope the</u>
  <u t="813120">best for the [music] future of this</u>
  <u t="814000">country and I really really hope that</u>
  <u t="815279">the war will stop because war is just</u>
  <u t="816880">absolutely terrible for anyone. Number</u>
  <u t="820480">six is Portugal. I'm going to sit down</u>
  <u t="824240">and enjoy this one because Portugal is</u>
  <u t="826240">that special. So of course you have</u>
  <u t="827920">Lisbon, the capital city. I've been</u>
  <u t="829360">there maybe six, seven times. I love the</u>
  <u t="831120">look of these Portuguese churches, man.</u>
  <u t="833760">So beautiful. I recently went to Porto.</u>
  <u t="835839">I took my team [music] on a road trip</u>
  <u t="837199">through northern Spain and down the</u>
  <u t="838480">northern coast of Portugal. And I really</u>
  <u t="840000">love Porto. It's like a [music] mini</u>
  <u t="841279">version of Lisbon. It's quaint, a lot of</u>
  <u t="843360">beautiful cafes and churches and it's</u>
  <u t="845120">just like a hip, cool vibe. I actually</u>
  <u t="846880">like Porto maybe [music] even more than</u>
  <u t="848240">Lisbon. But the best part about Portugal</u>
  <u t="849760">is the Algarve which is a region in the</u>
  <u t="851440">southern coast. Took my dad on a golf</u>
  <u t="853040">trip down there.</u>
  <u t="854480">Nice shot.</u>
  <u t="856560">Yes,</u>
  <u t="857120">Eagle. We had [music] an absolute blast.</u>
  <u t="860079">Talk about some of the best seafood I've</u>
  <u t="861839">ever had. Great sorts of wines, sangria.</u>
  <u t="865760">A</u>
  <u t="870240">really really friendly and warm people.</u>
  <u t="872800">What's up, bro?</u>
  <u t="873519">You're one of my favorites,</u>
  <u t="874639">dude.</u>
  <u t="876800">In my opinion, they're similar to the</u>
  <u t="878240">Spaniards and and in that they're just</u>
  <u t="880160">very loving and you know, they give you</u>
  <u t="882240">kisses on the cheeks when you see them</u>
  <u t="883519">and they're just they're just cool</u>
  <u t="884720">people to be around. Like you want to be</u>
  <u t="886160">around Portuguese people.</u>
  <u t="887440">Be [music] happy. Be happy. The country</u>
  <u t="890240">is pretty small, but they've obviously</u>
  <u t="891680">had a lot of influence on [music] the</u>
  <u t="893120">world through colonization. Brazil, Cape</u>
  <u t="895440">Ver, Guinea, Basau, Mosmbique, Angola, a</u>
  <u t="898079">lot of countries around the world speak</u>
  <u t="899600">Portuguese. [music] Whether or not</u>
  <u t="900639">that's a good thing or a bad thing,</u>
  <u t="902160">that's not the point. The point is</u>
  <u t="903440">Portugal is awesome. They have [music]</u>
  <u t="904639">great fruits. In fact, here's a random</u>
  <u t="906320">fact. In Iran, the word for orange is</u>
  <u t="908720">Portugal [music] because the Portuguese</u>
  <u t="910560">were able to bring really fresh oranges</u>
  <u t="912800">by boat to Iran way back in the day. I</u>
  <u t="915040">think that's a really cool [music]</u>
  <u t="915839">little fun fact. If you have a sweet</u>
  <u t="917199">tooth, you have to try pastel denata,</u>
  <u t="919040">which is a famous pastry that's made in</u>
  <u t="920959">Lisbon, the famous shop where the</u>
  <u t="923040">original one comes from. There's always</u>
  <u t="924320">a long line out the door, so you could</u>
  <u t="925920">probably try [music] it. So, if you want</u>
  <u t="926880">to wait, you can wait for it or you</u>
  <u t="928000">could try it somewhere else. It's also</u>
  <u t="929199">really affordable in Portugal. That's</u>
  <u t="930480">why a lot of young [music] entrepreneurs</u>
  <u t="932160">and tech and crypto people are moving to</u>
  <u t="933839">Portugal because of the lifestyle, and</u>
  <u t="935600">it's very cheap. Yes, it uses the euro,</u>
  <u t="937440">but it's way more affordable than almost</u>
  <u t="939279">any other country [music] in Western</u>
  <u t="940959">Europe. And I will always love Portugal</u>
  <u t="942880">and I can't wait to go back.</u>
  <u t="945839">Number seven is Romania. Just a nearby</u>
  <u t="948560">country to Ukraine. As I just mentioned,</u>
  <u t="950160">the Carpathian Mountains actually go</u>
  <u t="951680">down into Romania into a beautiful</u>
  <u t="953440">region called Transylvania [music] where</u>
  <u t="954720">you can find Dracula's castle.</u>
  <u t="956240">I am Dracula.</u>
  <u t="958079">A bunch of other really [music]</u>
  <u t="959040">historical monuments. There's a town</u>
  <u t="960480">called Barashov, which is my favorite in</u>
  <u t="962320">Romania. It's tucked away in the</u>
  <u t="963519">mountains. And there's another really,</u>
  <u t="964720">really beautiful village called Saya,</u>
  <u t="966136">[music] which you have to visit. Of</u>
  <u t="967440">course, Bucharest is the bustling</u>
  <u t="969040">capital city, and there's a lot of</u>
  <u t="970480">really cool development there. It's</u>
  <u t="972031">[music] really beautiful. There's hardly</u>
  <u t="973600">any tourists. Also very affordable.</u>
  <u t="975199">There's a lot of IT and tech out there.</u>
  <u t="976800">A lot of people are super smart coders.</u>
  <u t="978480">And so there's a lot of coffee shops, a</u>
  <u t="979839">lot of really, really fast Wi-Fi, which</u>
  <u t="981440">is amazing. And in general, Romania has</u>
  <u t="983199">a lot of rich folklore and medieval</u>
  <u t="985680">castles, dark stories. A lot of people</u>
  <u t="988399">who are interested in dark tourism like</u>
  <u t="990000">to go there for its haunted [music]</u>
  <u t="991199">vibes and medieval structures on every</u>
  <u t="993360">corner. I got lost in the villages there</u>
  <u t="994959">and I found a lot of really unique</u>
  <u t="996480">traditions. There was a beer drinking</u>
  <u t="997920">festival that I went to. There was a</u>
  <u t="999360">cheesemaking exhibition. People dressed</u>
  <u t="1001279">up in Romanian outfits, singing [music]</u>
  <u t="1003040">songs. It's very festive. I just really</u>
  <u t="1005440">love Eastern Europe. I think that'll be</u>
  <u t="1007199">one of the main themes in this video. I</u>
  <u t="1008959">just feel very alive there and I feel</u>
  <u t="1011199">very uplifted to see how people are</u>
  <u t="1013279">living their lives out here in Eastern</u>
  <u t="1014639">Europe. Food, I would say, is decent.</u>
  <u t="1016399">It's not really the best food I've ever</u>
  <u t="1017600">had in in Eastern Europe. Although</u>
  <u t="1019360">Ukraine and Romania, if we mix them</u>
  <u t="1021360">together, between borchup and between</u>
  <u t="1023199">dumplings and between a lot of the</u>
  <u t="1024559">cottage cheeses and jams that you can</u>
  <u t="1026319">find, honey, raspberries, grapes, it's</u>
  <u t="1028559">pretty good in that regard. But there's</u>
  <u t="1029919">not really like internationally [music]</u>
  <u t="1031120">known dishes that you have to try from</u>
  <u t="1032480">one of these two countries. Next on my</u>
  <u t="1034079">list in Romania is the western town</u>
  <u t="1035679">called Timasura, which is just like a</u>
  <u t="1037280">two-hour drive from Belgrade. I want to</u>
  <u t="1039120">check that place out. And yeah, I don't</u>
  <u t="1041039">know, guys. If you come in the autumn</u>
  <u t="1042480">season, which is where it is now, you</u>
  <u t="1043839">can see the trees changing colors and</u>
  <u t="1045199">all the tourists are gone from these</u>
  <u t="1046799">places. And in general, they're just not</u>
  <u t="1048240">touristy at all. And they're super</u>
  <u t="1049760">enjoyable. [music] I could not rave more</u>
  <u t="1051360">about Romania, Ukraine, and all these</u>
  <u t="1053600">countries in this part of Europe. Number</u>
  <u t="1056080">eight, the Netherlands. [music] We are</u>
  <u t="1057919">going to move out west to one of the</u>
  <u t="1059760">most beautiful countries in Europe. a</u>
  <u t="1061760">small country, a country that has a</u>
  <u t="1063200">massive impact on the world. [music] Did</u>
  <u t="1064880">you know that New York was at one point</u>
  <u t="1066320">or almost called New Amsterdam because</u>
  <u t="1068160">of Dutch colonizers? Indonesia,</u>
  <u t="1070080">Madagascar, these countries have a lot</u>
  <u t="1071760">of Dutch [music] words and Dutch</u>
  <u t="1073120">influence, which you would never</u>
  <u t="1074160">believe. The reason Madagascar is</u>
  <u t="1075760">because a lot of the people that live</u>
  <u t="1076960">there are actually ethnically from</u>
  <u t="1078480">Indonesia, which have traces back to</u>
  <u t="1080080">Netherlands. I love the open-mindedness</u>
  <u t="1081760">of Dutch people. They're tall. They're</u>
  <u t="1083520">really accepting to the world. Doesn't</u>
  <u t="1085440">matter if you're black, white, Asian,</u>
  <u t="1086657">[music] wherever you come from. Surinom.</u>
  <u t="1088480">That's actually a a Dutch-speaking</u>
  <u t="1090000">country in South America. [laughter]</u>
  <u t="1092320">People are really cool. They're genuine.</u>
  <u t="1093679">They like to go out and have fun. They</u>
  <u t="1094880">love parties. A lot of my favorite DJs</u>
  <u t="1096480">in [music] the world, come from the</u>
  <u t="1097600">Netherlands or Holland. I want to make</u>
  <u t="1099760">something straight, guys. Holland is</u>
  <u t="1101067">[music] just part of the Netherlands.</u>
  <u t="1102640">It's like there's North Holland and</u>
  <u t="1103679">South Holland. Obviously, Amsterdam and</u>
  <u t="1105200">Roderdam, the two biggest cities are in</u>
  <u t="1106640">the region of Holland, but the country</u>
  <u t="1108160">of Netherlands is much bigger than</u>
  <u t="1109679">Holland. You have amazing cities like</u>
  <u t="1111280">Kinderdikeke, which is where the</u>
  <u t="1112320">windmills are. It's a UNESCO site. You</u>
  <u t="1114559">have beautiful canals of Utre, which is</u>
  <u t="1116640">actually the most bike friendly place in</u>
  <u t="1118240">the world. And it's my favorite city in</u>
  <u t="1121120">the Netherlands because it's like</u>
  <u t="1122320">Amsterdam, but way smaller. It's a</u>
  <u t="1123840">university town, so there's a lot of</u>
  <u t="1125039">students, and it's just really amazing</u>
  <u t="1126640">with no tourists, [music] and it's way</u>
  <u t="1127760">cheaper as well. In the south and east,</u>
  <u t="1129520">you have Brada and Eintoven, which I've</u>
  <u t="1131120">been many, many times. They're just</u>
  <u t="1132400">chill spots. I mean, all these towns in</u>
  <u t="1134240">Netherlands have beautiful canals</u>
  <u t="1135840">running through them, just charming</u>
  <u t="1137360">people. [music] I just can't tell you</u>
  <u t="1138720">how enjoyable it is to walk around the</u>
  <u t="1140000">Netherlands. Like, I'm just smiling the</u>
  <u t="1141360">whole time for no reason. Like any day</u>
  <u t="1143039">that you're walking around Amsterdam is</u>
  <u t="1144640">just a great day. The layout of the city</u>
  <u t="1146320">is awesome. And whenever I tell people I</u>
  <u t="1147760">love the Netherlands, they're like, "Oh,</u>
  <u t="1148799">you like smoking weed." Actually, I</u>
  <u t="1149919">don't like smoking weed. And I like the</u>
  <u t="1151440">Netherlands for every reason apart from</u>
  <u t="1153679">smoking weed. Who cares if there's weed</u>
  <u t="1155433">[music] shops? It's just the</u>
  <u t="1156320">open-mindedness of the people. There's a</u>
  <u t="1157840">great beer selection.</u>
  <u t="1159039">Serious.</u>
  <u t="1160240">The food is actually pretty good.</u>
  <u t="1162080">That looks amazing. Wow.</u>
  <u t="1164080">They have great sandwiches. They [music]</u>
  <u t="1165280">have great hot dogs, wieners.</u>
  <u t="1166960">Really tasty.</u>
  <u t="1168799">There's actually a um a fast food place</u>
  <u t="1170480">called Fibo FBO. [music]</u>
  <u t="1171760">You basically put a euro into this like</u>
  <u t="1173679">microwave box looking compartment or</u>
  <u t="1176559">thing. It's like you're getting a soda</u>
  <u t="1177919">from a vending [music] machine, but you</u>
  <u t="1179039">turn the knob and then like a burger</u>
  <u t="1180480">comes out. So, I thought that's pretty</u>
  <u t="1181840">fun. And they also have a food called</u>
  <u t="1183440">bitter ball, which is like this fried</u>
  <u t="1185200">ball of I don't even know what's in it,</u>
  <u t="1186640">but it's delicious. Great cheeses in the</u>
  <u t="1188320">Netherlands. [music] Everyone speaks</u>
  <u t="1189440">perfect English. And the biking culture,</u>
  <u t="1191280">man, if the cities are like built for</u>
  <u t="1193039">biking [music] and where I currently</u>
  <u t="1194160">live in Prague, it's like a terrible</u>
  <u t="1195600">city for biking cuz there's no bike</u>
  <u t="1196960">lanes. in Amsterdam. Literally, every</u>
  <u t="1198559">city, [music] every single part of the</u>
  <u t="1199840">Netherlands is extremely bike friendly.</u>
  <u t="1201600">So, if you do go there, get on a bike</u>
  <u t="1203039">and explore. [music] You'll love it.</u>
  <u t="1206160">I just arrived safely in country number</u>
  <u t="1208080">nine, Austria. I'm in beautiful</u>
  <u t="1210480">Salsburg, and as you can see, it is an</u>
  <u t="1212400">absolute gem of a day. Look at this</u>
  <u t="1214720">perfect weather. Absolutely stunning out</u>
  <u t="1216720">here. What's significant about Austria</u>
  <u t="1218400">for me is that I'm Austrian. My</u>
  <u t="1220400">grandfather was born here, so I have a</u>
  <u t="1222080">really cool connection to this country.</u>
  <u t="1223600">It's so beautiful and it's really</u>
  <u t="1225360">underrated and overlooked by its</u>
  <u t="1227280">neighbors, Germany, Italy, and</u>
  <u t="1228960">Switzerland because there's so much</u>
  <u t="1230480">here. You have the Alps, you have</u>
  <u t="1231840">amazing food, hello schnitle,</u>
  <u t="1234799">it's the birthplace of classical music,</u>
  <u t="1237039">Beethoven, Mozart, and it's very</u>
  <u t="1239280">charming.</u>
  <u t="1240880">And believe it or not, people here</u>
  <u t="1242159">actually speak German. There's no such</u>
  <u t="1244000">thing as Austrian language. The language</u>
  <u t="1245440">is called German.</u>
  <u t="1249520">But it's really cool. It's really</u>
  <u t="1250640">beautiful. And as you can see, like you</u>
  <u t="1252400">can't really go wrong with coming to</u>
  <u t="1253840">Austria. It's one of those places that</u>
  <u t="1255280">you visit and you realize, okay, this</u>
  <u t="1257120">place is special. I'm going to come back</u>
  <u t="1258480">and back again. Some of my favorite</u>
  <u t="1259919">spots in Austria are Insbrook, which is</u>
  <u t="1262320">the gateway to the Austrian Alps. Really</u>
  <u t="1264320">good skiing up there. Beautiful town</u>
  <u t="1265840">high up in the mountains. [music] Of</u>
  <u t="1267120">course, you have the big bustling city</u>
  <u t="1268480">of Vienna with tons of palaces, great</u>
  <u t="1270400">food. Welcome to Vienna. We are at the</u>
  <u t="1272400">Stefan Plats. Right there is the</u>
  <u t="1274159">Stefan's Dome, the main church of</u>
  <u t="1276240">Austria. The city is thriving. There's</u>
  <u t="1278559">another small town called Lind, which is</u>
  <u t="1280159">stunning. And actually there's a place</u>
  <u t="1281600">on the border of Likenstein called</u>
  <u t="1283200">Felkerk. I went there in 2015. It was</u>
  <u t="1286159">really special. And of course you can't</u>
  <u t="1288000">beat Salsburg. Austria wins. That leads</u>
  <u t="1290640">me into country number 10, Italy.</u>
  <u t="1293120">Bonjouro.</u>
  <u t="1297039">Italy. There's so much to say about</u>
  <u t="1299280">Italy. A lot of people would tell me to</u>
  <u t="1300960">put this as number one. And Italy is so</u>
  <u t="1303039">great. It's hard to keep out of the top</u>
  <u t="1304320">10. We're here in the Plaza de Compo,</u>
  <u t="1305919">which the biggest square here in town.</u>
  <u t="1307360">It's just so charming. It's such an</u>
  <u t="1309039">amazing place. Oh wow.</u>
  <u t="1311760">Venice is probably my least favorite</u>
  <u t="1313200">place in Italy. It's a human zoo.</u>
  <u t="1314720">There's too much going on there. Too</u>
  <u t="1316400">many people walking around. You know, my</u>
  <u t="1318320">first time going to Italy, I went to</u>
  <u t="1319679">Florence and Rome. So, those two cities</u>
  <u t="1321360">really have a special place in my heart.</u>
  <u t="1323039">I've been back many, many times since</u>
  <u t="1324425">[music] then. You know, they say that</u>
  <u t="1325679">Rome is a walking museum, and it really</u>
  <u t="1327919">is. You just walk around and you see</u>
  <u t="1329679">things like this. I really enjoy</u>
  <u t="1331280">northern Italy. So, Lake Ko, the whole</u>
  <u t="1333280">area up there is so stunning. It's just</u>
  <u t="1335280">an hour and a half drive from Milan and</u>
  <u t="1336799">it's a totally different world. It's</u>
  <u t="1338240">clean here.</u>
  <u t="1339490">[snorts]</u>
  <u t="1339600">fresh air. You have cobblestone streets.</u>
  <u t="1342000">Really, really nice scenery.</u>
  <u t="1343840">Surprisingly, the lake is a lot clearer</u>
  <u t="1345679">than I thought. See these ducks? You can</u>
  <u t="1347840">see the ground. I also really like the</u>
  <u t="1349679">island of Sicily, which is technically</u>
  <u t="1351840">part of Italy. Part of the beauty of</u>
  <u t="1353520">traveling to a place like Sicily is</u>
  <u t="1355520">getting lost.</u>
  <u t="1356159">It's way more rugged and run down. You</u>
  <u t="1357840">got Polarmo. Beautiful church/bommo</u>
  <u t="1360320">here. Unbelievable. It's really kind of</u>
  <u t="1362000">where like the mafia was started and</u>
  <u t="1363600">invented. So, you kind of have those</u>
  <u t="1364799">vibes out there. Those who want respect</u>
  <u t="1368159">give respect.</u>
  <u t="1369280">Sicilian food is great. I'm going to go</u>
  <u t="1371280">as far as saying this is one of the best</u>
  <u t="1372960">street food snacks in Europe. Sicilian</u>
  <u t="1374480">rice ball. Yeah. And you have these</u>
  <u t="1376960">ancient Roman ruins in Sicily that are</u>
  <u t="1379200">unmissable.</u>
  <u t="1380080">Wo, check this out. I was not expecting</u>
  <u t="1382320">to see this in Sicily. Soon I want to</u>
  <u t="1383919">road trip the boot of Italy. There's a</u>
  <u t="1385440">lot to see down there. Milan is the</u>
  <u t="1387039">fashion capital of the world. There's so</u>
  <u t="1388880">much going on in this country and it's</u>
  <u t="1390559">so big that you always got to keep going</u>
  <u t="1392080">back and visit. And I feel like this was</u>
  <u t="1393440">obvious enough that I didn't have to</u>
  <u t="1394559">tell you this, but Italian food is</u>
  <u t="1396159">fantastic, and it goes way beyond pizza,</u>
  <u t="1398880">pasta, and wine.</u>
  <u t="1401360">Country number 11 is Slovenia. One of</u>
  <u t="1404080">the most beautiful places in the world</u>
  <u t="1405440">is Lake Bled. Right now, I'm at Lake</u>
  <u t="1407280">Bled in Slovenia, and it's really known</u>
  <u t="1409360">for having this 17th century church</u>
  <u t="1411280">right in the middle on this island. You</u>
  <u t="1412799">can see it behind me. It is so cool.</u>
  <u t="1414480">It's so pristine. The nature here is</u>
  <u t="1415919">incredible. I love it so much that I've</u>
  <u t="1417520">actually been three times, and I've</u>
  <u t="1418720">taken my family there cuz it's just so</u>
  <u t="1420400">awesome. The capital city of Ljubljana</u>
  <u t="1423200">actually has like the most coffee shops</u>
  <u t="1424640">per capita than any city in Europe. It's</u>
  <u t="1426960">awesome. You can just sit along the</u>
  <u t="1428240">river like this. You can have your</u>
  <u t="1429840">coffee. You just hang out. It's a</u>
  <u t="1431280">beautiful, beautiful place. They love</u>
  <u t="1432720">sports there. Luca Donuch, one of my</u>
  <u t="1434400">favorite basketball players is</u>
  <u t="1435200">Slovenian. So, you'll see people playing</u>
  <u t="1436720">basketball and sports all over the</u>
  <u t="1438000">place. It's very outdoorsy, very natury,</u>
  <u t="1440400">and a place that you really just can't</u>
  <u t="1442000">miss on your next Euro trip because it's</u>
  <u t="1443840">easy to miss. It's such a small place,</u>
  <u t="1445440">but you'll absolutely love it if you go</u>
  <u t="1447039">there. And uh Slovenia is just highly,</u>
  <u t="1449039">highly, highly recommended from me.</u>
  <u t="1450559">Also, the people are really charming.</u>
  <u t="1452159">The first time I ever couch stirked was</u>
  <u t="1453679">in Slovenia and I was with a really</u>
  <u t="1455120">sweet couple that I'll never forget how</u>
  <u t="1456880">they treated me. Just super super</u>
  <u t="1458480">respectful, super kind, and that's</u>
  <u t="1460400">really something special cuz I'll never</u>
  <u t="1461760">forget it. All right, I am back in the</u>
  <u t="1464480">car to head to a country that's coming</u>
  <u t="1465919">up in a few minutes from now. But for</u>
  <u t="1467600">now, we're going to talk about country</u>
  <u t="1469520">number 12, Switzerland.</u>
  <u t="1473520">Switzerland's a special place because</u>
  <u t="1475279">there's no Swiss language. It's three</u>
  <u t="1477679">languages, actually four, but the main</u>
  <u t="1479600">three are Swiss German, Swiss French,</u>
  <u t="1481919">and Swiss Italian, depending on the</u>
  <u t="1483360">region of Switzerland that you're in.</u>
  <u t="1484880">Yes.</u>
  <u t="1486720">There is actually one Swiss language</u>
  <u t="1488240">which few [music] people speak, and it's</u>
  <u t="1490000">actually really interesting. But for the</u>
  <u t="1491360">most part, you get those three</u>
  <u t="1492640">languages. And it's cool because it's</u>
  <u t="1494159">sectioned off in three different places</u>
  <u t="1496240">close to the countries that speak the</u>
  <u t="1497520">languages. I've been to Switzerland four</u>
  <u t="1499039">or five times, and every single time I</u>
  <u t="1500799">go back, I always say, "This is the most</u>
  <u t="1502320">beautiful place in the world."</u>
  <u t="1503279">Switzerland is just outrageously</u>
  <u t="1505520">stunning. Woo! You can't imagine</u>
  <u t="1508640">training through Switzerland and seeing</u>
  <u t="1510000">the Alps. Beautiful green rolling hills.</u>
  <u t="1512080">It looks like [music] a Dr. Seuss book.</u>
  <u t="1513520">It's perfect. All the streets are</u>
  <u t="1515279">beautiful. Some of my favorite places</u>
  <u t="1517840">are Lucern in the south. [music] It's</u>
  <u t="1519919">really nice down there. Lugano, which is</u>
  <u t="1521679">also in the Italian speaking part of</u>
  <u t="1523039">Switzerland on a beautiful lake. I'm now</u>
  <u t="1524799">walking next to Lake Lugano, which is</u>
  <u t="1526880">obviously the huge lake here. It kind of</u>
  <u t="1528400">looks like Lake Ko in Italy, and it's</u>
  <u t="1530240">very nearby. Look how the town is built</u>
  <u t="1532000">on the mountain right there. That's</u>
  <u t="1533200">pretty stunning. That's something you</u>
  <u t="1534480">don't see every day. You have</u>
  <u t="1535600">Interlockin, which is like the outdoor</u>
  <u t="1537039">sports capital of the world. It's where</u>
  <u t="1538240">I went bungee jumping from 150 meters</u>
  <u t="1540000">high, which was epic.</u>
  <u t="1542799">The big cities of Zurich Burn and</u>
  <u t="1544480">Interlockin are actually quite nice.</u>
  <u t="1546480">They're really expensive. Keep in mind,</u>
  <u t="1548000">Switzerland is [music] one of the most</u>
  <u t="1548960">expensive countries in the world. I</u>
  <u t="1550080">think like $30 for a pizza pie. But it</u>
  <u t="1552159">is totally worth it because the</u>
  <u t="1553520">experiences that you can have in</u>
  <u t="1554640">Switzerland [music] are just fantastic.</u>
  <u t="1556960">The air is pure. There's water coming</u>
  <u t="1558880">from the ground everywhere [music] cuz</u>
  <u t="1560080">it's so delicious. It's like the spring</u>
  <u t="1561840">water in Switzerland, even from the the</u>
  <u t="1563600">tap water, is like the cleanest in the</u>
  <u t="1565279">world, and it's so freaking good. And</u>
  <u t="1567120">they also produce a lot of really cool</u>
  <u t="1568640">niche things like watches [music] and</u>
  <u t="1570480">army knives and chocolate. All right,</u>
  <u t="1573360">country number 13 is Norway.</u>
  <u t="1577913">[music]</u>
  <u t="1579840">The beautiful Scandinavian country that</u>
  <u t="1581760">has just a population of a few million</u>
  <u t="1584320">people, but it's a huge place. It goes</u>
  <u t="1586559">all the way up almost to the North Pole.</u>
  <u t="1588240">You have Swalbard, which is a little</u>
  <u t="1589760">island many hours north of the mainland</u>
  <u t="1592080">by plane. It's really cool up there. I</u>
  <u t="1593840">just want to say that it's 1:00 in the</u>
  <u t="1595120">morning and this is like the only time</u>
  <u t="1596720">in my life that I've been able to film a</u>
  <u t="1598400">video when it's complete daylight.</u>
  <u t="1599919">There's like Norwegian settlements,</u>
  <u t="1601039">there's Russian settlements, there's</u>
  <u t="1602080">polar bears. Wow, there's like nobody</u>
  <u t="1604400">around. Look, I'm in the center of the</u>
  <u t="1606480">entire place. Not a soul in sight. All</u>
  <u t="1609279">these weird buildings around me. Oh man,</u>
  <u t="1611318">[snorts] this is so eerie. This has to</u>
  <u t="1613120">be one of the most bizarre settlements</u>
  <u t="1615039">in the entire world. and Longerbian</u>
  <u t="1616559">which is the capital of Swalbard is the</u>
  <u t="1618000">northernmost bigish town or city in</u>
  <u t="1619833">[music] the world which is pretty cool</u>
  <u t="1620960">and I highly recommend visiting</u>
  <u t="1622159">Swallbard</u>
  <u t="1624400">but on the mainland you have Oslo of</u>
  <u t="1626000">course which is a beautiful capital city</u>
  <u t="1627520">also really expensive so we came to this</u>
  <u t="1629360">food market everything is like more than</u>
  <u t="1631039">$20 each</u>
  <u t="1631840">I just paid $25 for a 3minut ride</u>
  <u t="1634799">Norway and Switzerland are like the two</u>
  <u t="1636159">most expensive cities in Europe so if</u>
  <u t="1637679">you are on a tight budget you [music]</u>
  <u t="1638960">might want to reconsider visiting these</u>
  <u t="1640559">two countries at least until you have</u>
  <u t="1641919">money saved up in the future</u>
  <u t="1643279">that's what I'm talking about those kind</u>
  <u t="1644880">of low This is This is so tiny.</u>
  <u t="1649120">But good.</u>
  <u t="1649600">One of the most beautiful places in</u>
  <u t="1650960">Norway are the fjords in the west in a</u>
  <u t="1653039">little town called Bergen, which has the</u>
  <u t="1654960">best salmon I've ever had in my entire</u>
  <u t="1656320">life. And you can take a boat tour of</u>
  <u t="1657600">the fjords. F O R D. It's actually a</u>
  <u t="1660240">Norwegian word, but there are fjords all</u>
  <u t="1661760">over the world, like in [music] Chile,</u>
  <u t="1663039">New Zealand. But the ones in Norway are</u>
  <u t="1664880">simply the best. I like Norwegian people</u>
  <u t="1666640">a lot. They're cool. They're fun.</u>
  <u t="1668159">They're friendly. They speak wonderful</u>
  <u t="1669840">English, like American accent English.</u>
  <u t="1671520">It's kind of crazy. Like they're like</u>
  <u t="1672880">perfect English in Norway. This is how</u>
  <u t="1674559">you do it. You break one, you take it</u>
  <u t="1676240">out and</u>
  <u t="1678799">better than Kit Kat, that's for sure.</u>
  <u t="1680320">You also have some cool towns called</u>
  <u t="1681840">Tronheim and Trumanzo, farther in the</u>
  <u t="1683520">north, which I visited both. Quaint</u>
  <u t="1685120">little walking streets, colorful</u>
  <u t="1686559">buildings, cobblestones. It's like a</u>
  <u t="1688320">freaking paradise in Norway, and it's a</u>
  <u t="1690240">country that I'm always going to go back</u>
  <u t="1691360">to in the future. Country number 14 is</u>
  <u t="1694799">Turkey.</u>
  <u t="1696469">[music]</u>
  <u t="1699200">I know what some of you guys are</u>
  <u t="1700320">thinking. Turkeyy's mostly in Asia, but</u>
  <u t="1702640">when you consider the biggest city in</u>
  <u t="1704159">Turkey being mostly in Europe, I'm going</u>
  <u t="1706480">to consider this country in Europe for</u>
  <u t="1708559">the purposes of this video at least.</u>
  <u t="1712080">Turkey is great. There are so many</u>
  <u t="1713760">different experiences to have in the</u>
  <u t="1714960">country. It's a [music] great road trip</u>
  <u t="1716320">nation. The roads are really clean, like</u>
  <u t="1718159">you see here on the Autobon. Turkey is</u>
  <u t="1719919">this really fascinating cross of like</u>
  <u t="1721919">European and Middle Eastern and Asian</u>
  <u t="1724000">cultures cuz it's literally right in the</u>
  <u t="1725440">middle. And it's a big place, so there's</u>
  <u t="1726720">a lot to see. We are now in the Sumela</u>
  <u t="1729039">Monastery way up in the mountains and</u>
  <u t="1730960">trib zone of northern Turkey. This is</u>
  <u t="1733200">all just incredible nature and it's just</u>
  <u t="1736080">really special to be up here. Some of my</u>
  <u t="1737840">favorite cities in Turkey to visit are</u>
  <u t="1739919">Diabakar and Martin which are both in</u>
  <u t="1741919">the eastern side in Mesopotamia where</u>
  <u t="1743840">the Kurds live. We're now walking</u>
  <u t="1745440">through the markets in the old quarter</u>
  <u t="1747520">of Mardin. It's so beautiful here and</u>
  <u t="1749919">you just feel like you're walking back</u>
  <u t="1751600">in time when you're through these</u>
  <u t="1752640">bizaars. It's amazing. You also have the</u>
  <u t="1754559">Hot Thai province where you can find</u>
  <u t="1755840">Gazian tap. It's unbelievable. Kaharaman</u>
  <u t="1758559">Marash, which is the birthplace of ice</u>
  <u t="1760480">cream.</u>
  <u t="1763520">Yep.</u>
  <u t="1766880">Thank you. It really is hard to explain</u>
  <u t="1768960">the consistency of this ice cream. It's</u>
  <u t="1770720">It doesn't melt in your mouth. You have</u>
  <u t="1771840">to chew it. But it's so good and</u>
  <u t="1773360">literally won't melt. You can keep it</u>
  <u t="1774640">outside all day and it will just stay in</u>
  <u t="1776240">the cone. That is Turkish ice cream for</u>
  <u t="1778320">you. Of course, you have Bodum, which is</u>
  <u t="1779919">like the seaside capital and the</u>
  <u t="1782000">beautiful beaches. The capital city of</u>
  <u t="1783600">Turkey, Ankara is kind of boring.</u>
  <u t="1784960">There's also a cool place in the north</u>
  <u t="1786320">called Trabzon where the tea comes from</u>
  <u t="1788240">in Turkey. I went to a village in the</u>
  <u t="1789919">north where they whistle like birds.</u>
  <u t="1791520">That's how they communicate, which was</u>
  <u t="1792799">really cool. There's beautiful hikes and</u>
  <u t="1795440">lakes. The oldest settlement in the</u>
  <u t="1797360">world is also in Turkey. The food is</u>
  <u t="1799360">delicious.</u>
  <u t="1801760">That is very good. Kebabs, this yogurt</u>
  <u t="1804640">stuff. You have Turkish tea, Turkish</u>
  <u t="1806240">coffee. They love shisha. Everything in</u>
  <u t="1808480">Turkey is great. M</u>
  <u t="1810399">I could keep talking about it, but we</u>
  <u t="1811679">got to get to the next country, which is</u>
  <u t="1813679">number 15. And the country that I have</u>
  <u t="1815919">just crossed the border in, which is</u>
  <u t="1818480">Germany. We're going to pick it up from</u>
  <u t="1820159">the [music] town of Dresden shortly.</u>
  <u t="1822960">Welcome to Dresden. Look how stunning</u>
  <u t="1825039">this main square is. Super super</u>
  <u t="1826880">underrated city in formerly East</u>
  <u t="1829039">Germany. Actually, most of the city in</u>
  <u t="1830799">Dresden was completely destroyed by</u>
  <u t="1832240">World War II.</u>
  <u t="1833120">Now they hit Dresden hardest of all</u>
  <u t="1836720">and it's rebuilt to be beautiful.</u>
  <u t="1838720">Germany as a whole is just so great.</u>
  <u t="1840480">I've been here maybe 20 times. I have</u>
  <u t="1842640">German roots. There's so much to offer</u>
  <u t="1844240">here. There's beaches if you want.</u>
  <u t="1845600">There's mountains. There's skiing.</u>
  <u t="1847360">There's quaint little charming towns.</u>
  <u t="1849279">Germany actually has the most UNESCO</u>
  <u t="1850799">sites in the world. I think they're tied</u>
  <u t="1852240">with Italy. Something like 60 different</u>
  <u t="1854000">UNESCO World Heritage sites in this</u>
  <u t="1855600">country. [music] So, there's so much to</u>
  <u t="1856640">see from small towns called Queenberg.</u>
  <u t="1859200">Cheese. [laughter]</u>
  <u t="1861200">A lot of cheese.</u>
  <u t="1863679">to bigger places like Berlin and Munich.</u>
  <u t="1865919">Even other towns like Augsburg and</u>
  <u t="1867919">Strutgart is cool. It is a lovely</u>
  <u t="1869840">morning here in Berlin. You can see the</u>
  <u t="1871200">Brandenburgg gate is behind me and the</u>
  <u t="1872880">city just has amazing vibe. Germany is</u>
  <u t="1874480">so much more than just like beer [music]</u>
  <u t="1875600">fest which is what American tourists</u>
  <u t="1877120">would come here for. There's so much to</u>
  <u t="1878480">offer in this country.</u>
  <u t="1882320">The food is great. You have sausages.</u>
  <u t="1884480">Oh my god.</u>
  <u t="1886799">Excellent hot dog here in Germany.</u>
  <u t="1888880">You have beer. I keep saying beer in</u>
  <u t="1890960">every city in Europe because I do like</u>
  <u t="1892240">to drink beer.</u>
  <u t="1894080">Ah, delicious. You have German pretzels.</u>
  <u t="1896399">You have Schetszel, which is a dish in</u>
  <u t="1897679">Bavaria, which is a really cool region</u>
  <u t="1899279">in southern Germany, which is amazing,</u>
  <u t="1901200">with the men dressed in the leader hosen</u>
  <u t="1902559">and the women dress in the durnle. But</u>
  <u t="1904000">my favorite city in Germany, probably</u>
  <u t="1905679">Hamburg. It's in the north. It's really</u>
  <u t="1907279">cool. It's traditional. It's where the</u>
  <u t="1908720">Beatles actually got their start in the</u>
  <u t="1910480">1960s, [music]</u>
  <u t="1913039">which is really cool. There's a lot of</u>
  <u t="1914159">Beatles history there. Actually, a</u>
  <u t="1915519">hamburger is just a burger from Hamburg,</u>
  <u t="1918080">if you can believe that. Blew my mind</u>
  <u t="1919519">when I first figured that out. Germany</u>
  <u t="1920960">is a great country to road trip.</u>
  <u t="1922240">Everything's safe. People are friendly.</u>
  <u t="1923919">Thank you.</u>
  <u t="1925519">They can all speak really good English.</u>
  <u t="1926799">Just get lost in the villages in the</u>
  <u t="1928240">countryside. Go to random bakeries.</u>
  <u t="1929840">That's where you'll find the joy of</u>
  <u t="1931279">Germany. [music]</u>
  <u t="1932640">Hello. Can I get one brought worse and</u>
  <u t="1934880">water? Thank you so much.</u>
  <u t="1940880">Nothing, and I mean nothing, is better</u>
  <u t="1943200">than a sausage in Germany. Which leads</u>
  <u t="1945200">me into number 16, Georgia.</u>
  <u t="1950880">FROM GEORGIA.</u>
  <u t="1952320">SO GEORGIA is another one of those</u>
  <u t="1953519">countries that's stuck in between Asia</u>
  <u t="1954799">and Europe. Something is Asia, something</u>
  <u t="1956159">is Europe. For the purpose of this</u>
  <u t="1957360">video, I'm going to call it Europe. When</u>
  <u t="1958799">I walk these streets of Tlisi, it really</u>
  <u t="1960720">feels like Eastern Europe. Something</u>
  <u t="1962159">like a cross between Prague and Kiev. We</u>
  <u t="1964080">have the cobblestone streets, the</u>
  <u t="1965519">beautiful buildings behind me, and just</u>
  <u t="1967200">the overall vibe. It really feels like</u>
  <u t="1969279">Europe.</u>
  <u t="1969919">We actually have these public drinking</u>
  <u t="1971440">fountains all over the city.</u>
  <u t="1973840">It's cool. It's grungy. It's hip. It's</u>
  <u t="1975679">modern. It kind of reminds me of Berlin,</u>
  <u t="1977440">which is just down the street from where</u>
  <u t="1978480">I am now. Um, in terms of the graffiti,</u>
  <u t="1980240">the edgginess, [music]</u>
  <u t="1981360">the youth walking the streets, the</u>
  <u t="1982720">ability for people to speak English.</u>
  <u t="1984000">When it comes to pop music, I think that</u>
  <u t="1986000">simplicity is really key.</u>
  <u t="1988000">But Georgia is really cool because</u>
  <u t="1989039">there's all these like Christian</u>
  <u t="1990240">Orthodox churches. This place is</u>
  <u t="1992159">incredible. The the architecture, you</u>
  <u t="1994159">can feel the ancient history happening</u>
  <u t="1995760">inside of this place. Beautiful</u>
  <u t="1997760">countryside with a lot of wine, really</u>
  <u t="1999679">good wineries in Georgia, and then the</u>
  <u t="2001360">Black Sea is awesome. There's a town</u>
  <u t="2002799">called Batumi, which is [music] really</u>
  <u t="2003919">beautiful. It's just one of those places</u>
  <u t="2005200">that you go and you just feel connected</u>
  <u t="2006720">to. It's a post Soviet country, so it</u>
  <u t="2008559">was the USSR back when Russia was one</u>
  <u t="2010640">piece. So the older generation speak</u>
  <u t="2012480">Russian as a second language. The</u>
  <u t="2014159">Georgian language itself is cool. It's</u>
  <u t="2015519">like all these little circles and</u>
  <u t="2017519">swirlies in the language.</u>
  <u t="2026720">Leave it alone.</u>
  <u t="2028640">But yeah, it's really a fantastic</u>
  <u t="2030240">country if you want to travel soon. It's</u>
  <u t="2031919">really safe. It's pretty affordable and</u>
  <u t="2033519">I think it's super up and cominging. You</u>
  <u t="2035279">have to try kinali and kacapori. My two</u>
  <u t="2037519">favorite dishes in Georgia and go soon</u>
  <u t="2039760">before it becomes overloaded with</u>
  <u t="2041279">tourists. Number 17 is Sweden. Beautiful</u>
  <u t="2045120">Scandinavian country in between Norway</u>
  <u t="2046880">and Finland. Similar to the reasons why</u>
  <u t="2048560">I love Norway. People are so nice and</u>
  <u t="2050560">respectful and cool. They speak English</u>
  <u t="2052399">really well.</u>
  <u t="2053119">You're so so welcome.</u>
  <u t="2054800">It's a great road trip country. You</u>
  <u t="2056079">could actually take a 20-minute train</u>
  <u t="2057520">from Copenhagen or just cross over the</u>
  <u t="2059200">bridge by car and you're in a town</u>
  <u t="2060399">called Mama, which is pretty cool in</u>
  <u t="2061919">southern Sweden. [music] Then you can</u>
  <u t="2063280">drive up the west coast to</u>
  <u t="2064480">Goththingberg. A great drive, just a few</u>
  <u t="2066240">hours.</u>
  <u t="2066639">We have Dudoy who's scared of the water.</u>
  <u t="2068639">We have Diana, Grandma and Grandpa, and</u>
  <u t="2071040">we're going to cruise around Gutenberg.</u>
  <u t="2072639">What do you think about Goththingberg,</u>
  <u t="2074000">Grandma?</u>
  <u t="2074720">Very, very nice.</u>
  <u t="2076079">And if you want to go to Stockholm,</u>
  <u t="2077440">which is my one of my favorite cities in</u>
  <u t="2078879">Europe, you could drive over there or</u>
  <u t="2080320">you could fly there. Uh Stockholm is a</u>
  <u t="2081919">city of many different islands. Awesome</u>
  <u t="2083679">nightife. I went to a club last time I</u>
  <u t="2085359">was there until like 6:00 in the</u>
  <u t="2086560">morning. Sweden's cool. It's really</u>
  <u t="2087919">clean. It's expensive, but it's worth</u>
  <u t="2089839">it. The quality of life there is</u>
  <u t="2091119">amazing. It's the birthplace of IKEA.</u>
  <u t="2092960">Peter Forsber, who's a hockey player.</u>
  <u t="2095119">Forsber is in. They score.</u>
  <u t="2097200">Ludvig Ober who's a golfer.</u>
  <u t="2099839">Got to put a lot of</u>
  <u t="2102720">And of course, you have Swedish</u>
  <u t="2104079">meatballs, which are fantastic.</u>
  <u t="2106160">Yum.</u>
  <u t="2107839">Delicious.</u>
  <u t="2108480">I can't say more amazing things about</u>
  <u t="2110000">Sweden, but [music] you have to visit to</u>
  <u t="2111119">know what it's like for yourself. Number</u>
  <u t="2112720">18 is Ireland. What a beautiful country.</u>
  <u t="2116160">I've been there many, many times. So,</u>
  <u t="2118000">we're out here in Kil Kenny, Ireland.</u>
  <u t="2120640">It's really hard not to like Ireland.</u>
  <u t="2122160">First off, the people are incredible.</u>
  <u t="2123599">They're funny. They're friendly.</u>
  <u t="2124960">Sometimes it's hard to understand them,</u>
  <u t="2126154">[music] even if they're speaking</u>
  <u t="2127040">English. Yes, they do have their own</u>
  <u t="2128320">language called Gaelic, which I can't</u>
  <u t="2129920">understand a lick of, but if they are</u>
  <u t="2131440">speaking English, sometimes it sometimes</u>
  <u t="2133440">you got to ask them a few times what</u>
  <u t="2135119">they're saying. But all jokes aside,</u>
  <u t="2136880">Dublin's a great place to start. As you</u>
  <u t="2138800">would think, they love drinking beer.</u>
  <u t="2142000">Everything there is very festive, clean,</u>
  <u t="2143599">but the best part about Ireland is road</u>
  <u t="2145119">tripping. So you could drive to Cork</u>
  <u t="2146459">[music] on the West Coast.</u>
  <u t="2147680">All right, we just got in the rental car</u>
  <u t="2149280">and it's kind of funny because I'm</u>
  <u t="2150960">driving on the right side of the road,</u>
  <u t="2152560">but I think we can handle it.</u>
  <u t="2153680">You could drive up to my favorite place</u>
  <u t="2155280">in Ireland, which is Donnagal County.</u>
  <u t="2157040">It's awesome. I'm a little biased</u>
  <u t="2158640">probably because I golfed all the best</u>
  <u t="2160000">courses uh in Donnagal County.</u>
  <u t="2161599">All right, so we're out here golfing and</u>
  <u t="2163200">it's pouring rain and it's windy. Look</u>
  <u t="2165680">at my dad's umbrella. There's beautiful</u>
  <u t="2168320">cliffs called the Sleevely Cliffs where</u>
  <u t="2170000">you can see incredible views over the</u>
  <u t="2171760">Atlantic Ocean. I'm standing here at the</u>
  <u t="2173599">Sleevely Cliffs in the northwestern</u>
  <u t="2175280">[music] part of Ireland. And as you can</u>
  <u t="2177119">see, it is absolutely fantastic. There's</u>
  <u t="2179359">more sheep than people in Ireland. So,</u>
  <u t="2180960">you'll see a lot of beautiful nature</u>
  <u t="2182560">countryside. You have really amazing</u>
  <u t="2184560">medieval towns all over the place. It's</u>
  <u t="2186880">actually a country that I want to go</u>
  <u t="2188079">back and explore more of because there's</u>
  <u t="2189680">so many hidden gems in Ireland. But all</u>
  <u t="2191599">I got to say is beautiful, peaceful.</u>
  <u t="2194275">[music]</u>
  <u t="2195920">Not to be missed are the other cities of</u>
  <u t="2198079">Galway and Limrich. They're actually</u>
  <u t="2199680">pretty cool. I I just drove through and</u>
  <u t="2201359">stayed a couple hours in each, [music]</u>
  <u t="2202800">but I just love the vibe. And if you</u>
  <u t="2204240">really just want to have fun in one</u>
  <u t="2205680">country in Europe, Ireland might be the</u>
  <u t="2207839">place. Number 19 is Russia.</u>
  <u t="2210960">LET'S [screaming]</u>
  <u t="2215599">know most of Russia is geographically</u>
  <u t="2217440">located in Asia, but two of the biggest</u>
  <u t="2219359">cities of Moscow and St. Petersburg are</u>
  <u t="2221440">in fact very European and also</u>
  <u t="2223280">geographically located in Europe. So,</u>
  <u t="2224800">we're going to roll with it. This is so</u>
  <u t="2226480">magical in the snow. Like, oh my god,</u>
  <u t="2228990">[laughter]</u>
  <u t="2229839">Russia's awesome. Unfortunately, there's</u>
  <u t="2231599">the war in recent years and a lot of</u>
  <u t="2233680">people are hating on it. But, if we're</u>
  <u t="2235119">just talking [music] pure culture and</u>
  <u t="2237200">food and hospitality and just overall</u>
  <u t="2239599">travel experience, nothing political,</u>
  <u t="2241760">Russia is as good as it gets. This is</u>
  <u t="2243440">something I've always dreamed of, ice</u>
  <u t="2245040">skating on Lake Bico. This lake is so</u>
  <u t="2247200">big. It's bigger than all the Great</u>
  <u t="2248880">Lakes combined. It's the oldest lake in</u>
  <u t="2250800">the world. It's ancient. This is</u>
  <u t="2252240">literally a dream come true right now.</u>
  <u t="2254000">It's beautiful.</u>
  <u t="2256720">They have really, really good dumplings</u>
  <u t="2258640">and cottage cheese. I'm telling you,</u>
  <u t="2260480">whatever it is, they do it right in</u>
  <u t="2261839">Russia. And of course, if you like</u>
  <u t="2263119">vodka, if you are a drinker, then it</u>
  <u t="2264720">might be a country for you.</u>
  <u t="2268160">Which one should I say?</u>
  <u t="2271280">All over Russia is beautiful views,</u>
  <u t="2273599">beautiful people. It's just one of those</u>
  <u t="2275359">places that you visit and you're like,</u>
  <u t="2276560">"Okay, I get it now. This place is super</u>
  <u t="2278480">super cool." Woo.</u>
  <u t="2281440">So, obviously the western side of Russia</u>
  <u t="2283359">is very European, but the farther east</u>
  <u t="2285599">you go becomes really interesting into</u>
  <u t="2287359">Siberia. I did the Trans Siberian train</u>
  <u t="2289520">for a bit. I even went all the way to</u>
  <u t="2291040">Vladib in the eastern tip of Russia, the</u>
  <u t="2293920">biggest coast of Russia. Believe it or</u>
  <u t="2295520">not, it's pretty landlocked because the</u>
  <u t="2296880">northern border of Russia is all ice.</u>
  <u t="2298560">It's too cold. Other cool places to</u>
  <u t="2300240">check out are Noirk, and of course,</u>
  <u t="2302480">Yakuz, which is the world's coldest</u>
  <u t="2303839">city.</u>
  <u t="2304160">Are you cold?</u>
  <u t="2304960">No. No. No. And it's interesting how</u>
  <u t="2306640">people in Eastern Russia look Asian and</u>
  <u t="2308640">some of them even speak fluent Japanese</u>
  <u t="2310240">or Korean because it's so close to those</u>
  <u t="2311760">countries.</u>
  <u t="2313839">America.</u>
  <u t="2315119">Yes.</u>
  <u t="2315440">But Russia is such a big place. There's</u>
  <u t="2317359">so many experiences to be had and</u>
  <u t="2318880">honestly now might not be the best time,</u>
  <u t="2320800">but in the future if things open up and</u>
  <u t="2322720">if war calms down, I highly recommend a</u>
  <u t="2324960">visit to Russia. I think that you'll</u>
  <u t="2326480">think differently ABOUT IT.</u>
  <u t="2327599">GOT THAT. GET IN. GET IN. [screaming]</u>
  <u t="2331119">Country number 20 is Croatia. a recent</u>
  <u t="2334400">member of the Shenen zone, which is like</u>
  <u t="2336079">the free travel and free trade zone of</u>
  <u t="2338240">Europe, where you don't need a visa to</u>
  <u t="2339440">cross borders. Croatia is awesome. It's</u>
  <u t="2340960">in former Yugoslavia. So, the language</u>
  <u t="2342880">is similar to what you'd [music] find in</u>
  <u t="2344079">Serbia. People are awesome.</u>
  <u t="2347760">One of the coolest towns in Europe is</u>
  <u t="2349440">called Dubnik. It's a medieval town on</u>
  <u t="2351520">the Adriatic Sea. You can walk on the</u>
  <u t="2353599">old medieval walls and [music] the</u>
  <u t="2355680">cobblestone streets like this are</u>
  <u t="2357119">incredible. You have to go to Dubnik.</u>
  <u t="2358960">Another cool town is called Split, which</u>
  <u t="2360800">is nearby Dubnik, which you have to</u>
  <u t="2362160">visit. There's Havar Island, HV A R.</u>
  <u t="2364400">There's actually like hundreds of</u>
  <u t="2365599">islands in Croatia, which most people</u>
  <u t="2366960">don't know about. Zagreb, the capital,</u>
  <u t="2368560">it's not the most interesting place.</u>
  <u t="2369599">There's some cool buildings, couple good</u>
  <u t="2371040">restaurants, but the beauty of Croatia</u>
  <u t="2372720">is in the south on the coast. You just</u>
  <u t="2374640">have to road trip it and really get to</u>
  <u t="2376160">feel it and experience it for yourself.</u>
  <u t="2377599">Seafood is amazing, and you should</u>
  <u t="2378960">actually do Croatia as part of a bigger</u>
  <u t="2380800">Yugoslavic road trip where you hit all</u>
  <u t="2382640">the six or seven countries that formerly</u>
  <u t="2384800">made up Yugoslavia. Uh, it's just</u>
  <u t="2386720">fantastic. Country number 21 is Poland.</u>
  <u t="2392087">[music]</u>
  <u t="2395119">Poland is huge. You look at the map and</u>
  <u t="2397359">you see Germany, which is where I am</u>
  <u t="2398960">now, which is huge. But if you just look</u>
  <u t="2400400">east of it, Poland is like almost as</u>
  <u t="2402000">big. It's Eastern Europe. It's way</u>
  <u t="2403599">cheaper. They're not even on the euro.</u>
  <u t="2404800">They use as latte. What I like about the</u>
  <u t="2406640">money is every bill is small. And like</u>
  <u t="2408640">the lower the count, the smaller it</u>
  <u t="2410400">gets. They have really, really good food</u>
  <u t="2411760">issa, which is like this pizza thing.</u>
  <u t="2414720">The bagel, as you know, today in New</u>
  <u t="2416160">York, actually came from Poland. These</u>
  <u t="2417760">little circular things. I forgot [music]</u>
  <u t="2419119">the name of them, but they're all over</u>
  <u t="2420160">the place.</u>
  <u t="2421440">M the beer is amazing. My favorite dish</u>
  <u t="2423680">in Poland is perogis. These little</u>
  <u t="2425440">dumpling things which you have to try.</u>
  <u t="2427280">I can't explain how fresh this tastes.</u>
  <u t="2429280">I'm telling you guys, perogis are the</u>
  <u t="2431440">best thing about Poland in the cuisine</u>
  <u t="2433280">world. [music]</u>
  <u t="2434720">Warsaw is a really cool big city, but</u>
  <u t="2436640">you have to get to Crackkow. It's a</u>
  <u t="2438000">university town, so it's very young.</u>
  <u t="2439359">There's a lot of bars. There's a lot of</u>
  <u t="2440480">restaurants. A lot of cool vibes there.</u>
  <u t="2442320">Wa man, this is cool. Beautiful.</u>
  <u t="2446079">The old square in Crackow is one of the</u>
  <u t="2447839">biggest in the world, and it's amazing.</u>
  <u t="2450000">We feel good. We're just like hanging</u>
  <u t="2451280">out and it's beautiful here in the</u>
  <u t="2452480">Oldtown Square. Just feeling the vibes.</u>
  <u t="2454400">The city is really cool. I love it.</u>
  <u t="2455760">There's also a city called Vclav. I know</u>
  <u t="2457520">I pronounced it wrong, but it's really</u>
  <u t="2458800">beautiful. Also reminds [music] me of</u>
  <u t="2460000">Prague and I soon want to go to Gdans,</u>
  <u t="2462240">which is in the north. There's a lot of</u>
  <u t="2463359">World War II history there, which I</u>
  <u t="2464640">heard is awesome. But, uh, soon I'll be</u>
  <u t="2466160">road tripping more of Poland, and I'm</u>
  <u t="2467599">excited to experience more of the</u>
  <u t="2470480">Eastern European flavor, which is which,</u>
  <u t="2472319">if you couldn't tell by this video</u>
  <u t="2473520">already, most of my countries, uh, that</u>
  <u t="2475359">are my favorite in Europe are on the</u>
  <u t="2476560">eastern side. It's just more interesting</u>
  <u t="2478240">out here. And I say out here because</u>
  <u t="2480319">technically I'm in East Germany right</u>
  <u t="2481839">now. Although Germany as a whole is</u>
  <u t="2483760">Western Europe, but Dresden's pretty</u>
  <u t="2485839">Eastern Europe and it has Prague vibes.</u>
  <u t="2487520">It was split when the Berlin Wall split</u>
  <u t="2489280">the two sides of Berlin or Germany into</u>
  <u t="2491440">two parts. This was Eastern Europe, so I</u>
  <u t="2493839">still consider it Eastern and I still</u>
  <u t="2496319">like saying Eastern even though Germany</u>
  <u t="2497839">is Western Europe. All right, it's time</u>
  <u t="2499119">to move across Europe to a little</u>
  <u t="2500800">country called the United Kingdom.</u>
  <u t="2507680">Well, technically it's not part of</u>
  <u t="2509440">Europe, but I still consider it Europe,</u>
  <u t="2511040">and most Americans that are ignorant</u>
  <u t="2512560">would consider it Europe. And for the</u>
  <u t="2513920">purposes of this video, it's Europe. I'm</u>
  <u t="2516319">in a tiny little town called Castle</u>
  <u t="2518079">Donington. You can see there's [music]</u>
  <u t="2520560">the castle. It's eerily quiet, which is</u>
  <u t="2522240">why I'm not screaming right now. It's</u>
  <u t="2523680">awesome to be here in England. I</u>
  <u t="2525280">actually just played in the ProAm with</u>
  <u t="2526800">Sergio Garcia in the Liv event, which</u>
  <u t="2528880">was like a dream come true. If anyone's</u>
  <u t="2530400">a golf fan out there, they'll know how</u>
  <u t="2531920">insanely [music] epic of an incredible</u>
  <u t="2533760">of an experience. But there's no doubt</u>
  <u t="2535520">the UK is awesome. It's made up of four</u>
  <u t="2537359">parts. Northern Ireland, Scotland,</u>
  <u t="2538880">Wales, and [music] England.</u>
  <u t="2542880">There's a lot going on. There's a lot to</u>
  <u t="2544160">do here. It's a big country. There's</u>
  <u t="2545359">like 80 million people here. It's where</u>
  <u t="2546960">the English language is derived from.</u>
  <u t="2548480">So, always this pleasure to be here and</u>
  <u t="2550480">hear people speaking, seeing what the</u>
  <u t="2552240">life's all about. I mean, look at this.</u>
  <u t="2553440">This little tiny town is so cool. It's</u>
  <u t="2556000">like so stereotypical British. I'm just</u>
  <u t="2558480">smiling cuz I haven't been in England</u>
  <u t="2559760">that many times in my life whenever I am</u>
  <u t="2561520">here. St. An's Lane. It's just awesome.</u>
  <u t="2564160">So, of course, London is one of the</u>
  <u t="2565520">coolest cities in the world. It's big.</u>
  <u t="2566720">It's massive. Shortage is my favorite</u>
  <u t="2568480">area there. There's a lot going on. What</u>
  <u t="2570160">I don't like about London is that the</u>
  <u t="2571280">bars close at like midnight. I wish they</u>
  <u t="2572880">stayed open later. But, wo,</u>
  <u t="2577520">look at this view. Oh my god. I totally</u>
  <u t="2579920">just discovered this right now. Wo.</u>
  <u t="2581920">Gives me goosebumps. It's like it's a</u>
  <u t="2583599">setting for a horror film.</u>
  <u t="2589520">But I've never been to Wales. And I know</u>
  <u t="2591200">all the Welsh people out there always</u>
  <u t="2592400">tell me it's a country. Well, it's</u>
  <u t="2593599">technically not a country by the UN, so</u>
  <u t="2595200">I can't count it as a country. I'm</u>
  <u t="2596640">actually not far from Wales. Maybe I'll</u>
  <u t="2597920">drive there after this. Scotland's</u>
  <u t="2599280">awesome. I've been there four times for</u>
  <u t="2600640">golf trips, just driving around. I love</u>
  <u t="2603119">Edinburghough. I love Aurora and the</u>
  <u t="2604880">Scottish Highlands up north. The Loch</u>
  <u t="2606319">Ness Monster. I will say the UK is</u>
  <u t="2608400">ranked in the middle of all my European</u>
  <u t="2610240">countries because I just haven't seen</u>
  <u t="2611520">that much of it, and I would really love</u>
  <u t="2612800">to see more as I get older and can</u>
  <u t="2614640">appreciate things more, have a little</u>
  <u t="2615839">more money to spend for nice hotels.</u>
  <u t="2618480">Man, look at this. So epic. All right,</u>
  <u t="2620480">that leads me into number 23, which is</u>
  <u t="2623680">Hungary. Hungary is amazing. Lake</u>
  <u t="2626480">Balaton, which is right in the center of</u>
  <u t="2628000">the country, is beautiful. It's a great</u>
  <u t="2629680">getaway if you're just driving around</u>
  <u t="2630960">Europe and you want a place to chill for</u>
  <u t="2632319">a few days, camp overnight. We're on</u>
  <u t="2633839">Lake Balaton, and it's a really, you</u>
  <u t="2635920">know, it's Sunday, so there's nobody</u>
  <u t="2637280">out, but we're just kind of walking</u>
  <u t="2638400">around, seeing some cool buildings, and</u>
  <u t="2640240">enjoying the Hungarian vibes. I'm</u>
  <u t="2642240">hungry. Are you hungry? I'm hungry. And</u>
  <u t="2643680">hungry.</u>
  <u t="2644079">Hungry.</u>
  <u t="2644480">Budapest, of course, one of the best</u>
  <u t="2645839">cities in Europe, if not top 10 best in</u>
  <u t="2647680">the world. That is the Hungarian</u>
  <u t="2649359">Parliament building. It is the third</u>
  <u t="2651119">largest parliament in the world.</u>
  <u t="2653040">Spectacular views. How would you</u>
  <u t="2654960">describe Budapest in one word?</u>
  <u t="2656640">Amazing.</u>
  <u t="2657520">Historic. The Jewish quarters thriving.</u>
  <u t="2659520">There's so much to [music] do. The ruin</u>
  <u t="2660880">pubs are amazing where you can have a</u>
  <u t="2662240">drink in these in these like World War</u>
  <u t="2663440">II bunkers.</u>
  <u t="2664560">Wow.</u>
  <u t="2665040">Oh, this is</u>
  <u t="2665760">Every room in here is different. It's so</u>
  <u t="2667359">cool. You got an amazing medieval castle</u>
  <u t="2669200">district there. People are nice. It's</u>
  <u t="2671599">like in the Shenen zone and in the EU,</u>
  <u t="2673200">but they use foreign as their currency</u>
  <u t="2675119">and like things are very different</u>
  <u t="2676240">there. It's the weirdest language in the</u>
  <u t="2677760">world.</u>
  <u t="2685359">Aside from Lake Balaton in Budapest, I</u>
  <u t="2687200">don't really have other recommendations</u>
  <u t="2688400">in Hungary. When I was driving through</u>
  <u t="2690000">the country last time, I got a flat tire</u>
  <u t="2691359">and it was really fun to go to a random</u>
  <u t="2692720">tire shop and try to get that changed.</u>
  <u t="2694160">But, um, but yeah, Hungary is a cool</u>
  <u t="2695440">place. Definitely add it to your list.</u>
  <u t="2696560">And the farther east you go in Europe,</u>
  <u t="2697839">as you found out already in this video,</u>
  <u t="2699119">the more interesting it gets culturally.</u>
  <u t="2700640">It's cheap and fun. Number 24 is Greece.</u>
  <u t="2705119">There are so many islands to visit in</u>
  <u t="2707040">Greece. Please don't only go to</u>
  <u t="2709200">Santorini and Mkos and Nakos and Peros.</u>
  <u t="2711760">Just like the touristy islands, there's</u>
  <u t="2713119">so many other ones you can visit. Cit,</u>
  <u t="2714880">which is a bigger island in the</u>
  <u t="2716160">Caribbean, which is one of the coolest</u>
  <u t="2717280">islands in the world. Zakonos, I think I</u>
  <u t="2719280">pronounced that wrong, is amazing. I</u>
  <u t="2721040">haven't been to Thessalaniki in the</u>
  <u t="2722480">north. I'm pronouncing all these names</u>
  <u t="2723760">wrong, but I've heard it's really</u>
  <u t="2724800">beautiful. And Greek is very Balkan,</u>
  <u t="2726400">like the culture, the food, like people</u>
  <u t="2727920">are super friendly and outgoing and I</u>
  <u t="2730160">just really really like it there. And I</u>
  <u t="2731440">feel comfortable in Greece.</u>
  <u t="2734160">Food is great.</u>
  <u t="2734880">I know it's going to be expensive, but</u>
  <u t="2736240">it's worth [music] every penny.</u>
  <u t="2737280">You have hummus. You have falafel. Even</u>
  <u t="2738960">though that's Mediterranean food, it</u>
  <u t="2740400">still kind of blends over into</u>
  <u t="2744160">church bells are ringing.</u>
  <u t="2746446">[bell]</u>
  <u t="2747440">Wow. This moment is surreal right now.</u>
  <u t="2750880">I've actually never been outside of</u>
  <u t="2752880">London in England. This is the first</u>
  <u t="2754640">It's the first time I'm like in a</u>
  <u t="2755920">countryside. It's so cool. [snorts]</u>
  <u t="2758640">Anyways, get on a yacht, get on a</u>
  <u t="2760640">sailboat, go around the islands. Like,</u>
  <u t="2762240">they're so pristine. They're so</u>
  <u t="2763359">beautiful. We made it to a [music] spot</u>
  <u t="2765200">with these beautiful black cliffs you</u>
  <u t="2767280">can see behind me. Really, really nice.</u>
  <u t="2770682">[music]</u>
  <u t="2771839">Of course, like you have history like</u>
  <u t="2773280">Greek gods. You have Parthonon, the</u>
  <u t="2775040">Acropolis in Athens. They don't miss</u>
  <u t="2776960">Athens. Don't skip it. It's really,</u>
  <u t="2778800">really, really cool. You get the same</u>
  <u t="2780160">goosebumps that you when you see the</u>
  <u t="2781359">coliseum or you see the Eiffel Tower,</u>
  <u t="2783359">Taj Mahal, Great Wall of China. It's</u>
  <u t="2785040">that cool. The Acropolis of Athens is so</u>
  <u t="2787920">beautiful. And this is a very, very</u>
  <u t="2789680">special experience.</u>
  <u t="2790332">[music]</u>
  <u t="2790480">That leads me to country number 25,</u>
  <u t="2792480">Bulgaria.</u>
  <u t="2797599">Now it's time to explore Sophia. The</u>
  <u t="2800319">only time I went, I was super sick when</u>
  <u t="2801760">I was in Sophia for a few days and that</u>
  <u t="2803520">wasn't so great. And then I got scanned</u>
  <u t="2805280">by a taxi driver, which was awful.</u>
  <u t="2807280">Really awful. He rigged the meter and so</u>
  <u t="2808960">he charged me like €100 and it was</u>
  <u t="2810720">supposed to be like €20 and just give me</u>
  <u t="2812480">a really sour taste in my mouth about</u>
  <u t="2814160">Bulgaria. But you know what? I have a</u>
  <u t="2815599">feeling that if I go back it's going to</u>
  <u t="2817599">be incredible. I know the people there</u>
  <u t="2819359">are go, "Oh my god, I'm stepping on</u>
  <u t="2820640">graves. I just realized that." That's no</u>
  <u t="2823040">bueno. The people in Bulgaria are are</u>
  <u t="2825280">cool. I've met many of them and I just</u>
  <u t="2827119">know that it has like this vibe and it's</u>
  <u t="2828800">just pulling me to come back. It's on</u>
  <u t="2830319">the Black Sea so you have cities like</u>
  <u t="2831920">Varna and Burgas which are like cool</u>
  <u t="2834000">party cities on the sea which is</u>
  <u t="2835680">awesome. Bulgarian food is great. Very</u>
  <u t="2837680">meat heavy, very thick soups, stews,</u>
  <u t="2839680">lots of beer and I don't know for me</u>
  <u t="2842160">like no one knows about Bulgaria and</u>
  <u t="2843760">that is what makes it cool. I mean,</u>
  <u t="2845440">everyone knows about England. Everyone</u>
  <u t="2847040">knows about France, but Bulgaria, like,</u>
  <u t="2849599">why not give it a chance? Number 26 is</u>
  <u t="2852319">Denmark.</u>
  <u t="2853200">Look how charming this place is. We got</u>
  <u t="2854800">parks, ferris wheels, people here with</u>
  <u t="2857440">their families, food. This is a great</u>
  <u t="2859839">Danish experience. A beautiful</u>
  <u t="2861680">Scandinavian country. Copenhagen was one</u>
  <u t="2863599">of the first cities I ever went to in</u>
  <u t="2864800">Europe. I just love how bike friendly it</u>
  <u t="2866400">is. so clean and safe and neat and</u>
  <u t="2868160">everyone dresses nice. You know, the</u>
  <u t="2869680">Scandinavian vibe with like the blonde</u>
  <u t="2871359">hair on the side and collared shirts and</u>
  <u t="2873359">everyone looks like they're just going</u>
  <u t="2874480">out on a date every night. It's funny.</u>
  <u t="2875839">Denmark underratedly has some of the</u>
  <u t="2877280">best food in the world. They have these</u>
  <u t="2878400">openf face sandwiches that are really</u>
  <u t="2879839">good. They have these really nice little</u>
  <u t="2881359">sausages. Somehow the Danish sausage is</u>
  <u t="2883359">better than anywhere else that I had in</u>
  <u t="2884720">Europe. And Dan are super friendly. They</u>
  <u t="2886319">speak perfect English. [music] It's just</u>
  <u t="2887599">a pleasure hanging out with them.</u>
  <u t="2891920">Wow. 8.8 seconds. Every time I'm with</u>
  <u t="2894240">Danish people, it's a it's a great scene</u>
  <u t="2895788">[music] every time. There's a town in</u>
  <u t="2897040">northern Denmark called Skagan. It's</u>
  <u t="2898640">actually where two oceans meet. I took</u>
  <u t="2900319">my grandparents [music] there and it was</u>
  <u t="2901599">our first time to Europe.</u>
  <u t="2902800">It's a nice experience and it's a part</u>
  <u t="2904720">of history.</u>
  <u t="2905599">And I took them to Copenhagen because</u>
  <u t="2907040">they really wanted to go when they were</u>
  <u t="2908079">85. And that was [music] to this day is</u>
  <u t="2909760">one of the best trips I've ever taken.</u>
  <u t="2910800">And if you ever get the chance to travel</u>
  <u t="2912240">with grandparents or parents, I highly</u>
  <u t="2914319">recommend you to do it. I'm so happy to</u>
  <u t="2916000">be here with you.</u>
  <u t="2916800">We're happy that you're with us, too.</u>
  <u t="2918880">Denmark is a really, really cool</u>
  <u t="2920079">country. And it's also the gateway to</u>
  <u t="2921680">get to Greenland, which I'm trying to</u>
  <u t="2922660">[music] go back to Greenland soon. So</u>
  <u t="2924240">yeah, really, really cool place and</u>
  <u t="2925839">really underrated place if you're trying</u>
  <u t="2927200">to start in Europe and if you want like</u>
  <u t="2928559">a fresh, clean place to go [music] with</u>
  <u t="2930319">easy to road trip, easy to get around,</u>
  <u t="2931920">friendly people, look no further than</u>
  <u t="2933760">Denmark. Number 27 is Slovakia, right in</u>
  <u t="2937200">the smack dab of Central Europe.</u>
  <u t="2940079">Used to be one country with Czech</u>
  <u t="2941599">Republic when it was called</u>
  <u t="2942319">Czechoslovakia until 1993 when it broke</u>
  <u t="2944160">up. Bradava is a way lesser cool version</u>
  <u t="2946079">of Prague, but I do recommend visiting.</u>
  <u t="2948188">[music]</u>
  <u t="2948960">Ratosava is a pretty cool city with a</u>
  <u t="2950800">buzzing atmosphere.</u>
  <u t="2951839">They do have big mountains in Slovakia,</u>
  <u t="2953440">like 3,000 mters, I think. So, it's some</u>
  <u t="2955200">of the highest uh in Europe. And I think</u>
  <u t="2956880">Eastern Slovakia is cool. It's a city</u>
  <u t="2958240">called Koship, which is like Yeah,</u>
  <u t="2959599">there's like gypsies and it's not like</u>
  <u t="2960960">super fancy, but it is cool and hip and</u>
  <u t="2962559">it's just a nice place to check out. And</u>
  <u t="2963920">I don't know, I think it's beautiful</u>
  <u t="2965040">countryside in Slovakia, and I like</u>
  <u t="2966319">driving through and because I have such</u>
  <u t="2967680">a fascination with that whole country. I</u>
  <u t="2969599">don't know. Slovakia is just one of</u>
  <u t="2970800">those like middleground countries. And</u>
  <u t="2972319">here's a cool fact. You could you could</u>
  <u t="2973599">visit [music] Vienna and Bradlava within</u>
  <u t="2975119">a 1-hour drive. They're the two closest</u>
  <u t="2976880">capital cities in the world. So you</u>
  <u t="2978480">could have breakfast in Vienna, lunch in</u>
  <u t="2980000">Bratoslava, and then you can have dinner</u>
  <u t="2981440">in Budapest or Prague. All three.</u>
  <u t="2982904">[music] Number 28 is Estonia. And once</u>
  <u t="2985440">again, I have to keep my voice down cuz</u>
  <u t="2986880">it's really weird like shooting in</u>
  <u t="2988400">Europe in general. This is a side note.</u>
  <u t="2990400">It's like everyone kind of stares at</u>
  <u t="2992079">you. Everyone's really private and they</u>
  <u t="2993440">don't really like people that are</u>
  <u t="2994480">obnoxious and they look at you funny. Um</u>
  <u t="2997760">so Estonia, going to Taleim was one of</u>
  <u t="3000720">the most eye opening trips ever and I</u>
  <u t="3002400">went back in um 2012 when I was only 1</u>
  <u t="3005760">years old. I took the boat from</u>
  <u t="3007119">Helsinki, which was awesome. You can</u>
  <u t="3008720">just take a 2-hour ferry. Everyone's</u>
  <u t="3010160">there just buying like booze and stuff</u>
  <u t="3011599">because it's way cheaper to drink in in</u>
  <u t="3013119">Estonia than it is in Finland. It's a</u>
  <u t="3014640">country in the Baltic region, which is</u>
  <u t="3016000">right near the Baltic Sea. But yeah,</u>
  <u t="3017280">going back to Tale, it's a medieval</u>
  <u t="3018720">town. It's got one of the most preserved</u>
  <u t="3020319">medieval vibes of any city in the world.</u>
  <u t="3022559">It's cool. There's like this young</u>
  <u t="3024240">population. It's like really techy</u>
  <u t="3026079">there. Like the headquarters of Skype is</u>
  <u t="3027599">there even though Skype is kind of dead.</u>
  <u t="3029119">I think there's another big tech</u>
  <u t="3030480">headquarters in Estonia. But very lovely</u>
  <u t="3032480">place. It's easy to to get around as a</u>
  <u t="3034400">tiny country and the young generation</u>
  <u t="3036079">speaks English and it really is just one</u>
  <u t="3037680">of those places that you'll visit and</u>
  <u t="3038800">you're and you're like, "Wo, this is a</u>
  <u t="3040720">really really cool place. I can't wait</u>
  <u t="3042079">to see more." Food is heavy. They like</u>
  <u t="3043920">their blueberry jams and yeah, it kind</u>
  <u t="3045599">of bleeds over from Russia a little bit.</u>
  <u t="3047280">But can't have any better things to say</u>
  <u t="3048559">about Estonia [music] and a country that</u>
  <u t="3050240">I really hope to go back soon. Number 29</u>
  <u t="3052400">is Latia. Just the next country down.</u>
  <u t="3055200">How do you say bye in Latia?</u>
  <u t="3059760">I think Latafia is super interesting.</u>
  <u t="3061280">There's a town called Sigula, which is</u>
  <u t="3063200">about 30 minutes outside Ria. It's like</u>
  <u t="3064800">a little resort town, like an outdoorsy</u>
  <u t="3066559">town, fancy town.</u>
  <u t="3067280">We're standing on top of this like 13th</u>
  <u t="3069359">century castle. And in about an hour,</u>
  <u t="3071920">we're going to bungee jump from this</u>
  <u t="3073440">high. [screaming]</u>
  <u t="3076000">And I have really great memories of</u>
  <u t="3077200">Latia. I also went to this really cool</u>
  <u t="3078800">lake. The capital, Ria, is another</u>
  <u t="3080640">really cool city. It's really historic.</u>
  <u t="3082559">There's beautiful castles like that one</u>
  <u t="3084160">that I'm walking around. There's a lot</u>
  <u t="3085839">of like cool bars there, cool</u>
  <u t="3087520">restaurants. The Baltics all blend</u>
  <u t="3089119">together kind of. So that's why they're</u>
  <u t="3090880">all kind of pushed in this in this</u>
  <u t="3092400">section of the video. But I have a lot</u>
  <u t="3093920">of friends from Latvia randomly. A girl</u>
  <u t="3095440">on my team named Annette is from Latvia.</u>
  <u t="3097280">She's awesome. How's life?</u>
  <u t="3099040">Ah, so peaceful and amazing.</u>
  <u t="3101280">And yeah, it's just nice to drive around</u>
  <u t="3102720">Lavia road trip in. It's just a really</u>
  <u t="3104480">cool place. I think you'll be pleasantly</u>
  <u t="3106160">surprised driving around the Baltics.</u>
  <u t="3108240">It's it's really clean, safe, and lots</u>
  <u t="3110880">going on. Which leads me to country</u>
  <u t="3112400">number 30, Lithuania.</u>
  <u t="3114000">It's about 38° outside, and we're going</u>
  <u t="3116079">to explore.</u>
  <u t="3118000">Lithuania is special to me because I am</u>
  <u t="3119760">Lithuanian. My great-grandmother came</u>
  <u t="3121520">from a little town where the Jews used</u>
  <u t="3123839">to live outside of Vius, which is a</u>
  <u t="3125359">capital. So, I actually went there and</u>
  <u t="3126800">found the synagogues and it was really,</u>
  <u t="3128160">really special. So, it has a soft place</u>
  <u t="3129680">in my heart. I did have a bad experience</u>
  <u t="3131119">in Lithuania one time trying to get the</u>
  <u t="3133119">Barus visa back in 2015 when Americans</u>
  <u t="3135440">needed visa. On the website, it says</u>
  <u t="3137119">express visa takes one day. I also</u>
  <u t="3139040">called them and they said it takes one</u>
  <u t="3140640">day, but she told me it takes 3 days for</u>
  <u t="3142240">me. And I asked her why and she pointed</u>
  <u t="3143839">to my passport and said I'm American. I</u>
  <u t="3145520">got denied and I had to go to Talian,</u>
  <u t="3147280">got denied and I finally picked it up in</u>
  <u t="3148720">Ria. So, I just had a really bad</u>
  <u t="3150240">experience at the embassy there. But</u>
  <u t="3151359">that's not a reason to hate the country.</u>
  <u t="3152559">Once again, Baltics region, these</u>
  <u t="3154640">countries are all right next to each</u>
  <u t="3155680">other. It's like Estonia, Lapia,</u>
  <u t="3156960">Lithuania, boom, boom, boom. You can't</u>
  <u t="3158720">really have a bad time there. I mean,</u>
  <u t="3160400">it's like one of those places where the</u>
  <u t="3161760">more you don't know, the better the</u>
  <u t="3163440">experience is. You just go with an open</u>
  <u t="3165200">mind, a willingness to learn, meet some</u>
  <u t="3166880">people, experience the culture, and</u>
  <u t="3168400">that's it. And it's just really, really,</u>
  <u t="3169839">really charming that way. I also</u>
  <u t="3171359">randomly have several Lithuanian friends</u>
  <u t="3173599">that I've met over the years. So that's</u>
  <u t="3175440">kind of cool. Hope to go back there</u>
  <u t="3176720">sometime soon and really get to explore</u>
  <u t="3178880">more not only of Villas, but of the</u>
  <u t="3180800">Jewish history there and just around the</u>
  <u t="3182559">country. It's easy to explore by car.</u>
  <u t="3184720">You're just like super quick. All right,</u>
  <u t="3186160">I'm going to pause here because I'm</u>
  <u t="3187440">about to travel to a nearby country for</u>
  <u t="3189760">a very special music festival that I</u>
  <u t="3192160">haven't been in 9 years and I'm going to</u>
  <u t="3194079">continue from there. See you shortly.</u>
  <u t="3197746">[cheering]</u>
  <u t="3199056">[music]</u>
  <u t="3199920">Number 31, Belgium.</u>
  <u t="3202640">I'm here at Tomorrowland, the most epic</u>
  <u t="3204559">music festival in the world. Look at</u>
  <u t="3206000">this. I'm standing on the back of the</u>
  <u t="3207440">main stage right now. Last time I was</u>
  <u t="3209119">here was in 2015, so it's been 9 years.</u>
  <u t="3212400">It's so epic to be back here. I love</u>
  <u t="3214400">Belgium because first of all, it's the</u>
  <u t="3216319">home of Tomorrowland. It's the coolest</u>
  <u t="3217680">place in the [music] world. Second of</u>
  <u t="3218960">all, you have many cool places like</u>
  <u t="3220720">Bruge, really historic.</u>
  <u t="3222240">Very cold. It's summer, but it's cold</u>
  <u t="3223599">here.</u>
  <u t="3224079">You have Brussels, which is a beautiful</u>
  <u t="3225599">capital city. You have Gent, which is</u>
  <u t="3227680">the Flemish speaking part of Belgium,</u>
  <u t="3229119">WHICH IS NOT FRENCH. They actually speak</u>
  <u t="3230559">Flemish, which is more like Dutch. And</u>
  <u t="3232079">everyone's super friendly and very</u>
  <u t="3233440">outgoing. It's an amazing place. Great</u>
  <u t="3235359">road trip country. You even have the</u>
  <u t="3236800">coastline if you want to go drive down</u>
  <u t="3238240">the coast. I mean, how could YOU GO</u>
  <u t="3239920">WRONG WITH BELGIAN WAFFLES, BELGIAN</u>
  <u t="3241599">CHOCOLATE, Belgian beer? It'sing</u>
  <u t="3243520">awesome. As I walk down this hill, I'm</u>
  <u t="3245440">going to continue telling you about</u>
  <u t="3246559">Belgium. And as we hear Lincoln Park in</u>
  <u t="3248800">the background, it's one of those places</u>
  <u t="3250160">where everybody speaks multiple</u>
  <u t="3251520">languages in this country because they</u>
  <u t="3253200">grow up learning English, French, Dutch,</u>
  <u t="3255280">German. It's so cool for that reason.</u>
  <u t="3258559">When you come here, you instantly feel</u>
  <u t="3259839">comfortable with the people. But I gotta</u>
  <u t="3261280">say, my favorite place in Belgium is</u>
  <u t="3262640">probably Bruge. It's like a beautiful,</u>
  <u t="3264480">perfect little charming town that you</u>
  <u t="3266240">could spend hours and hours walking</u>
  <u t="3267760">around and get lost in the side streets.</u>
  <u t="3269920">Oh man,</u>
  <u t="3271920">this is so cool. As we walk to the</u>
  <u t="3274319">center of the stage, I'm going to tell</u>
  <u t="3275440">you about number 32, Montenegro.</u>
  <u t="3278079">Montenegro is little Balkan country on</u>
  <u t="3280000">the coast. Very charming. Couture is a</u>
  <u t="3282160">beautiful city, very ancient. A lot of</u>
  <u t="3284000">CASTLES THERE. HI, DIANA. HOW ARE YOU</u>
  <u t="3286240">HAVING FUN? [music]</u>
  <u t="3288319">It's going to be really loud. I hope you</u>
  <u t="3289760">guys can hear me right now. The capital</u>
  <u t="3291359">of Ponita is okay. Kind of boring, but</u>
  <u t="3293680">there's some really cool towns, like</u>
  <u t="3295839">ancient towns on the coast of Montenegro</u>
  <u t="3297920">where you can like hang out with some</u>
  <u t="3299280">cool Europeans and just get a good vibe</u>
  <u t="3301280">like this.</u>
  <u t="3305040">It's cool to be surrounded by Europeans</u>
  <u t="3306880">here. Every everyone's super cool. My</u>
  <u t="3308800">favorite place in Montenegro is called</u>
  <u t="3310480">Peras. P E R A S T. There's like an</u>
  <u t="3313040">ancient little castle there. There's a</u>
  <u t="3314640">tennis court with a beautiful view of</u>
  <u t="3316400">the sea. Really good seafood over there.</u>
  <u t="3318559">It's also where NovakJokovic has a</u>
  <u t="3320400">second home or a fifth home. I really</u>
  <u t="3322240">hope you guys can hear me right now.</u>
  <u t="3323359">It's freaking loud. My first time in</u>
  <u t="3325040">Montenegro was 2012 when I was</u>
  <u t="3326800">hitchhiking there when I studied abroad.</u>
  <u t="3328480">I remember sleeping at a really dirty</u>
  <u t="3329760">hostel and hanging out with the</u>
  <u t="3330880">Montenegrid mafia. Crazy story which I'm</u>
  <u t="3333440">not going to get into right now. But</u>
  <u t="3334640">yeah, definitely give Montenegro a</u>
  <u t="3336079">chance. Hey,</u>
  <u t="3339040">what's up?</u>
  <u t="3339920">Hey, this is Gotham. You probably</u>
  <u t="3341040">recognize it from MY INDIA VIDEOS.</u>
  <u t="3343200">WHAT UP, BRO? RANDOM QUESTION JUST I'LL</u>
  <u t="3345760">explain it later. What do you think</u>
  <u t="3346800">about Montenegro? I love it. It's so</u>
  <u t="3348480">amazing. It's so so underrated. It's</u>
  <u t="3350559">like one of the best places I've been.</u>
  <u t="3351760">Unbelievable.</u>
  <u t="3353119">While I'm here, I'm going to tell you</u>
  <u t="3354160">about number 33, Fazia. And then I'm</u>
  <u t="3356400">going to go have fun because this place</u>
  <u t="3358000">is crazy. So Bosnia is another Balkan</u>
  <u t="3360400">country. You have Sieo, the capital</u>
  <u t="3362400">city, which is actually really</u>
  <u t="3363359">beautiful. It's a Muslim country along</u>
  <u t="3365040">with Kosovo and Albania.</u>
  <u t="3366400">So we're eating lunch here in Sievo, and</u>
  <u t="3369040">the call to prayer is going off.</u>
  <u t="3372559">There's a really beautiful city called</u>
  <u t="3374000">Postar, which is has a beautiful bridge.</u>
  <u t="3376160">It's like a medieval castle, like a</u>
  <u t="3377839">cobblestone street. It's super super</u>
  <u t="3379680">super beautiful there. The best food</u>
  <u t="3381599">there, which I also have in Spain. It's</u>
  <u t="3384240">a country I want to explore more of like</u>
  <u t="3385760">in the north. There's some different</u>
  <u t="3387200">places in Basio that seem amazing and I</u>
  <u t="3389520">really hope to get there. Okay, my voice</u>
  <u t="3390880">is going right now. I'm going to go have</u>
  <u t="3392160">some fun AND I'LL CATCH YOU GUYS AFTER</u>
  <u t="3393520">TOMORROWLAND for number 34.</u>
  <u t="3398079">All right, I am back in Antworp, the</u>
  <u t="3399760">nearest city to Tomorrowland. We are mid</u>
  <u t="3401599">festival and it's a great time to jump</u>
  <u t="3403200">into number 34, Albania. All right, we</u>
  <u t="3406480">have officially just entered Albania.</u>
  <u t="3408960">New country, babe.</u>
  <u t="3410319">Albania.</u>
  <u t="3411760">Albania is a strange place because in</u>
  <u t="3413839">the Balkans, but it's kind of like</u>
  <u t="3415200">Italian culture, but it's kind of like</u>
  <u t="3416799">Turkish culture. It's like all mixed</u>
  <u t="3418640">together. Turkish because it's a Muslim</u>
  <u t="3420319">country. It's one of three Muslim</u>
  <u t="3421359">countries in Europe, predominantly</u>
  <u t="3422880">Muslim. That is Italian because it's</u>
  <u t="3424720">right across the sea from Italy. And</u>
  <u t="3426799">you'll find a lot of coffee shops and</u>
  <u t="3428640">really like Italian vibes. And even some</u>
  <u t="3430640">people speak Italian in Albania. It's</u>
  <u t="3432079">really cool.</u>
  <u t="3434799">In the Balkans, you're next to</u>
  <u t="3435760">Montenegro, you're next near Serbia and</u>
  <u t="3437359">Kosovo and and Macedonia. So, it's a</u>
  <u t="3439599">really cool mix of places. In the north</u>
  <u t="3442000">of Albania, you have the mountains,</u>
  <u t="3443200">which I visited. It's awesome. There's a</u>
  <u t="3444799">town called Scoter. And if you go like 2</u>
  <u t="3446319">hours east of Schoer, I met these ladies</u>
  <u t="3448640">who are actually crossdressing as men,</u>
  <u t="3450319">but they're not trans, and they're</u>
  <u t="3451599">called Bernes. It's a super interesting</u>
  <u t="3453119">story.</u>
  <u t="3455040">You just hear just chopping wood in</u>
  <u t="3456960">half.</u>
  <u t="3460799">I'm not strong enough. Really?</u>
  <u t="3462369">[laughter]</u>
  <u t="3462880">It's just something deeply rooted in</u>
  <u t="3464079">Albanian culture because male's the</u>
  <u t="3465680">dominant figure of the family and if</u>
  <u t="3467119">there's no male figure in the family,</u>
  <u t="3468400">then they become male. Then you have</u>
  <u t="3469599">Toronto, the capital, which is just like</u>
  <u t="3470799">a bustling place.</u>
  <u t="3471599">It is so hot here. Holy. Walk into the</u>
  <u t="3474160">city center. I don't get run over by a</u>
  <u t="3475680">car.</u>
  <u t="3475920">And what's super interesting about</u>
  <u t="3476960">Albania is that there's all these</u>
  <u t="3478720">bunkers like the communist period from</u>
  <u t="3480799">like several decades ago. There's like</u>
  <u t="3482160">hundreds of thousands of bunkers around</u>
  <u t="3484160">the country and it would like there to</u>
  <u t="3485599">hide in case of war. It's really</u>
  <u t="3487119">interesting. A lot of them are</u>
  <u t="3488079">abandoned. Some of them have been turned</u>
  <u t="3489280">into hotels and art galleries and stuff.</u>
  <u t="3491280">Go ahead.</u>
  <u t="3492960">This is so cool. It's like an art</u>
  <u t="3494720">installation. [music]</u>
  <u t="3496880">This is a random bunker on the side of</u>
  <u t="3498559">the road. Actually, literally, there's a</u>
  <u t="3500000">gas station in front of me. So, we're</u>
  <u t="3501839">literally on the side of the road. I'm</u>
  <u t="3503280">going to go inside this one.</u>
  <u t="3507760">Wo. There's like a door here.</u>
  <u t="3511440">The fact that there's over a half a</u>
  <u t="3513280">million bunkers in this country freaking</u>
  <u t="3516079">blows my mind. So weird. Albanian people</u>
  <u t="3519119">are really warm and friendly and food is</u>
  <u t="3520960">good. And there's beaches in the south</u>
  <u t="3523280">which I really need to visit. Number 35,</u>
  <u t="3525920">Macedonia, or as they now call it, North</u>
  <u t="3527920">Macedonia. Another Balkan country. I got</u>
  <u t="3530079">to say, Scopier, the capital, is one of</u>
  <u t="3531839">the weirdest cities in the world.</u>
  <u t="3533200">There's all these statues, like really</u>
  <u t="3535440">nice looking realistic statues. All</u>
  <u t="3537440">along the banks of the river here, there</u>
  <u t="3538960">are like this bridge has like 50</u>
  <u t="3541280">statues, and then this walkway has</u>
  <u t="3543440">another 50. Statue, statue, statue,</u>
  <u t="3545680">statue, statue, statue, statue. Oh, and</u>
  <u t="3547440">the other bridge has statues. Look at</u>
  <u t="3548799">that. Statue, statue, statue, statue,</u>
  <u t="3550960">statue, statue, statue, statue, statue,</u>
  <u t="3552960">statue. It's a weird place. It's It's a</u>
  <u t="3554720">strange place. And I wonder if they took</u>
  <u t="3556640">all that money that they put on statues</u>
  <u t="3558000">and put it to something else. I don't</u>
  <u t="3559920">know how needed the statues are.</u>
  <u t="3561280">Anyways, the coolest lake in Europe is</u>
  <u t="3563200">called Oed. It's a really clear</u>
  <u t="3564720">freshwater lake. You can go diving in</u>
  <u t="3566319">it, cliff jumping, and just have a day</u>
  <u t="3568160">on the water. It's really, really</u>
  <u t="3569359">awesome. That was my favorite thing</u>
  <u t="3570319">about Macedonia by far. And overall,</u>
  <u t="3572000">it's just a really chill, cool, small</u>
  <u t="3573920">country. Easy to road trip, Balkan</u>
  <u t="3575680">vibes, good food. I highly recommend</u>
  <u t="3577440">Macedonia. I actually think it's super</u>
  <u t="3578960">underrated, and it's one of my favorite</u>
  <u t="3580559">Balkcon countries. I think I'm going to</u>
  <u t="3581760">be heading back there really soon. By</u>
  <u t="3583040">the way, how cool is this central train</u>
  <u t="3585119">station in [music] Anorp. It's one of</u>
  <u t="3586559">the oldest in Europe. This little square</u>
  <u t="3589280">here is very charming. Number 36,</u>
  <u t="3591440">Cypress.</u>
  <u t="3593371">[music]</u>
  <u t="3595440">So you have North Cypress, which is like</u>
  <u t="3597280">Turkish Cypress, and Southern Cypress,</u>
  <u t="3599200">which is Greek Cypress.</u>
  <u t="3601040">Right now I'm standing on the Greek side</u>
  <u t="3602640">of Cypress. Very different. There's a</u>
  <u t="3604640">border that splits between the two.</u>
  <u t="3606400">Could not be more wildly different. The</u>
  <u t="3607920">two different areas of Cypress. But</u>
  <u t="3609440">Cyprio people are amazing. The food is</u>
  <u t="3611200">great. It's a vacation spot for most</u>
  <u t="3612960">Europeans. They go there, they hang out,</u>
  <u t="3614720">there's beaches, there's wine.</u>
  <u t="3616240">Cheers.</u>
  <u t="3616799">Cheers.</u>
  <u t="3617520">But yeah, if you're in the southern</u>
  <u t="3618559">part, you're going to feel like you're</u>
  <u t="3619440">in Greece. And the northern part, you're</u>
  <u t="3620559">going to feel like you're in Turkey. I</u>
  <u t="3621920">mean like Muslims, they use Turkish LRA.</u>
  <u t="3624240">They don't drink alcohol in the north.</u>
  <u t="3626160">Well, at least not that much. There's a</u>
  <u t="3627760">cool castle in the north. It's called</u>
  <u t="3629040">Kyania. And then Nikicoia, the capital</u>
  <u t="3630960">city, is really cool. It's lined with</u>
  <u t="3632480">coffee shops. Everyone's like really</u>
  <u t="3634000">friendly and outgoing in Cypress. It's</u>
  <u t="3635680">really close to like Lebanon and Israel</u>
  <u t="3637760">and Palestine. It's just [music] like</u>
  <u t="3638880">right across the sea. It's it's</u>
  <u t="3640079">literally like a 20-minute flight. So,</u>
  <u t="3641680">it's it's just right there. But, it's in</u>
  <u t="3643040">the Mediterranean and it's a beautiful</u>
  <u t="3644240">spot. And if you're looking for a nice</u>
  <u t="3645520">vacation holiday, uh you want to</u>
  <u t="3647520">probably shouldn't get it by a car. You</u>
  <u t="3648880">want to just really have a nice time</u>
  <u t="3650640">under the sun, then uh I think Cypress</u>
  <u t="3652880">might be your answer. That leads me to</u>
  <u t="3654640">number 37, Malta.</u>
  <u t="3658000">Just woke up in Malta, my 90th country.</u>
  <u t="3660720">Really cool place. Betta, the capital</u>
  <u t="3662559">city. It's got crazy World War II</u>
  <u t="3664079">history. It's like Italy. It's very</u>
  <u t="3666000">similar to Italy, meaning there's really</u>
  <u t="3667280">good gelato and pizza, and the people</u>
  <u t="3668880">are really outgoing. And I found the sea</u>
  <u t="3670960">in Monta to be especially really clean</u>
  <u t="3673680">and blue with really nice beaches. And I</u>
  <u t="3676400">was kind of surprised by like the marine</u>
  <u t="3677839">life in in Malta. You wouldn't think of</u>
  <u t="3679520">it being something like Greece or or on</u>
  <u t="3681599">that caliber or on that level. But um</u>
  <u t="3683440">nice place, small island. Unfortunately,</u>
  <u t="3684960">I only got to visit Valleta and nearby</u>
  <u t="3686880">places by car. What's up, guys? I just</u>
  <u t="3688640">got off the boat in Valetta, the</u>
  <u t="3689920">southernmost capital city in Europe. And</u>
  <u t="3691920">I'm going to walk around this place.</u>
  <u t="3693280">Pretty cool so far. But I would like to</u>
  <u t="3695280">visit the other side of the island and</u>
  <u t="3697200">see more because Maltese people are</u>
  <u t="3699040">amazing, friendly. Yeah, that's all I</u>
  <u t="3701119">got to say for Malta. Number 38 is</u>
  <u t="3703359">Kosovo. We are just a few minutes away</u>
  <u t="3705599">from the border of Kosovo, which is</u>
  <u t="3708319">going to be amazing. Our 84th country</u>
  <u t="3710640">together. We got to add them up.</u>
  <u t="3711839">I know right off the bat all the</u>
  <u t="3713040">Serbians are going to comment and say</u>
  <u t="3714319">that Kosovo is not a country that's part</u>
  <u t="3715760">of Serbia. I don't care about politics.</u>
  <u t="3717280">I'm counting it as a country because a</u>
  <u t="3718720">lot of UN nations give it recognition</u>
  <u t="3720559">like the US.</u>
  <u t="3721359">The United States formally recognized</u>
  <u t="3723200">Kosovo as a sovereign and independent</u>
  <u t="3725440">nation.</u>
  <u t="3725839">Kosovo is awesome. It's very similar to</u>
  <u t="3727599">Serbian culture. It's Balkan. The</u>
  <u t="3728960">capital Pina is a cool place. There's a</u>
  <u t="3730559">lot going on there. Nice people. Prisen</u>
  <u t="3732799">is a hidden gem. It's on this beautiful</u>
  <u t="3735359">canal. The streets are amazing.</u>
  <u t="3737280">Everyone's like super super kind.</u>
  <u t="3739200">Where you from? Go. Dude, I'm so happy</u>
  <u t="3741040">to be here, man. This place is awesome.</u>
  <u t="3743280">You like me?</u>
  <u t="3744000">Yeah, bro.</u>
  <u t="3745119">In the people are beautiful there. I</u>
  <u t="3747280">think it's a UNESCO World Heritage site</u>
  <u t="3748799">for the history. There's an really nice</u>
  <u t="3750720">cobblestone bridge with coffee shops</u>
  <u t="3752640">lined up on it. This is an amazing view.</u>
  <u t="3754720">You have a castle here, the beautiful</u>
  <u t="3757040">old town of Prisan, and the historic</u>
  <u t="3759599">bridge. Wow. The nature is awesome.</u>
  <u t="3762079">There's like waterfalls around you.</u>
  <u t="3763760">There's trees. There's forests. There's</u>
  <u t="3765520">lakes. Kosovo is super underrated. But</u>
  <u t="3767520">if you do go there, be careful. You</u>
  <u t="3768640">cannot cross the border from Serbia.</u>
  <u t="3770160">They won't let you through. You have to</u>
  <u t="3771440">go through Albania. That's the best way</u>
  <u t="3772799">to get into Kosovo. It's another Muslim</u>
  <u t="3774480">majority country. So that's why Albania</u>
  <u t="3776160">and Kosovo get along. They speak the</u>
  <u t="3777839">same language and they basically are</u>
  <u t="3779119">very, very similar. The culture prayer</u>
  <u t="3780799">just came on, which is incredible here</u>
  <u t="3782319">in Kosovo. One of three countries in</u>
  <u t="3784960">Europe that is Muslim majority.</u>
  <u t="3789359">I know the Serbians are going to</u>
  <u t="3790400">disagree with me, so please take</u>
  <u t="3792079">everything with a grain of salt with an</u>
  <u t="3793599">American tourist bias. Number 39 is</u>
  <u t="3796559">Muldova. I actually really like Muldova</u>
  <u t="3799200">a lot. It's cool.</u>
  <u t="3800079">It's the greatest country in the world.</u>
  <u t="3801760">Kishnau is the capital. It's like the</u>
  <u t="3803599">least visited city and country in</u>
  <u t="3805200">Europe. No one really knows about it.</u>
  <u t="3806720">Very similar to Russian. They speak</u>
  <u t="3808000">Russian.</u>
  <u t="3810799">They look Russian. They act Russian, but</u>
  <u t="3812160">it's a weird mix of like kind of</u>
  <u t="3813599">European, a little bit Ukrainian vibes</u>
  <u t="3815359">cuz it's kind of sandwiched there on the</u>
  <u t="3816960">border. They have really good wine in</u>
  <u t="3818559">Muldova. There's a place called Or I'm</u>
  <u t="3820799">not pronouncing it right, but I went</u>
  <u t="3822000">down there for the winery tour and it</u>
  <u t="3823359">was fantastic.</u>
  <u t="3824160">Mut.</u>
  <u t="3824880">I baked all this fresh Mulovven bread.</u>
  <u t="3826640">The people were super nice. The</u>
  <u t="3827680">babushkas or the grandmothers were super</u>
  <u t="3829599">friendly and outgoing and willing to</u>
  <u t="3831200">help out. [music]</u>
  <u t="3833280">And yeah, Muldova is super interesting</u>
  <u t="3834720">and in fact I like it so much that I'm</u>
  <u t="3836319">planning to go back in a few weeks. In</u>
  <u t="3838240">this current Euro trip, I want to go</u>
  <u t="3839440">back to an unrecognized country called</u>
  <u t="3840880">Transnistria. But yeah, I think for me,</u>
  <u t="3842960">farther east you go, the more</u>
  <u t="3843920">interesting you get, the weirder it</u>
  <u t="3845440">gets, the more Soviet it feels, and</u>
  <u t="3847440">something that I hope to see more of cuz</u>
  <u t="3848640">I like different things and Moldov is</u>
  <u t="3850559">different. That leads me into country</u>
  <u t="3852079">number 40, Bellarus. I just went through</u>
  <u t="3854799">hell and back to get [music] a Bellarus</u>
  <u t="3857119">visa, but I got it. Similar to Muldova,</u>
  <u t="3861200">I mean, that Eastern Europe feel, the</u>
  <u t="3862960">Russia feel. The way Barus is different</u>
  <u t="3864720">is that it's a big place and it's way</u>
  <u t="3866559">more charming and beautiful. Minsk is</u>
  <u t="3868319">the capital. Just an awesome sunset</u>
  <u t="3870240">tonight in Minsk right outside my hotel</u>
  <u t="3872720">room.</u>
  <u t="3873119">I actually have blood that goes back to</u>
  <u t="3875119">Bellar Russian. So somehow I'm connected</u>
  <u t="3877280">to the culture there. A lot of former</u>
  <u t="3878720">Jews in Barus which is cool. Really nice</u>
  <u t="3880400">city. Minsk. Um unfortunately I only had</u>
  <u t="3882160">the chance to visit Minsk and it's such</u>
  <u t="3883520">a big country that I hope to see more</u>
  <u t="3884720">of. My friends recently went to Barus</u>
  <u t="3887039">and made an amazing story there and</u>
  <u t="3888240">really loved it. It's just like</u>
  <u t="3889920">unexpectedly charming. The buildings</u>
  <u t="3891839">feel like Disneyland cobblestone</u>
  <u t="3893359">streets. It's wildly inaffordable. You</u>
  <u t="3895760">would not believe the prices there. like</u>
  <u t="3897039">$3 for a 30-minute taxi ride, dollar for</u>
  <u t="3898960">a plate of food, which of course does</u>
  <u t="3900480">make it kind of nice uh when you can</u>
  <u t="3902240">save money. Nowadays, it's a little</u>
  <u t="3903520">trickier to get there with less flights</u>
  <u t="3905039">going in and with political tensions and</u>
  <u t="3906720">uprisings. But if you ever do get the</u>
  <u t="3908319">chance to visit Barus, I do think it</u>
  <u t="3909680">would be worth it. And it's really a</u>
  <u t="3911440">special country, special experience, and</u>
  <u t="3913039">something that you won't get elsewhere</u>
  <u t="3914240">because from my point of view, it's very</u>
  <u t="3916319">similar to Russia. But I actually really</u>
  <u t="3918160">like Russia. I think Russia is a cool</u>
  <u t="3919599">country. I think culturally and</u>
  <u t="3921839">cuisine-wise and historically, it's</u>
  <u t="3924000">fascinating. So definitely think it's</u>
  <u t="3925359">worth a try. But I think road tripping</u>
  <u t="3927039">outside of Minsk would be probably the</u>
  <u t="3928960">best option cuz it's a big country and</u>
  <u t="3930880">you don't know everything that's there.</u>
  <u t="3932160">So look forward to a video coming soon</u>
  <u t="3933920">from Barus.</u>
  <u t="3937250">[music]</u>
  <u t="3938160">I've just made it to country number 41.</u>
  <u t="3940400">Can you guess what it is?</u>
  <u t="3942799">France.</u>
  <u t="3948559">You might be wondering why it's so low</u>
  <u t="3950160">on this list. And well, I just got to</u>
  <u t="3952160">say I haven't had the best times in this</u>
  <u t="3953680">country. This is my second time in</u>
  <u t="3955039">Paris. My first time around, I didn't</u>
  <u t="3956720">love it so much. I thought the people</u>
  <u t="3957839">were snobby. I thought it was really</u>
  <u t="3959039">dirty. My wife Deanna got pickpocketed</u>
  <u t="3960960">here pretty bad. Was not a good</u>
  <u t="3962480">situation. I don't know. I just felt</u>
  <u t="3963839">like overall wasn't a city that I</u>
  <u t="3965200">connected with. I also went to Ruan in</u>
  <u t="3967039">the west. I went to Nice in the south,</u>
  <u t="3968799">which was amazing. And I went to Leon,</u>
  <u t="3971599">which wasn't so special. But I'm here</u>
  <u t="3973119">again for the Olympics, which is</u>
  <u t="3974319">happening right now. There's actually</u>
  <u t="3975440">events taking place in this moment</u>
  <u t="3976880">around me. I'm here for a few days. I'm</u>
  <u t="3978640">already loving it a lot more this time</u>
  <u t="3980160">around. I met my buddy Thomas from Yes</u>
  <u t="3982319">Theory last night. He's a good friend of</u>
  <u t="3983599">mine. And I'm sure a lot of you guys</u>
  <u t="3984480">know who he is. He's currently living</u>
  <u t="3985680">here and took me around his neighborhood</u>
  <u t="3987039">and it was fantastic. And I'm feeling</u>
  <u t="3989039">the vibes a little bit better now this</u>
  <u t="3990480">time around. I think what's really going</u>
  <u t="3991920">to convince me into being a France lover</u>
  <u t="3993920">is the nature. So there's amazing</u>
  <u t="3995839">beaches in the west and in the north</u>
  <u t="3997039">that I have not been to. There's amazing</u>
  <u t="3998720">mountains, the French Alps, there's</u>
  <u t="4000160">skiing. There's a lot going on in terms</u>
  <u t="4002000">of nature here that I haven't</u>
  <u t="4003440">experienced. I also haven't been to the</u>
  <u t="4004720">small villages and stuff which I know</u>
  <u t="4006799">are incredible. So I think I'm going to</u>
  <u t="4008240">like France more and it's going to creep</u>
  <u t="4009520">up the rankings. And I know that putting</u>
  <u t="4011119">it at number 41 is going to make a lot</u>
  <u t="4012559">of you guys upset. And please, I would</u>
  <u t="4014079">love to hear your thoughts. If you think</u>
  <u t="4015200">France is amazing, let me know. It is</u>
  <u t="4016720">true that the people aren't that</u>
  <u t="4017839">friendly and warm and open. If you speak</u>
  <u t="4019680">to them in English, they just kind of</u>
  <u t="4021039">like look at you and like, who's this</u>
  <u t="4022400">guy? It it is true. Like in most of the</u>
  <u t="4024240">cafes here, the cafe culture is really</u>
  <u t="4026160">cool. Everyone's sitting on chairs,</u>
  <u t="4027839">having to [music] smoke, drinking</u>
  <u t="4029119">coffee, and just looking out on the</u>
  <u t="4030640">street, which I think is awesome. It's</u>
  <u t="4032000">obviously historic here. I don't know.</u>
  <u t="4033280">It's a place I'm definitely going to</u>
  <u t="4034319">continue exploring. And as I'm at these</u>
  <u t="4035839">Olympic events here, I'm going to</u>
  <u t="4037466">[music] keep riffing off some of the</u>
  <u t="4038960">next countries because why not? Let's do</u>
  <u t="4041280">it. Country number 42 is Armenia. Kind</u>
  <u t="4044720">of stuck in between Asia and Europe, but</u>
  <u t="4046559">of course, I'm going to call it [music]</u>
  <u t="4047359">Europe for this video cuz I want to talk</u>
  <u t="4048799">about it. I only went to Dilly Jan,</u>
  <u t="4050400">which is a resort town in the central</u>
  <u t="4052160">north. I crossed the land border from</u>
  <u t="4053920">Georgia. It was pretty cool. I took a</u>
  <u t="4055520">marsha, which is like a public van bus</u>
  <u t="4057839">thing over the border. Hello everyone.</u>
  <u t="4059839">So, I made it to Armenia, this little</u>
  <u t="4062079">town in the mountains, and so far it's</u>
  <u t="4064400">pretty sweet.</u>
  <u t="4064960">I had a pretty good time in Dilly John,</u>
  <u t="4066559">to be honest. But I think in a few</u>
  <u t="4068559">weeks, I'm [music] going to cross the</u>
  <u t="4069599">land border from Iran into Armenia and</u>
  <u t="4071839">spend more time going from south to</u>
  <u t="4073280">north in Armenia. It's a country that I</u>
  <u t="4074799">feel like I really want to see more. I</u>
  <u t="4076240">thought the people were really friendly.</u>
  <u t="4077680">The culture is super interesting. It's</u>
  <u t="4079280">really hated by its neighbors of Turkey.</u>
  <u t="4080960">There have been genocides and millions</u>
  <u t="4082400">of Armenians have been killed, but they</u>
  <u t="4084000">have a strong presence around the world.</u>
  <u t="4085280">I've seen Armenian quarters all over the</u>
  <u t="4086960">place. The food's really good. It's just</u>
  <u t="4088960">a country I didn't get to see enough of</u>
  <u t="4090319">and I feel like I will love it a lot</u>
  <u t="4092000">more when I go back and so stay tuned</u>
  <u t="4093520">for more content coming [music] soon</u>
  <u t="4094720">from Armenia. Number 43 is Finland.</u>
  <u t="4098640">Probably my least favorite Scandinavian</u>
  <u t="4100400">country just because I was only in</u>
  <u t="4101679">Helsinki and Helsinki I found to be</u>
  <u t="4103359">really expensive and boring, but I know</u>
  <u t="4104719">that's not a reason to judge a whole</u>
  <u t="4106239">country because Finland goes way farther</u>
  <u t="4108000">north than Helsinki. I really want to go</u>
  <u t="4109759">to Lapland in the north. I want to go to</u>
  <u t="4112080">the Arctic Circle. I want to see the</u>
  <u t="4113759">communities up there. I want to see</u>
  <u t="4114880">reindeers and I think there's even polar</u>
  <u t="4116560">bears way up north. There's definitely</u>
  <u t="4118000">the northern lights. So, I definitely</u>
  <u t="4119279">got to give Finland another chance. But</u>
  <u t="4120880">if I'm going [music] to compare it to</u>
  <u t="4121920">Sweden or Denmark or Iceland or even</u>
  <u t="4124239">Norway, I got to say I'd rank Finland at</u>
  <u t="4126560">the bottom. The coolest part about</u>
  <u t="4127600">Helsinki was taking the boat over to</u>
  <u t="4129199">Talin Estonia, which I've already told</u>
  <u t="4130640">you about, and that was amazing. But</u>
  <u t="4132239">that was leaving Finland. I ate reindeer</u>
  <u t="4134319">there. It was pretty good. I was young</u>
  <u t="4135920">and naive also, but I'm looking forward</u>
  <u t="4137600">to going back to Finland. Uh maybe this</u>
  <u t="4139839">summer while I'm in Europe and and</u>
  <u t="4141120">hopefully able to experience more</u>
  <u t="4142719">Finnish hospitality and culture and food</u>
  <u t="4145040">and and yeah. Damn, that building is</u>
  <u t="4147679">stunning. Can you guys see that? Damn.</u>
  <u t="4151199">That takes us to number 44, Likenstein.</u>
  <u t="4154000">So, as we're walking here on beautiful</u>
  <u t="4155440">Shams, Diana's favorite street in the</u>
  <u t="4157600">world. We're going to tell you about</u>
  <u t="4158560">Likenstein. I've been twice, but I took</u>
  <u t="4160239">Diana last time</u>
  <u t="4161199">with our dog.</u>
  <u t="4161839">With our dog. I actually walked across</u>
  <u t="4163600">the country. I spent 8 hours like</u>
  <u t="4165520">walking by foot for a video, which was</u>
  <u t="4167520">really interesting. What did you think</u>
  <u t="4168640">about Likran?</u>
  <u t="4169359">To be honest, it's actually a cute</u>
  <u t="4171199">little city or I mean country. It's kind</u>
  <u t="4174480">of like if you get tired of Paris, like</u>
  <u t="4176719">people would move there.</u>
  <u t="4178560">It has more like a retirement vibe.</u>
  <u t="4180560">It's really relaxed, laidback. A lot of</u>
  <u t="4182080">old people.</u>
  <u t="4182560">Older people.</u>
  <u t="4184000">And we actually went shopping. You</u>
  <u t="4185359">bought some on shoes there.</u>
  <u t="4186719">Yes.</u>
  <u t="4187120">Right.</u>
  <u t="4187600">And what I love about there are like</u>
  <u t="4189520">hole in the wall like cafes. Remember we</u>
  <u t="4192080">sat in like one.</u>
  <u t="4193359">Yeah. It's it's it's quaint. It's</u>
  <u t="4195040">European. Bad is the capital. There's a</u>
  <u t="4197199">nice church there, but I got to be</u>
  <u t="4198480">honest, it's a little boring.</u>
  <u t="4199679">Uh, it's a little boring in our age, but</u>
  <u t="4201679">I feel like if you are in your 60s, 70s,</u>
  <u t="4205840">that's the beautiful.</u>
  <u t="4206560">We did take our dog there and he loved</u>
  <u t="4207920">it because it's clean and it's also</u>
  <u t="4209840">super expensive in Likenstein. It's</u>
  <u t="4211600">similar to Switzerland because it's</u>
  <u t="4212719">right next to Switzerland, so there's a</u>
  <u t="4214159">lot of crossover between culture,</u>
  <u t="4216159">language,</u>
  <u t="4216800">but I think it has a way nicer vibe than</u>
  <u t="4218719">Luxembourg.</u>
  <u t="4219840">Yes. Which is coming up later on the</u>
  <u t="4222080">list. Next is number 45, San Marino.</u>
  <u t="4226800">6:30 a.m. and just arrived in San</u>
  <u t="4228880">Marino, my 91st country. San Marino is a</u>
  <u t="4232320">tiny little country within Italy. And</u>
  <u t="4234400">the reason it's so low on this list is</u>
  <u t="4235760">just cuz of lack of things to do.</u>
  <u t="4237040">There's a nice cable car that you can</u>
  <u t="4238239">take to get some views. I recommend</u>
  <u t="4239520">going at night cuz then you can see on</u>
  <u t="4240960">top of the hill all the lights of San</u>
  <u t="4242400">Marino. But I don't know, it's basically</u>
  <u t="4244480">Italy to me. But they're very proud of</u>
  <u t="4246000">San Marino. They have their own flags</u>
  <u t="4247360">everywhere. I don't really have much</u>
  <u t="4248560">else to say about San Marino other than</u>
  <u t="4250080">I'm going to take Diana there at some</u>
  <u t="4251360">point because she's sitting at 96</u>
  <u t="4252960">countries right now. So, we're trying to</u>
  <u t="4254640">get her to 100. Pretty impressive. Are</u>
  <u t="4256480">you excited for San Marino?</u>
  <u t="4257920">Very excited.</u>
  <u t="4258480">So, we'll circle back with more San</u>
  <u t="4259840">Marino tips after Diana's there.</u>
  <u t="4261520">What are What are they?</u>
  <u t="4262560">There's not much going on there. It's</u>
  <u t="4263520">like there's like a little walkway.</u>
  <u t="4264640">Yeah. So, are they being like claimed by</u>
  <u t="4266320">other countries?</u>
  <u t="4266960">No, no, no. It's it's it's an</u>
  <u t="4268159">independent country within Italy. All</u>
  <u t="4269679">right, that's it for San Marino. Number</u>
  <u t="4271600">46 is Azeraijan.</u>
  <u t="4273520">Today, I'm going to take you around</u>
  <u t="4274560">Baku.</u>
  <u t="4275120">It is a country in between Asia and</u>
  <u t="4277120">Europe. It's in the Kcastus regions, but</u>
  <u t="4279040">for the purposes of this story, we're</u>
  <u t="4280320">going to include it in Europe.</u>
  <u t="4282400">Baku is the capital city and it's kind</u>
  <u t="4284239">of stuck in between a wannabe Dubai with</u>
  <u t="4286400">all these like modern cool buildings,</u>
  <u t="4287920">fancy shopping malls with this like Ooh,</u>
  <u t="4290480">you want to get a macaroon? Let's get</u>
  <u t="4291920">some pistachio ones. While we're getting</u>
  <u t="4294000">some macaroons,</u>
  <u t="4295920">I will say that the culture is kind of</u>
  <u t="4297679">stuck in between Central Asia and Iran.</u>
  <u t="4299360">So, you get these like Silk Road vibes,</u>
  <u t="4301280">these like Middle Eastern feels a little</u>
  <u t="4302719">bit. It is a majority Muslim country.</u>
  <u t="4304560">People are generally really friendly</u>
  <u t="4306400">there and they're really shocked to see</u>
  <u t="4307600">tourists because most tourists don't go</u>
  <u t="4309120">there. I only went to Baku,</u>
  <u t="4310560">unfortunately. I wish that I went to</u>
  <u t="4312239">more places in Azarbai and I'm actually</u>
  <u t="4313679">hoping to go back soon so I can visit</u>
  <u t="4315040">more places. I just remembered that</u>
  <u t="4316239">Azerbaijan was actually my hundth</u>
  <u t="4317760">country that I ever visited so I have a</u>
  <u t="4319120">cool picture sitting in the lawn with</u>
  <u t="4320560">this funky looking building behind me</u>
  <u t="4321920">holding up a sign that says 100 like</u>
  <u t="4323679">Will Chamberlain when he got 100 points</u>
  <u t="4325199">in a game.</u>
  <u t="4326000">100 countries feels great, man. Let me</u>
  <u t="4328159">tell you.</u>
  <u t="4328560">Let's get two of each. Two blue, two</u>
  <u t="4330159">pistachio.</u>
  <u t="4330719">And then I I don't want the roast. I</u>
  <u t="4332159">want like this one.</u>
  <u t="4333199">What else about Azerbaian? Um there's a</u>
  <u t="4335040">cool fortress in the old town there.</u>
  <u t="4336560">They have really good kebabs. Shisha.</u>
  <u t="4338320">That's about all I got for Azerbaijan.</u>
  <u t="4340239">By the way, don't you love Diana's hat?</u>
  <u t="4342239">She looks very Parisian.</u>
  <u t="4345679">Number 47 is Monaco, a place that Diana</u>
  <u t="4348400">actually wants to go.</u>
  <u t="4349600">Can we do take out here?</u>
  <u t="4352719">Inside. Okay.</u>
  <u t="4357040">Hi. Can we get a box, please, of like</u>
  <u t="4359120">different kinds?</u>
  <u t="4362640">Wa. Okay.</u>
  <u t="4363920">Oh, we got the cookie one.</u>
  <u t="4366640">M. Okay.</u>
  <u t="4368480">Good.</u>
  <u t="4368960">Worth the end. Okay.</u>
  <u t="4371040">All right. Back to Monaco after spending</u>
  <u t="4374560">$60 on an ice cream cookie.</u>
  <u t="4376480">That's a scam because you pay for the</u>
  <u t="4378239">bag</u>
  <u t="4378640">and eight macaroons. Okay.</u>
  <u t="4380320">All right. Just got to Monaco. [music]</u>
  <u t="4385679">Diana, what do you know about Monaco?</u>
  <u t="4387520">Why do you want to go there?</u>
  <u t="4388239">Rich people are there.</u>
  <u t="4389280">Yeah, she's right. Rich people are</u>
  <u t="4390719">there. Also, yeah, there's like famous</u>
  <u t="4392640">car racings there, good restaurants,</u>
  <u t="4395040">but like this is one country that I</u>
  <u t="4396480">spent like 15 hours in. and I walked all</u>
  <u t="4398239">around the country and then I left.</u>
  <u t="4399440">Actually didn't sleep in Monaco.</u>
  <u t="4400640">How much is a hotel there?</u>
  <u t="4401920">Super expensive. A lot of people have</u>
  <u t="4403360">their yachts and sailboats. It's right</u>
  <u t="4404960">on the sea. It's on the southern coast</u>
  <u t="4406080">of France. It's a dream vacation for</u>
  <u t="4407760">rich people. But if you aren't rich,</u>
  <u t="4410400">then you're going to be spending $60 for</u>
  <u t="4412400">macaroons like we just did.</u>
  <u t="4413920">If you're rich, just look at the rich.</u>
  <u t="4415520">True. It's a very aspiring place to go</u>
  <u t="4417199">if you have money. Look at the juice</u>
  <u t="4418560">inside of this.</u>
  <u t="4423760">Unfortunately for Monaco and all the</u>
  <u t="4425840">countries here in the lower part of my</u>
  <u t="4427120">list, I don't have too much content from</u>
  <u t="4429040">there because I went like 10 years ago</u>
  <u t="4430800">and I haven't returned. So that's why</u>
  <u t="4432239">we're just flashing photos and some</u>
  <u t="4434560">other random B-roll shots that we find.</u>
  <u t="4436320">But yeah, Monaco kind of boring. While</u>
  <u t="4439920">I'm standing here in front of the</u>
  <u t="4440960">beautiful Aka Triumph, we're going to</u>
  <u t="4443040">talk about country number 48, Andor. And</u>
  <u t="4446320">Pandora is actually near France, in</u>
  <u t="4448400">between France and Spain. and it's</u>
  <u t="4449600">nestled in between and it's really a</u>
  <u t="4451120">nature's lovers paradise. So if you like</u>
  <u t="4452880">nature, you should go. There's</u>
  <u t="4454080">mountains, there's skiing, there's all</u>
  <u t="4455440">kinds of cool things there. For me, I</u>
  <u t="4456719">found it really boring. The biggest</u>
  <u t="4457920">highlight of Andor for me was the main</u>
  <u t="4459440">shopping street with all the pedestrians</u>
  <u t="4460880">and the McDonald's, which I ate at which</u>
  <u t="4462560">was pretty interesting.</u>
  <u t="4463440">McDonald's and Andor,</u>
  <u t="4466400">I can't really say much more about Andor</u>
  <u t="4468560">just because it's so boring. There's a</u>
  <u t="4470400">couple monuments, there's a couple</u>
  <u t="4472400">little fountains. [music] It's charming.</u>
  <u t="4474080">It is nice. Like if you're in your older</u>
  <u t="4475600">age and you want to retire or you want</u>
  <u t="4477040">to go on a ski trip, then you should</u>
  <u t="4478400">definitely go to Andor. But if you're a</u>
  <u t="4480000">backpacker or a budget traveler or just</u>
  <u t="4481840">someone who's looking for culture, then</u>
  <u t="4483280">Andor is probably a country that you can</u>
  <u t="4485360">skip. And if you think I'm wrong or if</u>
  <u t="4487040">you disagree, please let me know in the</u>
  <u t="4488159">comments down below. That's kind of the</u>
  <u t="4489360">reason why I'm making this video is to</u>
  <u t="4490880">share my opinions and to also hear yours</u>
  <u t="4492880">as well. All right, that takes me into</u>
  <u t="4494320">country number 49, Luxembourg. As you</u>
  <u t="4497360">can imagine, it's low on this list</u>
  <u t="4498960">because I also find it boring and</u>
  <u t="4500480">expensive. like Latinstein, like San</u>
  <u t="4502400">Marino, like Monaco. There's just these</u>
  <u t="4504400">small city states within Europe, these</u>
  <u t="4506080">small countries that are just not so</u>
  <u t="4508560">filled with culture. For travelers, I</u>
  <u t="4510400">just think they're boring. And</u>
  <u t="4511199">Luxembourg is one of them. I remember</u>
  <u t="4512640">going there when I was 23 and I got a</u>
  <u t="4514719">$15 beer for like a half a liter of</u>
  <u t="4517120">beer. And I was coming from Prague at</u>
  <u t="4518560">the time where a half a liter of beer</u>
  <u t="4520159">was like $3. So I couldn't believe how</u>
  <u t="4522640">expensive it was in Luxembourg. It's</u>
  <u t="4524239">manageable. It's cool to walk around.</u>
  <u t="4525679">There's a cool fortress in the downtown</u>
  <u t="4527440">Luxembourg.</u>
  <u t="4528239">Awesome view of the old city. People are</u>
  <u t="4530560">friendly. They speak English. There's</u>
  <u t="4532000">actually a language called</u>
  <u t="4532800">Luxembburggish. And I have a buddy who</u>
  <u t="4534880">speaks eight languages fluently. He's</u>
  <u t="4536640">from Luxembourg. So, I feel like the</u>
  <u t="4538000">people there are really well educated</u>
  <u t="4539360">and really smart and really cultured</u>
  <u t="4541120">because they're surrounded by so many</u>
  <u t="4542239">other countries. But, I don't know, not</u>
  <u t="4543679">the most exciting place in the world if</u>
  <u t="4545040">you ask me. And that leads me to the</u>
  <u t="4546800">final country on this list, number 50.</u>
  <u t="4549440">Can you guess what it is? It is the</u>
  <u t="4551520">Vatican City. The smallest country in</u>
  <u t="4553440">the world with a population of around</u>
  <u t="4554960">800 residents.</u>
  <u t="4557600">Yes, they do have their own passports.</u>
  <u t="4558880">They have their own flag. They have</u>
  <u t="4559840">their own currency. It is within Rome,</u>
  <u t="4562480">but it is an independent country. They</u>
  <u t="4564400">have a seat in the UN.</u>
  <u t="4565600">Good morning from the Vatican City, that</u>
  <u t="4567840">new country.</u>
  <u t="4568800">This is really cool.</u>
  <u t="4569600">It's amazing. I love the monuments</u>
  <u t="4572480">there. Like, it's it's fascinating. Like</u>
  <u t="4574400">the home of the Pope. [music] You have</u>
  <u t="4575600">the amazing St. Peter's Basilica. It's</u>
  <u t="4577920">one of the most historical places in the</u>
  <u t="4579760">world for Catholicism, for just</u>
  <u t="4581679">incredible history.</u>
  <u t="4582800">Right now, you're going to get a glimpse</u>
  <u t="4583920">of the greatest Christian church in the</u>
  <u t="4585760">world. I'm standing inside the world's</u>
  <u t="4587840">biggest basilica here in the Vatican</u>
  <u t="4589679">City, St. Peter's Basilica. These are</u>
  <u t="4592560">all handdone mosaics, not paintings. It</u>
  <u t="4595760">is just spectacular in here. It's just</u>
  <u t="4598239">so beautiful. Wow. But it's so small.</u>
  <u t="4601440">There's no hotels there, so it's</u>
  <u t="4602640">impossible to stay overnight. And if you</u>
  <u t="4603840">try to sleep on the street like my</u>
  <u t="4604960">friend did, you'll get arrested. And</u>
  <u t="4606480">it's a place that you just visit for a</u>
  <u t="4608000">few hours. The lines are so brutal. So,</u>
  <u t="4610719">please go early or buy the fastpass</u>
  <u t="4612320">tickets if you're going to take a tour.</u>
  <u t="4613520">But yeah, I just think that the Vatican</u>
  <u t="4615440">is great to visit once and then once you</u>
  <u t="4618080">see it, it's like the Grand Canyon. It's</u>
  <u t="4619760">amazing to visit once. I love it. And</u>
  <u t="4621199">I'm from Arizona, but once you go once,</u>
  <u t="4623040">you don't really have to go again. So,</u>
  <u t="4624640">that's kind of my thoughts. But, thank</u>
  <u t="4626080">you so much for watching this video. I</u>
  <u t="4627520">really appreciate it if you made it all</u>
  <u t="4628640">the way to the end. I applaud you. This</u>
  <u t="4630480">video is based solely on my own personal</u>
  <u t="4632239">travel experiences after visiting every</u>
  <u t="4633840">country in Europe, most of them three or</u>
  <u t="4635280">more times. Would love to hear from you</u>
  <u t="4636560">guys in the comments down below if you</u>
  <u t="4637760">agree or disagree with my list. [music]</u>
  <u t="4639840">What would you rank higher? What would</u>
  <u t="4640880">you rank lower? Let me know in the</u>
  <u t="4642080">comments down below. Cheers from Paris.</u>
  <u t="4643840">I'm gonna go get some amazing dinner</u>
  <u t="4644960">tonight in Paris and I'll see you guys</u>
  <u t="4646640">later. Peace. Awa.</u>
  <u t="4664308">[music]</u>
  </text>
