<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="zkmKoQ5992c" uploader="kimincoree" channel="kimincoree" likes="12" title="I Went to Korea 🇰🇷 and Everything Got Weird 😆 (in the Best Way 💕)" year="2025" month="05" day="21" is_ac="true">
  <u t="80">I was mortified. So why naked? This</u>
  <u t="2000">mystery man. Why is this? Because yeah,</u>
  <u t="3200">it actually feels</u>
  <u t="4510">[Music]</u>
  <u t="5879">great. Hi, this is Kimmy Park from Kim</u>
  <u t="8639">Kore. And today we are going to talk</u>
  <u t="10400">about my first times in Korea because a</u>
  <u t="12880">few years ago I had no idea what kimchi</u>
  <u t="14639">was. I was not listening to K-pop. I had</u>
  <u t="17600">no interest in Korea really. But</u>
  <u t="19920">everything changed with one single trip.</u>
  <u t="22160">So let me take you on the journey of my</u>
  <u t="23840">first in Korea. From the first bite of</u>
  <u t="26240">kimchi on the plane to getting naked</u>
  <u t="28800">among stranger in Korea to finding my</u>
  <u t="31279">Korean name and reappropriating my</u>
  <u t="33040">Korean</u>
  <u t="35660">[Music]</u>
  <u t="38200">identity. So before 2016 and my first</u>
  <u t="41200">trip to Korea, I had really no idea</u>
  <u t="43840">about Korea. Like I knew that my mom was</u>
  <u t="46399">from there and had been adopted, but I</u>
  <u t="48559">grew up in France where Korea was not</u>
  <u t="50719">popular at the time. And yeah, so I knew</u>
  <u t="52640">very little. But when that friend went</u>
  <u t="54719">to do a year abroad in Korea, I decided</u>
  <u t="56559">it was time for me to go and in 2016 I</u>
  <u t="60480">went on the plane and went to Korea for</u>
  <u t="62960">the first time. My first biggest</u>
  <u t="64720">impression of Korea was in the subway.</u>
  <u t="68159">Actually, was the first word I learned</u>
  <u t="70560">in Korea because I knew and when I</u>
  <u t="74080">arrived, I couldn't pronounce them that</u>
  <u t="75600">well at the time, but was actually the</u>
  <u t="78400">first word I learned on the day of my</u>
  <u t="80960">arrival in Korea. Anyway, I was very</u>
  <u t="83680">impressed by how the diat the subway is</u>
  <u t="86400">very clean. It's very calm, how people</u>
  <u t="88960">are sleeping on it because in France, no</u>
  <u t="91280">one sleeps in a train really because</u>
  <u t="92799">otherwise they're going to steal your</u>
  <u t="93920">stuff. And I had a lots of fun doing all</u>
  <u t="95600">the tourist stuff like exploring</u>
  <u t="96799">palaces, doing a tea ceremony, going</u>
  <u t="98960">hiking in the mountain where we actually</u>
  <u t="100799">met some military guys that were there</u>
  <u t="102240">and I was like, why is the military in a</u>
  <u t="103840">mountain? I don't know. But one of them</u>
  <u t="106240">was called Kim cuz it was written on his</u>
  <u t="108000">tag and I was like, oh my god, your name</u>
  <u t="109439">is Kim like me. Uh because at the time I</u>
  <u t="111920">actually also didn't know that Kim is a</u>
  <u t="113680">super common last name um in Korea. And</u>
  <u t="116799">that's when I realized that me being</u>
  <u t="118159">called Kim and telling them, "Oh, my</u>
  <u t="119600">name is Kim." And they're like, "Okay,</u>
  <u t="121280">but when then what's your first name?" I</u>
  <u t="123360">realized that mistake that my mom made</u>
  <u t="125920">when I was born and she wanted to call</u>
  <u t="127840">me by your Korean name. And so she</u>
  <u t="129280">called me Kim because she thought that</u>
  <u t="131280">was a first name. And yeah, but we'll</u>
  <u t="134000">come back to my name later in number 10.</u>
  <u t="136640">So stay tuned.</u>
  <u t="138560">So yeah, great transportation, beautiful</u>
  <u t="141360">palaces and nature, the city lights,</u>
  <u t="143760">like it was the other thing like going</u>
  <u t="146400">at night outside and all these tall</u>
  <u t="148239">building with so many lights. And I</u>
  <u t="149760">remember going especially in Maong to do</u>
  <u t="151520">loads of shopping. I'd never done so</u>
  <u t="153440">much shopping in my life. Everything was</u>
  <u t="154720">so cheap. Like all the clothes were like</u>
  <u t="156160">so cool and affordable. And yeah, I</u>
  <u t="159280">really really had a blast. And I've been</u>
  <u t="160879">back several times to Korea since. I've</u>
  <u t="162800">lived in Korea as well. But yeah, that</u>
  <u t="165120">first impression of calm, beauty,</u>
  <u t="167959">business,</u>
  <u t="169640">lights, and</u>
  <u t="171879">shopping. Now, the other major thing</u>
  <u t="173920">that happened to me on this trip and in</u>
  <u t="175599">my life really is that during this first</u>
  <u t="177680">trip to Korea, I've reconnected with my</u>
  <u t="180080">adopted mother's family whom I found</u>
  <u t="183040">only a few weeks before going on this</u>
  <u t="185280">trip. It was not really planned, but it</u>
  <u t="187440">happened. It's a story for another video</u>
  <u t="189120">because it's way too long. We</u>
  <u t="190720">reconnected. We met for the first time.</u>
  <u t="193040">This is a reason why I continued to go</u>
  <u t="195440">in Korea after this trip. Even though</u>
  <u t="198000">they were still strangers for me, but we</u>
  <u t="201360">were to become very close over the next</u>
  <u t="203280">few trips and few meetings that</u>
  <u t="205840">happened. And it was a wonderful moment</u>
  <u t="208159">full of bittersweet emotions because we</u>
  <u t="210319">had to talk about a lot of difficult</u>
  <u t="211920">topics. But also there was this joy to</u>
  <u t="214400">have found each other. And it took a few</u>
  <u t="216720">years for us to really become close. But</u>
  <u t="219120">yeah, like now they really are my family</u>
  <u t="222319">and I love them so much. And um this is</u>
  <u t="224879">why this whole Korean journey, including</u>
  <u t="227440">this first journey, are so important to</u>
  <u t="230050">[Music]</u>
  <u t="233879">me. Now, the other thing I didn't</u>
  <u t="235920">mention before was the food. So, Korean</u>
  <u t="238319">food was a great mystery to me. I had no</u>
  <u t="241280">idea what Korean food was, and I was not</u>
  <u t="244000">very familiar with Asian food in</u>
  <u t="245519">general. Like for me, Asian food was</u>
  <u t="247360">Japanese</u>
  <u t="248519">sushi. Yeah, I know. And my first</u>
  <u t="251200">memorable encounter with Korean food was</u>
  <u t="253120">actually on the plane from Europe to</u>
  <u t="255599">Soul because Air France was serving a</u>
  <u t="258000">Korean meal. So, I had a bin even though</u>
  <u t="260239">I had no idea what it was at the time.</u>
  <u t="261680">And there was a little red box next to</u>
  <u t="263360">it, which I ate after finishing all the</u>
  <u t="266400">rest of my food. And I ate it. I just</u>
  <u t="268320">like opened it and took the whole thing</u>
  <u t="269759">and put it in my mouth at once. And</u>
  <u t="271440">after I was like, "Oh my god, what is</u>
  <u t="272960">this? It tastes weird. It's spicy. It's</u>
  <u t="277360">what is this? And at that and at that</u>
  <u t="279120">time there was a lady who was sitting</u>
  <u t="280240">next to me who was a Korean atuma. Like</u>
  <u t="281919">she was a older Korean lady who was</u>
  <u t="284240">actually a tour guide of a big group of</u>
  <u t="286639">aas and ais like a big group of Korean</u>
  <u t="289040">people that have been traveling in</u>
  <u t="291160">Europe and she was she looked at me and</u>
  <u t="294080">she was laughing cuz I was kind of</u>
  <u t="295639">like and she was like you should have</u>
  <u t="299919">eaten this with the BB pup like with the</u>
  <u t="302160">rice. you don't eat this by itself and</u>
  <u t="304960">it's called kimchi. It's a bantan you're</u>
  <u t="307039">supposed to eat with the rest of your</u>
  <u t="308479">food. I was like, okay, cool. Thank you.</u>
  <u t="312080">Yeah, I was a little bit embarrassed</u>
  <u t="313199">because I was already like so red from</u>
  <u t="314880">the spiciness and from coughing and from</u>
  <u t="316639">being surprised by the taste of that</u>
  <u t="318160">food and then that lady turned to her</u>
  <u t="321039">big group, started speaking with other</u>
  <u t="322800">people of the group. I'm like, why is</u>
  <u t="324080">she speaking with the foreigner? I I</u>
  <u t="326160">couldn't understand Korean obviously at</u>
  <u t="327919">the time, but she was she was pointing</u>
  <u t="330000">at me and being like, "Kimchi, kimchi."</u>
  <u t="333440">And I was like, "Oh my god, what did she</u>
  <u t="335560">say?" So yeah, my very first time eating</u>
  <u t="338320">Korean food and especially kimchi was</u>
  <u t="341039">yes, a very memorable, slightly shameful</u>
  <u t="343840">moment.</u>
  <u t="350160">Talking of shameful moment, another</u>
  <u t="351600">thing I've done for the first time when</u>
  <u t="352960">I went to Korea for that first time was</u>
  <u t="355360">getting naked among strangers. Now hold</u>
  <u t="358720">on. I have said I am French and some</u>
  <u t="361440">people have the misconception that</u>
  <u t="362960">French people likes to be naked in parks</u>
  <u t="365039">and at the beach and this is wrong and</u>
  <u t="367680">false. Mm- There are nudist beaches. It</u>
  <u t="370800">happens. There are some some places, but</u>
  <u t="373520">it's really not the norm. like French</u>
  <u t="374960">people are not as free as you guys think</u>
  <u t="377199">and I don't normally get naked in front</u>
  <u t="378880">of people um that easily. So why did I</u>
  <u t="382319">get naked? Actually um it was a cultural</u>
  <u t="385520">experience. Hear me out. Have you guys</u>
  <u t="387440">heard of gingerbang? These are public</u>
  <u t="389440">bath houses and it's very common in</u>
  <u t="391520">Korea. So back in the day people would</u>
  <u t="393280">go there to literally have a bath. Uh it</u>
  <u t="396560">was a hygienic service. Nowadays, people</u>
  <u t="399919">have bathroom in their houses, but they</u>
  <u t="401600">still go to a gingerbang for fun, to</u>
  <u t="404240">hang out, to scrub each other's back,</u>
  <u t="407039">which I find very strange because you're</u>
  <u t="408560">naked when you do that. If you ever go</u>
  <u t="410479">to one of those, I would recommend to go</u>
  <u t="412000">to one of those and to not be too</u>
  <u t="413600">scared. I was mortified the first time</u>
  <u t="417000">and the first 15 seconds were really</u>
  <u t="419840">hard for me who is really not used to</u>
  <u t="423039">this. But basically, men and women are</u>
  <u t="425840">separated in the like wet area. by wet</u>
  <u t="428319">area. This is where you have the actual</u>
  <u t="429680">bath. This is where you have some sauna,</u>
  <u t="432240">some steam rooms. You arrive, you take</u>
  <u t="434880">off all your clothes, you shower, then</u>
  <u t="436800">you go around the baths, etc. Um,</u>
  <u t="439280">another fun thing you can do there</u>
  <u t="441479">is get scrubbed. So, what happened is</u>
  <u t="447120">also funny. So, the scrubs there happen</u>
  <u t="448960">on tables, but you're all next to each</u>
  <u t="450880">other, completely naked, and you have an</u>
  <u t="454400">old lady in her underwear, black</u>
  <u t="457199">underwear. Why are they in underwear? I</u>
  <u t="459599">don't know. That literally scrubs your</u>
  <u t="462400">entire skin off. Like, they get rid of</u>
  <u t="464960">all the skin from your body by really</u>
  <u t="468039">scrubbing so hard. And it feels great.</u>
  <u t="470960">You feel like a new little snake. But</u>
  <u t="473120">it's a weird experience because you are</u>
  <u t="475120">right next to each other naked on those</u>
  <u t="476720">tables with those</u>
  <u t="478759">Korean in their underwear scrubbing the</u>
  <u t="482000">hell out of you and obviously she has to</u>
  <u t="484080">scrub the whole of your body. Like she</u>
  <u t="486160">leaves no place</u>
  <u t="488039">untouched. She also washes your hair</u>
  <u t="490240">which is nicer. Um but she has to do the</u>
  <u t="493919">front but also the back. And I couldn't</u>
  <u t="496960">speak Korean at the time and that lady</u>
  <u t="498319">didn't speak English. And so to turn me</u>
  <u t="501280">around, she said something and I was</u>
  <u t="504520">like, "What?" And didn't understand</u>
  <u t="507520">obviously. So, so I was lying down like</u>
  <u t="509280">this or rather like this. And she took</u>
  <u t="511520">my ankle and she just went and then I</u>
  <u t="515039">turned like a little fish because when</u>
  <u t="517360">they scrub you like you're actually full</u>
  <u t="518719">of soap and on that plastic table you</u>
  <u t="520560">just like</u>
  <u t="521560">slip really easily. So she turned me</u>
  <u t="524600">around and continued her work. And my</u>
  <u t="527839">final surprise with this was that I had</u>
  <u t="530160">requested a massage which I expected to</u>
  <u t="533200">be relaxing but no. She started by like</u>
  <u t="536480">hitting me real hard to get the blood</u>
  <u t="539360">flow moving. And I was like what is this</u>
  <u t="542040">torture? It's both humiliation and pain.</u>
  <u t="546399">But once you get out once you walk out</u>
  <u t="548080">of this experience you feel uh brand new</u>
  <u t="551120">with a new skin very soft like a baby</u>
  <u t="553200">baby skin and full of vitality.</u>
  <u t="556320">So, it was weird, but it was great.</u>
  <u t="558000">Actually, I don't know if I'm a</u>
  <u t="559600">masochist, but like, but now every time</u>
  <u t="561440">I go to Korea, I go to Gingerbang and I</u>
  <u t="563839">always get the scrub massage combo</u>
  <u t="566399">because yeah, it actually feels great.</u>
  <u t="568560">Once you get fine with this nakedness</u>
  <u t="570320">business, it's actually pretty good. So,</u>
  <u t="573200">highly</u>
  <u t="578040">recommended. So, if scrubbing is</u>
  <u t="580240">actually really part of Korean hygienic</u>
  <u t="583519">life, something else that I took from</u>
  <u t="585760">Korea for my very first trip that I was</u>
  <u t="587360">not doing before, but then became very</u>
  <u t="589440">obsessed and religious about in my</u>
  <u t="591920">beauty regimen is sun cream. I told you</u>
  <u t="595120">I grew up in Europe and in Europe,</u>
  <u t="597040">especially in 2000, you wanted to be</u>
  <u t="599600">thin and tanned. That's it. Maybe</u>
  <u t="603040">blonde. I don't know. Was it just me?</u>
  <u t="605120">Yeah. So me with my cousin, we would we</u>
  <u t="607760">would lather ourselves in oil and</u>
  <u t="609519">literally go at the beach and just wait</u>
  <u t="612640">for us to turn</u>
  <u t="615079">orange like Donald Trump. And we had no</u>
  <u t="617839">idea how bad this was for our skin. And</u>
  <u t="619839">when I went to Korea and I found that</u>
  <u t="622079">people had really good skin in general,</u>
  <u t="623600">like my my the women in my family, my my</u>
  <u t="625920">halman, my cousin had such nice skin.</u>
  <u t="628399">And I was like, what are they doing</u>
  <u t="630079">differently? We have the same genetics.</u>
  <u t="632800">What I realized is that they were very</u>
  <u t="634399">serious about putting sun cream every</u>
  <u t="635920">day. And I was like,</u>
  <u t="638279">"Oh." And that's when I started applying</u>
  <u t="640680">sunscreen 50 plus plus every day, even</u>
  <u t="644480">in winter, even if it rains, even if I</u>
  <u t="646320">stay in the house. And I actually think</u>
  <u t="648480">that it did wonder for my skin. Like, I</u>
  <u t="650560">think it keeps me looking young, doesn't</u>
  <u t="653279">it?</u>
  <u t="654470">[Music]</u>
  <u t="659680">Talking of beautiful people,</u>
  <u t="662880">um I just wanted to mention this thing</u>
  <u t="664480">that happened to me the first time I was</u>
  <u t="665760">in Korea was that I saw a celebrity in</u>
  <u t="669279">the street. And I know there's loads of</u>
  <u t="671120">Tik Tok that says like, "Oh my god, if</u>
  <u t="673120">you're just in Korea, you just see um</u>
  <u t="675600">actors and K-pop idols and just like</u>
  <u t="678399">Korean celebrities in the street all the</u>
  <u t="680480">time." And I don't know where these</u>
  <u t="682079">people go because I live for an entire</u>
  <u t="683920">year in Korea and in that entire year I</u>
  <u t="686000">saw nobody, right? Um, I saw people at</u>
  <u t="689279">concerts. I saw people at meetup events.</u>
  <u t="691760">Yes, sure they are supposed to be there.</u>
  <u t="693600">But in the street, no, not really. And I</u>
  <u t="696240">wish I had seen someone, okay? Because</u>
  <u t="699440">now I love Korean celebrities. But back</u>
  <u t="702079">in 2016, I knew nobody. And that's when</u>
  <u t="705680">I saw a celebrity.</u>
  <u t="709600">So, I was walking in Inadon, which is a</u>
  <u t="711760">place that's famous for having</u>
  <u t="713480">traditional items, and it's a bit of a</u>
  <u t="716480">tourist spot. And that's also where I</u>
  <u t="718079">bought this</u>
  <u t="718920">cup. Can you read what it says? It</u>
  <u t="723800">says, I had bought it for my boyfriend</u>
  <u t="725920">at the time, and now he's my husband.</u>
  <u t="727440">So, I think we can all thank this</u>
  <u t="729800">guy. And I was walking in the street</u>
  <u t="732079">when I saw a big group of people</u>
  <u t="733600">following this one guy. And I turned to</u>
  <u t="736079">my friend, and I was like, "What's</u>
  <u t="737839">happening?" and she's like, "Oh, it's a</u>
  <u t="739680">Korean celebrity." And I was like, "Oh</u>
  <u t="741519">my god, a Korean celebrity whom I don't</u>
  <u t="743680">know." So, what did I do? I just snapped</u>
  <u t="746160">a picture of the</u>
  <u t="747800">guy. That's it. Everybody was taking</u>
  <u t="750399">pictures. So, I just did like the</u>
  <u t="751680">others. Don't judge me. You would have</u>
  <u t="753440">done the same. Now, fast forward a few</u>
  <u t="755200">years. I was watching a Kdrama called</u>
  <u t="757519">Let's Eat. And who do I see? That guy.</u>
  <u t="761079">Correct. His name is, let me Google</u>
  <u t="763440">this. Dun. That guy whom I seen in this</u>
  <u t="766880">show. And yeah, I was like, "Oh my god,</u>
  <u t="768639">it's the guy I saw in the streets all</u>
  <u t="770240">these years ago. I finally know who he</u>
  <u t="773519">is." So I internally thank myself for</u>
  <u t="776240">having taken that pictures all these</u>
  <u t="777519">years ago. Otherwise, he would have</u>
  <u t="778800">always stayed this mystery man, this</u>
  <u t="781040">mystery celebrity man in the street in</u>
  <u t="787399">Korea. Now talking of Kama, the first</u>
  <u t="790000">one I watched was called Oh My Ghost.</u>
  <u t="792720">Not Oh my god, My Ghost. And I started</u>
  <u t="795760">Kidramama when I was in Korea actually,</u>
  <u t="799120">even though I only watched it on</u>
  <u t="800240">Netflix. But next week's Korea because I</u>
  <u t="802480">was there in August 2018. And if you</u>
  <u t="804959">have never been in Korea in August, it's</u>
  <u t="806800">actually really really hot and sticky</u>
  <u t="808399">cuz it's the rainy season. So it's</u>
  <u t="809760">raining all the time, but warm. So I was</u>
  <u t="811680">just chilling at home and not really</u>
  <u t="812880">knowing what to do. And I just started</u>
  <u t="814720">to randomly watch this really weird</u>
  <u t="817320">kidda which is a story of a girl who</u>
  <u t="820240">died a virgin and who's not happy about</u>
  <u t="823519">that.</u>
  <u t="826480">And so she takes the body of another</u>
  <u t="830000">girl who works in a kitchen who's</u>
  <u t="831600">suddenly going to become really hot for</u>
  <u t="834160">her chef. Now this is a Kdrama, so it</u>
  <u t="838560">was very very slow and very tame</u>
  <u t="842160">compared to the shows I was used to</u>
  <u t="844000">watch, you know, like American shows or</u>
  <u t="845360">whatnot. For some reason, I just</u>
  <u t="847199">couldn't stop watching. Like I was like,</u>
  <u t="848480">"My god, this show is so slow and</u>
  <u t="851240">so like a bit silly</u>
  <u t="855560">and and somehow I love it. I just do."</u>
  <u t="859760">So that's how I started with K drama and</u>
  <u t="861680">until now I've never really stopped.</u>
  <u t="863600">Right now I'm watching this um Heavenly</u>
  <u t="866480">Ever After which is a great show. If you</u>
  <u t="869120">haven't watched it, I highly recommend.</u>
  <u t="872000">It's with Suko, who is my favorite</u>
  <u t="874560">actor, who I've seen in real life when I</u>
  <u t="877040">went to Korea, but I've actually um seen</u>
  <u t="879279">him at the theater because I paid for</u>
  <u t="881440">tickets to go see his play even though I</u>
  <u t="885440">could not understand what was actually</u>
  <u t="887279">happening in this play, but I was so</u>
  <u t="890560">close to</u>
  <u t="892040">it.</u>
  <u t="897639">Anyhow, from K drama to K-pop, it's</u>
  <u t="901120">around the same time in 2018 that I</u>
  <u t="903120">really got into all the K things because</u>
  <u t="905920">until then I had a few trips to Korea,</u>
  <u t="907760">but it was really just about seeing the</u>
  <u t="910079">family. And the only thing I enjoyed</u>
  <u t="912000">about Korea was like seeing my family</u>
  <u t="914079">and food, eating, that was it. So, on my</u>
  <u t="916880">very first trip to Korea, I had heard</u>
  <u t="918720">K-pop obviously because it was blasting</u>
  <u t="920480">in the street all the time. At the time,</u>
  <u t="922880">they had that song everywhere which was</u>
  <u t="924639">like, "Pick me, pick me, pick me up,</u>
  <u t="926399">pick me, pick me, something like that."</u>
  <u t="927920">I don't know. It was super catchy, but</u>
  <u t="930079">also so annoying. Like, it wouldn't</u>
  <u t="931760">leave your head every time you would</u>
  <u t="932959">listen to it, which was all the time.</u>
  <u t="935199">Before that, I did not know K-pop so</u>
  <u t="937600">well. When I was in high school, a</u>
  <u t="940240">friend of mine who really liked K-pop</u>
  <u t="942720">had sent to me two songs that I had on</u>
  <u t="946480">my MP3 because yes, I am not as young as</u>
  <u t="951279">you think. Suncreen. She has sent me Big</u>
  <u t="954639">Bangs Lies</u>
  <u t="957020">[Music]</u>
  <u t="959440">and Strong Baby. And I like those songs</u>
  <u t="961600">and I was listening to them, but I had</u>
  <u t="964000">no particular interest. But I started to</u>
  <u t="965680">relisten to K-pop in 2018</u>
  <u t="969639">with Okay. Actually, it's a funny story</u>
  <u t="972079">because one night I was alone at home</u>
  <u t="973839">and I was just like, hm, I should like</u>
  <u t="976959">check</u>
  <u t="978440">K-pop. Yeah, as you do randomly and I</u>
  <u t="982000">just typed in Google like best K-pop</u>
  <u t="984000">song or something like that. And what</u>
  <u t="985839">came up was</u>
  <u t="989759">BTS My Drop. So I watched that music</u>
  <u t="992320">video and I was wondering why are those</u>
  <u t="994160">guys hair so weird but at the same time</u>
  <u t="996399">I really like the song and the dance</u>
  <u t="997920">move like yeah. So I clicked on the next</u>
  <u t="1001120">video which</u>
  <u t="1004120">was which again a little bit crazy but</u>
  <u t="1007199">somehow I liked it. And the third one I</u>
  <u t="1009519">clicked on</u>
  <u t="1011079">was and you know when at this beginning</u>
  <u t="1013360">they do like and I don't know I actually</u>
  <u t="1015600">thought that move was so beautiful and</u>
  <u t="1018399">the whole video clip was so beautiful</u>
  <u t="1020160">and I was confused about who was who</u>
  <u t="1021920">because they kept changing the hair once</u>
  <u t="1023440">again but I don't know there was</u>
  <u t="1025520">something about it and since that day I</u>
  <u t="1027679">could not stop listening to it and this</u>
  <u t="1029679">is how my obsession with BTS started and</u>
  <u t="1031839">with BTS came others because BTS was my</u>
  <u t="1034720">first K-pop love but you had also Monex</u>
  <u t="1036880">and Stray Kids and ETSs and many others.</u>
  <u t="1040079">And I'm so glad to have been able to</u>
  <u t="1042480">discover this whole world of K-pop</u>
  <u t="1044000">because I love the songs so much and I</u>
  <u t="1046240">especially love seeing the</u>
  <u t="1052440">performances. Which brings me to my</u>
  <u t="1054480">first K-pop concert which was actually</u>
  <u t="1056400">BTS. It was in 2019 and they were really</u>
  <u t="1060240">really big already and they were playing</u>
  <u t="1062400">at the start of France in in Paris and I</u>
  <u t="1065360">thought okay there's no way I'm actually</u>
  <u t="1067200">going to get any tickets and um I didn't</u>
  <u t="1070080">even try. I didn't want to be</u>
  <u t="1071600">disappointed. Whatever. Um but a girl</u>
  <u t="1074960">from my Korean class, we'll come back to</u>
  <u t="1076720">that. She said that she needed a</u>
  <u t="1079039">recommendation about Paris. And I was</u>
  <u t="1081200">like why? She said, "Oh, I'm going to</u>
  <u t="1083200">the BTS concert." And I was like, "Oh my</u>
  <u t="1084640">god, you're so lucky. like you got</u>
  <u t="1086799">tickets and she's like yeah I actually</u>
  <u t="1088640">have some spare but because I bought</u>
  <u t="1090320">some average ticket and then I managed</u>
  <u t="1091600">to get like much better tickets so I</u>
  <u t="1093520">actually want to sell the average</u>
  <u t="1094720">ticket. I was like wait a minute girl</u>
  <u t="1096799">I'm going to give you all the</u>
  <u t="1097760">recommendation for Paris but you give me</u>
  <u t="1100160">those tickets. Well, she gave me one uh</u>
  <u t="1102240">she gave me one ticket. Um well, I gave</u>
  <u t="1104559">I bought it, but I have a ticket for</u>
  <u t="1106320">BTS. And then when I was in Paris, I was</u>
  <u t="1108799">also looking for a ticket for the other</u>
  <u t="1111120">day because the concert was over 2 days</u>
  <u t="1113600">and I had a ticket for the one day and I</u>
  <u t="1115520">needed a ticket for the other ones, but</u>
  <u t="1117120">I had a budget that had already exploded</u>
  <u t="1119440">just with the, you know, buying the</u>
  <u t="1120640">tickets and flying to France, etc. So, I</u>
  <u t="1123200">had a budget of €50 and I just sent</u>
  <u t="1125840">messages to every single person on every</u>
  <u t="1128559">single platform that would sell ticket.</u>
  <u t="1130320">And I was like, "Hey, my budget is €50.</u>
  <u t="1132559">Um, I'm serious about this. If you have</u>
  <u t="1134400">any ticket, I don't care what it is.</u>
  <u t="1136000">I'll buy it off you." And nobody</u>
  <u t="1138320">responded or like people responded like,</u>
  <u t="1140320">"Girl, this is way too low." Yeah, I</u>
  <u t="1142799">know. But on the day of the concert,</u>
  <u t="1145520">like only a few hours before that,</u>
  <u t="1147520">someone responded was like, "I have</u>
  <u t="1148799">found no other seller." So yeah, you can</u>
  <u t="1151200">have it for €50. So, we met up at the</u>
  <u t="1154000">concert place and I got tickets for the</u>
  <u t="1156559">two days and it was a wonderful,</u>
  <u t="1159600">wonderful, wonderful experience. I did</u>
  <u t="1162160">not know about K-pop concert so much</u>
  <u t="1164240">because I had seen BTS's video clips a</u>
  <u t="1166880">lot and performances on broadcast, you</u>
  <u t="1168720">know, on YouTube and and whatnot, but I</u>
  <u t="1171039">had not seen what it's like at a concert</u>
  <u t="1174400">with all the light. I didn't know really</u>
  <u t="1176000">what the light sticks were for. I was a</u>
  <u t="1177679">really still a newbie to this whole</u>
  <u t="1179840">K-pop world and I saw all the light</u>
  <u t="1181840">sticks in all the colors and everybody</u>
  <u t="1183760">singing and it was like all of the def</u>
  <u t="1187039">France which is a huge stadium like</u>
  <u t="1189440">singing together. It was yeah the show</u>
  <u t="1192480">was like so big like I have been to so</u>
  <u t="1194640">many concert in my life. I used to work</u>
  <u t="1197120">in music festivals but I was blown away</u>
  <u t="1201120">by the actual performance put on with</u>
  <u t="1203360">from the staging the dances the change</u>
  <u t="1207039">of costume the the way everything is</u>
  <u t="1209520">thought to bring you each song's</u>
  <u t="1211360">universe and seeing the boys even though</u>
  <u t="1213919">they were the size of a Lego you know</u>
  <u t="1215360">you know Lego like that size they was so</u>
  <u t="1217679">small but I was seeing them in real and</u>
  <u t="1221440">it was</u>
  <u t="1223320">beautiful and I've seen other any K-pop</u>
  <u t="1226240">concert since, but this BTS, especially</u>
  <u t="1228880">the first time, like the first time I</u>
  <u t="1230320">saw it and these emotions I felt and</u>
  <u t="1233039">this things of seeing something for the</u>
  <u t="1235200">first time live, it really stays in my</u>
  <u t="1237679">heart.</u>
  <u t="1243120">And this whole interest I had in Korean</u>
  <u t="1244880">culture, the Halu uh wave really helped</u>
  <u t="1248320">me in taking learning Korean seriously</u>
  <u t="1251120">because I have two notebooks here. And</u>
  <u t="1253919">this one was from 2016 when I had just</u>
  <u t="1256960">met my family and I was going to go back</u>
  <u t="1259039">with my mom to meet them again so she</u>
  <u t="1261360">could meet her longlost mother. It was</u>
  <u t="1263919">me trying to</u>
  <u t="1266360">learn Oh my god, I haven't seen that in</u>
  <u t="1269280">so long. It's horrible.</u>
  <u t="1271840">So that's me trying to learn the</u>
  <u t="1273880">alphabet, trying to learn the roman</u>
  <u t="1276400">romanization rules. Do not learn the</u>
  <u t="1278559">romanization rule. Do not learn</u>
  <u t="1280240">romanization. Just learn your hunger.</u>
  <u t="1282159">Trust me. And the way I tried to learn</u>
  <u t="1284080">Korean is actually I decided to do a</u>
  <u t="1286960">language exchange from the very</u>
  <u t="1288640">beginning like from I knew nothing. And</u>
  <u t="1290320">I met with my first Korean tenant</u>
  <u t="1292320">partner who was learning English at the</u>
  <u t="1294720">time.</u>
  <u t="1295559">So, it's actually so funny because you</u>
  <u t="1298640">know like he's trying to like teach</u>
  <u t="1300679">me like ah ya or y or you like all of</u>
  <u t="1306559">this and his technique was telling me ah</u>
  <u t="1310080">think stabbed in the front. Ah then oh</u>
  <u t="1314640">you get stabbed in the back. So that's</u>
  <u t="1316480">why like the it go the you know it goes</u>
  <u t="1319200">to the front and then that goes to the</u>
  <u t="1320880">back. Yo, like rapping yo yo</u>
  <u t="1325159">yo like sexy kiss things cute girl. I</u>
  <u t="1331120">remember he was like cute girl. Ooh ooh.</u>
  <u t="1333360">I was like okay that's so</u>
  <u t="1335960">weird. And yeah like that's some of the</u>
  <u t="1338480">like thing he taught me. Like we are</u>
  <u t="1341039">still on my lesson my second lesson of</u>
  <u t="1343760">learning Korean. My second</u>
  <u t="1349400">hour. Um, how much is it? It's It's too</u>
  <u t="1357400">expensive. Yeah, we are still We still a</u>
  <u t="1359840">few pages down, but we still at Omayo.</u>
  <u t="1361840">Yeah, I could not deal with that. I</u>
  <u t="1364400">hadn't looked at this notebook, my first</u>
  <u t="1366440">Korean learning notebook in a very long</u>
  <u t="1368960">time. But we only met for a few weeks</u>
  <u t="1371520">and after that, I forgot everything</u>
  <u t="1374559">because I did not have time to learn</u>
  <u t="1376960">Korean properly and also he went back to</u>
  <u t="1379039">Korea. But this notebook is my first</u>
  <u t="1382240">serious Korean learning notebook and</u>
  <u t="1384640">that's from when I started learning</u>
  <u t="1386080">Korean at the Korean sett. This is 2016.</u>
  <u t="1389200">This is 2019. I started from the</u>
  <u t="1392480">complete beginner level and I went up to</u>
  <u t="1394400">level 4B. So, so from a complete</u>
  <u t="1397360">beginner to a high intermediate level.</u>
  <u t="1399200">And here if we look at these first</u>
  <u t="1401679">lessons that we learning, I mean</u>
  <u t="1402880">obviously we learn hunger first and then</u>
  <u t="1405039">the greetings in summer.</u>
  <u t="1416720">And at this lesson I remember she was</u>
  <u t="1419440">explaining</u>
  <u t="1420919">that come from which is a formal which</u>
  <u t="1424559">means to be there like to exist and ani</u>
  <u t="1427600">is peaceful. supposed to basic basically</u>
  <u t="1429360">stay there peacefully which is why it's</u>
  <u t="1432320">goodbye when the person when you were</u>
  <u t="1433919">leaving and the other person is staying</u>
  <u t="1435520">and you</u>
  <u t="1436440">say from kada which means to leave when</u>
  <u t="1440240">you stay here and the other person is</u>
  <u t="1442000">leaving and so it makes sense it's like</u>
  <u t="1444240">stay here peacefully or leave peacefully</u>
  <u t="1448159">which is something that um ton had never</u>
  <u t="1450880">told me he was just telling me like this</u>
  <u t="1452720">is the one where you leave and this is</u>
  <u t="1453760">the one where you stay and I could never</u>
  <u t="1455200">do the difference between the two of</u>
  <u t="1456799">them And that is why it's good to have a</u>
  <u t="1460000">proper teacher who knows what to say and</u>
  <u t="1462960">what to explain in detail to uh start</u>
  <u t="1465039">learning Korean. So I would recommend to</u>
  <u t="1467840">have a real textbook and a real teacher</u>
  <u t="1471039">either or or both ideally to start</u>
  <u t="1474159">learning Korean. But yeah, that's when I</u>
  <u t="1476240">first started to learn Korean. And it</u>
  <u t="1477840">was a really long journey, but I was</u>
  <u t="1479279">really really happy to learn Korean. And</u>
  <u t="1481679">I'm really happy now to be able to</u>
  <u t="1483200">communicate with my family fully. Like</u>
  <u t="1485440">when I'm there, we speak only Korean.</u>
  <u t="1487200">and I translate for my mom who doesn't</u>
  <u t="1488960">speak Korean because she was born there</u>
  <u t="1490720">but she grew up in France. Learning</u>
  <u t="1492159">Korean, learning to communicate even</u>
  <u t="1493760">though I'm not like 100% fluent. I'm not</u>
  <u t="1496000">100% comfortable speaking Korean. It was</u>
  <u t="1498880">really a massive change in</u>
  <u t="1501320">feeling like I am Korean</u>
  <u t="1508520">myself. And that the thing I never</u>
  <u t="1510799">really felt Korean until actually I</u>
  <u t="1513520">reckon about 2019 when I started</u>
  <u t="1515440">learning the language and starting to</u>
  <u t="1517360">feel familiar with the Korean culture,</u>
  <u t="1519039">starting to feel interested in the</u>
  <u t="1520720">Korean culture and also finding my</u>
  <u t="1523600">Korean name because that's the thing. I</u>
  <u t="1525679">grew up in the French countryside as a</u>
  <u t="1528720">French girl to whom other people were</u>
  <u t="1531039">saying that you don't look like you're</u>
  <u t="1532400">from here. You look Asian. But I didn't</u>
  <u t="1534320">felt Asian. I knew nothing about Asia. I</u>
  <u t="1536320">knew nothing about Korea. I knew I</u>
  <u t="1538720">couldn't identify with with any of this.</u>
  <u t="1541200">And so once I got familiar with the</u>
  <u t="1543760">culture, I got familiar with the</u>
  <u t="1545440">language. I started to really embrace</u>
  <u t="1547520">this side of my identity, I started to</u>
  <u t="1550240">become proud of my Korean heritage. And</u>
  <u t="1552720">another thing that happened in that very</u>
  <u t="1554240">first Korean class that I took was that</u>
  <u t="1557200">um I changed my name, I mean my nickname</u>
  <u t="1560000">because you see I'm called Kim on the</u>
  <u t="1562720">first day of class when they were like</u>
  <u t="1564320">oh if you're called Kim and you add she</u>
  <u t="1567360">at the end she which is sort of the</u>
  <u t="1568880">thing you put after a name to be polite</u>
  <u t="1570559">to people for example Jimn you would say</u>
  <u t="1572880">Jimni you know and with me if you say</u>
  <u t="1576960">the first time when the teacher asked</u>
  <u t="1578799">for my name she was like Kim so it going</u>
  <u t="1580880">to be like Kim</u>
  <u t="1582400">And everybody started laughing. She's</u>
  <u t="1584000">like, "She's called Kimchi." And I had a</u>
  <u t="1587520">wave of like that thing of like when</u>
  <u t="1589919">people were making fun of me at school</u>
  <u t="1591200">for being Asian, they were never</u>
  <u t="1592480">mentioning kimchi. Like no one knew</u>
  <u t="1593679">kimchi at the time, but like just like</u>
  <u t="1595039">oh the shin they were saying in French,</u>
  <u t="1597440">the Chinese girl like it was I was like,</u>
  <u t="1600720">"Oh my god, this is horrible." Like</u>
  <u t="1602080">let's not call me like this. And a lot</u>
  <u t="1604240">of my friends were calling me Kimmy as a</u>
  <u t="1606159">cute nickname. And I was telling the</u>
  <u t="1608320">teacher like, "Oh no, not Kim, Kimmy."</u>
  <u t="1610480">And that how it became Kimishi. And</u>
  <u t="1613600">that's why my name on this channel every</u>
  <u t="1616159">time I speak Korean is Kimmy. Now Park</u>
  <u t="1619440">is not my legal last name, but it was my</u>
  <u t="1622799">mom's name before she was adopted. And</u>
  <u t="1625039">it's my family name, my Korean family</u>
  <u t="1627200">name. So that's why my name is Pakimi.</u>
  <u t="1629039">And when I introduced myself in this</u>
  <u t="1630320">video, I said Pakima. So yeah, that's</u>
  <u t="1633120">full circle from my first trip, my first</u>
  <u t="1635120">Kimchi to now having my first and last</u>
  <u t="1638400">Korean name. and that whole journey of</u>
  <u t="1641440">many K first that brought me to today</u>
  <u t="1645360">being really proud of being Korean. So</u>
  <u t="1647679">yeah, that was my story and that's it</u>
  <u t="1649360">for today. If it was your first time on</u>
  <u t="1651520">this channel, don't forget to subscribe.</u>
  <u t="1653360">I hope you enjoyed the video. If so, let</u>
  <u t="1654960">me know by giving me a thumbs up. Thank</u>
  <u t="1656720">you so much for watching and I'll see</u>
  <u t="1657840">you in the next one.</u>
  </text>
