<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="4gcPpraTwRo" uploader="Unique Japan Travel" channel="Unique Japan Travel" likes="32669" title="Japan’s Unexplored Region | Train Trip on an Emerald Green Lake in Shizuoka | JAPAN TRAVEL VLOG" year="2025" month="5" day="10" date="20250510" date_ts="1746883144" is_ac="false">
  <u t="44336">Good morning everyone, this is Mona😊</u>
  <u t="49807">Today I’m at Senzu Station in Shizuoka Prefecture.</u>
  <u t="58347">Apparently, the Thomas Fair is being held around here starting today.</u>
  <u t="75193">The place I’m heading to from now is the unexplored region in Japan!</u>
  <u t="85335">I’m off to Okuoi Kojo Station, which is called a "hidden station" among Japanese people.</u>
  <u t="97344">I used to watch Thomas a lot when I was a child.</u>
  <u t="106518">"Hello everyone. I’m Hiro, a Japanese-born locomotive. Welcome to Senzu Station."</u>
  <u t="118027">Oh, the train is here!</u>
  <u t="125366">The view from the first car on the train.</u>
  <u t="137676">This time, I’m choosing to ride in the very last car of the train on purpose.</u>
  <u t="150086">Now, let’s go!</u>
  <u t="157358">This feeling of excitement is irresistible♡</u>
  <u t="180076">I’m the only one in this train car✨</u>
  <u t="195022">The red trolley train looks stunning against the fresh greenery.</u>
  <u t="218340">Wow, a long suspension bridge!</u>
  <u t="227681">The Japanese tea plantations are beautiful💚</u>
  <u t="235687">By the way, Shizuoka Prefecture boasts the highest tea production in Japan!</u>
  <u t="251833">The scenery is starting to feel very much like a mountain railway.</u>
  <u t="271682">Many of the stations we stop at are unmanned.</u>
  <u t="282524">That adds to the sense of being somewhere out of the ordinary.</u>
  <u t="294033">The color of the river is becoming more vivid🩵</u>
  <u t="317819">I have arrived at Abt Ichishiro Station.</u>
  <u t="331296">The Abt type electric locomotive will now connect.</u>
  <u t="341004">In fact, the section from here to the next station is said to have the steepest gradient of any railway line in Japan.</u>
  <u t="355415">This is the only place in Japan where Abt type trains run.</u>
  <u t="385006">The impressive Nagashima Dam!</u>
  <u t="392345">Wow, so beautiful😍</u>
  <u t="399817">I’m almost at the unexplored station!</u>
  <u t="437013">I have arrived at Okuoi Kojo Station.</u>
  <u t="449357">What a refreshing and wonderful station this is.</u>
  <u t="475410">This is a cafe located at Okuoi Kojo Station.</u>
  <u t="486252">It is a space with a gentle atmosphere where I can feel the warmth of wood.</u>
  <u t="515242">The curry is like a blue lake.</u>
  <u t="521347">I wondered what it would taste like, but it is a medium-spicy curry and rice.</u>
  <u t="540028">The train has arrived!</u>
  <u t="547001">It’s really picturesque.</u>
  <u t="569752">Thank you for a wonderful time♡</u>
  <u t="580294">Now, let’s go to the scenic spot of Okuoi Kojo Station.</u>
  <u t="596273">I walk along a pretty steep road.</u>
  <u t="604513">Wow, what a view🥰</u>
  <u t="610684">Looking at it like this, it looks like a small station floating on the lake.</u>
  <u t="626030">I’m back at Senzu Station.</u>
  <u t="649415">This is the Japanese tea specialty shop.</u>
  <u t="657688">They sell "Kawane tea", a brand of Japanese tea produced in this area.</u>
  <u t="670365">I think I’ll have the soft serve ice cream.</u>
  <u t="686411">Oh, it’s so delicious!</u>
  <u t="690681">The flavor of the tea fills my mouth♡</u>
  <u t="698087">Now, let’s head to my next destination.</u>
  <u t="714433">This is an experiential food park that gathers agricultural products from this region.</u>
  <u t="726409">I want to buy a lot of things as souvenirs.</u>
  <u t="757300">I feel like taking a short break.</u>
  <u t="764339">The stairs that resemble tea plantations are interesting.</u>
  <u t="786424">Refreshing sweetness!</u>
  <u t="793429">I feel relaxed💗</u>
  <u t="806273">I have arrived at Hamamatsu Station.</u>
  <u t="827289">This is the popular restaurant known as the originator of Hamamatsu Gyoza (Japanese dumplings).</u>
  <u t="838298">Since it’s a special opportunity, I’ll have dinner here.</u>
  <u t="862350">Cheers🍻</u>
  <u t="874593">I’m happy♡</u>
  <u t="891507">It’s lighter taste than I expected!</u>
  <u t="898179">They were juicy dumplings that brought out the natural flavors of the ingredients😋</u>
  <u t="907353">Today I’m staying at a hotel near the station.</u>
  <u t="930404">Good morning!</u>
  <u t="935175">I’m going for a morning walk from now♡</u>
  <u t="966299">The recommended coffee has a fruity taste.</u>
  <u t="978276">This is Bentenjima Seaside Park.</u>
  <u t="984347">The nice weather lifts my spirits.</u>
  <u t="991186">The red torii gate standing on the lake⛩️</u>
  <u t="998191">It’s beautiful.</u>
  <u t="1010167">I’m heading from now by rental car to a popular restaurant that always has a long line!</u>
  <u t="1031284">I received a numbered ticket and waited for quite a while.</u>
  <u t="1042360">Wow, it looks delicious🤤</u>
  <u t="1076186">It’s a hamburger steak made with 100% beef.</u>
  <u t="1086294">It was a very satisfying lunch.</u>
  <u t="1096503">I have come to the place I have been curious about for a long time.</u>
  <u t="1120255">This is the place created over more than 20 years by Shigeyoshi Sasaki, an architect born in Hamamatsu.</u>
  <u t="1138236">It’s a spot that is becoming popular among Japanese people, with people saying it’s like a "Ghibli Village".</u>
  <u t="1160286">Calm and peaceful time is passing♡</u>
  <u t="1200285">Let’s go into this restaurant!</u>
  <u t="1211193">No matter what scene I capture, it’s cute.</u>
  <u t="1237081">The cheese taste is rich, but the cake itself has a light taste❤️</u>
  <u t="1250525">This channel brings you unique travel experiences in Japan.</u>
  <u t="1259265">If you like it, please like, comment, and subscribe to my channel.</u>
  <u t="1268172">Thank you for watching!</u>
  <u t="1273009">See you again🌿</u>
  </text>
