<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="aIB5bt3EkQs" uploader="Project Happiness " channel="Project Happiness " likes="66006" title="LA VIA DEI SAMURAI: alla scoperta del Giappone autentico 🇯🇵" year="2023" month="11" day="26" date="20231126" date_ts="1701005409" is_ac="false">
  <u t="480">[music]</u>
  <u t="16240">"Are there bears here?"</u>
  <u t="18160">Yes.</u>
  <u t="21914">[in Italian] Good morning!</u>
  <u t="23360">Everything has life. Everything is alive.</u>
  <u t="27280">We are traveling along the Nakasendo Trail,</u>
  <u t="29440">one of the oldest and most historic in all of Japan.</u>
  <u t="37560">What is happiness to you?</u>
  <u t="43360">Well...</u>
  <u t="44920">What complex things you ask me.</u>
  <u t="52400">My name Giuseppe and I have a mission:</u>
  <u t="54720">to travel the world,</u>
  <u t="56143">to meet the most extraordinary people on the planet,</u>
  <u t="58800">And to ask them a simple question:</u>
  <u t="61080">"What does happiness mean to you?"</u>
  <u t="63120">Welcome to Progetto Happiness.</u>
  <u t="66200">THE TRAIL OF THE SAMURAI</u>
  <u t="71440">Tokyo, with its population of 40 million,</u>
  <u t="74300">is the largest city in the world</u>
  <u t="77000">as well as the most technological.</u>
  <u t="79240">Beginning in the 1950s, the Japanese capital</u>
  <u t="82480">became a symbol of Japan's economic miracle,</u>
  <u t="86320">which resurrected from the ashes of World War II</u>
  <u t="89160">as the world's second-largest economic powerhouse,</u>
  <u t="92520">betting everything on technological progress and innovation.</u>
  <u t="96280">Today it is nicknamed the "Cyborg City."</u>
  <u t="99920">But is this really the soul of Japan?</u>
  <u t="102560">We are about to begin a journey back in time.</u>
  <u t="108320">In the collective imagination, Japan is always seen</u>
  <u t="111720">as a big super-technological robot,</u>
  <u t="114080">but apart from Tokyo and Osaka,</u>
  <u t="115800">in small towns they still use floppy disks.</u>
  <u t="118240">It may sound absurd, but it's true.</u>
  <u t="120640">This sharp contrast between the past and the future</u>
  <u t="123400">can be seen in a special place in the Japanese Alps,</u>
  <u t="127160">where time seems to have stopped in the samurai era.</u>
  <u t="130440">And that's where we're headed.</u>
  <u t="132520">[music]</u>
  <u t="145320">Crazy, everything is like in anime.</u>
  <u t="147720">This is the first stage, Nagiso.</u>
  <u t="150360">Or maybe it says "station," I don't know.</u>
  <u t="153200">Everything is totally different from Tokyo, but there is one constant:</u>
  <u t="156720">the cars still make me smile</u>
  <u t="158640">because they look like washing machines on wheels.</u>
  <u t="165286">You don't know what a thrill it is for me to be here.</u>
  <u t="167943">I had dreamed of this moment for a very long time.</u>
  <u t="170763">I've visited Japan many times before,</u>
  <u t="172720">but not the real Japan.</u>
  <u t="174240">Here you can breathe in the culture and history of Japan.</u>
  <u t="177520">We are traveling along the Nakasendo Trail,</u>
  <u t="180040">one of the oldest and most historic in all of Japan.</u>
  <u t="182880">Between 1600 and 1800 it connected the ancient capital Kyoto</u>
  <u t="187080">to Edo, which is present-day Tokyo.</u>
  <u t="189520">The peculiarity of this path is that over the centuries</u>
  <u t="192840">beautiful "postal towns" were created every 10 kilometers.</u>
  <u t="196360">These were centers of communication where government officials</u>
  <u t="200315">or couriers would come to deliver or receive</u>
  <u t="203629">very important information.</u>
  <u t="206800">In addition, it was a place where merchants, travelers, and monks</u>
  <u t="210080">they could stop to rest and change horses.</u>
  <u t="212880">They were protected, since bandits were afraid to come here</u>
  <u t="216920">because these cities were protected by the samurai.</u>
  <u t="220280">Samurai were brave warriors,</u>
  <u t="222760">Skilled masters in the art of warfare</u>
  <u t="225000">and disciplined in the martial arts,</u>
  <u t="227440">but at the same time refined scholars of the arts and poetry.</u>
  <u t="231440">This dualistic nature reflected the balance</u>
  <u t="234120">between strength and wisdom that defined their being.</u>
  <u t="236880">Their lives were defined by Bushido,</u>
  <u t="239600">a moral code based on principles</u>
  <u t="241640">such as courage, honor and loyalty.</u>
  <u t="244680">Death in battle was preferred to shame,</u>
  <u t="248000">and service to one's feudal lord was a sacred responsibility.</u>
  <u t="252240">Even today, the legacy of the samurai persists,</u>
  <u t="255560">embodied in the timeless values of courage, integrity and self-control.</u>
  <u t="260880">Through time the samurai remain witness to a bygone era</u>
  <u t="265120">but their spirit lives on, immortal in the culture</u>
  <u t="268040">and in the identity of Japan.</u>
  <u t="271560">Suddenly, from a traditional house on the trail</u>
  <u t="274680">a gentleman appears with a globe in his hand.</u>
  <u t="277200">He asks me to show him where I am from.</u>
  <u t="279520">And so, somehow we begin to talk.</u>
  <u t="282760">Where do you sleep?</u>
  <u t="284200">Sleep...</u>
  <u t="287800">Here?</u>
  <u t="289480">Futon?</u>
  <u t="290560">Yes.</u>
  <u t="291760">89 years old!</u>
  <u t="293880">89?</u>
  <u t="295120">89 years old!</u>
  <u t="298080">I am a young man.</u>
  <u t="300160">The mailman has arrived, so the homeowner is preoccupied.</u>
  <u t="304760">At 89, he has the flexibility of a child.</u>
  <u t="307560">I could never kneel like that.</u>
  <u t="310840">[speaking Japanese]</u>
  <u t="318357">This is the living room?</u>
  <u t="325520">Ah, sure. Futon.</u>
  <u t="327920">Futon here.</u>
  <u t="332080">Now it looks empty, but it's because they take futons,</u>
  <u t="336320">which are their mattresses, unroll them and sleep.</u>
  <u t="340320">When they don't have to sleep, they put them back.</u>
  <u t="342840">So the room remains empty, simple.</u>
  <u t="345600">Clearly all the traditional Japanese houses here</u>
  <u t="349080">reflect the philosophy of wabi-sabi,</u>
  <u t="351521">that is, the philosophy of simplicity and modesty,</u>
  <u t="354400">which is found throughout Japanese culture.</u>
  <u t="357429">The house is so simple that it looks empty, uninhabited,</u>
  <u t="361000">but the gentleman keeps it spotless, perfect.</u>
  <u t="364480">See how they hang shirts.</u>
  <u t="367640">Crazy!</u>
  <u t="369760">So they don't even have to iron.</u>
  <u t="372560">I make videos.</u>
  <u t="375920">My job is to make videos.</u>
  <u t="378760">Advertisement?</u>
  <u t="382600">You are a video maker, aren't you?</u>
  <u t="385840">I don't understand what you are asking.</u>
  <u t="389400">Excuse me.</u>
  <u t="390720">No, no, no.</u>
  <u t="392040">Do you have WiFi here? So we can...</u>
  <u t="395320">Your WiFi?</u>
  <u t="397360">Do you have WiFi?</u>
  <u t="399520">[in Japanese] Wife?</u>
  <u t="403280">Because we have no connection I can't communicate</u>
  <u t="407200">with this gentleman, but if he has WiFi</u>
  <u t="410040">I can connect with total peace of mind</u>
  <u t="412920">because as you know, we use NordVPN.</u>
  <u t="415680">I have been keeping the NordVPN app active for years now.</u>
  <u t="418920">To surf online in total anonymity,</u>
  <u t="421000">protecting my privacy and sensitive data.</u>
  <u t="423960">NordVPN hides my real IP</u>
  <u t="425629">and the sites I visit never know my true position.</u>
  <u t="428920">This way I avoid many measures of censorship or restriction,</u>
  <u t="432280">Like watching Italian TV abroad or viceversa.</u>
  <u t="435080">I can watch foreign TV series</u>
  <u t="437640">that would not be available in Italy.</u>
  <u t="440240">Or even more useful, getting better deals</u>
  <u t="443000">on flights and hotels by changing the location of my IP.</u>
  <u t="445880">For me it becomes essential, especially when traveling,</u>
  <u t="448640">because when I connect to public WiFi,</u>
  <u t="451215">some networks may be traps used by criminals</u>
  <u t="454160">to break into my network and steal all my data.</u>
  <u t="457040">Whereas with NordVPN I have peace of mind</u>
  <u t="459429">even if I make a mistake or am careless, which happens.</u>
  <u t="462920">- English no? - Scottish.</u>
  <u t="465440">No English, Scottish.</u>
  <u t="468241">He's nice.</u>
  <u t="469720">Finally, we were able to communicate</u>
  <u t="472200">using his Internet and thanks to Google Translate.</u>
  <u t="476543">But when you go online with public Wi-Fi,</u>
  <u t="480301">be sure to always use NordVPN.</u>
  <u t="483000">I will leave you a link in the description</u>
  <u t="485320">to get a great deal and try NordVPN.</u>
  <u t="487760">He doesn't need NordVPN.</u>
  <u t="490101">I won't tell him about it.</u>
  <u t="492000">Look at his cellphone.</u>
  <u t="493786">Beautiful.</u>
  <u t="495040">I lived here from my birth until my 89th birthday.</u>
  <u t="503760">"What is your philosophy for having a happy life?"</u>
  <u t="512629">My life philosophy.</u>
  <u t="514515">What complex things you ask me. [laughs]</u>
  <u t="516920">The most important thing is to take care of your health.</u>
  <u t="521360">One must live with the energy of a young man.</u>
  <u t="523800">One should not let the transience of life get you down,</u>
  <u t="527720">but always live as a young man.</u>
  <u t="529360">And also, drink some sake.</u>
  <u t="531120">Sake? A little bit of sake.</u>
  <u t="534760">Yes, drink some sake before going to sleep.</u>
  <u t="537280">The truth, however, is that true happiness</u>
  <u t="540960">is the love I have had for my wife for 60 years</u>
  <u t="545440">since I married her and we went on our honeymoon</u>
  <u t="552120">- Thank you very much. - To you!</u>
  <u t="555040">Thank you for this wonderful talk.</u>
  <u t="559880">-Welcome to Tsumago. -Thank you.</u>
  <u t="564600">The lower we bow, the more you thank someone.</u>
  <u t="568960">So let's see if...</u>
  <u t="570560">Thank you!</u>
  <u t="572760">He bowed even lower than I did.</u>
  <u t="575560">Thank you.</u>
  <u t="578800">[music]</u>
  <u t="581840">The Nakasendo Trail passes through majestic cedar forests,</u>
  <u t="585400">which are not only appreciated by pilgrims,</u>
  <u t="587960">but also by bears.</u>
  <u t="589280">For this reason, along the path</u>
  <u t="591186">there are these little bells that are rung like this</u>
  <u t="594440">to also warn bears of the presence of passersby.</u>
  <u t="600520">The more I go into the forest, the louder I hear</u>
  <u t="603571">a little bell that seems to move among the trees.</u>
  <u t="606040">And so I decide to follow the noise and I find out</u>
  <u t="609429">that it's a mushroom hunter with a bell hanging from his belt</u>
  <u t="612844">to keep the bears away.</u>
  <u t="614240">I am following him, I don't know if he is happy</u>
  <u t="617000">that I'm keeping him company on the trail.</u>
  <u t="620229">But I am curious to see what he does.</u>
  <u t="623400">Communication is limited,</u>
  <u t="625787">I have to translate everything all the time.</u>
  <u t="629037">We are more or less getting by.</u>
  <u t="631080">I understood that he is a mushroom picker</u>
  <u t="633720">and he also set traps for animals.</u>
  <u t="637594">We are going there now.</u>
  <u t="640080">He seems like an interesting character, though.</u>
  <u t="642760">Maybe I should ask him an essential question.</u>
  <u t="646880">Yosushi, excuse me.</u>
  <u t="651871">"Are there bears here?"</u>
  <u t="655600">I am afraid of the answer.</u>
  <u t="658840">Yes.</u>
  <u t="660640">Ah!</u>
  <u t="663040">Okay.</u>
  <u t="666929">"And if we see one, what should we do?"</u>
  <u t="675240">[Japanese translation]</u>
  <u t="679334">Please don't move.</u>
  <u t="684720">Okay, okay.</u>
  <u t="686320">He has classical Japanese shoes that are very curious.</u>
  <u t="689200">They are called chikatabi.</u>
  <u t="691040">They divide the big toe from the rest of the foot.</u>
  <u t="694241">They give him more grip on the ground.</u>
  <u t="696840">Perfect for going in the mountains.</u>
  <u t="699329">It is counterintuitive; they look like flip-flops,</u>
  <u t="703440">but he uses them in the mountains and seems to do very well.</u>
  <u t="707760">Because he is so fast.</u>
  <u t="722200">-Eat! -Eat?</u>
  <u t="724160">-Is it good? -Edible.</u>
  <u t="725680">We found some mushrooms.</u>
  <u t="727640">In addition to being one of the most widely used ingredients</u>
  <u t="730960">in Japanese cuisine, mushrooms are also used</u>
  <u t="734093">in traditional medicine to strengthen the immune system,</u>
  <u t="737400">increase stamina, and reduce inflammation.</u>
  <u t="740200">For this reason, in Japanese folk legends</u>
  <u t="743280">it is said that eating mushrooms makes one immortal.</u>
  <u t="746322">When I enter the forest, the sounds around me</u>
  <u t="749044">become sharper in the silence.</u>
  <u t="751329">I listen to them and my body simultaneously absorbs</u>
  <u t="754786">negative ions that make me feel very relaxed.</u>
  <u t="758640">I hope very much that I can always live</u>
  <u t="762233">in synergy with the mountain all my life.</u>
  <u t="765640">What makes me happiest is the thought</u>
  <u t="769510">that I can continue to live like this</u>
  <u t="773160">and considering the mountain my home.</u>
  <u t="778960">In Japanese culture, this connection with nature</u>
  <u t="782480">is called shinrin-yoku, or "forest bathing."</u>
  <u t="786200">It is an age-old Japanese practice.</u>
  <u t="788120">It consists of immersing oneself in nature, especially in forests,</u>
  <u t="791840">to achieve mental and physical health benefits.</u>
  <u t="794840">It is not just a simple nature walk,</u>
  <u t="797426">but the experience of becoming one with nature,</u>
  <u t="801321">experiencing sounds, scents, light</u>
  <u t="803400">and contact with trees and plants.</u>
  <u t="805520">Japanese doctors prescribe it to reduce stress, depression</u>
  <u t="810108">and to improve the immune system.</u>
  <u t="812560">Through sensory awareness and attention to detail,</u>
  <u t="816760">forest bathing is an opportunity for reflection and contemplation.</u>
  <u t="823240">This practice invites you to slow down, to reflect</u>
  <u t="826160">and to find our balance in an increasingly fast-paced world.</u>
  <u t="829560">In ancient times, pilgrims who walked the Nakasendo Trail</u>
  <u t="833120">slept in minshuku, which means "people's home."</u>
  <u t="836400">They are homes of local families who open their doors</u>
  <u t="840720">to travelers who passed and pass through here.</u>
  <u t="844960">We are going to sleep in one of the oldest in the area,</u>
  <u t="848520">a minshuku that is almost 300 years old,</u>
  <u t="851040">in which even great samurai have slept.</u>
  <u t="854480">Each of these little houses has a very special detail,</u>
  <u t="857680">such as this one.</u>
  <u t="859160">Do you see that ball?</u>
  <u t="860640">It is called sugidama. It is a ball of cedar branches</u>
  <u t="864160">which are initially green, but when they turn brown</u>
  <u t="867920">it means the sake is ready.</u>
  <u t="870000">It can be found outside sake factories,</u>
  <u t="872760">so I assume they produce sake in here.</u>
  <u t="875480">Every place, every little house we encounter</u>
  <u t="879160">has a special feature like this.</u>
  <u t="885720">This should be our minshuku.</u>
  <u t="888200">And those are the mattresses that are left out during the day</u>
  <u t="892720">to air out and they're for sleeping on top of the futon,</u>
  <u t="896761">which is a mattress that sits on top of tatami floor mats.</u>
  <u t="899629">Let's go.</u>
  <u t="906000">Finally we are inside the minshuku and it is wonderful.</u>
  <u t="909200">It is a centuries-old historical minshuku.</u>
  <u t="912171">Yoko, who is the owner of the house, was telling me...</u>
  <u t="916360">Yoko, I beg your pardon, hi.</u>
  <u t="919000">Yoko, the owner of this minshuku.</u>
  <u t="921241">She is explaining to me that it is so ancient</u>
  <u t="923526">that samurai have also slept here.</u>
  <u t="925840">Even the samurai slept here.</u>
  <u t="928640">Yes, a long time ago.</u>
  <u t="931280">Now she is preparing our little room.</u>
  <u t="934360">This is the futon?</u>
  <u t="936640">That's right.</u>
  <u t="937680">Futon, tatami.</u>
  <u t="939720">And that is?</u>
  <u t="941160">Yukata.</u>
  <u t="942520">Is the yukata like pajamas?</u>
  <u t="944840">Yes.</u>
  <u t="947440">Thank you.</u>
  <u t="948480">I don't want to bother her too much.</u>
  <u t="950360">She is busy arranging the rooms.</u>
  <u t="953720">We've set up here.</u>
  <u t="956040">There is Nick, he will sleep there.</u>
  <u t="958400">Very nice, really cozy.</u>
  <u t="961760">You walk around without shoes.</u>
  <u t="965920">You always have to be careful where you walk.</u>
  <u t="968600">The roof is very low.</u>
  <u t="970200">Minshuku perfectly reflects Japanese philosophy,</u>
  <u t="974880">especially in the home, because everything is minimal,</u>
  <u t="978160">everything reduced to its essence</u>
  <u t="979883">to give more importance to the bare necessities.</u>
  <u t="983029">For example, this is a bedroom in which we find the futon,</u>
  <u t="988040">which is this mattress that you sleep on,</u>
  <u t="990051">you sleep right on the ground.</u>
  <u t="992057">This is the classic tatami.</u>
  <u t="994280">How curious, they don't cover the whole comforter,</u>
  <u t="998920">But they only cover the part where you sleep.</u>
  <u t="1002000">They leave it open to make it easier to put the cover on.</u>
  <u t="1007080">This is the yukata, the classic pajamas used at home,</u>
  <u t="1011081">So I'm going to put it on later.</u>
  <u t="1013120">But what I find the most amazing is the shoji,</u>
  <u t="1016400">which are these sliding panels.</u>
  <u t="1019119">Definitely not be the best for keeping out the cold,</u>
  <u t="1024280">they are made from rice paper or mulberry paper</u>
  <u t="1029320">to allow for softer light inside the house.</u>
  <u t="1034560">They diffuse the sun's rays to create a balanced light inside.</u>
  <u t="1039720">Also when it comes to light, everything in a Japanese home</u>
  <u t="1044520">is thought out and has always been so for centuries.</u>
  <u t="1047480">This room welcomes and receives travelers from all over Japan</u>
  <u t="1053360">who stayed here for days to rest and then resume their journey.</u>
  <u t="1057372">Tonight it's my turn.</u>
  <u t="1061800">Yoko and her husband invite me to have tea with them</u>
  <u t="1064921">and I take the opportunity to ask them a few questions.</u>
  <u t="1068560">I would like to speak in Japanese to understand you right away,</u>
  <u t="1073040">but more or less with technology we'll understand each other.</u>
  <u t="1076920">Do you think samurai slept here?</u>
  <u t="1080320">Yes.</u>
  <u t="1082280">In that corner there were the horses.</u>
  <u t="1089360">For horses.</u>
  <u t="1090640">Yes.</u>
  <u t="1091757">A that time horses were the only means of transport.</u>
  <u t="1099720">The door is so small because people used to be shorter.</u>
  <u t="1102529">Today everyone is banging their heads against it.</u>
  <u t="1105234">It was always been yours, and your family's?</u>
  <u t="1108720">Yes, I am the ninth generation.</u>
  <u t="1114743">Invaluable historical assets are kept here.</u>
  <u t="1122529">They cannot be purchased, for example, ancient katanas.</u>
  <u t="1137400">What is the Japanese philosophy behind minshuku?</u>
  <u t="1142200">At the base is hospitality.</u>
  <u t="1146386">For us, it is essential.</u>
  <u t="1150643">Making people who stay here feel good by</u>
  <u t="1154760">welcoming them and preparing special food.</u>
  <u t="1158600">In this way we keep the tradition of our ancestors alive.</u>
  <u t="1164240">That is why I chose to live here my whole life.</u>
  <u t="1168520">This house has such a long history.</u>
  <u t="1172240">Many people have lived here and passed through here.</u>
  <u t="1176515">It's a living house!</u>
  <u t="1177960">Thank you very much.</u>
  <u t="1179560">Thank you.</u>
  <u t="1181120">It was very interesting.</u>
  <u t="1187720">I have to whisper because here the walls</u>
  <u t="1190040">are literally made of paper.</u>
  <u t="1192040">This night will be very special.</u>
  <u t="1194920">I will sleep in a minshuku so ancient</u>
  <u t="1197520">that even real samurai have been here.</u>
  <u t="1200600">And then I will sleep in the yukata</u>
  <u t="1203400">on a futon and a wooden pillow.</u>
  <u t="1206440">So, a really special night.</u>
  <u t="1209040">And it will be the first night when I turn off the light...</u>
  <u t="1212080">Like this.</u>
  <u t="1214560">Almost. More or less.</u>
  <u t="1216160">[laughs]</u>
  <u t="1217880">Good night.</u>
  <u t="1219880">[music]</u>
  <u t="1233760">On the trail I notice the garden of a house</u>
  <u t="1236200">full of wooden sculptures.</u>
  <u t="1238200">And as is often the case on this path,</u>
  <u t="1240680">people leave their doors open, happy to welcome pilgrims</u>
  <u t="1245640">and to make contact with distant worlds.</u>
  <u t="1248000">Look at this garden...</u>
  <u t="1250560">It must be the woodworker's garden.</u>
  <u t="1254000">And if he's here, it might be interesting to meet him.</u>
  <u t="1260760">Hello.</u>
  <u t="1263480">Hello.</u>
  <u t="1264400">Nice to meet you!</u>
  <u t="1265400">Nice to meet you, too.</u>
  <u t="1274800">He just told me that his wife died two years ago</u>
  <u t="1278003">and he just did a prayer here with us.</u>
  <u t="1281320">What was her name?</u>
  <u t="1283600">Mariko.</u>
  <u t="1286361">Beautiful name.</u>
  <u t="1287600">You can call me Sumi!</u>
  <u t="1290800">My name is Giuseppe.</u>
  <u t="1293029">Yuseppe?</u>
  <u t="1293815">Giuseppe.</u>
  <u t="1295160">Yuseppe.</u>
  <u t="1297229">What is your country?</u>
  <u t="1298657">Italy.</u>
  <u t="1299360">Italy!</u>
  <u t="1300560">[in Italian] Good morning!</u>
  <u t="1302240">[in Japanese] Thank you!</u>
  <u t="1305520">It reminds me so much of the meeting we had in Iceland.</u>
  <u t="1310040">It is pretty much the same, just in Japan.</u>
  <u t="1318400">What is this?</u>
  <u t="1319880">Someone put the money, so after...</u>
  <u t="1323360">Many.</u>
  <u t="1324574">No, no! I don't need it!</u>
  <u t="1327760">I thought it was a little altar where believers put an offering,</u>
  <u t="1331371">but he explained that someone put a coin here</u>
  <u t="1334560">and since then they have filled it with coins.</u>
  <u t="1337000">But he says no, I don't need them!</u>
  <u t="1343440">Over the centuries some of the most legendary and famous samurai</u>
  <u t="1347757">have passed through here traveling along the road</u>
  <u t="1352158">that connected Edo (Tokyo) to Kyoto.</u>
  <u t="1355481">Today, on the other hand, it is a lot of fun</u>
  <u t="1358429">to talk to people who come here from all over the world.</u>
  <u t="1361560">That makes me so happy.</u>
  <u t="1363235">You know, so many people walk the Nakasendo.</u>
  <u t="1365920">"What is happiness to you?"</u>
  <u t="1369057">[Japanese translation]</u>
  <u t="1370814">Um.</u>
  <u t="1385960">It lasted much longer, but I will spare you.</u>
  <u t="1390440">I have always felt happy: from the time I was a child until now.</u>
  <u t="1398480">Also because I think Japan is a really happy country.</u>
  <u t="1403787">On the contrary, I am very concerned</u>
  <u t="1405779">about what is happening in the world,</u>
  <u t="1407657">such as the war in Ukraine and other countries.</u>
  <u t="1410440">It makes me feel heartbroken to think</u>
  <u t="1412640">about the suffering of the people who live in these places.</u>
  <u t="1416280">That's why I think, in the end, happiness is equivalent to peace.</u>
  <u t="1422320">This kind of time travel through the hidden wonders of Japan</u>
  <u t="1427040">offers enchanting landscapes painted by the seasons,</u>
  <u t="1430280">stone paths that tell ancient stories,</u>
  <u t="1433440">and villages that preserve traditions.</u>
  <u t="1435800">But above all, the opportunity to connect with people</u>
  <u t="1440080">who still cherish the essence of the true Japan</u>
  <u t="1443840">Little Japanese. Translate.</u>
  <u t="1446520">Yes.</u>
  <u t="1447800">Shall we try?</u>
  <u t="1449560">I am doing the Nakasendo Trail to discover real Japan.</u>
  <u t="1454960">What are you doing here?</u>
  <u t="1456800">What work do you do?</u>
  <u t="1458280">I am now working in the field.</u>
  <u t="1464400">Oh!</u>
  <u t="1466480">[in Japanese] Okay, okay. All right.</u>
  <u t="1469929">I am so excited.</u>
  <u t="1471640">I may know two words in Japanese.</u>
  <u t="1474600">"Sodesu ka," I think it means "okay."</u>
  <u t="1477800">And the lady is cultivating her vegetable garden.</u>
  <u t="1481160">Can I come with you to see your vegetable garden?</u>
  <u t="1489200">Yes, certainly!</u>
  <u t="1492920">Thank you. Thank you very much.</u>
  <u t="1498760">Eat this?</u>
  <u t="1500171">Eat.</u>
  <u t="1502840">I hope I understood correctly.</u>
  <u t="1508920">It's for a salad.</u>
  <u t="1512457">Spicy!</u>
  <u t="1513640">Spicy.</u>
  <u t="1515400">They are good!</u>
  <u t="1517120">Wait a moment.</u>
  <u t="1520000">Okay.</u>
  <u t="1522960">What is your name?</u>
  <u t="1527957">My name is Misao.</u>
  <u t="1530320">Giuseppe.</u>
  <u t="1532371">Nice to meet you.</u>
  <u t="1535360">Let's see if she'll have me eat this, too.</u>
  <u t="1540120">What is it?</u>
  <u t="1541600">This plant is called "makomo" (Manchurian wild rice)</u>
  <u t="1546360">The part you eat at the bottom is called "makomotake".</u>
  <u t="1554520">It is delicious, tastes like...</u>
  <u t="1557020">A kind of raw zucchini and coconut.</u>
  <u t="1560320">Japanese snacks.</u>
  <u t="1562760">Snack?</u>
  <u t="1565520">It is good.</u>
  <u t="1568280">I tried.</u>
  <u t="1569800">The ground beneath us is alive.</u>
  <u t="1573669">Everything is alive.</u>
  <u t="1578440">I think that's exactly right,</u>
  <u t="1583320">even when I cultivate my field I am not alone.</u>
  <u t="1590000">But in harmony with everything that grows and lives around me.</u>
  <u t="1593201">I'm actually not the one who grows the plants,</u>
  <u t="1596044">but it is the plants themselves that grow by their own will.</u>
  <u t="1599200">Communicating in Japan is complex,</u>
  <u t="1601480">but in fact, through their genuine kindness</u>
  <u t="1604800">and goodness of heart, it somehow becomes possible.</u>
  <u t="1607480">And you actually learn so much,</u>
  <u t="1609480">especially when you find that you can also speak in English.</u>
  <u t="1612760">I think that every living being has a conscience.</u>
  <u t="1619880">A spirit!</u>
  <u t="1623600">This grain of rice is alive.</u>
  <u t="1628000">And everything, every being has life.</u>
  <u t="1634160">This life, that of humans,</u>
  <u t="1640619">or animals, and plants or insects</u>
  <u t="1647723">all come from the same thing.</u>
  <u t="1654000">Since ancient times.</u>
  <u t="1656960">We travel the world to understand</u>
  <u t="1661057">how happiness can change all over the world.</u>
  <u t="1665143">I would love to know what happiness is for you,</u>
  <u t="1668757">because you feel so connected with nature</u>
  <u t="1671480">and I am very curious about what happiness is for you.</u>
  <u t="1676440">I -- I feel happy.</u>
  <u t="1680631">With everything.</u>
  <u t="1685857">And...</u>
  <u t="1690200">When I am here in my garden, I am happy.</u>
  <u t="1696160">It can teach me anything.</u>
  <u t="1703360">Nature is my teacher.</u>
  <u t="1706600">[laughs]</u>
  <u t="1708857">And my buddy, my friend.</u>
  <u t="1712316">I feel happy.</u>
  <u t="1714280">I wanted to walk the Nakasendo with an open heart,</u>
  <u t="1718200">welcoming whatever happened on my path,</u>
  <u t="1721360">just like one does on big adventures.</u>
  <u t="1723640">Retracing the footsteps of proud samurai, adventurers, dreamers,</u>
  <u t="1727720">I found myself immersed in a world of timeless beauty,</u>
  <u t="1730995">forests thousands of years old,</u>
  <u t="1732640">villages that look like living paintings</u>
  <u t="1735031">and views that take your breath away,</u>
  <u t="1737280">Which together create a performance that goes beyond words.</u>
  <u t="1741080">Yet the real richness of this path</u>
  <u t="1744240">lies not only in its natural beauty,</u>
  <u t="1747240">but in the smiling faces of the people who populate these places,</u>
  <u t="1751160">keepers of the wisdom of a forgotten time</u>
  <u t="1754520">and witnesses to an ancient culture</u>
  <u t="1756920">where respect for the land is passed down as a precious legacy.</u>
  <u t="1761160">In this Japan outside of the big cities,</u>
  <u t="1764280">time seems to flow with a different rhythm.</u>
  <u t="1767240">A time where there is room for unconditional kindness,</u>
  <u t="1770840">for curiosity, and for caring about the small gestures</u>
  <u t="1774840">and the essentials which have always and forever defined</u>
  <u t="1778400">this millennia-old culture.</u>
  <u t="1782520">ENGLISH SUBTITLES: Kayla Baker</u>
  </text>
