<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="rvmEz9RiDZ8" uploader="Kanishk Gupta" channel="Kanishk Gupta" likes="109807" title="Most Beautiful Villages of Sikkim | Lachung and Lachen | Gurudongmar Lake | Northeast India" year="2025" month="5" day="3" date="20250503" is_ac="true">
  <u t="80">Nestled in the Eastern Himalayas of India is a</u>
  <u t="3840">beautiful place which is undoubtedly one of the smallest states of India.</u>
  <u t="8160">But</u>
  <u t="11759">some of the highest and most beautiful mountains of India reside here.</u>
  <u t="16600">And in these mountains resides a</u>
  <u t="20560">world where the sky is bluer than the sky.</u>
  <u t="25840">And waterfalls flowing from the sky-touching mountains</u>
  <u t="31320">where there are white valleys covered with snow</u>
  <u t="34719">and fields wrapped in greenery.</u>
  <u t="48200">Sikkim is one of the most beautiful places in India. Situated in the lap of the Himalayas, this place</u>
  <u t="51920">has many beautiful villages, one of which</u>
  <u t="55760">is Lachak.</u>
  <u t="68439">Lachuk is situated in a valley surrounded by high mountains from all sides, where many snow-capped</u>
  <u t="72479">mountains can be seen peeping from behind the mountains. And through these</u>
  <u t="75920">mountains flows the Lajuk</u>
  <u t="79530">[music]</u>
  <u t="80840">river. At the same time, waterfalls flow over some mountains. The one that</u>
  <u t="88640">is Lachuk is at almost a height of 10,000.</u>
  <u t="91759">Such a beautiful view of the waterfall in front of you at such a high altitude.</u>
  <u t="97439">What a beautiful waterfall one would see while sitting in the village</u>
  <u t="99840">and that too from such close quarters, it is very beautiful,</u>
  <u t="103920">friend. Right now</u>
  <u t="106000">you might be able to see from here that the sun</u>
  <u t="108799">is rising from behind this mountain and its</u>
  <u t="111280">beautiful rays are also visible. These</u>
  <u t="113680">are absolutely heavenly views, really</u>
  <u t="119399">a spiritual side is visible</u>
  <u t="122640">in this sunrise, friends.</u>
  <u t="124750">[Music] To</u>
  <u t="128479">explore this village further, I left the road and</u>
  <u t="132160">started wandering through its streets. Where</u>
  <u t="136239">I could see beautiful houses at every turn.</u>
  <u t="147280">[Music]</u>
  <u t="159280">Look, I found this beautiful house. There are</u>
  <u t="161120">entire trees growing on the walls of this house. There</u>
  <u t="164160">is so much greenery. Meaning,</u>
  <u t="166160">starting from the bottom here, we are</u>
  <u t="168000">covering the walls of the entire house.</u>
  <u t="170160">This looks very beautiful, friend. It's all</u>
  <u t="172560">full of greenery</u>
  <u t="174530">[music].</u>
  <u t="176120">And in this house, the one you see installed on the side, they</u>
  <u t="178959">burn incense in it. We do</u>
  <u t="181599">puja etc. And early in the morning</u>
  <u t="183760">you will see this pot kept in front of every house in</u>
  <u t="186080">which incense keeps burning.</u>
  <u t="190400">This village has a very pure and spiritual vibe.</u>
  <u t="195900">[Music]</u>
  <u t="208879">Along with these beautiful houses, some small</u>
  <u t="212239">farms or gardens are also visible. In which they</u>
  <u t="215280">grow almost every vegetable needed.</u>
  <u t="219959">Like here below, this local spinach is</u>
  <u t="223760">planted from Lachum which is very</u>
  <u t="225920">famous. And there are some apple trees</u>
  <u t="228879">that have just started flowering. At</u>
  <u t="231200">some places he has also cultivated potatoes etc.</u>
  <u t="233599">Meaning there is home grown culture here.</u>
  <u t="235840">Make it all at home. Grow it at home</u>
  <u t="238319">and</u>
  <u t="243879">eat it at home. And these organic vegetables grown here.</u>
  <u t="247760">How good it is for health. I came to know about this</u>
  <u t="250720">when I saw a grandmother of more than 70 years of age doing</u>
  <u t="254560">farming even at this age. He</u>
  <u t="260560">says okay, leave it, don't do all this, he</u>
  <u t="262560">says no. So you like</u>
  <u t="264320">farming like this? This is not a little bit, the house is</u>
  <u t="266560">complete from the first one. You have become used to it, right? It's a</u>
  <u t="269280">habit. It is your habit. It feels good,</u>
  <u t="272000">meaning you should do it like this. It</u>
  <u t="273759">feels good if you do a little work. If he doesn't work, he wo</u>
  <u t="276160">n't be able to sit properly. No, it doesn't feel good. I don't feel like it.</u>
  <u t="280840">Okay, great, great. Some work should be done. Should</u>
  <u t="284320">work. Absolutely. Yes, that's right.</u>
  <u t="286320">Pass a little time. Yes. The</u>
  <u t="295360">name Lachung means small pass. That</u>
  <u t="299440">is, a short route to the mountains.</u>
  <u t="302800">Because Lachung is the only way to</u>
  <u t="306240">go deeper into these high mountains.</u>
  <u t="311750">[Music]</u>
  <u t="314639">As we come up from Lachung, it</u>
  <u t="317280">feels like the doors to a different world have opened.</u>
  <u t="319840">Like, you see this mountain behind. It</u>
  <u t="323360">is so beautiful. There are so many unique</u>
  <u t="327120">mountains with so many ages. While being in the Lachos, one does</u>
  <u t="329840">not realize that such</u>
  <u t="332960">sights are hidden in front of one. And when we</u>
  <u t="335680">go deep into these mountains, we come across a very</u>
  <u t="339440">beautiful valley called Yamdhang.</u>
  <u t="349700">[MUSIC]</u>
  <u t="352160">[APPLAUSE]</u>
  <u t="357199">This is the view. This is called looking so beautiful.</u>
  <u t="361440">Meaning, all these white flags are hoisted. There are so</u>
  <u t="366639">many mountains visible all around and behind.</u>
  <u t="369199">Snow peaks and the river flowing right in front of me.</u>
  <u t="372160">Such a beautiful view of the water.</u>
  <u t="374960">What a complete view, friend. It</u>
  <u t="377199">is very beautiful. And when I came to Lach, I was</u>
  <u t="380080">waiting to</u>
  <u t="382639">stand at this point of Yamdhang Valley because this</u>
  <u t="384800">entire frame that is formed, whatever</u>
  <u t="387520">view you see, it is absolutely picture</u>
  <u t="390080">perfect, friend. There is a very beautiful view</u>
  <u t="392720">here.</u>
  <u t="394880">Seeing so many white flags here, you might be</u>
  <u t="398479">wondering the reason for their presence here.</u>
  <u t="401919">So the reason is that here in North Sikkim,</u>
  <u t="405039">these</u>
  <u t="408240">white prayer flags are put up when someone dies in the family. That too</u>
  <u t="411600">only in a clean and very windy place</u>
  <u t="415880">and it is believed that whenever the wind</u>
  <u t="420160">passes through them, they spread positivity and peace.</u>
  <u t="429039">These views become even more beautiful beyond Yamthan.</u>
  <u t="441080">Now this mountain that you see behind me is a</u>
  <u t="445240">very joint mountain. extremely</u>
  <u t="448680">large. It feels like</u>
  <u t="451759">I am standing on a movie set. It's a fantasy movie.</u>
  <u t="456350">[MUSIC]</u>
  <u t="460639">And it has a lot of stones down in front. This was</u>
  <u t="462960">some old launch.</u>
  <u t="465520">Because of that, this entire area, the entire site is lying like this. It is</u>
  <u t="467599">filled with stones. And there's a</u>
  <u t="469840">little bit of grass on them now. After looking at it for a while,</u>
  <u t="472479">you will definitely feel a slight thrill after</u>
  <u t="475039">seeing this mountain.</u>
  <u t="479919">And while walking on this road, finally there</u>
  <u t="483840">comes a point where this road ends</u>
  <u t="487280">which is called zero point.</u>
  <u t="493200">[Music]</u>
  <u t="498639">So this is the point, and it's called the zero point,</u>
  <u t="501280">and the road ends here.</u>
  <u t="504240">This is the closest point you</u>
  <u t="509680">can get to Tibet or these beautiful mountains. You</u>
  <u t="511919">can come only up to this close and tourists are allowed beyond this.</u>
  <u t="513760">Just a little further ahead is the road, about</u>
  <u t="516080">1 km. And for all those army camps</u>
  <u t="519200">and bunkers etc.</u>
  <u t="523599">Situated at an altitude of 15,000 feet, this place remains covered with</u>
  <u t="527920">snow for most of the year. Rather, the</u>
  <u t="532000">water coming out from these ice glaciers</u>
  <u t="534959">forms the Lachung River below.</u>
  <u t="539480">All this water is melting from this glacier and going down</u>
  <u t="542800">to Lachung. And it's</u>
  <u t="545839">creating the entire river. And by looking at this</u>
  <u t="548080">glacier, this blue colored</u>
  <u t="550720">piece of ice, you will understand</u>
  <u t="552399">how old this ice</u>
  <u t="554519">is. The entire bluish tent is visible. It's</u>
  <u t="557600">very old snow</u>
  <u t="559250">[music].</u>
  <u t="563000">And near the zero point, the</u>
  <u t="567200">last village of this road is Yungsodon. Where the</u>
  <u t="572000">houses of some yak herders are visible. Who</u>
  <u t="579279">come from the lakes in search of good grass in the summer and come here to stay for a few days</u>
  <u t="585250">[music]. The</u>
  <u t="590040">name of the zero point is zero. But the</u>
  <u t="592800">views here are 100 out of 100. I mean, it's such a</u>
  <u t="596720">beautiful view. Wherever you look like this,</u>
  <u t="600399">your gaze will stop there. It is such a</u>
  <u t="602320">beautiful view.</u>
  <u t="604890">[Music]</u>
  <u t="610160">As I came back down to Lachung, I</u>
  <u t="617920">wanted to go to this waterfall visible from Lachung. But little did I know that just by</u>
  <u t="621839">hiking for 10 minutes from the road, I would</u>
  <u t="625040">reach near this waterfall.</u>
  <u t="642560">Water is falling so fast. The sound is so loud</u>
  <u t="644800">that it can be heard far and wide.</u>
  <u t="647040">But this waterfall that you see is not just this.</u>
  <u t="648880">Such a big part of it from</u>
  <u t="651040">where it is falling from the top is</u>
  <u t="653519">not visible completely from here.</u>
  <u t="656920">And much like</u>
  <u t="666720">Lajuk, it was just a village in Sikkim. But on the</u>
  <u t="670320">other side of these high mountains, there is an even more</u>
  <u t="673920">beautiful village. But on my</u>
  <u t="678399">way there, I saw something that was</u>
  <u t="682399">very difficult to ignore.</u>
  <u t="692880">So, the flood that occurred in North Sikkim two years ago has</u>
  <u t="701040">completely destroyed this road as well, and not just this road, but the</u>
  <u t="704160">entire mountain, houses and villages have completely</u>
  <u t="709920">disappeared, everything has been wiped out,</u>
  <u t="713360">only now these mountains are seen cut</u>
  <u t="717279">by the soil. So all the mountains that you</u>
  <u t="719920">see cut like this, brown</u>
  <u t="721680">patches on the mountains, up to this height, the</u>
  <u t="725360">river that is visible so far below, its water was till here</u>
  <u t="728279">and going further it broke the Chang dam.</u>
  <u t="733279">All the debris and all the water that flowed out created a</u>
  <u t="736160">very dangerous scene.</u>
  <u t="740560">All that must have been very dangerous.</u>
  <u t="743120">And standing here now, it</u>
  <u t="746519">feels very strange to see such a broken road.</u>
  <u t="753600">This flood in the Teesta River was caused by the breaking of a glacier lake. Due to whose water this</u>
  <u t="757760">village was saved by just a few meters. But</u>
  <u t="762800">not all homes were so lucky.</u>
  <u t="769340">[Music]</u>
  <u t="782160">How in just a few seconds, this whole place</u>
  <u t="785440">changed forever.</u>
  <u t="792240">I was ready to see the beauty of nature but not this form of nature. And since then the</u>
  <u t="796800">respect for nature has</u>
  <u t="800240">increased even more.</u>
  <u t="803800">But life does not stop. And now</u>
  <u t="807920">a new path has been created again.</u>
  <u t="811120">After some time, I reached that beautiful village</u>
  <u t="815200">named Lachin.</u>
  <u t="819300">[Music] Sitting</u>
  <u t="828399">at 9000 feet, nestled in the lap of some beautiful green mountains,</u>
  <u t="837399">Lachin is a small area filled with a number of</u>
  <u t="841360">houses, each with</u>
  <u t="845600">large prayer flags fluttering on its rooftops. It is</u>
  <u t="853120">summer in the lawn right now and at</u>
  <u t="855680">this time in the summer the temperature is -2° in the morning.</u>
  <u t="859440">So my whole hands are freezing. The</u>
  <u t="862399">whole feet are freezing. It</u>
  <u t="864800">is very cold. You will</u>
  <u t="867760">see a beautiful peak in front. It has turned golden which is</u>
  <u t="870560">very beautiful right now, i.e. at the time of sunrise.</u>
  <u t="876560">This snow-covered mountain, visible in every view of Lachen,</u>
  <u t="880480">is Lamo Akam, whose height is about</u>
  <u t="885839">20,000 feet, which makes these views of Lachen</u>
  <u t="890160">even more beautiful.</u>
  <u t="896930">[Music]</u>
  <u t="908320">So right now I'm walking around the streets of Nachin</u>
  <u t="910800">and one thing I noticed here is</u>
  <u t="913279">that there are all kinds of houses here. Right now, as</u>
  <u t="916160">you can see behind me, this is a wooden house.</u>
  <u t="918160">What you see behind him is the Mud</u>
  <u t="921120">House. The bottom is completely made of mud and the top is made of</u>
  <u t="923360">wood. And there are pucca houses here.</u>
  <u t="925920">Now the number of pucca houses</u>
  <u t="927760">is increasing. But it is amazing. Otherwise I</u>
  <u t="930320">see either wooden houses or mud houses.</u>
  <u t="932560">I find the wooden houses the most beautiful among all these houses.</u>
  <u t="935440">I</u>
  <u t="938320">also feel like building a wooden house.</u>
  <u t="940680">Wooden houses look very beautiful.</u>
  <u t="944320">How beautiful it is. And behind there is such a beautiful</u>
  <u t="947680">backdrop of mountains. While</u>
  <u t="955120">roaming around like this, I also got a chance to see a house from inside.</u>
  <u t="961759">Which was a house made of mud. Can I see from inside</u>
  <u t="965600">?</u>
  <u t="970000">hello.</u>
  <u t="971350">[Music]</u>
  <u t="975680">Hello.</u>
  <u t="978639">How old is this house? Now that has happened, it has been</u>
  <u t="980639">80 years. It's been 80 years.</u>
  <u t="984399">Okay, okay, so this is good, a mud</u>
  <u t="986639">house is good? It gets hot. It gets hot.</u>
  <u t="988639">Well, it is very warm in the cold months.</u>
  <u t="991199">Yes, its roof is made of</u>
  <u t="994959">wood. Yes, there is a sheet on top. Okay okay.</u>
  <u t="998079">This is lucky. All those walls</u>
  <u t="1000720">are pot. The walls are made of mud. This is made of clay.</u>
  <u t="1003279">Yes.</u>
  <u t="1004920">Yes, it is all soil. This is all soil.</u>
  <u t="1009440">Why keep the kitchen open like this? It</u>
  <u t="1012320">is like this. This has been happening traditionally since before. It happens</u>
  <u t="1014480">traditionally. It is slightly opened in the second house. After</u>
  <u t="1017519">innovating, you did</u>
  <u t="1020320">not innovate here.</u>
  <u t="1023120">Just opposite to today's era of modular kitchens, there is a</u>
  <u t="1030000">tradition of displaying all the kitchen utensils in the house.</u>
  <u t="1034240">After some time uncle asked, will you have tea</u>
  <u t="1039120">and then</u>
  <u t="1042000">take this one from here, oh ho</u>
  <u t="1044799">thank you, what do you call it, kabe</u>
  <u t="1048640">khabaje, ok, ok, it is like a</u>
  <u t="1051440">salty ...</u>
  <u t="1065600">Saltpare. Salt and mercury. Yes. Have you guys also had</u>
  <u t="1069760">tea? Did you drink it? I drank it well. After having</u>
  <u t="1073120">tea and local snacks here, I left.</u>
  <u t="1076640">Visit Lachin. Thank you so much. I liked it</u>
  <u t="1078720">very much.</u>
  <u t="1080330">[Music] The</u>
  <u t="1083200">beautiful Lachan Monastery is built at the highest point here.</u>
  <u t="1091070">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1096080">Very vibrantly colored building and</u>
  <u t="1098880">definitely the most peaceful</u>
  <u t="1109480">place in Lachen. But the most beautiful thing about this monastery is</u>
  <u t="1113440">its lamp house.</u>
  <u t="1123520">So many lamps are burning together.</u>
  <u t="1126640">Seeing this, it makes him feel so good, it is</u>
  <u t="1129760">very positive. And it is so hot in this room.</u>
  <u t="1132320">I'm feeling hot right now, not wearing a jacket.</u>
  <u t="1134000">And this entire jacket became hot.</u>
  <u t="1136320">I am heated up. They are</u>
  <u t="1138559">kept closed like this so that these lamps do not go off. Let the</u>
  <u t="1141520">wind not accidentally come in from inside and extinguish these lamps. That is</u>
  <u t="1143600">why doors and windows always</u>
  <u t="1146400">remain closed. There's just a chimney up there</u>
  <u t="1149240">[MUSIC].</u>
  <u t="1159400">Like the name Lachum means small pass. The</u>
  <u t="1163520">name Lachen means</u>
  <u t="1166559">Big Pass. Because Lachen gives way to the</u>
  <u t="1170880">highest mountains of Sikkim</u>
  <u t="1177799">and the beauty of the first place on this route is</u>
  <u t="1181960">astonishing.</u>
  <u t="1187420">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1202559">This place, covered in snow at an altitude of 13,000 feet, is</u>
  <u t="1209880">Thangoveli. The</u>
  <u t="1214000">crystal clear Teesta River flowing through the snow-capped mountains and</u>
  <u t="1218080">some snow-covered wooden houses situated along the river. These</u>
  <u t="1221440">scenes once and for all erase the difference between reality and dream.</u>
  <u t="1230120">I just came a little ahead of Lachin</u>
  <u t="1233600">and here midway I found out that everything had turned</u>
  <u t="1236559">white because it had snowed the whole night. It</u>
  <u t="1238640">looks so beautiful.</u>
  <u t="1241200">Everything is completely white and there is a</u>
  <u t="1245039">layer of white everywhere. Like there are trees</u>
  <u t="1246960">, wires, prayer flags, there</u>
  <u t="1249440">is a layer everywhere. You look very beautiful, friend.</u>
  <u t="1256280">But these mountains of snow were just the beginning. Of</u>
  <u t="1260080">higher and more beautiful</u>
  <u t="1264159">views to come. But before going there, I</u>
  <u t="1268240">want to tell you one special thing. Nowadays</u>
  <u t="1271200">AI has come everywhere and is making everything easier.</u>
  <u t="1274240">So imagine what it would be like if</u>
  <u t="1277360">AI makes the task of making videos easier.</u>
  <u t="1281039">Well, there is no need to think. Now this has become a</u>
  <u t="1283200">reality. Yes, indeed,</u>
  <u t="1286159">with Artlist's AI Image &amp; Video feature, you can now turn</u>
  <u t="1289440">any of your video ideas</u>
  <u t="1292240">into reality. That too</u>
  <u t="1294720">in just a few minutes. Let me tell you how. First of all,</u>
  <u t="1298080">go to this AI feature of Artlist and</u>
  <u t="1300880">tell us the idea of ​​your video.</u>
  <u t="1303520">Enter text and then enhance that text</u>
  <u t="1306400">for detailing. And then AI will generate a high</u>
  <u t="1309280">quality image of your idea.</u>
  <u t="1312159">And then you can convert that image into a video by clicking on Animate.</u>
  <u t="1315360">And you can generate</u>
  <u t="1318000">all the shots for your videos in just a few minutes.</u>
  <u t="1320640">And the best part is that you can</u>
  <u t="1326159">also generate voice overs for the story or narration of those videos on Artlist itself.</u>
  <u t="1328960">Rather, music, sound</u>
  <u t="1331360">effects and if needed, footage also. You get</u>
  <u t="1334480">it all in one place</u>
  <u t="1336880">with a single subscription</u>
  <u t="1338880">with Artlist Max. If you want, you</u>
  <u t="1341440">can try it by taking a one month subscription</u>
  <u t="1343840">and if you like it then only take the annual subscription in</u>
  <u t="1346320">which</u>
  <u t="1348720">you will also get two months extra free from the link in my description. Then it is</u>
  <u t="1351440">worth trying.</u>
  <u t="1357880">Beyond Thangu Valley, as the height</u>
  <u t="1362320">increases beyond 13,000 feet, the views also change.</u>
  <u t="1366640">In just a few minutes, those</u>
  <u t="1370000">greenery and snow-covered mountains</u>
  <u t="1373679">appear to transform into a cold desert.</u>
  <u t="1378919">So, from Lachin to here, the</u>
  <u t="1381640">altitude has increased a lot and the</u>
  <u t="1385520">temperature has decreased a lot. Right now no</u>
  <u t="1388240">trees etc. are visible here.</u>
  <u t="1390159">Where trees were still visible. There are no trees here now. The</u>
  <u t="1394400">area has become completely like a cold desert. It feels like</u>
  <u t="1396559">I am standing in Ladakh. I am not even standing in Sikkim.</u>
  <u t="1398799">But it is really very</u>
  <u t="1401440">beautiful. Just</u>
  <u t="1404159">look at this mountain behind me. Both the mountains and the clouds are mixed. I do</u>
  <u t="1406799">n't know the full extent yet.</u>
  <u t="1408080">It is white, it is the white of snow or the</u>
  <u t="1410080">white of clouds and it looks very beautiful, friend. It's</u>
  <u t="1413120">very beautiful</u>
  <u t="1415460">[music].</u>
  <u t="1419480">While travelling on these routes, the altitude</u>
  <u t="1423760">increases up to 18,000 feet. And after reaching this height,</u>
  <u t="1427840">within a short time,</u>
  <u t="1436240">Gurudon, one of the tallest lakes of India, appears in front.</u>
  <u t="1442300">[Music] Nestled</u>
  <u t="1459679">right in the middle of the Eastern Himalayas, this beautiful</u>
  <u t="1464400">blue water body is nestled in Gurudambaram. A</u>
  <u t="1469159">strong breeze</u>
  <u t="1473200">creates small waves in the water. Apart from their voices,</u>
  <u t="1476559">everything is quiet here.</u>
  <u t="1480039">So quiet that even the silence can be heard.</u>
  <u t="1484200">Rather, it is so quiet that you can hear every breath you take.</u>
  <u t="1490880">But not just because it's peaceful here.</u>
  <u t="1493880">Also because it is at a</u>
  <u t="1497240">height of 17800 feet. This is such a high</u>
  <u t="1500880">altitude that the oxygen here is</u>
  <u t="1503919">only half as compared to sea level.</u>
  <u t="1507799">So welcome all of you to India.</u>
  <u t="1513840">Gurudo Lake is one of the highest lakes in India and this is an unbelievable view.</u>
  <u t="1520080">Which I can't believe. Such</u>
  <u t="1524000">beautiful water and that mountain in front,</u>
  <u t="1528720">friend, there is no mountain more beautiful than this, it is a very</u>
  <u t="1531520">beautiful mountain. I am standing at a height of about 17800 feet and</u>
  <u t="1536400">I am still out of breath. It is becoming</u>
  <u t="1540960">very difficult.</u>
  <u t="1543200">I can't say much. But this lake</u>
  <u t="1545840">is really beautiful, man.</u>
  <u t="1550210">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1551760">Gurudambar Lake</u>
  <u t="1555279">is barely 5 km from the Tibet border. And because of its proximity to the border,</u>
  <u t="1559039">only</u>
  <u t="1561919">Indian tourists can come here. But</u>
  <u t="1565360">this place is very sacred for the people living here.</u>
  <u t="1568799">Because there is a part of this writer that does</u>
  <u t="1572960">n't freeze no matter how cold it gets. And</u>
  <u t="1577760">people here believe that that part of the writer was</u>
  <u t="1580640">touched by the Buddhist guru Padma Sambhava.</u>
  <u t="1585080">And for this reason this article is called Guru Domber</u>
  <u t="1589279">article.</u>
  <u t="1599400">Such a peaceful place surrounded by nature</u>
  <u t="1603880">slowly changes you. Where</u>
  <u t="1608400">we are not used to so much peace or silence in cities. One feels</u>
  <u t="1612559">a little uneasy as soon as one comes to such places.</u>
  <u t="1617240">But then after some time that peace starts</u>
  <u t="1622240">giving us comfort. Nor is</u>
  <u t="1626120">life as slow as</u>
  <u t="1630000">we are used to here. Because</u>
  <u t="1634480">in this era of 10-minute delivery in cities, here</u>
  <u t="1637919">some things still have to be brought on foot for hours.</u>
  <u t="1642400">But this anxious wait</u>
  <u t="1646240">also gradually turns into patience.</u>
  <u t="1651360">Because such places change you slowly.</u>
  <u t="1656840">And as you move at this slow pace,</u>
  <u t="1660520">you</u>
  <u t="1663720">gradually start considering yourself a part of these places.</u>
  <u t="1671440">hello.</u>
  <u t="1674000">But this change hidden within us also</u>
  <u t="1677760">teaches us that there is not always a need to change the place for this.</u>
  <u t="1682559">Just need to change the speed.</u>
  <u t="1691380">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1709690">[Music]</u>
  </text>
