<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="t1qyeZzZft0" uploader="Breanna Quan" channel="Breanna Quan" likes="38352" title="my first time in italy 🍋 a week in amalfi coast &amp; sorrento, girls trip, beaches &amp; lots of food" year="2025" month="8" day="31" date="20250831" is_ac="true">
  <u t="340">[Music]</u>
  <u t="8710">[Music]</u>
  <u t="11200">Not</u>
  <u t="16440">[Music]</u>
  <u t="19600">screen.</u>
  <u t="23930">[Music]</u>
  <u t="34399">Hi guys, welcome to my Italy vlog. It is</u>
  <u t="36719">my first time here and we're staying in</u>
  <u t="38239">Positano and I'm here with one of my</u>
  <u t="40000">best friends for the next seven days.</u>
  <u t="41840">And this is just a quick overview of our</u>
  <u t="43760">Airbnb which was really cute. And this</u>
  <u t="46399">week is going to be super jam-packed</u>
  <u t="48000">with so many day trips and activities</u>
  <u t="49680">and a few familiar YouTube faces. So, I</u>
  <u t="52079">hope you enjoy. And without further ado,</u>
  <u t="54000">let's get into the video.</u>
  <u t="55950">[Music]</u>
  <u t="62160">I love this view. What?</u>
  <u t="66799">What is life right now? This is</u>
  <u t="69040">literally insane. A dream. It's such a</u>
  <u t="71760">dream. For real. This is Lonnie's. Looks</u>
  <u t="74240">so good. And then I got spaghetti of</u>
  <u t="77360">bongoli. I've been filming on time</u>
  <u t="79040">lapse, but I already had my first bite</u>
  <u t="80640">and it is so good. I'm obsessed.</u>
  <u t="84330">[Music]</u>
  <u t="100720">I just finished lunch at Utrian which</u>
  <u t="103600">was in the hotel Poseidon and honestly</u>
  <u t="105840">it was so good. We got our classic</u>
  <u t="107680">pastas again and now we're just walking.</u>
  <u t="110000">But honestly this morning we had to rush</u>
  <u t="111920">out. It was like 15 minutes away, but we</u>
  <u t="114000">didn't realize that it was going to be</u>
  <u t="115119">26 flights of stairs. So, we walked</u>
  <u t="117759">2,000 steps first thing in the morning,</u>
  <u t="119680">literally on an empty stomach. Nothing,</u>
  <u t="121439">no caffeine, no water. We weren't</u>
  <u t="123360">mentally prepared either. So, just</u>
  <u t="124960">straight up like, "Here's 26 flights of</u>
  <u t="126719">stairs. Can you climb it?" And we were</u>
  <u t="128479">like, "We're going to make this reso."</u>
  <u t="130720">So, like halfway through, I was like,</u>
  <u t="132400">"My heart is literally going to beat out</u>
  <u t="133920">of my freaking chest. I think I should</u>
  <u t="135440">turn around." But then I was like,</u>
  <u t="136560">"We're halfway through, so I can't give</u>
  <u t="138319">up now." Was it worth the climb?</u>
  <u t="141280">&gt;&gt; Yes. Yeah, I think so, too. But now</u>
  <u t="143040">we're just shopping along and heading to</u>
  <u t="144720">a cafe to get a little gelato because</u>
  <u t="146800">it's like 28° right now.</u>
  <u t="151660">[Music]</u>
  <u t="156879">&gt;&gt; This is the shop that's like super viral</u>
  <u t="159760">on the internet and it has like really</u>
  <u t="161280">cute patterns and stuff. It kind of</u>
  <u t="163040">reminds me of Love Shack Fancy, which is</u>
  <u t="165360">super cute. Like it's all sorts of</u>
  <u t="168400">patterns. They even have like different</u>
  <u t="170400">sizes. Like this is like a little one.</u>
  <u t="171680">It's a much bigger one. Like I love</u>
  <u t="173760">these little makeup bags. I think they</u>
  <u t="175280">are so cute. It's been on my wish list</u>
  <u t="176720">for the last couple of years, but I</u>
  <u t="178080">wanted one where I could get like my</u>
  <u t="179440">name on it. They're all really cute.</u>
  <u t="181440">Like this bag is honestly the same</u>
  <u t="182879">pattern as the my mom made it bag, but</u>
  <u t="184959">it's also €78, which is crazy. But I</u>
  <u t="189120">think I might get like a makeup bag.</u>
  <u t="192940">[Music]</u>
  <u t="201680">I had planned on getting vanilla, but</u>
  <u t="203519">then she recommended this one. So,</u>
  <u t="205440">that's Jessia.</u>
  <u t="208879">It is so rich.</u>
  <u t="214720">&gt;&gt; Hello.</u>
  <u t="216080">&gt;&gt; Hi.</u>
  <u t="220159">&gt;&gt; The water is so blue.</u>
  <u t="222870">[Music]</u>
  <u t="236159">Bro,</u>
  <u t="239530">[Music]</u>
  <u t="248879">&gt;&gt; the book I packed for this trip is We</u>
  <u t="251120">Are All Guilty by Karen Slaughter. It's</u>
  <u t="252720">her newest release. I'm really excited</u>
  <u t="254400">to see where it goes. On the plane, I</u>
  <u t="256320">already read, I think, 200 pages. And I</u>
  <u t="259359">will say that it is a little bit</u>
  <u t="260880">different than her other books because</u>
  <u t="262560">there's a big time skip by almost 12</u>
  <u t="264880">years. And I haven't read a single one</u>
  <u t="266479">of her books that has that. Usually like</u>
  <u t="268479">goes backwards in time. So, I don't</u>
  <u t="270400">really know if I like it, but I also</u>
  <u t="272960">haven't finished the book yet, so I</u>
  <u t="274639">can't tell for sure. We're going to</u>
  <u t="277759">dinner now after washing up from the</u>
  <u t="279759">beach. We're at this place called Max</u>
  <u t="281520">and it is so beautiful, guys. I have to</u>
  <u t="283600">show you this interior. We also</u>
  <u t="284960">collected some friends. We have Sarah</u>
  <u t="286639">and then Daisy's on her way, too.</u>
  <u t="293030">[Music]</u>
  <u t="306320">We went to Kina's again. This is where</u>
  <u t="308479">we're at. It's so good.</u>
  <u t="309759">&gt;&gt; What did you get, Lonnie? I got</u>
  <u t="310880">hazelnut. Okay, cute. I got vanilla.</u>
  <u t="313199">&gt;&gt; I got a pistachio and I got lemon. It's</u>
  <u t="316080">a sorbet.</u>
  <u t="316960">&gt;&gt; Oh my god.</u>
  <u t="321880">[Music]</u>
  <u t="328880">All right.</u>
  <u t="331600">[Music]</u>
  <u t="350080">The</u>
  <u t="351110">[Music]</u>
  <u t="358010">[Music]</u>
  <u t="362960">It's so cold. Oh my god.</u>
  <u t="367520">&gt;&gt; Okay, now that I'm in, it's not as bad.</u>
  <u t="370180">[Music]</u>
  <u t="379360">The paddle</u>
  <u t="384000">Lonnie and I just got out of the water</u>
  <u t="386000">and honestly, it's so fun and so</u>
  <u t="388720">refreshing. I feel like I never been in</u>
  <u t="390400">the water. I'm just going to do Lonnie's</u>
  <u t="392240">hair care routine now.</u>
  <u t="400370">[Applause]</u>
  <u t="400400">[Music]</u>
  <u t="403120">Mediterranean octopus salad. And then</u>
  <u t="405600">Lonnie got the bara, which looks so</u>
  <u t="407919">good.</u>
  <u t="422319">Okay, now this is our second course for</u>
  <u t="424319">lunch. I got a lobster burger. It looks</u>
  <u t="428000">so good. And then Lonnie got a Neurono</u>
  <u t="431440">pasta. I think I'm just going to full</u>
  <u t="432880">scent.</u>
  <u t="437039">At first, I only tasted the celery, but</u>
  <u t="439520">the mayo or the dressing they're using</u>
  <u t="440960">is really good.</u>
  <u t="442460">[Music]</u>
  <u t="467070">[Music]</u>
  <u t="473960">[Applause]</u>
  <u t="474390">[Music]</u>
  <u t="493400">[Applause]</u>
  <u t="494540">[Music]</u>
  <u t="502319">Good morning, guys. We just got ready</u>
  <u t="503840">really quickly because we're actually</u>
  <u t="505199">having a full boat day today. And before</u>
  <u t="507360">we head out, I just want to show you how</u>
  <u t="508400">I stay connected in Italy. Obviously, to</u>
  <u t="510240">stay online with you guys, but also with</u>
  <u t="511919">my friends and family back home. So,</u>
  <u t="513760">thank you to Saley for making this</u>
  <u t="514959">possible. SLY is an eim app that helps</u>
  <u t="516959">you stay connected at an affordable rate</u>
  <u t="518560">in over 200 countries around the world.</u>
  <u t="520560">And if you don't know what an eim is, it</u>
  <u t="522159">is exactly like a normal one, but is</u>
  <u t="524000">digital and it just downloads into your</u>
  <u t="525600">phone and just helps you start any trip</u>
  <u t="527040">hassle-free. Ever since I learned about</u>
  <u t="528640">eims like 2 or 3 years ago, I honestly</u>
  <u t="530959">haven't gone back to a physical card</u>
  <u t="532560">because it's just such a hassle to get</u>
  <u t="534000">it at the airport. And then you also</u>
  <u t="535440">need the pin to unlock it in your phone.</u>
  <u t="537360">And so sometimes if you don't have that</u>
  <u t="538640">on hand, then it just becomes a lot more</u>
  <u t="540000">work and then something for you to worry</u>
  <u t="541600">about. So s is compatible with all iOS</u>
  <u t="543920">and Android devices and you can just</u>
  <u t="545440">download the app and search the country</u>
  <u t="546880">or location that you're going to. There</u>
  <u t="548480">are various plans at various price</u>
  <u t="549839">points so you can just choose what is</u>
  <u t="551040">best suited for you and your trip. You</u>
  <u t="552800">guys can get an exclusive 15% off on</u>
  <u t="554800">sale eim data plans. You can download</u>
  <u t="556959">the sale app on the app store or play</u>
  <u t="558959">store and use code brianna at checkout.</u>
  <u t="585490">[Music]</u>
  <u t="595760">Oh.</u>
  <u t="596560">Oh, that's so nice.</u>
  <u t="601310">[Music]</u>
  <u t="612860">[Music]</u>
  <u t="617839">From the water line and I took the bus</u>
  <u t="619600">up from the beach all the way up and now</u>
  <u t="621279">we're getting lunch. I was super excited</u>
  <u t="622560">and I said I was going to stop getting</u>
  <u t="623920">seafood pasta cuz it's the only thing</u>
  <u t="625200">I've been getting but I got another one.</u>
  <u t="627839">So, and the boat was so much fun as</u>
  <u t="629760">well. We took so many photos and swam so</u>
  <u t="632560">much. I'm honestly like kind of fading</u>
  <u t="634720">now. We have a whole day ahead of us.</u>
  <u t="637200">It's only 118. So, I feel like gelato</u>
  <u t="639519">will perk me up. And I forgot to show</u>
  <u t="641040">you this restaurant's view is insane.</u>
  <u t="643690">[Music]</u>
  <u t="662240">Lonnie and I made it to Srento and</u>
  <u t="664000">before we get into anything, we need to</u>
  <u t="665920">eat because we're getting hungry and</u>
  <u t="667920">we're starving. We haven't eaten since</u>
  <u t="670320">last night. Had dinner at 7:00 p.m. and</u>
  <u t="672240">it is now 1:00 p.m. the next day. So,</u>
  <u t="674800">we're having a little drink before our</u>
  <u t="676800">sandwiches and then we're going to get</u>
  <u t="678800">sauté</u>
  <u t="680330">[Music]</u>
  <u t="699040">postcard shopping. I think I'm going to</u>
  <u t="701200">make these into prints for my wall.</u>
  <u t="705600">That red ball</u>
  <u t="707839">Lobby</u>
  <u t="710850">[Music]</u>
  <u t="732480">and I just came to the shop and it</u>
  <u t="734079">literally is called Santa's</u>
  <u t="736240">and everything is</u>
  <u t="739300">[Music]</u>
  <u t="745360">&gt;&gt; Annie and I have left the city center of</u>
  <u t="747360">Sarto and now we're at the beach or</u>
  <u t="749680">getting really close. So, we're going to</u>
  <u t="751040">head down and have a little beach day</u>
  <u t="752720">for the next couple of hours before</u>
  <u t="754800">coming back for dinner and then have to</u>
  <u t="756399">take the ferry back to Positano, which</u>
  <u t="758240">is where we're staying. But, we're super</u>
  <u t="760240">excited.</u>
  <u t="763330">[Music]</u>
  <u t="776000">This is an extreme sport. We just have</u>
  <u t="778959">to climb literally down all of those</u>
  <u t="780959">rocks and then change in public in an</u>
  <u t="784560">open space and then put our things up on</u>
  <u t="787040">a high rock so that no one can really</u>
  <u t="788480">get into them. And they're right up</u>
  <u t="790639">there in blocking London. The water is</u>
  <u t="793760">so blue. I just took my hair out. Nice.</u>
  <u t="797680">Oh my god, people keep jumping off the</u>
  <u t="799440">cliff.</u>
  <u t="801240">[Music]</u>
  <u t="813040">Three,</u>
  <u t="814800">two,</u>
  <u t="816480">one.</u>
  <u t="821510">[Music]</u>
  <u t="824000">situation that I have to get down from</u>
  <u t="826079">if I want to swim. So,</u>
  <u t="829440">it doesn't seem that high, but honestly,</u>
  <u t="831519">the rocks are so sharp, it's like not</u>
  <u t="834160">even funny. Oh my god,</u>
  <u t="838399">it's a little crab, guys. That's kind of</u>
  <u t="840880">scary.</u>
  <u t="842880">My feet. Sorry, Mr. Crab. Just going to</u>
  <u t="845199">step around him.</u>
  <u t="849120">I need to find Lonnie.</u>
  <u t="851440">Lonnie.</u>
  <u t="855100">[Music]</u>
  <u t="870630">[Music]</u>
  <u t="876720">Oh my gosh. Oh my GoPro.</u>
  <u t="880030">[Music]</u>
  <u t="883440">That's so</u>
  <u t="884700">[Music]</u>
  <u t="919519">Lonnie and I just made it to Amalfi</u>
  <u t="921120">today. We had to take the ferry at 9:00</u>
  <u t="923040">a.m. One of the earlier days that we've</u>
  <u t="924720">woken up this trip. Now we're just going</u>
  <u t="926880">to get a little breakfast. But I think</u>
  <u t="928560">we're going to go down a sweet treat</u>
  <u t="930160">route because yesterday we had like</u>
  <u t="931760">paninis and stuff and that wasn't really</u>
  <u t="933600">what we wanted. So today we're going to</u>
  <u t="936000">get a sweet treat for breakfast.</u>
  <u t="939040">And then I just got orange juice and</u>
  <u t="941519">apricot cookie and a raspberry tart as</u>
  <u t="945360">my breakfast.</u>
  <u t="949120">Freshly squeezed. Super good. There's a</u>
  <u t="950720">lot of salt though.</u>
  <u t="954650">[Music]</u>
  <u t="991600">This is the first top that I tried on. I</u>
  <u t="994000">really like the pattern. I love red</u>
  <u t="995839">gingham as you guys probably know cuz</u>
  <u t="997199">I've been wearing it this entire trip.</u>
  <u t="999199">But I just can't tell if this top kind</u>
  <u t="1000959">of looks frumpy because it's not like</u>
  <u t="1004000">cinched tight. It's like loose. Okay,</u>
  <u t="1007839">this is top two. Now, this is what it</u>
  <u t="1010399">looks like on me. I think this one's a</u>
  <u t="1012320">little bit more flattering just because</u>
  <u t="1014160">it's like tight all the way through. And</u>
  <u t="1016800">this is the third shirt that I'm trying</u>
  <u t="1018639">on. I thought this tank top would be a</u>
  <u t="1020480">little bit tighter, but it's quite loose</u>
  <u t="1022720">and it's not very form fitting. I could</u>
  <u t="1024400">probably cinch it in like this much. So,</u>
  <u t="1026799">I really like this pattern. I love blue</u>
  <u t="1028799">stripes, but I don't think I'm going to</u>
  <u t="1030480">get this one. And I made it to our</u>
  <u t="1032160">cooking. We made it. Somehow, I know I'm</u>
  <u t="1035280">sweating. We are also 30 minutes late,</u>
  <u t="1037120">but first we're starting off</u>
  <u t="1040260">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1058160">Heat. Heat.</u>
  <u t="1060600">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1068160">Heat. Heat.</u>
  <u t="1070720">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1091360">Heat.</u>
  <u t="1093270">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1101360">Heat.</u>
  <u t="1102810">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1108400">Heat.</u>
  <u t="1110360">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1116090">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1121840">Heat.</u>
  <u t="1123510">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1148720">Heat. Heat.</u>
  <u t="1156560">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1185679">We finish.</u>
  <u t="1187610">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1233280">Bye-bye.</u>
  <u t="1234570">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1270960">Hey,</u>
  <u t="1275270">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1279919">honey.</u>
  <u t="1283580">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1347039">I don't know.</u>
  <u t="1350080">Oh.</u>
  <u t="1354920">[Music]</u>
  </text>
