<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="CzQUvwoARto" uploader="Breanna Quan" channel="Breanna Quan" likes="22330" title="my first time in france 🥖 a few days in paris, french food, eiffel tower, biking &amp; lots of shopping" year="2025" month="10" day="17" is_ac="true">
  <u t="2800">[Music]</u>
  <u t="6330">[Laughter]</u>
  <u t="7200">[Music]</u>
  <u t="11840">Thank you.</u>
  <u t="17550">[Music]</u>
  <u t="29920">We have officially made it to Paris.</u>
  <u t="32000">We're in the Airbnb now and it is so</u>
  <u t="34239">cute. I have to show you guys a little</u>
  <u t="35760">tour. This is what it looks like when</u>
  <u t="37120">you first walk in. And this is the</u>
  <u t="39600">kitchen. I think it is so cute. I love</u>
  <u t="41680">that it is all out. I love the</u>
  <u t="43920">industrial feel of everything. And</u>
  <u t="45840">there's even a desk and like</u>
  <u t="47200">workstation. I'm not going to do any</u>
  <u t="48879">work this trip. Let me turn this on. So</u>
  <u t="51280">now you guys can see what the view looks</u>
  <u t="53280">like. And then this is what the bedroom</u>
  <u t="55840">looks like. And there's even shades that</u>
  <u t="57520">go up and down. So, I think that is so</u>
  <u t="59840">cute and perfect for a good night's</u>
  <u t="61680">sleep. This is the bathroom. It's also</u>
  <u t="63920">super spacious. There's a washing</u>
  <u t="65519">machine as well. And then a really nice</u>
  <u t="67119">shower. And so, I'm going to be in here</u>
  <u t="68880">for the next 4 days. But now, I'm</u>
  <u t="70400">literally starving, so I'm going to get</u>
  <u t="71680">ready and head out to a little beastro</u>
  <u t="73360">for some dinner. I have not made any</u>
  <u t="75119">reservations during this trip. I have</u>
  <u t="76799">more of a bucket list planned for this</u>
  <u t="78479">trip. So, things that I want to see and</u>
  <u t="79920">do, but not necessarily all planned out</u>
  <u t="81680">hour by hour. Yeah, let's get ready.</u>
  <u t="84320">&gt;&gt; Okay, so Ainsy and I have just made it</u>
  <u t="86080">out of the Airbnb. We got dressed really</u>
  <u t="88320">quickly in matching brown and we've</u>
  <u t="90400">walked approximately 200 m before</u>
  <u t="92320">someone came up to us and asked to take</u>
  <u t="93520">a picture of us. So, we said no</u>
  <u t="96720">obviously because that's kind of odd and</u>
  <u t="98320">I also don't really understand like what</u>
  <u t="100000">they were asking for. It was a man</u>
  <u t="102079">laughing too.</u>
  <u t="102799">&gt;&gt; Yeah, it was a man also. He was on the</u>
  <u t="104720">phone and it was so odd. I was like no.</u>
  <u t="106640">And he was like really</u>
  <u t="107759">&gt;&gt; a peace sign.</u>
  <u t="108720">&gt;&gt; Yeah, he was like really take a photo.</u>
  <u t="110479">But anyways,</u>
  <u t="115500">[Music]</u>
  <u t="122320">&gt;&gt; okay and I managed to get a table</u>
  <u t="123759">without a reservation. We only had to</u>
  <u t="125600">wait like 7 minutes, so honestly not bad</u>
  <u t="128160">timing, but it is like 8:00 right now.</u>
  <u t="130479">And we just ordered starters of</u>
  <u t="133599">And then we got a steak freeze to share</u>
  <u t="136319">dessert at home.</u>
  <u t="140800">What happened?</u>
  <u t="146730">[Music]</u>
  <u t="153519">&gt;&gt; Okay, Angie and I wanted to get a little</u>
  <u t="155280">bit of sweet and sour, so we got a Paris</u>
  <u t="158640">breast. And the one that we had last</u>
  <u t="160160">time was so so small. So, this is truly</u>
  <u t="162800">the best thing ever.</u>
  <u t="164720">&gt;&gt; That looks so good.</u>
  <u t="167920">M.</u>
  <u t="172720">&gt;&gt; Right. It's so good. This looks so good.</u>
  <u t="178640">Look.</u>
  <u t="182560">I've had this dream and this goal to</u>
  <u t="184239">bike to the Eiffel Tower on my first day</u>
  <u t="185920">in Paris to watch it sparkle, but it is</u>
  <u t="188000">4 km away. So, we're going to city bike</u>
  <u t="190720">it. I honestly haven't even city biked</u>
  <u t="192560">in Toronto, so we're going to have to</u>
  <u t="194239">see how it goes in Paris.</u>
  <u t="198570">[Music]</u>
  <u t="205599">We made it. We made it to the Eiffel</u>
  <u t="208400">Tower. Barely following a route or a</u>
  <u t="210720">map. We were kind of just going with the</u>
  <u t="212080">flow of traffic. That was a little</u>
  <u t="214239">chaotic. We had no idea where the lanes</u>
  <u t="216239">were. We were like trying to follow</u>
  <u t="218080">them, but yeah, we can't see.</u>
  <u t="220319">&gt;&gt; Yeah. No, my contacts are also like not</u>
  <u t="222000">the right prescription, but now the</u>
  <u t="223519">Eiffel Tower is going to twinkle. So,</u>
  <u t="227250">[Applause]</u>
  <u t="228300">[Music]</u>
  <u t="235280">&gt;&gt; hi guys. It is day two of Paris. I've</u>
  <u t="237200">just gotten ready super quickly. I'm</u>
  <u t="238720">wearing a matching set today. It's like</u>
  <u t="240159">a corset and mini skirt. And we just</u>
  <u t="242080">come to one of the oldest bakeries that</u>
  <u t="243519">make croissants and it's called Soher as</u>
  <u t="245519">recommended to us by our friend Vincent.</u>
  <u t="247040">We're just going to get a classic</u>
  <u t="248239">croissant and then probably a cappuccino</u>
  <u t="249920">or espresso at a nearby cafe before</u>
  <u t="252080">getting into the day. So, let's go</u>
  <u t="253439">inside.</u>
  <u t="255920">I decided to get a hot chocolate this</u>
  <u t="258000">morning because not a very big coffee or</u>
  <u t="260239">espresso person.</u>
  <u t="263050">[Music]</u>
  <u t="298479">Now, we've just come to Seson because</u>
  <u t="300240">they were super kind and gave us a</u>
  <u t="301919">little gift card. So, we're going to</u>
  <u t="303280">pick out a few things and try on a few</u>
  <u t="304960">of their new styles for fall.</u>
  <u t="312160">Okay, this is the first cardigan that</u>
  <u t="314560">I'm trying on. I think it is so cute. I</u>
  <u t="316639">really love this color. I think I'm</u>
  <u t="318000">going to be able to wear it with</u>
  <u t="319039">multiple things. I like that the sleeves</u>
  <u t="320880">are not too short and so I think I'm</u>
  <u t="323199">going to go with this one. I'm going to</u>
  <u t="324479">show you guys this other color and other</u>
  <u t="326080">size, but I think it's too big. So, this</u>
  <u t="327840">is the same cardigan in a different</u>
  <u t="329360">color. And I think it just looked a</u>
  <u t="330880">little too big for me, especially</u>
  <u t="332240">because the arms are going to be tight.</u>
  <u t="334320">So, I think it doesn't make sense for it</u>
  <u t="336080">to be tight and then super duper loose.</u>
  <u t="338479">I like this color, though.</u>
  <u t="345240">[Music]</u>
  <u t="365280">Hey guys, I just got in from Saison and</u>
  <u t="367360">I've just had a little outfit change and</u>
  <u t="369039">I feel like I usually stray away from</u>
  <u t="370479">color in my wardrobe, but this trip</u>
  <u t="372080">we're definitely changing that. And the</u>
  <u t="373199">same goes for dressing up my phone. And</u>
  <u t="375280">of course, that's all thanks to Caseify.</u>
  <u t="377600">Every time I change my phone, the one</u>
  <u t="378800">thing that I do is make sure that it's</u>
  <u t="380080">wearing a Caseify case. And so with the</u>
  <u t="381919">launch of the iPhone 17, that is no</u>
  <u t="383600">exception. I can take this off and you</u>
  <u t="385120">can see the print a little bit better. I</u>
  <u t="386639">feel like it matches my outfit so</u>
  <u t="388080">perfectly. I even have this other one</u>
  <u t="389840">which is more fun and I think even</u>
  <u t="391360">matches my lip shade perfectly. Casey</u>
  <u t="393600">always just makes the most fun prints. I</u>
  <u t="395280">have this Matcha made in heaven and it</u>
  <u t="396960">is a glaze case and so it's super high</u>
  <u t="398720">shine and of course all their cases are</u>
  <u t="400319">Mag Safe because I always like to have</u>
  <u t="401919">accessories on it. This is the snappy</u>
  <u t="403600">snap and stick grip stand and so it</u>
  <u t="405440">suctions onto smooth surfaces so you can</u>
  <u t="407199">do a fit check or if you just want to</u>
  <u t="408560">prop it up somewhere and then also just</u>
  <u t="410000">pops out like this. And that's just how</u>
  <u t="411440">you use it as the grip stand. But I</u>
  <u t="413360">really just love how the cases are so</u>
  <u t="414880">customizable. It can go with any of your</u>
  <u t="416560">aesthetics. I just love that Caseify has</u>
  <u t="418319">scratch resistant, strong, and</u>
  <u t="419919">protective for your actual phone</u>
  <u t="421440">products. There are so many different</u>
  <u t="422479">prints to choose from and accessories.</u>
  <u t="424240">They even have really cute phone straps</u>
  <u t="426000">that are perfect just to have around</u>
  <u t="427280">your hand. If you're kind of clumsy like</u>
  <u t="428560">me and you like drop your phone often,</u>
  <u t="430080">it's good to just have a little strap</u>
  <u t="431280">around your wrist. Not to mention, it's</u>
  <u t="432800">very cute and there are so many</u>
  <u t="433919">different styles. And obviously, today I</u>
  <u t="435520">picked up more cases from the Lou. The</u>
  <u t="437360">store is so cute. They had so many</u>
  <u t="438880">different options on the wall. There are</u>
  <u t="440080">artwork inspired cases as well. So, if</u>
  <u t="441919">you want to get 15% off at Caseify or</u>
  <u t="443840">see the other Caseify aesthetics, then</u>
  <u t="445599">you can go to my link in the description</u>
  <u t="446880">box below or scan the QR code on screen.</u>
  <u t="448960">We're headed over to the Lou right now.</u>
  <u t="450800">I've heard from so many people that you</u>
  <u t="452240">can spend days exploring the Lou. So,</u>
  <u t="454080">we're allocating a big chunk of the</u>
  <u t="455680">afternoon and I'm actually going to</u>
  <u t="456960">break out the new shoes that I got in</u>
  <u t="458560">Nice. I got these really cute ballerinas</u>
  <u t="460479">and I think it just goes well with my</u>
  <u t="462160">outfit right now. So, yeah, let's get</u>
  <u t="463759">going.</u>
  <u t="465710">[Music]</u>
  <u t="475960">[Music]</u>
  <u t="485450">[Music]</u>
  <u t="490479">It is so incredibly busy here. Oh my</u>
  <u t="493199">gosh.</u>
  <u t="495120">So, we have made our way through all of</u>
  <u t="498000">level one here. We started at Napoleon</u>
  <u t="500319">III's apartment and then obviously saw</u>
  <u t="502560">all of these antiques and then ended up</u>
  <u t="504720">at the Mona Lisa, which was so packed.</u>
  <u t="507919">And now we're on level zero just looking</u>
  <u t="511039">at all of these different sculptures,</u>
  <u t="512880">which is the room that I'm in right now.</u>
  <u t="515360">Some of these sculptures are so insane.</u>
  <u t="517519">But we're trying to make our way down to</u>
  <u t="520000">minus one as well, just to see like</u>
  <u t="522159">history of the Lou. We finished at the</u>
  <u t="524640">lube and now we're headed to the six</u>
  <u t="526560">arandis mall for a steaks dinner part</u>
  <u t="529920">two because it includes two rounds of</u>
  <u t="531519">steak and then unlimited fries.</u>
  <u t="534330">[Music]</u>
  <u t="545680">So that is where we were supposed to go</u>
  <u t="547600">for dinner but the line literally is out</u>
  <u t="550480">of frame. So, we are not going there</u>
  <u t="552560">because I do not want to wait more than</u>
  <u t="554640">like an hour and a half to have dinner</u>
  <u t="556800">because it's already 7:00. So, we're</u>
  <u t="558800">just going to pop in to another place</u>
  <u t="560480">and then I do have a cafe spot that I</u>
  <u t="562480">want to go to for dessert. So, that's</u>
  <u t="564399">our plan for now. Also, I want to talk</u>
  <u t="566640">about our bike ride. It was literally</u>
  <u t="569200">supposed to take 10 minutes. It was 5</u>
  <u t="571279">km. It's not even that far and it took</u>
  <u t="573200">45. 10 minutes turned into 45. Well, to</u>
  <u t="575839">be fair, there was rush hour and then we</u>
  <u t="577600">got lost. I have never seen that many</u>
  <u t="579040">bikers on the road unless it was for an</u>
  <u t="580640">actual race. Like, this is insane. I'm</u>
  <u t="582480">not even a biker. I don't know why I'm</u>
  <u t="583760">biking during rush hour here.</u>
  <u t="587680">[Music]</u>
  <u t="607900">[Music]</u>
  <u t="619690">[Music]</u>
  <u t="642240">We are in Pen this morning. The bags are</u>
  <u t="645120">so cute. You guys know I have been</u>
  <u t="646320">wearing them for several years now. And</u>
  <u t="647920">so I'm finally in one of the Paris</u>
  <u t="649440">showrooms, but I'm torn between a few</u>
  <u t="651120">styles. So I'm going to show you guys.</u>
  <u t="652640">So, this is the first style that I</u>
  <u t="655040">really love and I am really close to</u>
  <u t="656720">getting just because I love a little</u>
  <u t="658079">shoulder bag. But then I also really</u>
  <u t="660640">love this style. It's a little bit</u>
  <u t="662399">chunkier and I feel like can hold more</u>
  <u t="664160">things. I just feel like the odds of me</u>
  <u t="665920">wearing it are a little bit slimmer</u>
  <u t="667519">because it's more of a handheld bag and</u>
  <u t="669600">I am more of a shoulder girl bag. So,</u>
  <u t="672640">I'm going to try both on and see what</u>
  <u t="674399">works.</u>
  <u t="678340">[Music]</u>
  <u t="682399">I got my first matcha latte in Paris.</u>
  <u t="684800">And of course, it is a strawberry one.</u>
  <u t="686160">It also matches my top today.</u>
  <u t="688890">[Music]</u>
  <u t="694390">[Music]</u>
  <u t="701200">Our breakfast spans two tables, but we</u>
  <u t="704399">got a French breakfast, which is one hot</u>
  <u t="707200">drink, orange juice, and I just chose</u>
  <u t="708800">bread and butter. And then the English</u>
  <u t="710320">breakfast was two eggs, and we chose an</u>
  <u t="712480">omelette, bread, yogurt, and also a hot</u>
  <u t="714880">drink and orange juice.</u>
  <u t="718650">[Music]</u>
  <u t="730240">I completely forget the building we were</u>
  <u t="731839">just in, but I did a bunch of souvenir</u>
  <u t="733680">shopping and I'm so excited to show you</u>
  <u t="735120">guys a haul when I get home. But now</u>
  <u t="736560">we're headed back just to drop off some</u>
  <u t="738000">stuff because it's getting a little bit</u>
  <u t="739279">heavy. And then we're going to explore</u>
  <u t="741040">Le Mar.</u>
  <u t="747270">[Music]</u>
  <u t="752000">We got raspberry, pistachio, a Halloween</u>
  <u t="755120">special, matcha, lemon, and tiramisu.</u>
  <u t="761920">&gt;&gt; That's little strong matcha flavor.</u>
  <u t="767370">[Music]</u>
  <u t="769279">&gt;&gt; You with your heels,</u>
  <u t="771440">your boots.</u>
  <u t="774770">[Music]</u>
  <u t="783290">[Music]</u>
  <u t="785839">I will figure it out eventually.</u>
  <u t="791160">[Music]</u>
  <u t="796959">tower</u>
  <u t="802780">[Music]</u>
  <u t="806880">right now.</u>
  <u t="815930">[Music]</u>
  <u t="820959">Guys, I have just gotten in and I'm</u>
  <u t="822880">already seated in this chair because I</u>
  <u t="825200">have been in these tall boots since</u>
  <u t="827519">10:30 a.m. It is now 12:30 a.m. That's</u>
  <u t="830720">literally over 12 hours. These heels are</u>
  <u t="832720">literally not a joke. They are at least</u>
  <u t="834720">3 to 4 inches tall. They are so dirty</u>
  <u t="836720">now. But I literally just need to take</u>
  <u t="838480">these off with you because this is</u>
  <u t="840480">insane. Oh my gosh, my feet are actually</u>
  <u t="843519">so freaking dead. And you guys know I'm</u>
  <u t="845600">literally a flat shoe girl, too. I don't</u>
  <u t="847199">even know if my feet remember how to lay</u>
  <u t="848959">flat. They've just been like this</u>
  <u t="850399">literally all day. But yeah, now I'm</u>
  <u t="852079">going to massage and raise my feet.</u>
  <u t="859680">[Music]</u>
  </text>
