<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="5pYZUy-6Ssc" uploader="Luisito Comunica" channel="Luisito Comunica" likes="287164" title="Probando comida callejera en ALEMANIA | ¡El paraíso de la salchicha! 🇩🇪🌭" year="2025" month="4" day="22" date="20250422" is_ac="false">
  <u t="0">Wow! See! The size of this sausage is massive.</u>
  <u t="4320">Of course it is, we can't be in the land of sausage without devouring some good</u>
  <u t="8669">ones. It's not for nothing that Germany is called the sausage capital.</u>
  <u t="23680">Welcome to another edition of Luisillo, El Gordillo.</u>
  <u t="28328">We are in Germany, beautiful European lands, the capital of beer and sausage.</u>
  <u t="36103">It's been years since I've been here, it's been a long, long time since I've visited.</u>
  <u t="41408">And look how beautiful it is, it is a delight and something tells me that in</u>
  <u t="45051">this video, we are going to give more than hard to the fattening.</u>
  <u t="48282">We will only be touring the city of Munich, in fact, that's all I will be</u>
  <u t="53636">visiting during my trip, and we start in the Vigtualen Market area, a lively</u>
  <u t="59212">market where you can get everything from the finest butchery, the most</u>
  <u t="64346">intoxicating beer and the freshest of rivers.</u>
  <u t="68268">And something tells me it's going to be tasty, it's going to be succulent.</u>
  <u t="71939">So, come on, let's not make more time, let's find out what the Germans get fat</u>
  <u t="76069">on in these beautiful streets.</u>
  <u t="78040">Normally, I would say: Let's hit it, but we are in Germany, so I'll say: Gemma.</u>
  <u t="89240">We start this gastronomic adventure with some authentic sausages.</u>
  <u t="98800">Of course, we can't be in the land of sausages without devouring some good,</u>
  <u t="104417">thick, all colors, all flavors.</u>
  <u t="106880">In fact, did you know that Munich is nicknamed the City of One Hundred and One</u>
  <u t="111288">Sausages? Just like the One Hundred and One Dalmatians, here they are the One</u>
  <u t="115640">Hundred and One Sausages, because in fact they boast of having many different</u>
  <u t="119991">types with different animals, different preparations, the sausage paradise.</u>
  <u t="124480">So, send this video to your sausage-loving friend right now and say: Brother,</u>
  <u t="129452">what are you doing? You need to go to Germany right now.</u>
  <u t="133534">Let's start with a local classic, the very famous Weissewurst.</u>
  <u t="138400">This literally means white sausage, which is a sausage prepared with veal, that</u>
  <u t="144288">is, with cow, baby.</u>
  <u t="146180">I am told that this is what explains the color of the sausage, as well as its</u>
  <u t="150565">preparation and the spices used. Check it out here, it is very interesting.</u>
  <u t="154960">To eat this in a proper way, we are going to soak it in this mustard, which is a</u>
  <u t="160222">sweet mustard, but we are not going to eat all of it, we are just going to eat</u>
  <u t="165354">the inside and leave the skin intact.</u>
  <u t="168040">This is the method, I am told, so that the sausage does not get cold and you</u>
  <u t="172772">always have warm meat inside.</u>
  <u t="174840">So, let's see if I can do it.</u>
  <u t="176910">We soak the sausage in this delicious way and then we have to bite the meat</u>
  <u t="182493">gently so as not to break the skin.</u>
  <u t="185240">Let's see if I can do it, okay?</u>
  <u t="188789">Wow! And yes, it's really good. Come on! No, my guide, here is a crack of the</u>
  <u t="194859">veal tasting.</u>
  <u t="196029">And now, it caught my attention that right now it's morning, okay? And look how</u>
  <u t="201029">many people are really here tasting a delicious sausage.</u>
  <u t="205040">They tell me that this type of sausage, the white sausage, is eaten until 12</u>
  <u t="209757">o'clock in the morning. That's the traditional way, after 12:00, man, a heavier sausage.</u>
  <u t="215349">But to start the day well with German energy, before 12: 00, your white sausage.</u>
  <u t="220921">By the way, prices, they sold me three sausages with a pretzel, with a bun for</u>
  <u t="226772">6.50 €, impressive, for those Europeans, it is what it is.</u>
  <u t="231665">Let's move on to the next thing: I ordered this other typical dish called</u>
  <u t="236176">Lieblkäse. I hope I'm pronouncing it right, I don't know any German.</u>
  <u t="240506">Basically, what it is, is a bread made with pork.</u>
  <u t="244211">In fact, we can see, check the texture, how strange it is, like the famous pork</u>
  <u t="248244">cheese that we eat in Mexico, for example, something like that I think.</u>
  <u t="252019">And what it is, is basically a sausage, ground pork, then covered with bread</u>
  <u t="256666">dough, put in the oven and it comes out with this rather curious texture, which</u>
  <u t="261497">I personally had never seen before.</u>
  <u t="264031">We are going to dip this one in the spicy mustard. Look at this marvel.</u>
  <u t="268229">Provechito, as they say around here. Guten Appetit.</u>
  <u t="272039">What a funny taste and above all what a funny texture.</u>
  <u t="275800">Indeed, it is a meaty bread. I don't even know how else to describe it.</u>
  <u t="279680">We're going to pair it with a tasty mash here.</u>
  <u t="282950">And with the authentic Crowd Sour, it couldn't be more authentic.</u>
  <u t="287520">Look, I'm not a big fan of Crowd Sour, but being here, we are not going to</u>
  <u t="291330">disrespect it. We are going to taste everything that the carnals provide us.</u>
  <u t="295560">No, but complain that with this little porky bun, it makes a nice contrast.</u>
  <u t="299520">And then, don't you see this little sausage called rosfrasburst? Basically,</u>
  <u t="304263">roasted sausage.</u>
  <u t="305560">Check it out, they tell me you eat it in a bun. So, let's grab it, let's put all</u>
  <u t="310182">the meat in this bun.</u>
  <u t="311520">It's going inside. Oh, man, oh, man, it's so good. Honestly, a 10 out of 10</u>
  <u t="317094">delicacy, tall sausages.</u>
  <u t="319019">And you may be wondering why I didn't order a cervezón to go with my sausages.</u>
  <u t="323087">Let's see, it's too early, we're on beer right now.</u>
  <u t="325866">But what is cool is that here in Munich I have seen that there are many drinking</u>
  <u t="330494">fountains that are marked with this sign, Trink Varser.</u>
  <u t="333800">They also come here in Baraila, for our carnals who can't see, let them know.</u>
  <u t="338005">And yes, you don't spend on soda, no more spending 6,50 € on a bottle of water</u>
  <u t="343464">from the fridge.</u>
  <u t="344720">Here, for free. Well, Lucita. That's cold. I hope no bums peed in there,</u>
  <u t="349958">wherever the water goes, because I really enjoyed it.</u>
  <u t="354000">Tasty, we stayed hydrated. Let's continue the swallowing.</u>
  <u t="364598">Not even 10 minutes passed and I was already thirsty. It was already past noon,</u>
  <u t="369782">and we were about to drink a beer.</u>
  <u t="372506">They brought us this one called Tegernser, which is delicious. Also, check out</u>
  <u t="377633">this other one. A beer with lemon.</u>
  <u t="380000">Are you watching this? Light, tasty. No, man, it's really tasty to be here and</u>
  <u t="385558">know that it's part of the culture to drink beer.</u>
  <u t="389400">Here they even sell beer at McDonald's. It's a wonderful thing.</u>
  <u t="393093">As my grandfather used to say: Wherever you go, do what you see. And I see that</u>
  <u t="397586">here everyone is drinking wine and beer all the time, so it's okay.</u>
  <u t="401520">It is a cultural exchange.</u>
  <u t="403370">Now they have brought me to the fish corner, that's what it's called, the fish</u>
  <u t="409480">corner, to try some fish sandwiches.</u>
  <u t="412779">They tell me that culturally these sandwiches are eaten when you have a hangover</u>
  <u t="417535">or when you know you are going to drink a lot during the day.</u>
  <u t="421688">I don't know, the theory here is that the fish does something to dampen the</u>
  <u t="425858">alcohol in your body, so you hold on longer.</u>
  <u t="428495">And in the same way, if you have a hangover, it kind of makes the hangover pass</u>
  <u t="432530">less painfully, more smoothly. How much science is there in that? Well, I don't</u>
  <u t="436565">know, but it's popular belief.</u>
  <u t="438505">And we ordered two different sandwiches, each priced at 4,50 €, around there.</u>
  <u t="444011">This is a salmon sandwich with onions, which, from what our guide tells me,</u>
  <u t="448846">words of not my words, this is a sandwich that women tend to order more.</u>
  <u t="453954">Don't attack me in the comments, that's what my 60 year old guide told me. No</u>
  <u t="457836">one will get mad at me. And this other one is the one most often ordered by men.</u>
  <u t="462040">This fish is called, I'm reading it here, bismarck hermin.</u>
  <u t="465520">This is a local name because they tell me that Mr. Bismarck was someone in the</u>
  <u t="470799">army who promised his men that when they were at sea sailing, battling,</u>
  <u t="475605">whatever, they would never lack food.</u>
  <u t="478400">So, that's what he was fed and that's why to this day he is known by his name of</u>
  <u t="483084">the general, the captain, the advisor, Bismarck.</u>
  <u t="486353">So, I have neither a hangover nor do I plan to drink much today, although we</u>
  <u t="490899">shall see.</u>
  <u t="491880">We will taste this sandwich. Provechito. Guten Appetit.</u>
  <u t="496400">Interesting preparation. The fish is not really cooked, it feels a bit raw, but</u>
  <u t="500878">they put a lot of lemon in it and this gives it an excellent taste.</u>
  <u t="504800">And in fact, something that I didn't mention just now, something special about</u>
  <u t="508519">this fish is that it can last a long time without refrigeration, as long as you</u>
  <u t="512286">leave it with an appropriate amount of salt.</u>
  <u t="514848">That is also why it is said that General Bismarck, this guy I am telling you</u>
  <u t="518318">about, used to feed his troops with this, because even if suddenly there was no</u>
  <u t="521926">fish at all, everything was empty, they would keep it there with salt.</u>
  <u t="525280">Everything was fine, everybody was happy, everybody was a winner. Now, what?</u>
  <u t="528592">Let's go with this salmon with onion, which by the amount of onion I'm seeing, I</u>
  <u t="532078">guess it's more of an onion sandwich with salmon.</u>
  <u t="534368">Those of you who are followers of Luisillo El Gordillo know that we are not fans</u>
  <u t="538459">of onion at all here, but again, wherever you go, do what you see, then, onion</u>
  <u t="542448">and all.</u>
  <u t="543720">This is a much more familiar taste. This one, of course, has been eaten many</u>
  <u t="547437">times. How wonderful, how excellent and above all, I love that it is time to</u>
  <u t="551155">drink a good beer.</u>
  <u t="552200">Salucita, they said it around here. Just.</u>
  <u t="555789">It tastes good, it tastes good. I feel more like my baracho. Let's move on.</u>
  <u t="563697">Time for a more substantial dish. Let's devour an exquisite Schweine</u>
  <u t="568592">Schweinbratten. I hope I'm pronouncing it right.</u>
  <u t="572186">I felt like Christopher Walsh in Bastard Without Glory. Schweinbratten.</u>
  <u t="577344">This is one of the most beloved dishes from the southern region of Germany and</u>
  <u t="581672">also Austria.</u>
  <u t="582916">It is basically a massive piece of pork, accompanied, of course, by cabbage,</u>
  <u t="589224">dumplings or potato dumplings and bathed in a dark beer sauce.</u>
  <u t="594520">Of course, we're going to pair it with a cervezota, but look at this</u>
  <u t="598366">cervezazota, it's the one with my face on it.</u>
  <u t="601034">It weighs more than a newborn baby, it is really tremendous.</u>
  <u t="605040">More than drinking it, it's more like you're going to take a dive, a dip, a swim.</u>
  <u t="610677">Let's see how the tasty piglet is. Let's slice a good piece. No, man, this eats</u>
  <u t="616751">two. We bathe it well with the sauce. In you go.</u>
  <u t="621121">And we're going to slice this dumpling too. They're basically little balls of</u>
  <u t="625198">dough, like a tasty filling. We're still going to bathe it well.</u>
  <u t="630097">A full, hearty meal.</u>
  <u t="632120">And let's see how much they jammed it in, because this place is very touristy.</u>
  <u t="636103">Here behind me is the top plaza, very touristy. Let's bet, I'm going to bet that</u>
  <u t="640502">they've stuck us with 35 €.</u>
  <u t="642109">How much do you bet? Let's see. Nothing more and nothing less than... Ah! 22</u>
  <u t="647039">euros. Nememen! And the barrel of beer? 13 euros.</u>
  <u t="650350">All added to the 35 I said. With everything and beer, it's not bad at all. I</u>
  <u t="653761">understand why it is one of the most loved dishes in the region.</u>
  <u t="657024">Hearty, fattening and tasty.</u>
  <u t="669837">Well, the sausage was very tasty a while ago, but I want you to appreciate,</u>
  <u t="674991">please, the size of this bestiality.</u>
  <u t="677600">Joloburgo, it's really huge. How much will this thing tell me? Let's see, it's</u>
  <u t="681696">bigger than my forearm. Are you seeing this? I want to make it very clear that</u>
  <u t="685793">it's a single sausage.</u>
  <u t="687120">No, it's not several. I'm going to open the bread a little bit and check. It is</u>
  <u t="691000">only one, there is no division. There is no trickery here, no tricky magic trick.</u>
  <u t="695095">For 8,50 €, I bought this marvel.</u>
  <u t="698560">And look, I now understand why, indeed, Germany is the land of the sausage,</u>
  <u t="703639">because Munich is the city of the seat, a sausage.</u>
  <u t="707160">We agree that for the first bite, having so much bread, you have to deep-throat</u>
  <u t="713251">it a little bit, that is, you have to choke, there is no other way.</u>
  <u t="718560">Let's start with just sausage and then we will gradually add more. Come on,</u>
  <u t="723597">first the sausage. Actually, it's brutal. A pork sausage.</u>
  <u t="727560">I'm going to cheat a little bit, I'm going to move it a little bit here. There</u>
  <u t="730132">it is, so we can eat with everything and everything.</u>
  <u t="732099">Now it's time for the master test, the sausage bite. Hey, powerful combination.</u>
  <u t="737120">And I don't know what it is about the preparation of this specific sausage that</u>
  <u t="741165">makes it a little bit spicy. Let's see, also the cabbage, obviously, is strong</u>
  <u t="745159">in flavor.</u>
  <u t="745840">The mustard is also slightly spicy, but look how delicious it is. I think that</u>
  <u t="749974">eight euros is a fair price for this, especially because of the impression factor.</u>
  <u t="754440">In other words, it is very impressive, very beautiful.</u>
  <u t="757524">Do two people eat, or one person with a sweet tooth? I don't know how typical</u>
  <u t="761997">this is.</u>
  <u t="762930">Please, people from Germany, comment. But look what impressed me.</u>
  <u t="767601">I am told that if we had come to this place on a weekend, we would have found it</u>
  <u t="772913">full of drunk Germans.</u>
  <u t="774842">This is a real beer garden, it is a beer garden, a very fashionable concept</u>
  <u t="779512">nowadays in the world, maybe in your city there is one.</u>
  <u t="783183">Well today, being in Munich, I wanted to come to one and boy did they bring me,</u>
  <u t="787704">but unfortunately we are shooting this on a Wednesday and boy is it closed.</u>
  <u t="792120">Nevertheless, I will have my beer with a classic schnitzel.</u>
  <u t="797840">Schnitzel is actually a dish from Austria, I want to make that clear. But of</u>
  <u t="802044">course it is eaten a lot in Germany as well.</u>
  <u t="804600">The main difference is that in Austria the schnitzel or milanesa, as we know it</u>
  <u t="809552">from our side of the world, is usually made with veal.</u>
  <u t="813280">Here in Germany it is usually made with pork or chicken.</u>
  <u t="817440">And this makes me wonder why in our part of the world we call this recipe milanesa.</u>
  <u t="822240">Well, it's not from Milano, is it? Or I don't know, or is there some debate</u>
  <u t="825860">there? Just like our carnals, the Peruvians and Chileans, no one knows where the</u>
  <u t="829721">pisco is from.</u>
  <u t="830560">Something like that will happen between Italy and Austria, that nobody knows</u>
  <u t="834633">where the schnitzel or Milanese Milanese is from? Look, if anyone knows, please</u>
  <u t="838867">post it in the comments I'm intrigued, I'm curious.</u>
  <u t="842109">Now, I want to clarify that surely the girl at the place saw me super touristy</u>
  <u t="847877">because she put katzup, she put ketchup, ketchup there.</u>
  <u t="852120">And as far as I know and as far as I've observed anyone else the day we go to</u>
  <u t="855834">Austria, boy we'll try a real one. Well come on, I'll dip with ketchup because</u>
  <u t="859596">that's how they served it to me. Guten Appetit.</u>
  <u t="862320">Look, very tasty, but I wish I could tell you something more interesting. I feel</u>
  <u t="866840">like when I go to Bips, when I go to Tox to eat my milanecita.</u>
  <u t="870737">A food that never fails, a safe food, a food that has traveled the world.</u>
  <u t="875375">I was pleased to have been able to order my Schnitzel, something that gets</u>
  <u t="878896">crossed off the list. Beautiful, tasty, an ordinary Milanese, but in an</u>
  <u t="882274">authentic German beer garden.</u>
  <u t="883840">It's closed, but it exists. Here we are. And you know what's brutal about these</u>
  <u t="888514">beer gardens? As I was telling you, there are these drinking fountains.</u>
  <u t="892840">And imagine, if you are here with your colleagues, after many beers, Luisillo is</u>
  <u t="898076">already drunk at his best here, taking the steps that are not forbidden, but</u>
  <u t="903051">allowed, because our back still doesn't give us much mobility.</u>
  <u t="907307">If you already feel very drunk, just get to the fountain and hydrate yourself</u>
  <u t="912932">and the next one.</u>
  <u t="914715">It's good, look, it's even responsible, it's tasty. Has anyone vomited here in</u>
  <u t="918870">the fountain? I'm sure I have, more than once.</u>
  <u t="921440">Someday I would love to come to Germany in October to experience an authentic</u>
  <u t="925668">Oktoberfest. That would be cool.</u>
  <u t="927546">Comment if you would like to see a video of an authentic Oktoberfest to see one</u>
  <u t="931727">of these squares full to overflowing and not that goat peeling merendo we came</u>
  <u t="935856">to find today.</u>
  <u t="944211">They brought me a pickle to try.</u>
  <u t="946600">I didn't know that pickles are something like very traditional in the Munich</u>
  <u t="950238">region, that in fact, for example, when it's Oktoberfest and such, and people</u>
  <u t="953924">come to celebrate here, it's like beer and pickle.</u>
  <u t="956480">And I'm told that in this specific place it's like very well known, that they go</u>
  <u t="960138">very viral a lot of TikToks and such, so there are people who come and say, did</u>
  <u t="963752">you know that for 70 cents you can buy a pickle of this size and it's massive</u>
  <u t="967273">and it's delicious.</u>
  <u t="968468">So, look, let's try it. Probechin, let's see how it is.</u>
  <u t="973640">How tasty. I've never bitten into a pickle like that before, check it out. And</u>
  <u t="978027">for 70 cents, it's brutal, isn't it? 80. For 80, my brother-in-law corrected me.</u>
  <u t="982983">When you come to Munich, you can have a sausage and a very fat pickle.</u>
  <u t="987120">Don't be afraid. We will now try a very typical food from this region of</u>
  <u t="995360">Germany, the Bavarian region, which is O'Basda.</u>
  <u t="1000920">O'basda is basically a cheese mixed with butter, with onion, with different</u>
  <u t="1007163">seasonings, all squashed together.</u>
  <u t="1010143">And I'm told that people from all over the country come to this region, to the</u>
  <u t="1014334">south of Germany, to taste it.</u>
  <u t="1016149">And even though it's a delicacy, it's really not expensive. It sells for 2.50 €</u>
  <u t="1021141">per 100 grams.</u>
  <u t="1022480">The owner of the store here tells us that on weekends they usually sell up to 30</u>
  <u t="1027450">kilos of this delicacy every day.</u>
  <u t="1029630">Let's see what all the fuss is about, what the hype is about.</u>
  <u t="1034401">I understand what the hype is about, I really do. And the guy here told us that</u>
  <u t="1039715">after taking a bite, a grape.</u>
  <u t="1041800">That will accentuate the notes. I agree wholeheartedly. What a delicacy, long</u>
  <u t="1047865">life, that's enough.</u>
  <u t="1050360">Ironically, despite Germany being the sausage capital of the world, internet</u>
  <u t="1056957">data says that 10 to 12% of the German population identify themselves as</u>
  <u t="1063207">vegetarians and 2 to 3% as vegans.</u>
  <u t="1066733">How's that? Curious. Just because you love sausage doesn't mean you can't also</u>
  <u t="1072809">eat organically.</u>
  <u t="1074200">There is also the very interesting fact that about 20% of the food, at least in</u>
  <u t="1080211">Munich, is produced organically, from local farms, no imports, no mass slaughtering.</u>
  <u t="1086880">Is this true? Look, we don't know, but we came to this section of the market</u>
  <u t="1091992">that is dedicated to vegetarian food places and in this place, called Michael's</u>
  <u t="1097306">Farm, from Mejael, they have prepared this dish for us, but tasty.</u>
  <u t="1101969">They have prepared for us here a little dish with cheese, cream and ravioli,</u>
  <u t="1106228">this is not vegan, it is vegetarian. Pesto and tomato, this is indeed vegan.</u>
  <u t="1110611">And something I was told is called pesto peperoncini. Whatever that means, look</u>
  <u t="1115922">it sounds interesting, it sounds peculiar.</u>
  <u t="1118880">Ok, so I made it in a very farmhouse, very artisanal way.</u>
  <u t="1123600">This tastes so good. Wow! Look how tasty it is.</u>
  <u t="1126927">Many times, I confess, I say to myself: How could anyone be a vegan when there</u>
  <u t="1131326">are so many delicious things that used to live?</u>
  <u t="1134280">I am the most carnivorous, but then I try this kind of dishes and I say: Okay,</u>
  <u t="1137776">it's not so bad.</u>
  <u t="1138939">If someday I go to India or what do I know, some territory like that with a lot</u>
  <u t="1143527">of vegetarian people who hardly eat meat, yes, I could.</u>
  <u t="1147247">This one is also delicious. You can eat tasty, of course you can.</u>
  <u t="1150600">And we are going to wash it down with this little shot that does not have</u>
  <u t="1153716">alcohol, but it is a ginger ferment drink, which I am told that if it is left to</u>
  <u t="1157131">ferment a little longer, it can be made into alcohol.</u>
  <u t="1159593">Salucita, as they say around here. Prost.</u>
  <u t="1162930">What a succulence. Right behind me we are looking at a real May tree.</u>
  <u t="1169000">Check this out. I've seen these many times on the internet and such, but I don't</u>
  <u t="1171936">think I've ever seen them in person.</u>
  <u t="1173360">Basically, what we are looking at is a tree trunk, as such, that instead of</u>
  <u t="1178010">leaves, has different illustrations, different drawings, and these are usually</u>
  <u t="1182847">found in markets around the cities of the villages.</u>
  <u t="1186200">The explanation why they have drawings on them is because....</u>
  <u t="1189320">Let's see, this is a tradition of maybe more than 500 years ago and people</u>
  <u t="1193651">didn't know how to read, only the most literate people really knew how to</u>
  <u t="1197925">interpret texts on a paper, on a wall.</u>
  <u t="1200560">So in order for people to know what was in the market, what was being sold, how</u>
  <u t="1204972">to identify a doctor, how to identify a beer place, it was all with little drawings.</u>
  <u t="1209800">So, to this day it is the custom that every five years the tree is changed with</u>
  <u t="1215515">new illustrations and it is quite an event, it is a big party, drunk Germans everywhere.</u>
  <u t="1222240">Nice, I had never seen a May tree so close.</u>
  <u t="1225726">There is no doubt that Germany is a country with a great quality of life.</u>
  <u t="1229880">They have very good transportation, they have security, it is a very cool</u>
  <u t="1234759">country. But what our people don't have is a great variety of fruits.</u>
  <u t="1239506">In fact, they tell me that until the 90's, people didn't know what a mango was.</u>
  <u t="1245920">They had seen it in photographs, in magazines, in newspapers, but it wasn't</u>
  <u t="1249845">like: I know the taste of a mango, I know the taste of an avocado.</u>
  <u t="1253420">And this place that they brought us to, which is called Exotent Müller, was one</u>
  <u t="1258890">of the first places that more than 30 years ago started to bring exotic fruits.</u>
  <u t="1265040">So it became famous among people because they could come here and get enchiladas.</u>
  <u t="1270040">I don't know, maybe people didn't know what enchilarse was, they didn't know</u>
  <u t="1273932">what it was to eat a navanerito, a chipotle, a chile guajillo.</u>
  <u t="1277226">And let's see, all this that they are teaching us is really nothing new to me. I</u>
  <u t="1281328">have this in the market around the corner, but here it is something very special.</u>
  <u t="1285600">And check this thing out, it is very curious to think about this. I mean, these</u>
  <u t="1290234">mangoes that we are seeing here, each mango costs 10 €.</u>
  <u t="1293680">Olo, borgo.</u>
  <u t="1294828">I don't know, for people who see me from Mexico, these are like 220 €, right?</u>
  <u t="1299195">For a mango.</u>
  <u t="1300120">We have to appreciate our crops. They gave me here a little juice that...</u>
  <u t="1303840">Let's see, it's a sugar cane juice, it's nothing special, but here they gave it</u>
  <u t="1307618">to me like that: It's a sugar cane juice from Brazil and I don't know what.</u>
  <u t="1311320">Look, a sample that we have to value a little more our delicious fruits we have.</u>
  <u t="1315645">How tasty.</u>
  <u t="1316350">Now, you know what really caught my attention? This fruit I am looking at here,</u>
  <u t="1320894">called Buddha's hand. Let's order some and let's try it.</u>
  <u t="1324240">They are selling me this Buddha's hand for 15 €, just borbo. Let's see how our</u>
  <u t="1329883">curious fruit is at 15 €.</u>
  <u t="1332165">They tell me that it is originally from Thailand, Vietnam, but curiously, this</u>
  <u t="1337004">fruit that we are seeing here in Germany grows in a humid, rainy climate, and</u>
  <u t="1341782">apparently, according to what my brother told me, it can grow here in the</u>
  <u t="1346312">winter. Let's see how it goes.</u>
  <u t="1348549">He told me to tear off a little piece like this and bite it in one bite.</u>
  <u t="1352753">This smells very acidic. Let's see if I don't get a tremendous gastritis here.</u>
  <u t="1357324">Probechin. What a rare fruit. I'm going to tell you what it tastes like. It's</u>
  <u t="1360755">like eating the peel of a lemon. That's all there is to it.</u>
  <u t="1363840">You take the lemon that's towards the back of your fridge, the one they sent you</u>
  <u t="1367249">with the tacos, which has been there for four weeks already, watching you ask</u>
  <u t="1370530">for more deliveries like this.</u>
  <u t="1371960">You take it and peel off the peel and that's what you taste. No, well yes, no</u>
  <u t="1376390">juice, very little carnita. Well look, I don't plan on wasting my 15 €.</u>
  <u t="1380600">I ordered my bag to go, I will eat it by force. I don't plan to waste that 15 €.</u>
  <u t="1385485">Okay, let's continue.</u>
  <u t="1390480">And to sweeten the to-go a bit, of course, we came for a real apple strudel.</u>
  <u t="1400200">Few desserts are as German as this one, it is true, but, fun fact, there is</u>
  <u t="1405759">possibly a theory that strudel is not a German dessert.</u>
  <u t="1410310">It is actually believed to be a recipe that comes from Austria.</u>
  <u t="1414080">Although, really, southern Germany and Austria share a lot of culture, as we</u>
  <u t="1418545">have been learning throughout this video.</u>
  <u t="1421080">And yes, apparently, apple strudel, which is somewhat known for being very</u>
  <u t="1424925">German, comes from Austria, although of course it is consumed a lot here in the</u>
  <u t="1429031">Czech Republic, in many parts of Europe.</u>
  <u t="1431280">This one we ordered is, of course, apple strudel with warm vanilla sauce.</u>
  <u t="1436320">Let's see how it goes. Taste. My weak point is what hurts me the most.</u>
  <u t="1442576">Why do I like beer and sweets so much? I don't quite understand, but how</u>
  <u t="1446065">wonderful. Applause for the chef. I can't say it in German, but it was delicious.</u>
  <u t="1450384">With this we sweeten it in a very German-Austrian way.</u>
  <u t="1461094">Well, there you have it. What an exquisite, fattening, intoxicating experience</u>
  <u t="1467401">this has been.</u>
  <u t="1468680">There is no doubt that Germans eat in a very, very succulent way.</u>
  <u t="1473360">What did they crave the most? I'll read them below in the comments.</u>
  <u t="1477311">And please, people who are familiar with German culture, let me know what I</u>
  <u t="1481761">missed so that the next time I come, I can document it.</u>
  <u t="1485240">Thank you so much for joining me on one more adventure. See you as always, you</u>
  <u t="1488709">know, in a few days with a new video.</u>
  <u t="1490720">Good bye to you. Tschüssss..</u>
  </text>
