<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="lhWgQxbgywc" uploader="Project Happiness " channel="Project Happiness " likes="45718" title="SOPRAVVIVERE SOTTOTERRA NELLE MINIERE DI SMERALDI IN COLOMBIA 🇨🇴" year="2025" month="6" day="25" date="20250625" date_ts="1750851029" is_ac="false">
  <u t="10125">Emeralds are not for everyone.</u>
  <u t="11708">You either feel the emerald's energy or you don't.</u>
  <u t="14166">Emerald is a stunning gemstone.</u>
  <u t="16166">To me, it's unmatched. I've seen diamonds, rubies, sapphires...</u>
  <u t="21041">But emeralds have something that pulls you in.</u>
  <u t="25375">And when you break the stone off the pole, you can actually feel the energy it radiates.</u>
  <u t="33041">This is the square where emeralds sell best in the world.</u>
  <u t="37083">This one's worth 300 thousand pesos, and that one 100 thousand.</u>
  <u t="40500">This one's worth 2 million.</u>
  <u t="42375">Emeralds delivered to your door!</u>
  <u t="47833">Plaza del Rosario.</u>
  <u t="48916">Better known as Emerald Square, because everyone around me here</u>
  <u t="52250">is selling and trading emeralds.</u>
  <u t="54583">But why is such a precious stone sold out in the open, in broad daylight?</u>
  <u t="58125">Well, because it's the sunlight itself that helps buyers tell if a stone is real or not.</u>
  <u t="62583">But for us, this is just the start of a great journey.</u>
  <u t="65166">A journey that will take us deep into the earth to understand and discover the stories of the people</u>
  <u t="70125">who dedicate their whole lives to searching for the most precious stone in the world.</u>
  <u t="107416">My name is Giuseppe and I have a mission:</u>
  <u t="110833">to explore the most remote corners of the planet</u>
  <u t="113958">to meet guardians of ancient secrets,</u>
  <u t="116833">men and women with extraordinary stories</u>
  <u t="120041">and lives that can inspire us and make us see the world through different eyes.</u>
  <u t="125208">And to each of them I’ll ask the most important question of all:</u>
  <u t="129208">“What does happiness mean to you?”</u>
  <u t="132000">A question so powerful it reveals the deepest essence of humanity.</u>
  <u t="139916">Welcome to “PROGETTO HAPPINESS”.</u>
  <u t="167333">We’ve all heard about gold fever.</u>
  <u t="170500">But the people we’re about to meet are struck by a very different kind of fever.</u>
  <u t="177250">The green fever.</u>
  <u t="179416">An obsession to find an emerald that might even be here in this cart.</u>
  <u t="185458">Or maybe never be found.</u>
  <u t="186916">But they say that once your eyes catch even a glimpse</u>
  <u t="191500">of the shine, the sparkle of an emerald, you’ll chase it for the rest of your life.</u>
  <u t="196583">And we are going to meet those miners who actually aren’t ordinary miners.</u>
  <u t="202041">They’re the legendary “guaqueros”.</u>
  <u t="203625">That is, treasure hunters.</u>
  <u t="206375">The word “guaquero” means someone who looks for hidden treasure under the mountains.</u>
  <u t="211666">But why are they illegal miners here?</u>
  <u t="214125">Because they’re looking for what now belongs to multinational companies who bought this land,</u>
  <u t="218458">monopolizing emerald extraction.</u>
  <u t="220541">But these people have been here for centuries.</u>
  <u t="223208">Since precolumbian times they’ve been searching for emeralds that they see as their rightful heritage.</u>
  <u t="226625">So they stand against the government, against the multinationals.</u>
  <u t="230500">But that’s only part of their story.</u>
  <u t="233166">We want to go into the mines</u>
  <u t="235041">to follow them during the actual extraction of emeralds from the bowels of the earth.</u>
  <u t="240708">We just need to find someone willing to take responsibility for bringing us into a real mine.</u>
  <u t="247041">The “guaqueros” have been digging for centuries.</u>
  <u t="249166">Long before the multinationals, long before someone claimed this land as theirs.</u>
  <u t="254125">Here, knowledge is passed down quietly from father to son or daughter.</u>
  <u t="257291">Through tunnels, dirty hands, and shared dreams.</u>
  <u t="260416">They have no protections or contracts but have created their own rules.</u>
  <u t="263541">Shifts, shared tools, leaders — a parallel system born to resist.</u>
  <u t="268083">To the big companies, they’re just a nuisance.</u>
  <u t="271416">Ants to be blown away.</u>
  <u t="273000">But those born here never leave.</u>
  <u t="275333">To them, this land is no concession.</u>
  <u t="277875">It’s home.</u>
  <u t="278750">It’s identity.</u>
  <u t="280000">And sometimes the mountain answers.</u>
  <u t="282000">With a stone.</u>
  <u t="283291">Here they call it “inguaqarse”.</u>
  <u t="284791">Which means, when fate tells you: today it’s your turn.</u>
  <u t="288875">It’s rare, but it happens.</u>
  <u t="299916">Getting into the tunnels isn’t easy.</u>
  <u t="302250">You need a leader’s approval.</u>
  <u t="303875">And to find them, we have to go into the small towns born around the mines.</u>
  <u t="308666">This is one of the typical miners' villages.</u>
  <u t="311375">In fact, in front of us are lots of young guys returning from work, covered in black dirt.</u>
  <u t="316041">Just like the ground we’re walking on.</u>
  <u t="318000">It's no coincidence that it’s black.</u>
  <u t="319333">Because this is the actual earth extracted from the mountains.</u>
  <u t="322458">What does that mean?</u>
  <u t="323458">That dirt was dug up even here.</u>
  <u t="326291">It’s all waste rock from the mountains.</u>
  <u t="328291">So this used to be a mine.</u>
  <u t="330541">Imagine that.</u>
  <u t="331250">Now they’ve built some pretty rundown homes here</u>
  <u t="334750">where miners rest for a bit before going back on shift.</u>
  <u t="354041">Many of the miners we meet are very young.</u>
  <u t="356833">They didn’t choose the mines.</u>
  <u t="358625">They were practically born into them.</u>
  <u t="361250">Like Maria, who’s just over twenty and already an expert miner.</u>
  <u t="366208">Many people wouldn’t do what we do, they say it scares them.</u>
  <u t="371791">Sometimes you feel alive, and sometimes you come out (of the mine) completely, utterly exhausted.</u>
  <u t="377083">It gets unbearably hot, over 40°, your skin feels like it’s burning, and there are places where oxygen…</u>
  <u t="387416">Where there is no oxygen.</u>
  <u t="389666">There are places where oxygen levels are extremely low.</u>
  <u t="393875">One day we’re poor, and the next day we’re rich — it changes a lot.</u>
  <u t="399541">It’s all about God and luck.</u>
  <u t="402208">And have you been lucky so far?</u>
  <u t="404625">We make it out alive every day.</u>
  <u t="406375">That means we’re lucky, and that the Lord is walking with us for good.</u>
  <u t="412708">But yes, it’s actually really cool.</u>
  <u t="415458">I totally recommend trying it!</u>
  <u t="426541">No, not that way, no, grab that one!</u>
  <u t="446625">Guys, what you see behind me are the typical lookouts for the "guaqueros".</u>
  <u t="450500">At the back there’s a mine entrance, and he’s watching to make sure the police don’t show up.</u>
  <u t="455500">If the police show up, he radios his colleagues with a walkie talkie,</u>
  <u t="459541">to warn them to hide inside because the police would never dare go deep into a mine.</u>
  <u t="463916">It’s too dangerous for them, they lack the experience.</u>
  <u t="466000">While the others can run inside and wait for the police to leave.</u>
  <u t="469791">That’s his job.</u>
  <u t="471750">Right now I’m in charge of security.</u>
  <u t="474250">I have to stay here and watch out for the police, and raise the alarm.</u>
  <u t="480541">If for any reason they come, I have to warn them over there.</u>
  <u t="484291">So they can hide the tools, so they don’t get taken away.</u>
  <u t="488250">Has it ever happened?</u>
  <u t="490166">Yes.</u>
  <u t="491458">And you all hid inside?</u>
  <u t="493458">Yes, of course, we have to go hide the tools.</u>
  <u t="498125">And hide ourselves.</u>
  <u t="500208">And the police never enter the mines?</u>
  <u t="501708">No… or yes, sometimes.</u>
  <u t="504041">But why do the police show up?</u>
  <u t="509583">Because what we do is sort of illegal.</u>
  <u t="512541">More or less.</u>
  <u t="514333">So they come to stop us from working.</u>
  <u t="518041">They take our tools so we can't work.</u>
  <u t="521208">Hey, how do we get up? What's up?</u>
  <u t="529416">We’re reaching one of the hidden entrances.</u>
  <u t="531708">A passage secretly dug by the "guaqueros" in the heart of the mountain.</u>
  <u t="548000">This is the only thing they found in the load we just saw — and it's worthless.</u>
  <u t="560208">Look.</u>
  <u t="561083">This is what comes out of the mine — still no sign of emeralds.</u>
  <u t="565208">We’re working in this mine, and even though we know</u>
  <u t="569416">there are many people inside,</u>
  <u t="571208">we hope to strike it lucky here.</u>
  <u t="573208">Have you found anything today?</u>
  <u t="574916">No, not even enough to buy soap to wash our clothes.</u>
  <u t="579125">But maybe, with God's help...</u>
  <u t="581500">We’ll be…</u>
  <u t="583583">We’ll be there when it happens, if God wills it.</u>
  <u t="586541">If all goes well, we’ll get rich.</u>
  <u t="589458">Our job is to go in there and blast the rock,</u>
  <u t="596541">and then, along with everyone else working inside, extract the earth</u>
  <u t="600250">and hope that with a single blast we find something.</u>
  <u t="603000">Maybe luck will smile on us and we’ll find the product we’re looking for — the emerald.</u>
  <u t="609458">And...</u>
  <u t="610500">That’s why we ask God and the Virgin to let us come out safe and sound, just like we went in.</u>
  <u t="615333">Because that’s the point.</u>
  <u t="617583">We have family and lots of friends waiting for us outside, too.</u>
  <u t="625875">One of the leaders agrees to take us inside,</u>
  <u t="628375">asking us to respect the mountain because, sadly, it doesn’t forgive mistakes.</u>
  <u t="632708">Once you go in, you have to be very careful — no mine is truly safe.</u>
  <u t="636750">There is no such thing as a 100% safe mine.</u>
  <u t="639125">So the moment you enter, you’re taking a risk.</u>
  <u t="642041">You have to be cautious, always wear a helmet and gloves.</u>
  <u t="646375">Always check the ceiling,</u>
  <u t="648291">because by doing so, you’re also protecting your friend, the person ahead of you.</u>
  <u t="653375">In the mine, think first of yourself, then of yourself, and then again of yourself.</u>
  <u t="657041">Because otherwise, you won’t know if you’ll have the strength to help someone else.</u>
  <u t="660333">You don’t know if your body will make it out of there.</u>
  <u t="662875">First save yourself — only then can you think about helping someone else.</u>
  <u t="669208">You always have to stay alert, always — you can’t let your guard down… because you’re in a mine.</u>
  <u t="674708">Helmet on!</u>
  <u t="676333">Water's coming in — something’s happening.</u>
  <u t="699166">We’re literally entering the bowels of the earth.</u>
  <u t="703083">These tunnels were built by thousands of people before us who died building this,</u>
  <u t="707791">who dedicated their lives to digging these tunnels.</u>
  <u t="714958">This part is usually busy — carts going back and forth — and we have to let them pass.</u>
  <u t="720750">They’re carts full of rocks that must be taken out to keep the tunnels clear,</u>
  <u t="725750">but also to check if inside any of those stones there’s a microscopic trace of emerald.</u>
  <u t="735208">We’re getting closer...</u>
  <u t="736208">No, from here we still have a long walk.</u>
  <u t="738208">Today we’ll find the treasure.</u>
  <u t="740041">Come on, let’s see if you find it. First, dig up the earth.</u>
  <u t="744541">What does "guaquear" mean?</u>
  <u t="745625">It means finding the "guaqo".</u>
  <u t="747125">Finding the treasure.</u>
  <u t="748500">We always have to watch our heads.</u>
  <u t="750541">So… among miners they say "Inguacarse".</u>
  <u t="755041">To get rich — and that’s everyone’s dream.</u>
  <u t="759041">It’s the hope and wish they give each other at the start of every shift.</u>
  <u t="763333">Let’s see how I get out of this adventure.</u>
  <u t="766041">If I didn’t have the helmet by now...</u>
  <u t="768416">Let’s go, it’ll be a long one!</u>
  <u t="770333">This tunnel goes on for kilometers.</u>
  <u t="781333">“Guaqueras” at work!</u>
  <u t="783291">Good afternoon!</u>
  <u t="784291">How’d it go?</u>
  <u t="785208">Very well, very well.</u>
  <u t="787208">We work hard to get rich.</u>
  <u t="791541">There are also many women in the mines.</u>
  <u t="795541">It’s definitely not just a men’s job.</u>
  <u t="799291">In fact, they say women have a lot more patience.</u>
  <u t="802250">It’s hard to talk to you like this, but I’ll try to tell you about this adventure</u>
  <u t="808250">as best I can.</u>
  <u t="817416">Obviously all these supports were built to hold up this tunnel, which isn’t always safe.</u>
  <u t="826708">If at any point someone panics, suffers from claustrophobia, or feels unwell…</u>
  <u t="833458">…they need to tell us right away, so we can step in, help them get out, or do whatever’s needed.</u>
  <u t="850208">Every time you connect without protection, you’re not alone.</u>
  <u t="853375">Hackers are out there, invisible, ready to intercept your every bit of data.</u>
  <u t="858625">Passwords, bank details, browsing history.</u>
  <u t="861875">And you don’t even need to be a specific target.</u>
  <u t="864333">One wrong click, a fake website, an unsecured connection — and you’re an easy target.</u>
  <u t="870541">With NordVPN instead, your connection becomes powerful.</u>
  <u t="873500">Think of it as a digital shield that encrypts your data</u>
  <u t="876458">hides your IP, and makes your connection invisible.</u>
  <u t="879666">In fact, it can block viruses, dangerous websites, and even fraudulent shopping sites</u>
  <u t="884625">that try to trick you and steal your banking info.</u>
  <u t="888041">Don’t be the next target.</u>
  <u t="889458">Click the link in the description to get 4 extra months on the 2 year plan and 30 day moneyback guarantee.</u>
  <u t="895208">Protect your data with NordVPN.</u>
  <u t="901500">We’ve been walking like this, crouched down, for about half an hour now. This is probably the hardest part.</u>
  <u t="907041">By now we can’t even stretch out anymore, and our backs are starting to hurt a bit.</u>
  <u t="912541">But we keep going.</u>
  <u t="915958">We’re not even halfway there.</u>
  <u t="917291">Now comes the hardest part.</u>
  <u t="919583">Very tight, very low, we need to crouch down even more.</u>
  <u t="922958">And we still have about half an hour to go like this.</u>
  <u t="926375">Let’s go.</u>
  <u t="934916">All these tubes are air ducts, bringing fresh air inside for the miners.</u>
  <u t="941208">And then there are the wires — the electric cables used to detonate the dynamite.</u>
  <u t="962125">Here the excavation front is like an anthill.</u>
  <u t="964041">Right now there are several entry and exit points leading to where the digging is happening.</u>
  <u t="969333">But we have to go up the other side, because we can’t get through here.</u>
  <u t="974916">Not up there either, it’s way too hot, impossible to pass.</u>
  <u t="977041">Are you blowing it up from that side? Or from over there?</u>
  <u t="981041">From there.</u>
  <u t="981875">And we stay here?</u>
  <u t="983291">On this side, here.</u>
  <u t="985750">Germán, they still need to get into position.</u>
  <u t="990291">And as soon as you connect it, it explodes?</u>
  <u t="991708">Immediately, yes.</u>
  <u t="996875">Fire! Fire, fire!</u>
  <u t="1007333">You can really feel the shock wave!</u>
  <u t="1009166">Let’s go to the other side, plug the other one.</u>
  <u t="1025625">What’s happening now?</u>
  <u t="1026250">They just detonated this part of the mine. To blow up another section</u>
  <u t="1031750">they need to pull the electric wire to create a short circuit in the other part</u>
  <u t="1035625">and blow up that corridor too.</u>
  <u t="1038291">Let’s follow them.</u>
  <u t="1042125">Done, it’s ready to explode.</u>
  <u t="1048541">Perfect.</u>
  <u t="1052708">Now!</u>
  <u t="1056250">We’ll go when the smoke comes out.</u>
  <u t="1059291">Want some water?</u>
  <u t="1059875">No, we’re good — you need it more than we do.</u>
  <u t="1062375">No worries.</u>
  <u t="1063041">No, we’ll go get it now, thanks.</u>
  <u t="1066041">If you want it, don’t hesitate.</u>
  <u t="1068708">Alright.</u>
  <u t="1070250">I got myself into this and... every day that goes by I feel more like leaving.</u>
  <u t="1073708">But there’s still hope for tomorrow...</u>
  <u t="1075916">The next day, and the next, and the one after that, and before you know it, a year has passed.</u>
  <u t="1079041">Today makes exactly one year.</u>
  <u t="1080541">And did you find anything?</u>
  <u t="1081625">Nothing. In a year I earned 1,200,000 pesos (€257).</u>
  <u t="1084583">Nothing more.</u>
  <u t="1086041">I earned 1,200,000 pesos (€257) in a year.</u>
  <u t="1088375">But you keep going because you believe that one day...</u>
  <u t="1090208">The hope that... maybe!</u>
  <u t="1092875">You never know when the blessing of...</u>
  <u t="1094166">...finding the treasure will come.</u>
  <u t="1095041">Finding the treasure — one day.</u>
  <u t="1096666">What would it mean to you to find the treasure?</u>
  <u t="1098208">Finding an emerald... would mean earning well, improving quality of life.</u>
  <u t="1103208">That’s what everyone here hopes for.</u>
  <u t="1105791">But it’s tough, isn’t it?</u>
  <u t="1106583">Yes, and I’m telling you, this stretch is still the easy part — I work here.</u>
  <u t="1109750">It’s not so bad here, there’s still a bit of fresh air!</u>
  <u t="1111708">But when you think you might find it… well, you imagine a completely different life.</u>
  <u t="1116875">You wouldn’t have to kill yourself working anymore, with a stable income, you could slow down and live more calmly.</u>
  <u t="1123541">That’s what everyone dreams of — at least, I dream of it.</u>
  <u t="1126833">You see? There are people here who’ve been digging for months...</u>
  <u t="1132458">…and haven’t even made enough to buy soap.</u>
  <u t="1136208">That’s the bitter side of the mine.</u>
  <u t="1138041">Every day there’s hope, prayer, asking God to find even just one little precious stone...</u>
  <u t="1142833">…that could change your life. That’s what people dream of down here.</u>
  <u t="1149250">Thank you.</u>
  <u t="1150666">Thank you.</u>
  <u t="1157708">We don’t even know where we’re going.</u>
  <u t="1159708">Our camera is completely fogged up.</u>
  <u t="1162750">Now we’re really descending into the bowels of the earth.</u>
  <u t="1170333">Okay, I think we’re here.</u>
  <u t="1189166">It’s hotter that way.</u>
  <u t="1192291">Where are we?</u>
  <u t="1193458">We’re at the first work level.</u>
  <u t="1196250">We came from up there and came down to the first level — now we have to go lower.</u>
  <u t="1202541">It’s a bit hot, but it’s fine.</u>
  <u t="1206375">It’s different from the first part of the tunnel.</u>
  <u t="1208833">Here, you can’t breathe at all.</u>
  <u t="1211083">There’s no air.</u>
  <u t="1214333">It’s tough.</u>
  <u t="1215791">It’s tough, really tough.</u>
  <u t="1217041">We go down the tunnel and head to the production front to break up the vein.</u>
  <u t="1221791">Then we gather up some earth, carry it out and wash it — that’s how we get the emerald out.</u>
  <u t="1227708">Do we have to go lower?</u>
  <u t="1228875">Yes, three meters — just a small tunnel — then we reach the front and see what we find.</u>
  <u t="1236125">Alright.</u>
  <u t="1238041">Down here, the temperature goes over 40 degrees and humidity hits 95%.</u>
  <u t="1244125">The air is heavy, and ventilation is almost nonexistent.</u>
  <u t="1247666">Every extra meter means less oxygen.</u>
  <u t="1251041">Your body wears out quickly.</u>
  <u t="1253083">The darkness messes with your head, and if you don’t manage your energy right, you won’t make it back out.</u>
  <u t="1258083">And in fact, a collapse isn’t the only danger.</u>
  <u t="1260666">Here, you can also die just like that, by staying too long.</u>
  <u t="1264458">Blinded by that hope of finding something.</u>
  <u t="1269416">I don't know if you can hear the sound of the air ducts blowing wind.</u>
  <u t="1274208">The guys advised me to get some fresh air</u>
  <u t="1276750">before going down into this very, very tight hole.</u>
  <u t="1280041">There's a lot of people, I didn't expect this many.</u>
  <u t="1282666">There must be hundreds of people underground.</u>
  <u t="1286041">As if there were another city, a bustling city searching for emeralds.</u>
  <u t="1291375">And today we're part of it.</u>
  <u t="1293875">There could be an emerald over there.</u>
  <u t="1296250">We can proceed, if we keep going, emeralds might show up here.</u>
  <u t="1310041">We enter backwards to get in.</u>
  <u t="1314041">It’s easier this way.</u>
  <u t="1316083">Yes.</u>
  <u t="1317041">You place your hands.</u>
  <u t="1322916">Now it's getting serious.</u>
  <u t="1325125">Let's go.</u>
  <u t="1336083">Come on, come on.</u>
  <u t="1342291">It’s like touching the heart of the mine, so hot, I’m going down.</u>
  <u t="1348625">Okay, let’s go.</u>
  <u t="1350250">Lean here.</u>
  <u t="1351416">Yes, and then?</u>
  <u t="1352208">Keep going that way.</u>
  <u t="1355875">What a feeling, it really feels like we’re in the beating heart...</u>
  <u t="1361375">it's hotter, the earth is warm as if it were alive.</u>
  <u t="1366791">And here...</u>
  <u t="1368208">Here there are more chances to find emeralds, right?</u>
  <u t="1372458">Yes.</u>
  <u t="1373375">It takes a bit more courage and physical effort, but here you might find some.</u>
  <u t="1383041">This looks greenish.</u>
  <u t="1385291">Don’t shine the light.</u>
  <u t="1387291">No, there’s nothing here...</u>
  <u t="1391125">Look.</u>
  <u t="1398166">Film it, there’s green here, look.</u>
  <u t="1401791">Emerald?</u>
  <u t="1402458">Emerald green.</u>
  <u t="1404333">Here, don’t shine the light directly.</u>
  <u t="1406875">Yes, yes, yes, I see it.</u>
  <u t="1408041">This is an emerald.</u>
  <u t="1408666">I see it, I see it.</u>
  <u t="1409833">So that means here there is?</u>
  <u t="1410916">Yes.</u>
  <u t="1412166">There's a chance, it's likely.</u>
  <u t="1415166">What do you feel when you come down here?</u>
  <u t="1418750">The feeling is that you might find something that changes your life, that lifts you out of poverty.</u>
  <u t="1428208">That’s our ambition: to find the treasure, to get rich and live better.</u>
  <u t="1433291">To give a different future to our families.</u>
  <u t="1435708">That’s what we feel every time we go down: the hope of finding the treasure.</u>
  <u t="1438333">Don’t you get the feeling you're in the heart of the earth, where everything began?</u>
  <u t="1445041">Yes.</u>
  <u t="1446375">It’s something prehistoric, you know?</u>
  <u t="1450416">I think the guys are more focused on finding emeralds</u>
  <u t="1454333">than on thinking about something philosophical, but...</u>
  <u t="1459291">that’s what I feel, what you feel here.</u>
  <u t="1465708">A little piece.</u>
  <u t="1468250">Leave it, look here... emerald.</u>
  <u t="1470333">Oh, can I?</u>
  <u t="1471666">Yes.</u>
  <u t="1475625">Can you see it?</u>
  <u t="1476750">This is a piece of emerald, a sign... you can’t see it well, but...</u>
  <u t="1483000">signs that here...</u>
  <u t="1484375">There are emerald veins.</u>
  <u t="1486083">There’s not a breath of air.</u>
  <u t="1487041">Do you want some air? You okay?</u>
  <u t="1488791">Yes, I’m fine. I’m fine, I’m fine.</u>
  <u t="1506166">Also the hand.</u>
  <u t="1515916">Wow!</u>
  <u t="1518625">What an experience!</u>
  <u t="1519750">I don't know if you heard.</u>
  <u t="1522375">It’s like... I was just born again.</u>
  <u t="1524125">Water, the water!</u>
  <u t="1524708">Give him water here and air there.</u>
  <u t="1529375">Amazing guys. Thank you so much.</u>
  <u t="1535833">No, they thought I was fainting, but I’m fine, I’m just emotional.</u>
  <u t="1539000">I’m just emotional, I’m fine.</u>
  <u t="1541208">Okay, okay.</u>
  <u t="1543125">No, I’m fine, I’m fine.</u>
  <u t="1550583">Thanks, guys.</u>
  <u t="1553791">I know for you this is work, not fun, but for me it was something special.</u>
  <u t="1559708">And I really want to thank you in front of everyone, because you let me come down with you, do something tough</u>
  <u t="1567916">and I’m grateful, because I’ll never forget it.</u>
  <u t="1571416">You’re welcome, we’re showing a little bit of our work to the whole world.</u>
  <u t="1575375">Thank you.</u>
  <u t="1575958">To show that it’s not easy to turn that precious stone into a jewel, there’s always sacrifice behind it.</u>
  <u t="1580750">Can you say this stuff is adrenaline packed? This is adrenaline.</u>
  <u t="1584791">This is adrenaline...</u>
  <u t="1586458">Pure.</u>
  <u t="1587041">Daily, pure.</u>
  <u t="1590208">I can assure you.</u>
  <u t="1592166">You go in and don’t know if you’ll come out alive again.</u>
  <u t="1597375">You leave in the morning, say goodbye to your kids and your wife, but you don’t know if you’ll be back, because here</u>
  <u t="1603333">so many, so many things have happened, so many tragedies around these mines.</u>
  <u t="1608833">So here, adrenaline is always at 100%.</u>
  <u t="1612125">And like my mate said, we have the hope of extracting that stone so precious to the world,</u>
  <u t="1618708">to entire nations.</u>
  <u t="1621708">Guys, if I asked you now what happiness is to you, what would you say?</u>
  <u t="1627708">A vein full of emeralds. The thrill you get, the unique feeling of being able to gather them,</u>
  <u t="1633458">to extract them from mother earth.</u>
  <u t="1635791">And holding them in your hand is a unique sensation.</u>
  <u t="1638375">Who’s the first person you think of when you find the stone?</u>
  <u t="1642041">Family.</u>
  <u t="1643291">Family, right?</u>
  <u t="1644041">Family, you immediately think of family.</u>
  <u t="1646375">Because all this sacrifice—who do you do it for?</u>
  <u t="1648583">For the family, for the well being of the family.</u>
  <u t="1651625">If we found something today, I’d just want each of us to bring home a bit of bread.</u>
  <u t="1657333">So no one gets left behind.</u>
  <u t="1659083">Because we’re a team, we’re one.</u>
  <u t="1662375">If something happens to one of us, it’s like losing a family member.</u>
  <u t="1668041">We support each other every day, we keep each other standing.</u>
  <u t="1673291">And if a tragedy were to happen... we’d all feel it, as if it happened to us.</u>
  <u t="1678083">And you know this well, because they didn’t see it, but I slipped and...</u>
  <u t="1683750">And he caught me mid air, I don’t know if my face is scratched.</u>
  <u t="1688000">He grabbed my face mid air, to keep me from falling.</u>
  <u t="1691416">And you saved my life, thank you so much.</u>
  <u t="1695125">I don’t know, I don’t know.</u>
  <u t="1697458">All I know is I’m so happy.</u>
  <u t="1699750">These experiences really make me feel alive.</u>
  <u t="1702750">And you know it.</u>
  <u t="1704000">You two who travel with me, you know how it feels.</u>
  <u t="1706916">But now we need to get out.</u>
  <u t="1708416">Now we need a bit of...</u>
  <u t="1709666">We need to save some breath to get out, because it’s still a long way...</u>
  <u t="1714166">Yeah, yeah.</u>
  <u t="1714583">Let’s go.</u>
  <u t="1715625">This way.</u>
  <u t="1722500">It’s been seven hours and I can already feel my body giving up, yet for them it’s just another normal day.</u>
  <u t="1728958">Always down here, but together, united.</u>
  <u t="1737708">Down here there’s a dig front and there’s some soil that seems to show a little emerald reflection.</u>
  <u t="1747750">So people come here and they’re given some soil to take outside and wash.</u>
  <u t="1751583">So is it legal or illegal?</u>
  <u t="1753500">According to the law, we’re illegal.</u>
  <u t="1755375">You too?</u>
  <u t="1756000">Yeah, all of us here are technically illegal.</u>
  <u t="1758666">Illegal on our own land, which is illogical.</u>
  <u t="1762333">But we’re not really illegal, you know why?</u>
  <u t="1763916">Because before the multinationals and everyone else came, we were already working here.</u>
  <u t="1768583">Right.</u>
  <u t="1769041">So, we’re on our own land. We’ve been here... it’s work that’s gone on for decades, millennia.</u>
  <u t="1775541">It’s like it’s your right.</u>
  <u t="1777250">Yes, it’s our right, it’s our land.</u>
  <u t="1781541">It’s a tradition we carry on from...</u>
  <u t="1784416">Since the time of the indigenous people, right?</u>
  <u t="1787083">Yes, from the indigenous people.</u>
  <u t="1788166">We dug all these tunnels.</u>
  <u t="1790041">Your parents, your great grandparents...</u>
  <u t="1791708">Our grandparents...</u>
  <u t="1792875">It’s not like a multinational came and dug here, no.</u>
  <u t="1795708">All these tunnels were already here when they arrived.</u>
  <u t="1798458">But they were built by our hands.</u>
  <u t="1801208">Were your parents "guaqueros" too?</u>
  <u t="1802375">Yes, of course, my parents were "guaqueros".</u>
  <u t="1803875">And that’s common here?</u>
  <u t="1805041">Just like all of them, their parents too.</u>
  <u t="1807458">Really?</u>
  <u t="1807833">Yes of course, it’s a tradition, you understand?</u>
  <u t="1811333">Your dad passed it on to you.</u>
  <u t="1813291">Yes, and so on.</u>
  <u t="1815125">Wow, wonderful.</u>
  <u t="1816666">Yes.</u>
  <u t="1823583">Every end of shift becomes a ritual.</u>
  <u t="1825458">You climb up in line, each with their own cart full of soil</u>
  <u t="1829750">hoping the mountain left something in it.</u>
  <u t="1832625">Once we’re out, we’ll see.</u>
  <u t="1841416">Phew, it’s hot.</u>
  <u t="1843541">Looks like a magic trick.</u>
  <u t="1846666">Voilà.</u>
  <u t="1864250">And the “guaqueros” are absolutely right when they say emeralds aren’t found.</u>
  <u t="1868208">Emeralds are earned.</u>
  <u t="1870291">And even if we don’t find any today in this load, we’ve understood how much effort, how much sacrifice,</u>
  <u t="1876791">how much toil and courage these people put into searching for a stone that could change your life.</u>
  <u t="1885416">I see the exit.</u>
  <u t="1886708">We’re almost there.</u>
  <u t="1887291">The last 100 meters.</u>
  <u t="1891625">No, not at the end, no!</u>
  <u t="1899666">We did it!</u>
  <u t="1901708">Jonathan, you’re the best! Thank you so much.</u>
  <u t="1907416">We made it, we still don’t know if or what we found, but it doesn’t really matter.</u>
  <u t="1912375">At least for us.</u>
  <u t="1913208">Now let’s see what the guys found.</u>
  <u t="1927583">It should shine if we find it.</u>
  <u t="1942250">But it’s easy...</u>
  <u t="1943708">Here’s another little piece.</u>
  <u t="1945916">Is it worth anything?</u>
  <u t="1946708">No.</u>
  <u t="1947708">What’s this?</u>
  <u t="1950166">There’s something green over there.</u>
  <u t="1955833">And after all these hours of work, here’s what we found.</u>
  <u t="1958625">Emerald shards.</u>
  <u t="1959458">They’re worth absolutely nothing, but it doesn’t matter.</u>
  <u t="1962625">Because it was, as always, a great adventure in search of the formula for happiness.</u>
  <u t="1966583">And today we’ve learned something more.</u>
  <u t="1978041">We were leaving.</u>
  <u t="1979416">And I had already wrapped up this report.</u>
  <u t="1981333">And the guys found an emerald.</u>
  <u t="1982958">A real emerald, look.</u>
  <u t="1984833">Wonderful.</u>
  <u t="1988208">It’s not big.</u>
  <u t="1989416">It’s not perfect.</u>
  <u t="1990791">But that tiny green fragment is like a mirror.</u>
  <u t="1994625">Inside it, you see everything you long for.</u>
  <u t="1997041">Wealth, redemption, luck.</u>
  <u t="2000000">But if you look closer, all you see is yourself.</u>
  <u t="2003791">Your fears.</u>
  <u t="2004958">Your dreams.</u>
  <u t="2006041">What you’re searching for.</u>
  <u t="2007166">Even if you don’t know its name.</u>
  <u t="2009291">And maybe it makes me think we should search for happiness in the same way.</u>
  <u t="2014208">Not as a prize to win, but...</u>
  <u t="2016375">But as a mirror to step through.</u>
  <u t="2019375">A process.</u>
  <u t="2020500">A journey.</u>
  <u t="2021541">An opportunity to truly see yourself.</u>
  <u t="2023916">Because in the end, happiness isn’t what you find.</u>
  <u t="2027416">It’s what you discover about yourself.</u>
  <u t="2029958">While you're still searching for it.</u>
  <u t="2033666">We found it.</u>
  </text>
