<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="aPiaIKTpHLs" uploader="Natalie Zacek" channel="Natalie Zacek" likes="7182" title="the perfect switzerland trip *hikes, paddleboard, paraglide, and travel chaos" year="2025" month="9" day="7" date="20250907" date_ts="1757253615" is_ac="true">
  <u t="0">Heat.</u>
  <u t="5240">[Music]</u>
  <u t="15920">Heat.</u>
  <u t="17670">[Music]</u>
  <u t="22800">Heat.</u>
  <u t="24590">[Music]</u>
  <u t="38480">Heat.</u>
  <u t="39910">[Music]</u>
  <u t="62620">[Applause]</u>
  <u t="64890">[Music]</u>
  <u t="72799">Heat. Heat.</u>
  <u t="78820">[Music]</u>
  <u t="96720">That feels really good.</u>
  <u t="100799">We made it to Switzerland and we did get</u>
  <u t="104240">off our flight, pick up a rental car and</u>
  <u t="106560">then immediately go to the first hike</u>
  <u t="108320">that we wanted to.</u>
  <u t="110640">&gt;&gt; So, did we sleep on the flight?</u>
  <u t="114640">&gt;&gt; My watch says I got 3 hours of sleep.</u>
  <u t="116799">So, we are doing the Stew's Ridge Trail</u>
  <u t="120159">hike and we took the steepest finicular</u>
  <u t="124320">get up here. It was very cool.</u>
  <u t="125680">&gt;&gt; Are they only called that or is that</u>
  <u t="128000">Italian? I don't know. I'm gonna say</u>
  <u t="130000">that we hitched a ride, a very steep</u>
  <u t="132239">ride to get up here. And then I think</u>
  <u t="134879">we're going to take a chair lift to get</u>
  <u t="136160">up even higher before we do a two-mile</u>
  <u t="138640">hike.</u>
  <u t="141280">You're about to get sweeped off your</u>
  <u t="142640">feet.</u>
  <u t="147410">[Music]</u>
  <u t="148879">Why do they look bigger than American</u>
  <u t="150879">cows?</u>
  <u t="154080">&gt;&gt; New York City.</u>
  <u t="156319">I cannot believe there is blue sky. It's</u>
  <u t="158400">so pretty.</u>
  <u t="164560">&gt;&gt; Wow.</u>
  <u t="168959">&gt;&gt; So,</u>
  <u t="170560">why is he up here?</u>
  <u t="172160">&gt;&gt; Very sweet. And then sour.</u>
  <u t="179560">[Music]</u>
  <u t="199040">So,</u>
  <u t="199920">&gt;&gt; so we</u>
  <u t="202720">&gt;&gt; are we here or here? I think we came up</u>
  <u t="206000">this one</u>
  <u t="206560">&gt;&gt; here.</u>
  <u t="208080">&gt;&gt; So, there is a chair lift the cling</u>
  <u t="210560">stock to go from frumple</u>
  <u t="214319">frmpletock to cling stock.</u>
  <u t="218560">&gt;&gt; Simple.</u>
  <u t="245599">Whoa.</u>
  <u t="247040">&gt;&gt; Oh gosh.</u>
  <u t="248080">&gt;&gt; I'm so scared that you're going to step</u>
  <u t="249519">in.</u>
  <u t="249920">&gt;&gt; Oh no. I don't want you in the car if</u>
  <u t="251840">you step in one of these boot piles.</u>
  <u t="257919">God.</u>
  <u t="260290">[Music]</u>
  <u t="270160">Very</u>
  <u t="273320">[Music]</u>
  <u t="293440">good.</u>
  <u t="294540">[Music]</u>
  <u t="308110">[Music]</u>
  <u t="316320">I was in charge of picking the hotel for</u>
  <u t="318240">this trip and I feel like I did a really</u>
  <u t="320080">good job immediately upon checking in.</u>
  <u t="322560">And it has so much cute character. But</u>
  <u t="324400">the best part of all is right here.</u>
  <u t="328800">The view.</u>
  <u t="332560">I think it's going to be even more</u>
  <u t="334240">insane when the sun comes out and when</u>
  <u t="337039">the sky is blue. But the room itself is</u>
  <u t="339280">very cute. We have a porch. Picture Josh</u>
  <u t="342000">and I sitting there. A cup of coffee.</u>
  <u t="343919">And then inside it is very cozy. I feel</u>
  <u t="346320">like the more that I've booked places to</u>
  <u t="347919">stay, the more that I want places that</u>
  <u t="349600">have character. And I'm kind of digging</u>
  <u t="351759">the green carpet. All of the little wood</u>
  <u t="353919">features. The bed looks extremely comfy.</u>
  <u t="356720">And I'm seeing that they did the two</u>
  <u t="358160">comforter thing, which I feel like is</u>
  <u t="360000">just a cool touch of giving people their</u>
  <u t="362320">own comforters. I'll probably end up</u>
  <u t="364400">stealing both. And a desk area if Josh</u>
  <u t="367280">needed to edit, but he doesn't because</u>
  <u t="369520">he's not editing this trip, which is</u>
  <u t="371120">fun.</u>
  <u t="374720">Sometimes my issue with places with</u>
  <u t="376560">character is that they feel very old or</u>
  <u t="379199">like they could be dirty. This bathroom</u>
  <u t="381199">feels exceptionally clean. So, I'm</u>
  <u t="383039">loving that. And I'm already scheduling</u>
  <u t="385039">when I need to have a bath because that</u>
  <u t="387199">looks so nice. I just realized this is a</u>
  <u t="389120">towel warmer.</u>
  <u t="392160">Day is made. Slippers, robes. Okay,</u>
  <u t="396479">every door that I open, I'm loving this</u>
  <u t="398319">place more and more. This will be me</u>
  <u t="400960">tomorrow morning.</u>
  <u t="403680">transition to me with a coffee tomorrow.</u>
  <u t="417520">&gt;&gt; Josh and I just got back from dinner. We</u>
  <u t="419599">are so tired. We showered, kind of got</u>
  <u t="422240">our stuff like put away and picked out</u>
  <u t="424160">for tomorrow morning because tomorrow is</u>
  <u t="426160">supposed to be the one day that is like</u>
  <u t="427919">completely full sun. So, we want to go</u>
  <u t="430080">on another hike that we really have on</u>
  <u t="432160">our mind, especially since the one today</u>
  <u t="434560">was like so cloudy. And I feel like</u>
  <u t="436319">that's such a pivotal thing when you're</u>
  <u t="438479">going to obviously viewpoints is that</u>
  <u t="440960">you're in the mountains, so there's</u>
  <u t="442240">clouds most of the time. So, if there's</u>
  <u t="443680">a full Sunday, we wanted to take</u>
  <u t="445039">advantage of that. So, I'm pretty sure</u>
  <u t="446960">we're waking up at like 4:30 in the</u>
  <u t="449199">morning, which is not going to be</u>
  <u t="451599">pleased. Like, which wow, I can't even</u>
  <u t="455039">speak right now. We are waking up at</u>
  <u t="456479">4:30 in the morning. I will not be</u>
  <u t="458639">pleased in the morning. I also don't</u>
  <u t="460080">know where I'm going to get coffee or</u>
  <u t="461599">breakfast or food. And as a planner, I</u>
  <u t="464240">don't like that. But I know that we're</u>
  <u t="466400">going to have a really good day. And</u>
  <u t="468560">even just being here, driving in already</u>
  <u t="470880">doing a hike, seeing the town we're</u>
  <u t="472560">staying in, I'm like blown away how</u>
  <u t="474800">magical it is. So, I know that tomorrow</u>
  <u t="476879">is going to be just the same, if not</u>
  <u t="479199">even better. There's supposed to be a</u>
  <u t="480720">lake at the bottom that we can swim in.</u>
  <u t="482479">So, that's going to be really exciting,</u>
  <u t="483840">too. But all of that to say, we are</u>
  <u t="486639">exhausted and I need to go to sleep</u>
  <u t="489840">because I'm going to be up in far too</u>
  <u t="492800">little hours.</u>
  <u t="511120">Well, we definitely have a situation. We</u>
  <u t="514320">parked our car in the parking garage</u>
  <u t="515919">because Wen, the town we're staying in,</u>
  <u t="517760">is a carless village. So, we're here</u>
  <u t="519839">parked down in Lauder Brunen and we have</u>
  <u t="523039">our parking ticket in our hotel room.</u>
  <u t="525519">So, we literally woke up at 4:30 a.m.</u>
  <u t="528800">Got down to the train station, took the</u>
  <u t="530800">train, came down here, whatever. And</u>
  <u t="533839">then the next train to go back up isn't</u>
  <u t="535519">until 6:00 a.m. But we have like walked</u>
  <u t="537519">around the parking garage, tried to call</u>
  <u t="539680">the contact office, tried to pay it</u>
  <u t="541920">online, tried to find anybody working</u>
  <u t="544959">here. No one is working yet. So the next</u>
  <u t="547839">train to go back up was 6:00 a.m. So</u>
  <u t="549839">we've waited in the car. Josh is now on</u>
  <u t="551920">that train, but he has 10 minutes to run</u>
  <u t="555279">to the hotel, find the parking ticket,</u>
  <u t="557839">run back to the train station before</u>
  <u t="559680">that train leaves. And if he misses that</u>
  <u t="561279">one, it's another half an hour. So, it</u>
  <u t="563760">is really sad because we woke up like</u>
  <u t="565519">hoping to see sunrise going on all of</u>
  <u t="567440">this and then just like a silly mistake.</u>
  <u t="570000">Makes it where, you know, we can't do</u>
  <u t="571760">that. But Josh feels really bad that he</u>
  <u t="573920">forgot. I feel bad because I moved the</u>
  <u t="575920">parking ticket. I put it in like another</u>
  <u t="577920">bag of stuff cuz I was like, "Oh, let me</u>
  <u t="579760">just pick up." And so I'm like, "You</u>
  <u t="582480">don't have to feel bad. There's</u>
  <u t="583600">literally I don't know. That's on both</u>
  <u t="585360">of us. I should have thought of it,</u>
  <u t="586640">too." But yeah, it is so weird that</u>
  <u t="588720">there's not like something we can do to</u>
  <u t="590880">just pay a maximum fee or anything.</u>
  <u t="593519">You're just stuck. And with the train</u>
  <u t="595519">station schedules and all of that. So</u>
  <u t="598320">yeah, definitely took a turn for making</u>
  <u t="600399">this morning later. I'm tracking Josh's</u>
  <u t="602880">dot and he is running so fast. I</u>
  <u t="605839">literally feel like I'm watching a</u>
  <u t="607120">little video game. And he made his way</u>
  <u t="609120">to the hotel, assuming he found it</u>
  <u t="611279">because now he's booking his way back.</u>
  <u t="613040">So fingers crossed that he makes that</u>
  <u t="614800">train coming back down. I feel so</u>
  <u t="616880">useless like sitting here. And I hope I</u>
  <u t="619440">have water for him.</u>
  <u t="626800">Wow, you did run</u>
  <u t="630640">up and back and get the ticket in 7</u>
  <u t="633519">minutes.</u>
  <u t="634560">&gt;&gt; Yes.</u>
  <u t="636560">&gt;&gt; I didn't think it was even going to be</u>
  <u t="637920">possible.</u>
  <u t="639200">&gt;&gt; You were running so fast.</u>
  <u t="640880">&gt;&gt; Yeah.</u>
  <u t="642640">Well, I always say when you have a</u>
  <u t="644240">little hiccup for something, you were</u>
  <u t="645600">protected for something or we don't know</u>
  <u t="647920">what. So, we're having a slower start to</u>
  <u t="650079">our morning, but we do have water. And</u>
  <u t="652320">we</u>
  <u t="652800">&gt;&gt; had a slow start.</u>
  <u t="655040">&gt;&gt; I had the most aggressive start.</u>
  <u t="658800">&gt;&gt; We had a little delayed start to our</u>
  <u t="660720">morning, but we can finally get out of</u>
  <u t="663839">the parking garage.</u>
  <u t="664800">&gt;&gt; Wait, let's have a real time emotional</u>
  <u t="666399">breakdown right now. I'm going to sob.</u>
  <u t="674800">&gt;&gt; Oh my gosh,</u>
  <u t="676480">&gt;&gt; all of that just</u>
  <u t="678399">&gt;&gt; get out of here.</u>
  <u t="679440">&gt;&gt; Get out of the parking garage. Um, now</u>
  <u t="682240">we're taking our trek up to a very</u>
  <u t="684240">beautiful hike and it looks like a</u>
  <u t="685600">gorgeous day. So, we will not let this</u>
  <u t="687680">get us down.</u>
  <u t="694580">[Music]</u>
  <u t="699040">You having a nice snap?</u>
  <u t="702550">[Music]</u>
  <u t="704959">&gt;&gt; Hey buddy,</u>
  <u t="706720">me and my fam</u>
  <u t="709200">Switzerland.</u>
  <u t="722000">shedding multiple layers because we are</u>
  <u t="723920">about to be going up.</u>
  <u t="734079">&gt;&gt; Well, first looks.</u>
  <u t="736959">&gt;&gt; I'm so excited. I think I'm going to</u>
  <u t="739279">swim. That was like one of the big</u>
  <u t="741440">points of this hike was that you can</u>
  <u t="742800">swim at the bottom. But when I started</u>
  <u t="744480">it in my puffy like fuzzy sherpa, that</u>
  <u t="746720">was Josh's. I was like, there's</u>
  <u t="747839">absolutely no way. Wait, Josh, look how</u>
  <u t="749920">where we came from.</u>
  <u t="751600">zoom. That's crazy.</u>
  <u t="754800">And we're a mile in the third in</u>
  <u t="768890">[Music]</u>
  <u t="799690">[Music]</u>
  <u t="814480">That hurts.</u>
  <u t="817020">[Music]</u>
  <u t="834250">[Applause]</u>
  <u t="837660">[Music]</u>
  <u t="849920">But it's like I don't want Drop it down.</u>
  <u t="856180">[Music]</u>
  <u t="866030">[Music]</u>
  <u t="881770">[Music]</u>
  <u t="886160">They were so nervous.</u>
  <u t="891890">[Music]</u>
  <u t="912420">[Music]</u>
  <u t="923760">Wow, that is cool.</u>
  <u t="932639">I'm going.</u>
  <u t="935680">&gt;&gt; Wow.</u>
  <u t="969120">I'm tired.</u>
  <u t="974639">She currently at 12 hours awake steps.</u>
  <u t="981120">Don't need to gas me up like that.</u>
  <u t="1014560">What's going on?</u>
  <u t="1015440">&gt;&gt; I'm very tired.</u>
  <u t="1017600">&gt;&gt; I need raw time. You're not scheduling</u>
  <u t="1019680">in any raw time.</u>
  <u t="1021040">&gt;&gt; What did we do that was so demanding</u>
  <u t="1022800">today?</u>
  <u t="1023920">&gt;&gt; 30k steps.</u>
  <u t="1027039">Why are you not needing any rest? I need</u>
  <u t="1031360">food.</u>
  <u t="1031839">&gt;&gt; In the past two nights, we've gotten a</u>
  <u t="1034400">collective 8 hours of sleep.</u>
  <u t="1038240">&gt;&gt; Which is fine. I'm very tired.</u>
  <u t="1041439">&gt;&gt; Mhm.</u>
  <u t="1044400">&gt;&gt; So, you're just going to sleep while the</u>
  <u t="1045760">sky is blue?</u>
  <u t="1046480">&gt;&gt; No. I You're Do you not understand</u>
  <u t="1048400">rotting? It's laying for some time.</u>
  <u t="1052000">&gt;&gt; So, you're just going to lay inside when</u>
  <u t="1053360">the sky is blue?</u>
  <u t="1054400">&gt;&gt; Yes, I have to.</u>
  <u t="1062000">We spent some time rotting and I was</u>
  <u t="1063840">looking through the photos of today. I'm</u>
  <u t="1065440">already so excited. Everything was</u>
  <u t="1067440">absolutely gorgeous. And I did have a</u>
  <u t="1069760">little guilt of the sun being out and</u>
  <u t="1071360">the sky being so pretty and just</u>
  <u t="1073200">chilling. But especially since being up</u>
  <u t="1075440">so early and then having like a very</u>
  <u t="1078160">intense day, I just needed some time to</u>
  <u t="1080320">chill. So, I did throw on this little</u>
  <u t="1082480">outfit. I'll give you more of a fit</u>
  <u t="1084000">check with both Josh and my fit. But I</u>
  <u t="1086400">think we're gonna eat dinner at our</u>
  <u t="1088160">hotel because we heard that the food is</u>
  <u t="1090000">really, really yummy here and we wanted</u>
  <u t="1091760">to check that out while we're staying</u>
  <u t="1093600">here. Um, so I think we're gonna do</u>
  <u t="1095520">that. And we have</u>
  <u t="1099919">like 2 and 1/ half hours until sunset.</u>
  <u t="1102160">So hopefully dinner won't be too long</u>
  <u t="1103919">and then we can find some little sunset</u>
  <u t="1106320">location to watch that from either our</u>
  <u t="1109440">hotel somewhere around in town. But it</u>
  <u t="1112160">feels really, really good to have a</u>
  <u t="1114160">little bit of rest and to have had such</u>
  <u t="1116000">an amazing day. I can feel myself being</u>
  <u t="1119200">very tired. You guys can probably see</u>
  <u t="1120720">it. I don't know if you can fully see</u>
  <u t="1122480">that, but this is my fit. Just a long</u>
  <u t="1124720">sleeve. The vest is from Midnight Lunch.</u>
  <u t="1127039">And then these are some Old Navy jeans,</u>
  <u t="1128799">the only jeans I packed. And my Adidas</u>
  <u t="1131039">shoes. I fear that I packed really</u>
  <u t="1133360">wrong. I've been cold pretty much this</u>
  <u t="1135360">whole trip. So, I have a lot of shorts</u>
  <u t="1138080">and active sets that I don't know if</u>
  <u t="1139840">I'll be wearing as well as like tank</u>
  <u t="1141919">tops, t-shirts. I brought maxi skirts</u>
  <u t="1144640">with tank tops and I'm like, girl, I'm</u>
  <u t="1147840">cold.</u>
  <u t="1151360">&gt;&gt; Do you think you could do it?</u>
  <u t="1153760">&gt;&gt; Actually, don't know. I feel like I'm</u>
  <u t="1154960">not very good at these surprisingly.</u>
  <u t="1158080">&gt;&gt; If you don't get across, we have to do</u>
  <u t="1160640">the via.</u>
  <u t="1163520">&gt;&gt; You have You have to get across. This is</u>
  <u t="1165600">all that Josh and I can think about</u>
  <u t="1166960">tonight is if we should do the scariest</u>
  <u t="1170080">thing I've ever seen. Quite truly.</u>
  <u t="1174240">&gt;&gt; I cannot do this.</u>
  <u t="1177039">&gt;&gt; Sorry to have no faith in myself, but</u>
  <u t="1178960">like</u>
  <u t="1182220">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1188799">&gt;&gt; Wow.</u>
  <u t="1190000">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1196799">Your ankles are going to snap off.</u>
  <u t="1206080">&gt;&gt; That was good.</u>
  <u t="1208160">&gt;&gt; I feel pretty solid. My weight just</u>
  <u t="1210240">likes to</u>
  <u t="1211280">&gt;&gt; The middle of it is harder.</u>
  <u t="1214530">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1217679">&gt;&gt; That's pretty brutal. We stopped at the</u>
  <u t="1219600">cocktail bar and Josh got this delicious</u>
  <u t="1221840">looking hot chocolate.</u>
  <u t="1223520">&gt;&gt; Very good.</u>
  <u t="1226080">Check this out.</u>
  <u t="1232320">&gt;&gt; Okay.</u>
  <u t="1264080">Not another hike, please.</u>
  <u t="1272720">In an interesting turn of events, we are</u>
  <u t="1275280">going paragliding.</u>
  <u t="1277919">&gt;&gt; Yes.</u>
  <u t="1279200">&gt;&gt; Yes, we are.</u>
  <u t="1279919">&gt;&gt; We just kept seeing the people doing</u>
  <u t="1281520">paragliding here. And then I asked on my</u>
  <u t="1283600">Instagram story and almost every other</u>
  <u t="1285760">one was people saying that you should go</u>
  <u t="1287360">paragliding.</u>
  <u t="1288559">&gt;&gt; So, I feel like at first I was like, is</u>
  <u t="1290320">this just a very touristy thing? And</u>
  <u t="1292400">maybe it is, but we are tourists. I</u>
  <u t="1294880">don't know many tourists that are like,</u>
  <u t="1296960">I'm going to 100% go 3,000 meters high</u>
  <u t="1301760">for my excursion.</u>
  <u t="1302960">&gt;&gt; So, you speak in meters now.</u>
  <u t="1306000">He goes to Switzerland one time. I</u>
  <u t="1307520">&gt;&gt; actually don't know if that's even</u>
  <u t="1308480">accurate</u>
  <u t="1309919">&gt;&gt; because we don't know me.</u>
  <u t="1311120">&gt;&gt; Look up the conversion of 3,000 meters.</u>
  <u t="1313120">&gt;&gt; Um, whoever</u>
  <u t="1313760">&gt;&gt; whoever our editor is,</u>
  <u t="1314640">&gt;&gt; whoever I was just gonna say the same</u>
  <u t="1316400">thing. The longer we're married, the</u>
  <u t="1318400">more we're actually the same person. But</u>
  <u t="1320480">yeah, to whoever's editing this video,</u>
  <u t="1322159">if you want to convert meters to feet,</u>
  <u t="1326159">&gt;&gt; yards,</u>
  <u t="1327200">&gt;&gt; meters,</u>
  <u t="1328159">&gt;&gt; and inches.</u>
  <u t="1329280">&gt;&gt; If you want to convert meters to</u>
  <u t="1330720">centimeters, this is how high we're</u>
  <u t="1332240">going to be going.</u>
  <u t="1334960">Pause for dramatic effect.</u>
  <u t="1338320">Um, I'm not that nervous. I feel like we</u>
  <u t="1341520">kind of need to go into the lore of what</u>
  <u t="1343280">we've been so nervous about. And I'm</u>
  <u t="1345760">just going to put a photo or a video.</u>
  <u t="1348640">just speak its name.</u>
  <u t="1350400">&gt;&gt; The via</u>
  <u t="1352320">My palms are sweating.</u>
  <u t="1353600">&gt;&gt; Every single time we say it,</u>
  <u t="1355760">&gt;&gt; we</u>
  <u t="1357280">&gt;&gt; I feel like I could throw up.</u>
  <u t="1359120">&gt;&gt; It's a hike that you go and there's</u>
  <u t="1362240">metal rungs and you're looking like</u>
  <u t="1364080">2,000 ft down. You have cables clipped</u>
  <u t="1366480">in.</u>
  <u t="1366799">&gt;&gt; How many meters?</u>
  <u t="1368720">&gt;&gt; Please stop. You have cables clipped in.</u>
  <u t="1371520">So, in doing research, as long as you</u>
  <u t="1373360">have the proper equipment, it's beginner</u>
  <u t="1375760">friendly, which is what keeps throwing</u>
  <u t="1377679">us off. Like, why am I reading something</u>
  <u t="1379280">that is beginner friendly and my stomach</u>
  <u t="1381679">feels like it is dropping out of my body</u>
  <u t="1384400">&gt;&gt; to do it? Maybe America has kind of</u>
  <u t="1386480">ruined us because it's like that simply</u>
  <u t="1389039">would not exist.</u>
  <u t="1391360">&gt;&gt; It just just wouldn't. And obviously</u>
  <u t="1393039">something that scary, you need to be</u>
  <u t="1395039">safe. Take all the proper precautions.</u>
  <u t="1397200">But it's like you have the helmet, the</u>
  <u t="1399120">gloves, the cables, the harness, so you</u>
  <u t="1402640">should be safe doing it. And that's what</u>
  <u t="1404480">I feel like we keep getting stuck on.</u>
  <u t="1406080">But then every time we watch photos or</u>
  <u t="1407679">videos of it, we're like, how? So I</u>
  <u t="1410559">think we just had to do something also</u>
  <u t="1413520">like kind of dangerous to make ourselves</u>
  <u t="1415919">feel like to make ourselves feel</u>
  <u t="1417919">something.</u>
  <u t="1419120">&gt;&gt; We came to Switzerland wanting to feel</u>
  <u t="1420720">something.</u>
  <u t="1421360">&gt;&gt; Yeah. So we're going paragliding. This</u>
  <u t="1423039">paragliding it.</u>
  <u t="1425770">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1442480">&gt;&gt; Bye. I'll see you at the bottom.</u>
  <u t="1447930">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1454640">There she goes. That's so crazy.</u>
  <u t="1460950">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1479840">That was awesome.</u>
  <u t="1482240">&gt;&gt; Yeah, let's do it.</u>
  <u t="1486410">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1511039">That was insane. I'm so happy that we</u>
  <u t="1513760">decided to do that. Both of our flight</u>
  <u t="1515520">instructors were literally so nice. And</u>
  <u t="1518320">I feel like I was expecting like when</u>
  <u t="1519919">you go on a helicopter and it's loud.</u>
  <u t="1522159">&gt;&gt; It was so peaceful. It was literally the</u>
  <u t="1524400">prettiest view. So peaceful. We did cool</u>
  <u t="1526880">tricks. They to got like cool videos. We</u>
  <u t="1529360">got to like see each other while we were</u>
  <u t="1530880">going. That was awesome.</u>
  <u t="1533120">&gt;&gt; That was incredible.</u>
  <u t="1534880">&gt;&gt; The view couldn't have been better. 10</u>
  <u t="1537039">out of 10 experience.</u>
  <u t="1538159">&gt;&gt; Weather beautiful.</u>
  <u t="1540720">&gt;&gt; Mountains</u>
  <u t="1542480">beautiful.</u>
  <u t="1545840">&gt;&gt; Life beautiful.</u>
  <u t="1549120">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1570480">I feel like the definition of us</u>
  <u t="1572080">traveling is that we're in a rush. And</u>
  <u t="1574799">it's because we both like being as</u>
  <u t="1576400">efficient as possible and literally</u>
  <u t="1579520">capturing every single thing in one trip</u>
  <u t="1582159">and never wasting a good sunny day and</u>
  <u t="1585039">never wasting a sunset. So, we need to</u>
  <u t="1587760">learn how to slow down.</u>
  <u t="1591679">Why is that giving me anxiety?</u>
  <u t="1623600">I'm so exhausted. A half mile in.</u>
  <u t="1653440">It's feeling a lot more like rock</u>
  <u t="1654799">climbing.</u>
  <u t="1672320">He is our leader.</u>
  <u t="1681919">This is like I'm in race to survive and</u>
  <u t="1684399">the other team is catching up.</u>
  <u t="1687840">Go Josh.</u>
  <u t="1689679">This vlog is not building my portfolio</u>
  <u t="1691520">that I'm athletic.</u>
  <u t="1694960">&gt;&gt; But look where we are.</u>
  <u t="1696320">&gt;&gt; ASMR of me heavy breathing.</u>
  <u t="1704640">Heart rate 149.</u>
  <u t="1707520">Not that bad.</u>
  <u t="1709600">&gt;&gt; Lead the way.</u>
  <u t="1710799">&gt;&gt; Okay,</u>
  <u t="1712080">&gt;&gt; I think I see something.</u>
  <u t="1717360">&gt;&gt; Oh</u>
  <u t="1719600">my</u>
  <u t="1721200">goodness.</u>
  <u t="1724960">That's insane.</u>
  <u t="1726530">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1754799">Heat. Heat.</u>
  <u t="1757890">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1760480">Heat. Heat.</u>
  <u t="1762690">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1770480">Heat.</u>
  <u t="1774770">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1788000">Heat.</u>
  <u t="1792640">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1800320">Hey,</u>
  <u t="1802030">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1814320">hey, hey.</u>
  <u t="1819039">Heat. Heat.</u>
  <u t="1821980">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1845919">Heat. Heat.</u>
  <u t="1849860">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1854159">Heat. Heat.</u>
  <u t="1855990">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1862630">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1890640">Hold on for dear life. So, we can either</u>
  <u t="1892799">continue our journey down more spines</u>
  <u t="1894320">for miles and miles or follow that back</u>
  <u t="1897919">to the I can't even speak. Follow that</u>
  <u t="1900159">back to the car. We're going with option</u>
  <u t="1902320">B.</u>
  <u t="1909760">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1913519">Now that we've made it through Mordor,</u>
  <u t="1916159">which was the rocks things, if you watch</u>
  <u t="1917760">the Lord of the Rings, then you know</u>
  <u t="1919519">what we're talking about. It looks like</u>
  <u t="1921279">we're in a vegetable p.</u>
  <u t="1923200">&gt;&gt; This is very much Lord of the Rings.</u>
  <u t="1926640">&gt;&gt; Motus,</u>
  <u t="1928640">&gt;&gt; are you going to put that in? Is my</u>
  <u t="1930240">editor going to leave that?</u>
  <u t="1931519">&gt;&gt; I don't know.</u>
  <u t="1934080">Total time 3 hours and 50 minutes. Wow,</u>
  <u t="1938000">we did it.</u>
  <u t="1955360">&gt;&gt; We just woke up and it's 10:15. Our</u>
  <u t="1957760">hotel breakfast closes at 10:30, so I</u>
  <u t="1960399">quickly got dressed and we're heading</u>
  <u t="1961840">down there.</u>
  <u t="1964470">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1971030">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1983840">Two people who have had a lot of hiking</u>
  <u t="1986480">and cannot wait for a massage. My feet</u>
  <u t="1989919">are literally crunched. I need them to</u>
  <u t="1993840">to my</u>
  <u t="2024799">After the most glorious and relaxing</u>
  <u t="2027360">day, sleeping in, getting massages,</u>
  <u t="2030159">hanging out at the pool area, eating</u>
  <u t="2031600">lunch out there, reading.</u>
  <u t="2034159">Am I missing anything?</u>
  <u t="2040559">Not wearing hiking shoes. Guess what?</u>
  <u t="2043120">We're back in hiking shoes. Um, where</u>
  <u t="2046320">we're staying up in Wan, they have a</u>
  <u t="2048000">cable car that goes up to the top of the</u>
  <u t="2049839">mountain, and you can do a very simple</u>
  <u t="2051760">hike there. You can do more hikes, but</u>
  <u t="2053760">there is a pretty simple one. So, we</u>
  <u t="2055839">kind of got fitted in some simple hiking</u>
  <u t="2058240">fits. Hopefully, I don't get too cold. I</u>
  <u t="2060320">am a little nervous, but it's been hot</u>
  <u t="2061679">today. Um,</u>
  <u t="2063119">&gt;&gt; it's warm.</u>
  <u t="2064240">&gt;&gt; Yeah. So, we're going to go catch the</u>
  <u t="2065440">cable car and</u>
  <u t="2066480">&gt;&gt; 70°.</u>
  <u t="2067839">&gt;&gt; Oh, we are so fine. We're going to go</u>
  <u t="2070560">catch the cable car,</u>
  <u t="2072800">spend maybe an hour or so up there, and</u>
  <u t="2075119">it's supposed to be very pretty. Let's</u>
  <u t="2077919">go.</u>
  <u t="2083040">Who's going to go back for that?</u>
  <u t="2084960">&gt;&gt; It's not my fault.</u>
  <u t="2087839">&gt;&gt; I think what's so cool and Josh and I</u>
  <u t="2089599">were just talking about is that so many</u>
  <u t="2091119">of the hikes here you can reach by doing</u>
  <u t="2093679">gondilas up or trains or something like</u>
  <u t="2095760">that. So, you can make it like a very</u>
  <u t="2097680">short little trip with a gorgeous view</u>
  <u t="2099760">or you can then embark on harder ones if</u>
  <u t="2102079">you want to do more mileage. But, I feel</u>
  <u t="2103920">like there's not a lot of places I've</u>
  <u t="2105200">been to that is accessible for like</u>
  <u t="2107040">wherever you're at in your hiking</u>
  <u t="2108480">journey and that's cool. Update. We</u>
  <u t="2110320">decided to go on a two and a half mile</u>
  <u t="2112320">hike because it's looking very paved and</u>
  <u t="2115599">downward like this.</u>
  <u t="2118079">It says that it's going to take us about</u>
  <u t="2119440">an hour and 10 minutes. Then we're going</u>
  <u t="2121839">to arrive at a town called Kleinsteg, I</u>
  <u t="2124640">think is how you say it. And once we</u>
  <u t="2126960">arrive there, we have 10 minutes to make</u>
  <u t="2128640">the last train out of there. So, I don't</u>
  <u t="2130880">really know why we left ourselves with</u>
  <u t="2132400">that much pressure, but you know, it's</u>
  <u t="2135520">about being efficient and we had a very</u>
  <u t="2137440">slow, relaxing day. So, why not just amp</u>
  <u t="2140160">up the heart rate with a good hike and a</u>
  <u t="2143440">little angst? Music to my ears,</u>
  <u t="2146000">literally.</u>
  <u t="2148970">[Music]</u>
  <u t="2157280">You set me up.</u>
  <u t="2159440">&gt;&gt; Do it harder.</u>
  <u t="2160560">&gt;&gt; No, Josh. This one is stuck.</u>
  <u t="2165760">Slow</u>
  <u t="2169440">[Music]</u>
  <u t="2184900">[Applause]</u>
  <u t="2186060">[Music]</u>
  <u t="2191590">[Applause]</u>
  <u t="2195280">down.</u>
  <u t="2197119">Why you talk so mean?</u>
  <u t="2200320">Good lord, man. It ain't what you say.</u>
  <u t="2204960">Got nice clothes and late night shows.</u>
  <u t="2208000">Boogie down at the bar</u>
  <u t="2211760">and homemade booze, but it always goes</u>
  <u t="2214240">too far.</u>
  <u t="2214880">&gt;&gt; One of the things I wanted to try in</u>
  <u t="2216320">Switzerland was fresh milk from the side</u>
  <u t="2218480">of the road. But apparently they have</u>
  <u t="2219760">vending machines where you can actually</u>
  <u t="2221920">just dispense the milk yourself and get</u>
  <u t="2224079">it straight from the cow. So had to</u>
  <u t="2225599">check that out.</u>
  <u t="2229040">&gt;&gt; That is it.</u>
  <u t="2231200">&gt;&gt; You open it up. Well, and just like</u>
  <u t="2233200">that, we have a liter of fresh milk.</u>
  <u t="2235520">That was so much fun.</u>
  <u t="2240320">&gt;&gt; Cheers.</u>
  <u t="2242400">Look who's crossing the road.</u>
  <u t="2245359">They're coming for their milk.</u>
  <u t="2247760">No, this is actually unreal.</u>
  <u t="2252160">Did we buy insurance if a cow hits the</u>
  <u t="2254560">car?</u>
  <u t="2258800">This is crazy.</u>
  <u t="2263150">[Music]</u>
  <u t="2288160">I got</u>
  <u t="2291600">[Music]</u>
  <u t="2305350">[Music]</u>
  <u t="2343200">nice.</u>
  <u t="2343680">&gt;&gt; If you as a woman are watching this and</u>
  <u t="2346320">wondering what are they doing, just know</u>
  <u t="2348800">that we did take the time to stop over</u>
  <u t="2351200">at the lake for probably at least 10</u>
  <u t="2353520">minutes to make sure Josh can get the</u>
  <u t="2355599">perfect rock skip. And I said it was</u>
  <u t="2358079">nice and he said that's all. So I am</u>
  <u t="2361520">telling him he should send it in his</u>
  <u t="2362720">voice group message because it's nice.</u>
  <u t="2366079">&gt;&gt; It was an amazing rock skip.</u>
  <u t="2369040">&gt;&gt; It's nice. This is my position right</u>
  <u t="2372000">now. I have it on five times one. So do</u>
  <u t="2375040">the eclipse. Nope. Duck crossing. You</u>
  <u t="2376720">need to wait now.</u>
  <u t="2377520">&gt;&gt; I'll wait.</u>
  <u t="2386720">That was pretty.</u>
  <u t="2389839">That was insane.</u>
  <u t="2406960">Yay! He did it.</u>
  <u t="2411359">I can't believe I get to be married.</u>
  <u t="2416320">&gt;&gt; All right, let me show you how it's</u>
  <u t="2417440">done.</u>
  <u t="2420640">&gt;&gt; Uh,</u>
  <u t="2426480">that's how you I think you have to get</u>
  <u t="2428720">lower.</u>
  <u t="2432720">&gt;&gt; Man, slaining.</u>
  <u t="2436560">Let me show you.</u>
  <u t="2442480">And then take it back and then allow</u>
  <u t="2449200">and then release. Yep. Okay.</u>
  <u t="2454720">The depths are now just waiting here.</u>
  <u t="2456480">So, we're going to have to take an</u>
  <u t="2457599">intermission before I can put that into</u>
  <u t="2459680">work.</u>
  <u t="2460880">&gt;&gt; Or go that way. The video can see</u>
  <u t="2464319">myself there.</u>
  <u t="2466800">I do.</u>
  <u t="2471599">I told you I wasn't going to be good</u>
  <u t="2473920">that way.</u>
  <u t="2474319">&gt;&gt; That was the best noise ever.</u>
  <u t="2478640">&gt;&gt; Really?</u>
  <u t="2479760">&gt;&gt; We checked into our little lakefront</u>
  <u t="2481520">Airbnb that's down in more of the</u>
  <u t="2483520">village area or like the lakefront area.</u>
  <u t="2486319">And it is so cute. Driving in, it was</u>
  <u t="2488800">rainy and cloudy and all of that. And</u>
  <u t="2490640">then I was like, man, I love the rain.</u>
  <u t="2493040">It looks so cute, but also it would be</u>
  <u t="2494880">really cool to see a pretty sunset. We</u>
  <u t="2496960">went to the grocery store, kind of</u>
  <u t="2498319">walked around the town, got a little</u>
  <u t="2499520">settled in, and now look at the clouds.</u>
  <u t="2501680">Josh was just out here admiring the</u>
  <u t="2503200">view.</u>
  <u t="2505520">He looks so cute.</u>
  <u t="2513570">[Music]</u>
  <u t="2525700">[Music]</u>
  <u t="2530800">We're having a really romantic date</u>
  <u t="2533520">night.</u>
  <u t="2534960">&gt;&gt; Yeah.</u>
  <u t="2536160">&gt;&gt; The best table in the house. This quaint</u>
  <u t="2538560">little town.</u>
  <u t="2540319">We just ordered some fish and a corn and</u>
  <u t="2543359">blue. We're going to do a little</u>
  <u t="2545280">splitzies. That's what we love. That's</u>
  <u t="2547280">my love language. And John had his best</u>
  <u t="2549599">rock ski today.</u>
  <u t="2552560">&gt;&gt; Yeah, I did.</u>
  <u t="2554480">That's all I can think about. Like</u>
  <u t="2556400">genuinely all I can think about.</u>
  <u t="2558960">&gt;&gt; Yeah. I mean, that's to be expected.</u>
  <u t="2563680">&gt;&gt; I'm really good at rocking.</u>
  <u t="2567200">&gt;&gt; Possibly the best.</u>
  <u t="2569040">&gt;&gt; And if everyone can see</u>
  <u t="2572720">&gt;&gt; you would say that.</u>
  <u t="2573920">&gt;&gt; Yes.</u>
  <u t="2574560">&gt;&gt; You would say I'm the best rock skipper.</u>
  <u t="2576319">&gt;&gt; Yes.</u>
  <u t="2590079">outside.</u>
  <u t="2602960">Okay.</u>
  <u t="2615839">Nice.</u>
  <u t="2618640">&gt;&gt; Josh caught our walk short again</u>
  <u t="2621440">because the water is more still.</u>
  <u t="2629760">Okay.</u>
  <u t="2639359">&gt;&gt; Did you see that?</u>
  <u t="2640319">&gt;&gt; I did and I got it on video. Good job.</u>
  <u t="2643520">No. Leave on high.</u>
  <u t="2646079">&gt;&gt; I could do better.</u>
  <u t="2647440">&gt;&gt; My little brother asked us a question</u>
  <u t="2649359">and it's always on my mind. And he said,</u>
  <u t="2651119">"Would you rather have a guaranteed 10</u>
  <u t="2653280">more years of your life? You have 10</u>
  <u t="2655359">left. That's it. Or you have a</u>
  <u t="2657119">guaranteed 40." But you always have a</u>
  <u t="2660800">snail that if it touches you, you</u>
  <u t="2663920">instantly die.</u>
  <u t="2665520">&gt;&gt; So,</u>
  <u t="2666079">&gt;&gt; and the snail's mission is to touch you.</u>
  <u t="2668240">&gt;&gt; Yes. But like a snail moves so slow, so</u>
  <u t="2670480">you could always outrun it. You're</u>
  <u t="2671920">always faster, always better. But it's</u>
  <u t="2674000">like you would never rest. So anyway, we</u>
  <u t="2676480">saw this snail in Switzerland and I'm</u>
  <u t="2678160">going to send my brother a photo and be</u>
  <u t="2679760">like, "We found your snail." So you're</u>
  <u t="2681599">good unless the snail finds a way to get</u>
  <u t="2683440">into an airport.</u>
  <u t="2684400">&gt;&gt; He gets on our car. We bring him to the</u>
  <u t="2686319">airport. He gets on the plane, then he's</u>
  <u t="2688480">in the US.</u>
  <u t="2690000">&gt;&gt; He could make his way.</u>
  <u t="2690960">&gt;&gt; He parachutes down out of the plane on</u>
  <u t="2694160">top of Freedom.</u>
  <u t="2695440">&gt;&gt; Yeah.</u>
  <u t="2695839">&gt;&gt; Shout out Freedom.</u>
  <u t="2696800">&gt;&gt; So, we're letting him know that his</u>
  <u t="2698720">snail is in Switzerland. So, pending he</u>
  <u t="2700560">doesn't do that, he's safe for a little</u>
  <u t="2701760">while longer.</u>
  <u t="2705920">&gt;&gt; You stay right there.</u>
  <u t="2709440">Watch this view from our window.</u>
  <u t="2712480">Let's go.</u>
  <u t="2719180">[Music]</u>
  <u t="2757680">I saw you.</u>
  <u t="2762870">[Music]</u>
  <u t="2789920">How could I come to such a pretty place</u>
  <u t="2791440">and not have my favorite coffee ever? We</u>
  <u t="2793920">are attempting by getting a little</u>
  <u t="2795520">portable espresso machine to make our</u>
  <u t="2797760">coffee. And then we have local honey and</u>
  <u t="2800000">the fresh milk we got yesterday. So, I'm</u>
  <u t="2802560">excited for a latte this morning. And</u>
  <u t="2805760">let's make some.</u>
  <u t="2810240">I sound like the cows on the the hikes</u>
  <u t="2813200">we've been going on.</u>
  <u t="2814480">&gt;&gt; Give me a little cow, though.</u>
  <u t="2816770">[Music]</u>
  <u t="2823599">Whoa.</u>
  <u t="2837920">Nice.</u>
  <u t="2839760">&gt;&gt; Okay, after</u>
  <u t="2842240">15 minutes, we got our first sip. Here</u>
  <u t="2844880">we go.</u>
  <u t="2845440">&gt;&gt; It smells really good, but I am a little</u>
  <u t="2847760">scared just seeing how this was pumped</u>
  <u t="2849839">out.</u>
  <u t="2855920">Josh, that is very good. Like I almost</u>
  <u t="2860640">didn't</u>
  <u t="2861359">&gt;&gt; You're looking at me.</u>
  <u t="2862560">&gt;&gt; Well, yeah, cuz I'm talking to you.</u>
  <u t="2864480">&gt;&gt; The camera's all the way up here.</u>
  <u t="2866640">&gt;&gt; Here's the thing. I did not want this to</u>
  <u t="2868960">be so good because that was so much</u>
  <u t="2870800">effort and I kind of wanted it to be</u>
  <u t="2872240">like that effort. It couldn't be. That</u>
  <u t="2875280">hits.</u>
  <u t="2875920">&gt;&gt; You did You did even tell me you're</u>
  <u t="2877280">like, "Oh, no. You can have the first</u>
  <u t="2878560">one."</u>
  <u t="2880079">Yeah, I did.</u>
  <u t="2881680">&gt;&gt; Because you were expecting it to be bad.</u>
  <u t="2885119">&gt;&gt; This is very good.</u>
  <u t="2886560">&gt;&gt; Yeah. Give me my coffee back.</u>
  <u t="2887760">&gt;&gt; I know that I'm biased, but I our beans</u>
  <u t="2889599">are the best. Okay.</u>
  <u t="2891440">&gt;&gt; Best coffee we had in Europe in</u>
  <u t="2893359">Switzerland.</u>
  <u t="2894000">&gt;&gt; I'm not going to say that cuz we've had</u>
  <u t="2895520">really good coffee, but it's my</u>
  <u t="2898319">favorite.</u>
  <u t="2898800">&gt;&gt; Here, I'll turn the camera away.</u>
  <u t="2900880">&gt;&gt; That is the best coffee I've had this</u>
  <u t="2902640">whole trip.</u>
  <u t="2904640">Huh?</u>
  <u t="2917440">We definitely took this morning as a</u>
  <u t="2919599">slow morning. We enjoyed making our</u>
  <u t="2921200">coffee, which was like a whole process.</u>
  <u t="2923599">And now it's lunchtime and we're going</u>
  <u t="2925760">to go start a walk. There's a waterfall</u>
  <u t="2928000">that I guess is I think a 3mile walk</u>
  <u t="2930880">from here, but it's all just paved in a</u>
  <u t="2933200">nice way. So, put on my rain jacket and</u>
  <u t="2935839">some warmer clothes because today is</u>
  <u t="2937680">definitely our cloudiest and rainiest</u>
  <u t="2939599">yet. But we're not letting that keep us</u>
  <u t="2941599">inside all day. So, we're going to do</u>
  <u t="2943200">that and then maybe take a bus or a</u>
  <u t="2945599">ferry back here. Either way, sounds</u>
  <u t="2948000">pretty magical.</u>
  <u t="2949280">&gt;&gt; Your water bottle looks so silly.</u>
  <u t="2951599">&gt;&gt; Does it?</u>
  <u t="2952559">&gt;&gt; No, it doesn't.</u>
  <u t="2954480">&gt;&gt; I said that I would bring the big</u>
  <u t="2955839">backpack because Josh put his rain</u>
  <u t="2957599">jacket in my very small bag. This bag</u>
  <u t="2960400">perfectly fits my water bottle, tripod,</u>
  <u t="2962319">film, camera, phone, wallet.</u>
  <u t="2964960">With this rain jacket, it doesn't fit my</u>
  <u t="2966640">water bottle. And I was like, I'll just</u>
  <u t="2967920">bring your big backpack if you're going</u>
  <u t="2969119">to put stuff in there, too. And he's</u>
  <u t="2970800">like, no, no, this fits perfect. So, no.</u>
  <u t="2983359">&gt;&gt; I think it looks great. It compliments</u>
  <u t="2985359">your outfit.</u>
  <u t="2986640">&gt;&gt; That's what I was asking. I just can't</u>
  <u t="2987920">see</u>
  <u t="2988160">&gt;&gt; the cap. Look cap</u>
  <u t="2991599">lid.</u>
  <u t="2994079">I don't know where the orange fits in,</u>
  <u t="2995359">but the orange is complimentary.</u>
  <u t="2998240">Okay, I'm trusting you that I don't look</u>
  <u t="3000319">like a queen.</u>
  <u t="3008270">[Laughter]</u>
  <u t="3016090">[Applause]</u>
  <u t="3033300">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3045280">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3068800">Josh in his natural habitat. at eating</u>
  <u t="3071359">an apple with a plant stand.</u>
  <u t="3077400">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3097450">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3104319">She's shaking.</u>
  <u t="3107520">&gt;&gt; All right. Press up.</u>
  <u t="3110330">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3112160">&gt;&gt; Yeah.</u>
  <u t="3114890">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3115180">[Laughter]</u>
  <u t="3124160">We may have gotten a to- go carrot cake.</u>
  <u t="3127580">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3133660">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3149920">Oh yeah.</u>
  <u t="3160640">&gt;&gt; Wa.</u>
  <u t="3161920">&gt;&gt; That's a different cure cake.</u>
  <u t="3163280">&gt;&gt; Is it?</u>
  <u t="3164480">&gt;&gt; It's like lemony.</u>
  <u t="3165839">&gt;&gt; Interesting.</u>
  <u t="3166960">&gt;&gt; Taste it.</u>
  <u t="3168240">&gt;&gt; I will.</u>
  <u t="3173040">Oh,</u>
  <u t="3175200">&gt;&gt; isn't it different?</u>
  <u t="3178079">&gt;&gt; It's the icing. The icing has to be like</u>
  <u t="3181200">&gt;&gt; like a lemon,</u>
  <u t="3182319">&gt;&gt; but the cake itself isn't overly sweet.</u>
  <u t="3184240">It's almost like a granola bar.</u>
  <u t="3185920">&gt;&gt; Yeah.</u>
  <u t="3216800">Oh, grocery delivery.</u>
  <u t="3219599">Thank you. Some fresh pastries, yogurt.</u>
  <u t="3231680">The coffee is starting. Fresh cheese</u>
  <u t="3233839">grated. Eggs are starting to cook.</u>
  <u t="3236800">&gt;&gt; And the sun.</u>
  <u t="3238240">&gt;&gt; And the sun is out today.</u>
  <u t="3240000">&gt;&gt; Honey.</u>
  <u t="3241660">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3243280">&gt;&gt; What?</u>
  <u t="3244480">&gt;&gt; No. There's a bee who wants his honey</u>
  <u t="3246160">back. But I just need a little more.</u>
  <u t="3248559">&gt;&gt; He's going to come get you.</u>
  <u t="3250319">&gt;&gt; I know. He's been following me around</u>
  <u t="3251680">the kitchen.</u>
  <u t="3253599">I hear him.</u>
  <u t="3255680">&gt;&gt; He's so</u>
  <u t="3256160">&gt;&gt; Oh, there he is.</u>
  <u t="3258240">&gt;&gt; I'm closing the honey.</u>
  <u t="3262079">&gt;&gt; You're supposed to help me in these</u>
  <u t="3263440">situations.</u>
  <u t="3264480">&gt;&gt; He's just hanging by the window.</u>
  <u t="3266079">&gt;&gt; I know. I want him to be happy in life.</u>
  <u t="3269200">I just want him to go out the window and</u>
  <u t="3272240">not be upset at me.</u>
  <u t="3275680">&gt;&gt; Okay, go out.</u>
  <u t="3276400">&gt;&gt; Close the window. He went out.</u>
  <u t="3277839">&gt;&gt; Good morning. It is our last full day</u>
  <u t="3280000">here and it is so stunning today. I feel</u>
  <u t="3283280">like yesterday with it being cloudy and</u>
  <u t="3284880">gloomy, it was fine because we went on a</u>
  <u t="3287200">waterfall hike and just kind of got to</u>
  <u t="3289359">see everything. It still was very green</u>
  <u t="3291280">and lush, but I was hoping for sun on</u>
  <u t="3294240">the last day. And it hasn't quite hit</u>
  <u t="3296559">the water yet, but we're hoping for</u>
  <u t="3299119">beautiful water, which I don't see why</u>
  <u t="3300800">we want to have. And we actually found a</u>
  <u t="3302880">place when we were on our walk that</u>
  <u t="3304160">rents stand up paddle boards. So, we are</u>
  <u t="3306800">going to go paddle boarding on Lake</u>
  <u t="3308480">Brens.</u>
  <u t="3311680">&gt;&gt; I'm pretty excited.</u>
  <u t="3312800">&gt;&gt; It does sound magical. I did just</u>
  <u t="3314240">realize I forgot my sunglasses. So, if</u>
  <u t="3316960">I'm squinting, that's why.</u>
  <u t="3319040">&gt;&gt; This might be the most perfect rock</u>
  <u t="3320559">ever.</u>
  <u t="3330000">&gt;&gt; You think we're going to end up</u>
  <u t="3330880">swimming?</u>
  <u t="3332400">&gt;&gt; Yes.</u>
  <u t="3334100">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3355200">We made it out onto the lake and it is</u>
  <u t="3357280">so so beautiful. I can't even believe</u>
  <u t="3360160">how blue it is. But Josh had a vision</u>
  <u t="3362400">for the drone. So, he's going to try to</u>
  <u t="3364160">put the drone up on a paddle board in</u>
  <u t="3366240">the middle of this lake. Hopefully, a</u>
  <u t="3367760">ferry doesn't go past. And I guess if</u>
  <u t="3371359">you see the footage,</u>
  <u t="3373520">then you know that we were successful.</u>
  <u t="3375200">And if not,</u>
  <u t="3377760">I'm so sorry to our drone.</u>
  <u t="3379960">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3414400">Heat.</u>
  <u t="3420480">Hey, heat. Hey, heat.</u>
  <u t="3422740">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3429680">I'm finding a lot of peace right now.</u>
  <u t="3433839">This trip is the peace that I needed.</u>
  <u t="3439910">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3451200">&gt;&gt; Huh?</u>
  <u t="3451680">&gt;&gt; It's a perfect</u>
  <u t="3466960">We paddled from the place that we rented</u>
  <u t="3468720">our boards back to our house and now</u>
  <u t="3470400">we're going to drop off the drone and</u>
  <u t="3471920">Josh's jacket because we do not need a</u>
  <u t="3474000">jacket anymore and we're trying to amp</u>
  <u t="3475520">ourselves up to swim. So, we'll see if</u>
  <u t="3477760">that happens. It's so clear and blue</u>
  <u t="3480240">though that I really want to. Hey, why</u>
  <u t="3482559">are you ease dropping?</u>
  <u t="3484960">&gt;&gt; Are my socks in it?</u>
  <u t="3487040">&gt;&gt; Yes.</u>
  <u t="3488000">&gt;&gt; Action socks.</u>
  <u t="3489760">&gt;&gt; Josh always wears compressions because</u>
  <u t="3492000">vein stuff.</u>
  <u t="3494000">So now you know.</u>
  <u t="3497599">I've always been an ocean girl, but also</u>
  <u t="3500400">paddling in the lake here is so</u>
  <u t="3502559">refreshing. There's no salt in the</u>
  <u t="3504400">water. I will say it is very cold. It's</u>
  <u t="3506960">58 degrees outside, but it feels a lot</u>
  <u t="3508960">warmer. Like with the sun on me, I'm</u>
  <u t="3510799">actually cooking. I'm like, should I</u>
  <u t="3512480">have put on some sunscreen? I don't</u>
  <u t="3513920">know. But it's so peaceful, so relaxing.</u>
  <u t="3517839">Josh is on his board in front of me and</u>
  <u t="3519760">we're just taking in the blue water, the</u>
  <u t="3522079">blue skies. It is so clear, so very</u>
  <u t="3525440">clear that I know a dip in would be</u>
  <u t="3527359">good. I just don't know if I'm feeling</u>
  <u t="3528799">brave enough. As much as we've taken a</u>
  <u t="3530880">lot of time on this trip to capture</u>
  <u t="3532799">content, be vlogging, taking photos, all</u>
  <u t="3535440">of that stuff, we've also had a lot of</u>
  <u t="3537680">downtime of just doing enjoying things</u>
  <u t="3539920">together. Josh and my favorite thing to</u>
  <u t="3542000">do is activities. And I feel like hiking</u>
  <u t="3544079">is a really bonding thing because you're</u>
  <u t="3545839">doing something challenging with a</u>
  <u t="3547440">reward together. And like it's very</u>
  <u t="3550079">sweet. He'll offer to help carry my bags</u>
  <u t="3552400">or I will pick up the sandwiches for us</u>
  <u t="3555119">or share water or just do things. I</u>
  <u t="3558000">don't know. like there's something just</u>
  <u t="3559280">very precious about accomplishing things</u>
  <u t="3561200">together and I feel like that's why we</u>
  <u t="3563760">enjoy it so much especially living in</u>
  <u t="3565839">Florida where it is so flat there and I</u>
  <u t="3569040">love Florida. I feel like I I post about</u>
  <u t="3570799">it all the time. I love the beach. I</u>
  <u t="3572960">love everything about it. But getting to</u>
  <u t="3575280">travel places like this is so eye</u>
  <u t="3576960">opening of how you don't have to live</u>
  <u t="3579520">near the beach to enjoy water obviously</u>
  <u t="3581680">or you don't have to um only enjoy the</u>
  <u t="3584400">sunsets there, but it makes you</u>
  <u t="3586160">appreciate even though Florida doesn't</u>
  <u t="3588000">have any mountains or hikes or things</u>
  <u t="3589760">like that how great the weather is or</u>
  <u t="3592160">there's just pros and cons of every</u>
  <u t="3593760">different place. And I feel like I</u>
  <u t="3595520">always say that when I get comments of</u>
  <u t="3597920">people being like, "Oh, I would be happy</u>
  <u t="3599440">or enjoy my life if I lived in Florida</u>
  <u t="3601440">or warm weather." And while I will say</u>
  <u t="3603280">that there is truth behind the sun</u>
  <u t="3606799">bringing a lot of happiness and joy and</u>
  <u t="3608480">so I get that a lot, but there's also so</u>
  <u t="3611119">much joy to be had when it's like, wow,</u>
  <u t="3613599">all of these hikes that you get to do or</u>
  <u t="3615440">all of the greenery that comes with this</u>
  <u t="3617040">or the elevation or how the air is so</u>
  <u t="3619680">crisp or people can work outside because</u>
  <u t="3621760">you're not sweating to death and</u>
  <u t="3623200">sweltering in the summer. So, I feel</u>
  <u t="3625280">like that's an important thing about</u>
  <u t="3626640">life is obviously you have to do what's</u>
  <u t="3628559">best for you and live in the places and</u>
  <u t="3630880">do things that bring you happiness, but</u>
  <u t="3633520">that the grass isn't always greener on</u>
  <u t="3635520">the other side and there's always things</u>
  <u t="3637040">to be thankful for or to just appreciate</u>
  <u t="3640000">about whatever your situation is.</u>
  <u t="3642480">Obviously, easy to say being in</u>
  <u t="3644319">Switzerland, but I remember thinking</u>
  <u t="3645920">that when I visited the Midwest or out</u>
  <u t="3648880">out west anywhere or just all of these</u>
  <u t="3650960">different places have so many cool</u>
  <u t="3652480">things about them. So, I'm just having a</u>
  <u t="3654319">grateful moment right now. Place where</u>
  <u t="3655760">we got our paddle boards does have a</u>
  <u t="3657119">little dock over there. And I think if</u>
  <u t="3659599">I'm going to jump somewhere, it's going</u>
  <u t="3660640">to be there.</u>
  <u t="3670480">&gt;&gt; Three, two, one.</u>
  <u t="3678079">&gt;&gt; Cold. Really cold.</u>
  <u t="3682880">Wow. Like I'm inside of a water bottle</u>
  <u t="3685920">with ice.</u>
  <u t="3692320">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3726960">Oh gosh.</u>
  <u t="3730480">Oh boy.</u>
  <u t="3732160">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3743119">Option one,</u>
  <u t="3745839">we're going to go grab lunch and then go</u>
  <u t="3747920">to this cute valley and stream little</u>
  <u t="3750319">area that you can see the mountains in</u>
  <u t="3751599">the back. So, I don't know if I want to</u>
  <u t="3753599">wear this white skirt with this denim</u>
  <u t="3756160">top. Pretty cute loose vibes or</u>
  <u t="3763040">Josh is also trying to pick out his</u>
  <u t="3764559">outfit. Or do we like this one?</u>
  <u t="3767839">Okay, switch.</u>
  <u t="3772319">&gt;&gt; I think I might like the other one</u>
  <u t="3773520">better.</u>
  <u t="3773920">&gt;&gt; The white skirt. I feel like the white</u>
  <u t="3775680">skirt is more fun. This one's more</u>
  <u t="3777839">casual, which I do like this top, but</u>
  <u t="3780880">white skirt.</u>
  <u t="3787280">&gt;&gt; I didn't have to travel with this one</u>
  <u t="3788799">for so far.</u>
  <u t="3796319">It's the one.</u>
  <u t="3797760">&gt;&gt; Mhm.</u>
  <u t="3799760">&gt;&gt; Try that right now.</u>
  <u t="3801039">&gt;&gt; I will.</u>
  <u t="3801920">&gt;&gt; We're currently driving to a very pretty</u>
  <u t="3804079">valley and stream and I feel like I'd</u>
  <u t="3806079">seen this on Tik Tok. It's so funny to</u>
  <u t="3808319">me the amount of places that I've seen.</u>
  <u t="3810400">No one has mentioned the driving to them</u>
  <u t="3812799">and everything is like little teeny</u>
  <u t="3815520">bridges. This is honestly the easiest</u>
  <u t="3817839">part of it, but the road can only fit</u>
  <u t="3820000">one car and it will be sheer cliff</u>
  <u t="3823280">switchbacks. Buses will be going up on</u>
  <u t="3825599">the other end. And so Josh and I were</u>
  <u t="3827440">just laughing. We're like, "How is it</u>
  <u t="3829599">that no one mentions how crazy these</u>
  <u t="3832720">drives are?"</u>
  <u t="3833359">&gt;&gt; And people are saying it's like the one</u>
  <u t="3834880">or two comments that it's a fairy tale</u>
  <u t="3836640">drive or that it's like the most scenic</u>
  <u t="3838480">beautiful drive. And no doubt,</u>
  <u t="3840240">&gt;&gt; no,</u>
  <u t="3840799">&gt;&gt; it's pretty, but if you if you make a</u>
  <u t="3842880">mistake, you actually do die. like</u>
  <u t="3845440">forewarning or fair warning. It's like</u>
  <u t="3849039">&gt;&gt; your hands are probably cramped.</u>
  <u t="3850400">&gt;&gt; It's sheer and there's no protection.</u>
  <u t="3853359">You're exposed.</u>
  <u t="3854559">&gt;&gt; So, I feel like we haven't really rented</u>
  <u t="3856640">a car in other countries before. We</u>
  <u t="3858160">usually do public transportation. We've</u>
  <u t="3860319">been able to do way more things with</u>
  <u t="3862960">having a rental car, but with that comes</u>
  <u t="3866000">its own fair share of challenges. All</u>
  <u t="3869119">right.</u>
  <u t="3871820">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3887510">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3901440">And back down the windy</u>
  <u t="3904880">little roads we go. We did just pass a</u>
  <u t="3907440">bus.</u>
  <u t="3909839">&gt;&gt; You got this. You're doing amazing.</u>
  <u t="3922960">&gt;&gt; Does he have the right away?</u>
  <u t="3925039">&gt;&gt; I don't know. Do we split? Do you split</u>
  <u t="3927839">the swan?</u>
  <u t="3929680">Why did the swan cross the road, man?</u>
  <u t="3932160">He's got some feet.</u>
  <u t="3935200">&gt;&gt; That's a U looking</u>
  <u t="3942160">sound like tires.</u>
  <u t="3944559">&gt;&gt; Looks</u>
  <u t="3948300">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3951280">back on ours.</u>
  <u t="3955440">Heat.</u>
  <u t="3959870">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3964960">Heat.</u>
  <u t="3967050">[Music]</u>
  </text>
