<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="hnBCfnOYeNo" uploader="Sleepy Charlie" channel="Sleepy Charlie" likes="12601" title="Traveling Europe Alone With Absolutely No Plan" year="2025" month="12" day="23" date="20251223" is_ac="true">
  <u t="160">I will see you on the other side.</u>
  <u t="2619">[sighs and gasps] All right.</u>
  <u t="7205">[laughter] It sounds cliche cuz I'm sure</u>
  <u t="9440">you've heard a million Tik Toks saying</u>
  <u t="10960">the same dumb [ __ ] but please, like,</u>
  <u t="13280">everyone says it cuz it's true. You are</u>
  <u t="15599">so much more capable than you think you</u>
  <u t="18080">are. Trust me. I told myself I would go</u>
  <u t="20400">frolicking by myself at least once. I</u>
  <u t="23039">guess a lesson that like people</u>
  <u t="24640">sometimes don't really realize. It's</u>
  <u t="26320">like there's no reason to freak out in</u>
  <u t="28640">any case scenario.</u>
  <u t="31599">You absolutely 100% underestimate your</u>
  <u t="35040">ability to just figure it out.</u>
  <u t="38559">I just I never I never thought I</u>
  <u t="40719">couldn't travel to Europe by myself.</u>
  <u t="43885">[music] It was just a matter of whether</u>
  <u t="45200">I actually pursued it or not. [singing]</u>
  <u t="48480">The plan was simple. to fly to</u>
  <u t="50800">Switzerland on September 1st, take a</u>
  <u t="52719">train to a town called Interlockin, and</u>
  <u t="54800">from there wing it. The goal to explore</u>
  <u t="58719">the continent of Europe for two months</u>
  <u t="60719">completely alone with no plan.</u>
  <u t="65040">This place is gorgeous and it's like</u>
  <u t="66640">literally just Zurich. It's just a city.</u>
  <u t="69600">It's not any It's I'm not even in the</u>
  <u t="71119">Alps yet. This place is awesome. But</u>
  <u t="72960">this is day one. This is hostel number</u>
  <u t="76080">one. I'm leaving this hostel on Friday</u>
  <u t="78320">to go to the Alps.</u>
  <u t="82000">After two quick days in the city of</u>
  <u t="84560">Zurich, I hopped on my first big train</u>
  <u t="87439">headed for interlocking.</u>
  <u t="89360">I got to my hostel in the afternoon,</u>
  <u t="92560">like 3:00 p.m.ish.</u>
  <u t="95520">My back hurts. I was happier than ever</u>
  <u t="98320">to be in the mountains finally,</u>
  <u t="101280">of course, until the very next morning</u>
  <u t="103520">when I hit my first major mental</u>
  <u t="106000">challenge.</u>
  <u t="109600">made it to Louder Vernon. It is the 6th.</u>
  <u t="113520">This place is It's cool. Uh I'm just I'm</u>
  <u t="116399">struggling. I This is a little bit</u>
  <u t="117840">harder than I thought it was going to</u>
  <u t="119119">be, to be honest with you. The hostel</u>
  <u t="120960">I'm staying in is cool. There's cool</u>
  <u t="122880">people. It's a cool little hostel. But</u>
  <u t="124719">the bunk room, like where I'm sleeping,</u>
  <u t="127119">it is. There's a part of me that's like</u>
  <u t="129520">screaming at me like, I want to go home.</u>
  <u t="131520">I want to go home. I want to go home.</u>
  <u t="132800">It's literally only been like 5 days,</u>
  <u t="135040">but I I don't want to go home</u>
  <u t="136480">empty-handed. That's ultimately what I'm</u>
  <u t="137920">trying to say. Like I came here to</u>
  <u t="139599">figure figure some [ __ ] out. And so when</u>
  <u t="142160">I start feeling these things, it makes</u>
  <u t="143760">me feel like I'm on the right path, but</u>
  <u t="145920">it [ __ ] sucks. I don't know, man. I'm</u>
  <u t="148800">going to just wrap this up cuz it's been</u>
  <u t="150640">really fun. Yeah, I've thought about it</u>
  <u t="152480">a lot since that day. I think the only</u>
  <u t="156160">thing that was really bringing me any</u>
  <u t="157760">sort of comfort in that moment in time</u>
  <u t="159760">was that I knew that the sort of pain I</u>
  <u t="163360">was feeling was my growth happening in</u>
  <u t="165280">real time.</u>
  <u t="167760">Are you kidding me? I decided to start</u>
  <u t="170239">walking from Louderder Burnon to a town</u>
  <u t="172239">called Merin. And this is turning out to</u>
  <u t="174239">be like the best decision I've made on</u>
  <u t="175760">the whole trip so far. I I I keep</u>
  <u t="177680">stressing out about like planning out</u>
  <u t="179920">decision, decision, like what's next?</u>
  <u t="182000">What's next? What's next? Like, but then</u>
  <u t="183599">I was like, you know what? [ __ ] it. I'm</u>
  <u t="185680">going to just do it. I will figure out</u>
  <u t="187120">how to get back later. I also just like</u>
  <u t="190159">don't really care right now cuz I'm kind</u>
  <u t="193120">of in heaven. [music]</u>
  <u t="202397">&gt;&gt; [music]</u>
  <u t="205519">&gt;&gt; Man, yeah, that hike was emotional.</u>
  <u t="210912">[music]</u>
  <u t="214000">&gt;&gt; I was really struggling that morning and</u>
  <u t="216400">I didn't really know what to do. [music]</u>
  <u t="222480">I was scared to make a move because I</u>
  <u t="224560">didn't [music] know really how I would</u>
  <u t="226319">get back.</u>
  <u t="233440">&gt;&gt; And that's when I realized it would</u>
  <u t="235200">probably be better if I just jumped and</u>
  <u t="237360">I'll figure out how to get back later.</u>
  <u t="245680">And that was the mindset that led me to</u>
  <u t="249439">some of the most beautiful places I had</u>
  <u t="251760">ever seen</u>
  <u t="253519">to meet some of the coolest people I had</u>
  <u t="255439">ever met.</u>
  <u t="257040">&gt;&gt; A classic a classic football</u>
  <u t="259040">&gt;&gt; throughout the rest of this two-month</u>
  <u t="260400">adventure.</u>
  <u t="261040">&gt;&gt; About to eat [ __ ]</u>
  <u t="263440">&gt;&gt; One of the main destinations that I</u>
  <u t="265680">really wanted to see along this trip was</u>
  <u t="267919">the Doommites located in northern Italy.</u>
  <u t="271520">uh they were going to be kind of</u>
  <u t="273120">difficult to get to from where I was in</u>
  <u t="275120">Switzerland. So I decided to take a</u>
  <u t="277360">couple stops along the way. One of which</u>
  <u t="280000">was a place called Chinqutere. I'm</u>
  <u t="282880">currently in Laspzia, Italy um in</u>
  <u t="286320">Chikatere. It's been such an interesting</u>
  <u t="288320">experience so far. I I have Yeah. I</u>
  <u t="290960">don't know. I It's like I'm starting to</u>
  <u t="293120">realize how capable I actually am of</u>
  <u t="296000">doing this stuff. [music]</u>
  <u t="304578">&gt;&gt; [music]</u>
  <u t="311128">[music]</u>
  <u t="318988">[music]</u>
  <u t="322320">&gt;&gt; Shutter was the first [music]</u>
  <u t="324960">solo like completely solo stay of the</u>
  <u t="327840">trip. I wasn't in a hostel. I was in a</u>
  <u t="329840">private room [music] for the first time</u>
  <u t="330880">in like two weeks, which is really nice.</u>
  <u t="332639">But I mean, it definitely was a little</u>
  <u t="334400">bit lonely at times, but I was still</u>
  <u t="337440">kind of just [music] in dreamland</u>
  <u t="339440">because I was just doing this by myself.</u>
  <u t="342568">[music] So, I I felt pretty good. The</u>
  <u t="345039">only thing with Chin with Terry was this</u>
  <u t="347280">place was packed with people. I did a</u>
  <u t="349600">couple hikes drenched in sweat. There</u>
  <u t="351919">was a lot of people on the hikes and</u>
  <u t="353680">ultimately it wasn't my favorite place</u>
  <u t="356400">uh by any means for the whole trip. But</u>
  <u t="358880">I'm glad I stopped there at the very</u>
  <u t="360479">least because it broke up the trip</u>
  <u t="362219">[music] to the next stop which was the</u>
  <u t="365280">Doommites which was probably the best</u>
  <u t="367759">stop of the entire trip. But I wouldn't</u>
  <u t="370160">get there [music] before probably one of</u>
  <u t="371759">the most stressful days of my entire</u>
  <u t="373600">life.</u>
  <u t="376000">&gt;&gt; First like kind of legitimate problem.</u>
  <u t="378880">my literal first train of the [ __ ]</u>
  <u t="381120">day got uh delayed. And so now I'm like</u>
  <u t="384319">kind of screwed in a way. I was supposed</u>
  <u t="386400">to get to the town that I'm going to in</u>
  <u t="388880">the Doommites at like 300 p.m. And now</u>
  <u t="391520">I'm not going to get there till like</u>
  <u t="392800">7:30. Well, I'm not even I'm not going</u>
  <u t="394960">to get to a town called Bzano until</u>
  <u t="396800">7:30. And then it's an hour and a half</u>
  <u t="398560">car ride from Bzano to the town I'm</u>
  <u t="400720">trying to get to. And there are no</u>
  <u t="402639">trains and no buses by the time I'm</u>
  <u t="404720">going to get there. So, my only options</u>
  <u t="407840">are to rent a car or get an extremely</u>
  <u t="410240">expensive Uber or taxi. And I've been</u>
  <u t="412479">sitting at this train station for like</u>
  <u t="416080">an hour. This sucks, but uh it's going</u>
  <u t="419360">to be a long day. I figured it was going</u>
  <u t="420720">to be a long day, but this is even</u>
  <u t="421919">longer than I was hoping. Since I had</u>
  <u t="424800">five trainers, that means I would be</u>
  <u t="426880">obviously switching trains five times,</u>
  <u t="429440">which means if one of the trains was too</u>
  <u t="431520">late, I would miss the rest of the</u>
  <u t="433360">trains. And the very first train of the</u>
  <u t="435680">of the day was like 40 minutes late,</u>
  <u t="438880">screwing up my entire day. I have been</u>
  <u t="442319">Oh my god. Yeah, we're doing this. I</u>
  <u t="444720">have been on trains for the last 12</u>
  <u t="448319">hours. We made it not to the hotel that</u>
  <u t="451039">I'm supposed to stay in. Actually, I was</u>
  <u t="453599">supposed to take a bus from Bzano to Val</u>
  <u t="456960">Gardina, but the last bus was at 7:25</u>
  <u t="460160">and my train got in at 7:30. The two</u>
  <u t="462639">options were Ubers or um I spend</u>
  <u t="465710">[snorts] the night at the train station.</u>
  <u t="467280">So I decided to do neither of those</u>
  <u t="469599">things and get an emergency hotel in</u>
  <u t="472240">Bolzano. Cost me $170 for the night.</u>
  <u t="475919">Today was a stressful day. I'm not going</u>
  <u t="477599">to lie. It was stressful and I feel</u>
  <u t="479680">actually like really amazing that I'm</u>
  <u t="481919">here and alive and breathing. Tomorrow I</u>
  <u t="484560">take the hour and a half bus to Val</u>
  <u t="487440">Gardina. And I hope I don't [ __ ] that</u>
  <u t="489680">up. But the good news is that if I do</u>
  <u t="491120">[ __ ] it up, I have the entire day to</u>
  <u t="492960">figure it out. So 10:00 a.m. the next</u>
  <u t="496240">morning, I took the bus straight to the</u>
  <u t="499919">town I was staying in called Val</u>
  <u t="501440">Gardina, right in the middle of the</u>
  <u t="503520">Doommites. And it quickly became</u>
  <u t="506720">apparent to me that the suffering I had</u>
  <u t="508560">endured the day prior was completely</u>
  <u t="510800">worth it.</u>
  <u t="511280">&gt;&gt; I'm just now seeing the room that I</u>
  <u t="512800">booked here a few days ago in the</u>
  <u t="514800">Doommites. Dude,</u>
  <u t="518320">are you kidding me? What have I done?</u>
  <u t="520959">I'm here for four nights. I think it's</u>
  <u t="522959">safe to say that like the entire</u>
  <u t="524959">shenanigans that I had to go through</u>
  <u t="526480">yesterday and today was worth it cuz</u>
  <u t="529600">holy [ __ ] I'm so glad to be back in the</u>
  <u t="532000">mountains, too. [music]</u>
  <u t="539071">[music]</u>
  <u t="546276">&gt;&gt; [music]</u>
  <u t="551040">&gt;&gt; What? What? I'm pretty sure I actually</u>
  <u t="554800">just died in an [music] elevator. I was</u>
  <u t="557200">still alone, but this time it was</u>
  <u t="558640">different. This wasn't loneliness. It</u>
  <u t="560640">was solitude. I didn't speak to very</u>
  <u t="562880">many people over those 3 days, but I was</u>
  <u t="564640">happier than I had ever been.</u>
  <u t="566160">&gt;&gt; I told myself I would go frolicking by</u>
  <u t="568160">myself at least once on this trip. I</u>
  <u t="570560">logged over like 30,000 [music] steps on</u>
  <u t="572959">all three days in the Doommites. I hiked</u>
  <u t="575040">up thousands of feet. My body was</u>
  <u t="577040">screaming at me, but I didn't hear it.</u>
  <u t="584921">[music]</u>
  <u t="589200">Every second I got to myself out in</u>
  <u t="591360">these [music] mountains, I was convinced</u>
  <u t="592880">I was the happiest person on earth. This</u>
  <u t="594880">was the most beautiful place I had ever</u>
  <u t="596720">seen.</u>
  <u t="597519">&gt;&gt; Look at that.</u>
  <u t="601296">&gt;&gt; [music]</u>
  <u t="602640">&gt;&gt; I went through some serious challenges</u>
  <u t="604320">and spent a lot more money than I wanted</u>
  <u t="606320">to in order to get here. But I can</u>
  <u t="608240">confidently say that every second of</u>
  <u t="610160">stress, every penny spent was completely</u>
  <u t="613120">worth it.</u>
  <u t="618959">All right, today is day 22.</u>
  <u t="622880">I don't know when the [ __ ] that</u>
  <u t="624079">happened. I made it to Insrook, Austria</u>
  <u t="626720">yesterday. There's really no like</u>
  <u t="628959">objective today at all which um</u>
  <u t="631920">definitely is [ __ ] with my head as it</u>
  <u t="634079">usually does when I try to not do</u>
  <u t="636320">anything for a day. I feel depressed.</u>
  <u t="638480">Something I did realize in the doommites</u>
  <u t="640800">actually kind of enjoy my own company a</u>
  <u t="642880">lot more than I thought I did. Like I</u>
  <u t="644399">don't know back at home I always felt</u>
  <u t="645760">like it was definitely getting to a</u>
  <u t="647040">point where I started to kind of like</u>
  <u t="648640">hate myself for some reason. Whether it</u>
  <u t="650959">was because I couldn't do things I</u>
  <u t="652320">wanted to do or thought I wasn't good</u>
  <u t="654399">enough or whatever it was. I kind of</u>
  <u t="655920">just like didn't like myself and didn't</u>
  <u t="658160">really like who I was, I guess. I don't</u>
  <u t="660320">know. But here, I still feel like a lot</u>
  <u t="662959">more comfortable with myself, if that</u>
  <u t="665600">makes any sense. Which is just a weird</u>
  <u t="667519">feeling cuz I guess I've never really</u>
  <u t="668959">felt that way before. Like I feel more</u>
  <u t="671279">like secure and like a little bit more</u>
  <u t="673360">confident in my own skin.</u>
  <u t="676622">[music]</u>
  <u t="679760">I think Insbrook was the first time that</u>
  <u t="684079">I actually started to miss home.</u>
  <u t="689067">[music]</u>
  <u t="690480">Up until that point, I had been pretty</u>
  <u t="693040">decently distracted by everything and</u>
  <u t="695519">still adjusting to the life.</u>
  <u t="698480">&gt;&gt; Yeah. [music]</u>
  <u t="701760">&gt;&gt; Yeah. I remember sitting down on that</u>
  <u t="703279">bench and didn't have much of an</u>
  <u t="706000">objective that day and I definitely was</u>
  <u t="708000">starting to think about home a little</u>
  <u t="709279">bit more than weeks past.</u>
  <u t="712560">But on the second day, I was able to uh</u>
  <u t="716079">spend the day up in the mountains again,</u>
  <u t="717600">which made me feel a lot better. [music]</u>
  <u t="720560">I went up to the top of Insbrook, which</u>
  <u t="722720">is a mountain that's at about I think</u>
  <u t="724640">7,000 ft.</u>
  <u t="727440">It was nice to forget that feeling for a</u>
  <u t="729680">day.</u>
  <u t="730720">This is ridiculous.</u>
  <u t="733040">&gt;&gt; Yeah. The the more you sit still, the</u>
  <u t="734959">more everything catches up to you, you</u>
  <u t="737279">know, start thinking about my dog. And</u>
  <u t="741519">um you know, when you're in the</u>
  <u t="743440">mountains, it doesn't really matter how</u>
  <u t="745360">homesick you may or may not be. Like,</u>
  <u t="747839">you don't really think about it. You</u>
  <u t="749600">don't really care. But uh on the on the</u>
  <u t="752480">in the quiet moments</u>
  <u t="756079">in between,</u>
  <u t="758480">it definitely starts to hit you.</u>
  <u t="783200">The next stop after that was Salsburg,</u>
  <u t="786000">but Salsburg was really just like a home</u>
  <u t="788480">base in order for me to go visit</u>
  <u t="790320">Hallstat.</u>
  <u t="791904">[music]</u>
  <u t="798454">[music]</u>
  <u t="804560">Holstat is a crazy little town buried in</u>
  <u t="808079">the mountains on a lake only accessible</u>
  <u t="811200">by boat.</u>
  <u t="812639">&gt;&gt; I was in Salsburg for</u>
  <u t="815519">three full days. I think this [music]</u>
  <u t="818160">was definitely the highlight of that</u>
  <u t="820320">little excursion.</u>
  <u t="824654">[music]</u>
  <u t="829920">This was another one of those touristy</u>
  <u t="831680">spots. When you look up places to see in</u>
  <u t="833680">Austria, the first thing that's going to</u>
  <u t="835360">come up is probably H Hallstat. So,</u>
  <u t="838000">there was a fair amount of people there,</u>
  <u t="839519">but I tried to make do with the</u>
  <u t="842000">experience as much as as well as I</u>
  <u t="844000">could.</u>
  <u t="846959">&gt;&gt; Today is</u>
  <u t="848880">day 28. I'm feeling something I never</u>
  <u t="852160">thought I would feel. Um, I'm bored.</u>
  <u t="854959">Like I'm not even I'm literally bored</u>
  <u t="857760">for the past like five days. I've just</u>
  <u t="860160">been like I don't know. I I I'm like I</u>
  <u t="863279">don't like I'm going to Budapest</u>
  <u t="865199">tomorrow, so Budapest will be cool. I'm</u>
  <u t="867120">there for 2 days, but the cities to me</u>
  <u t="869440">are just like and I know Budapest is</u>
  <u t="872800">supposed to be really cool, I guess. But</u>
  <u t="877199">I don't know. And little did I know I</u>
  <u t="879920">could not have been more wrong. The next</u>
  <u t="882480">few days would be some of the most</u>
  <u t="883839">challenging of the entire trip.</u>
  <u t="891839">Today is October</u>
  <u t="895120">1st. I've been in Europe for 30 days.</u>
  <u t="899279">Um, I'd love to tell you that I'm like</u>
  <u t="901279">having such a great time and this is so</u>
  <u t="903279">cool, but the past like</u>
  <u t="906560">week has been kind of [ __ ] and the past</u>
  <u t="909040">like two days in particular, today</u>
  <u t="911199">included, definitely not um having a</u>
  <u t="915120">great time. I don't know. I just have</u>
  <u t="917839">not been enjoying myself here at all and</u>
  <u t="919760">I haven't met anyone here either. I've</u>
  <u t="922000">tried a a couple times to talk to people</u>
  <u t="925279">and meet people in my own hostel to no</u>
  <u t="927360">avail. So, I was going to go to Vienna</u>
  <u t="930000">and then Prague. I'm still going to</u>
  <u t="931600">Vienna cuz I already booked it. But</u>
  <u t="933040">honestly, I just I don't think I'm going</u>
  <u t="934560">to go to Prague. I dead ass think I'm</u>
  <u t="936079">just going to go back to [ __ ]</u>
  <u t="937519">Switzerland, dude. I genuinely think</u>
  <u t="940079">where I belong is the mountains. I'm</u>
  <u t="941920">just going to go back to the mountains.</u>
  <u t="944240">I do not like cities.</u>
  <u t="947279">Even if they're surrounded by mountains,</u>
  <u t="949120">I don't really like them. Budapest was</u>
  <u t="952079">the first time that I think I like</u>
  <u t="954320">really really struggled. My hostel was</u>
  <u t="957120">this weird like Squid Game looking</u>
  <u t="960000">place. The it was hot at night, so I was</u>
  <u t="963360">sweating in my sleep. The bathroom was</u>
  <u t="965199">on the other side of the the building.</u>
  <u t="967279">It it just the whole thing was kind of a</u>
  <u t="968959">disaster. And I was really concerned</u>
  <u t="971759">because I my plan was to go to Vienna</u>
  <u t="975120">and then Prague and then Munich and</u>
  <u t="977680">those are all cities. And it was very</u>
  <u t="980240">clear to me at this point that I did not</u>
  <u t="982000">like cities. But regardless of this, I</u>
  <u t="984480">decided to just follow through on my</u>
  <u t="986160">plan anyways. And that's when I ran into</u>
  <u t="988639">an absolute disaster of a 4-hour train</u>
  <u t="991839">ride.</u>
  <u t="994480">We made it to Prague. It's October</u>
  <u t="997920">6. I can't believe it's been over a</u>
  <u t="1000800">month at this point. Uh yesterday I took</u>
  <u t="1002800">the train from Vienna to Prague which</u>
  <u t="1005440">was 4 hours and I didn't have a reserved</u>
  <u t="1008000">seat cuz you didn't need one but it</u>
  <u t="1009839">recommended it but they were all sold</u>
  <u t="1011199">out so I wound up on the floor for 4</u>
  <u t="1013120">hours. Great stuff. Lost feeling in my</u>
  <u t="1015360">legs but I got here and it was raining.</u>
  <u t="1017680">That sucked. And um there's a just a</u>
  <u t="1020800">great nice old gentleman in my six bed</u>
  <u t="1024959">dorm here in Prague that snores like I</u>
  <u t="1028240">don't even like a sailor. It is so oof.</u>
  <u t="1031439">And on top of that, he loves to make</u>
  <u t="1032880">lots of funny noises in the middle of</u>
  <u t="1034559">the night. So regardless of my sleep-d</u>
  <u t="1036720">deprived and sick state, I actually feel</u>
  <u t="1038959">pretty good cuz I only have one day here</u>
  <u t="1040480">in Prague cuz I'm getting sick of cities</u>
  <u t="1042319">to be honest with you. Although I will</u>
  <u t="1043679">say Prague is pretty sick. Vienna was</u>
  <u t="1045520">also pretty cool. Vienna was actually</u>
  <u t="1047120">not that bad cuz I met some cool people</u>
  <u t="1048720">and spent the day with them.</u>
  <u t="1051287">[music]</u>
  <u t="1059147">&gt;&gt; [music]</u>
  <u t="1070282">[music]</u>
  <u t="1075522">[music]</u>
  <u t="1079200">&gt;&gt; I booked my flight home for October 31st</u>
  <u t="1082000">from London. So, I got to find my way</u>
  <u t="1083919">over there. I see the end of the tunnel.</u>
  <u t="1085919">Not that this is a [music] dark, scary</u>
  <u t="1087600">tunnel necessarily, but I I see the end</u>
  <u t="1089440">of the end of the road, which is</u>
  <u t="1091600">comforting for sure. Has definitely had</u>
  <u t="1093760">a bit of an impact [music] on my my</u>
  <u t="1095760">mental state knowing that there's an end</u>
  <u t="1097919">now. I just think that the last few last</u>
  <u t="1100320">couple [music] weeks have been like</u>
  <u t="1102559">Vienna was nice cuz I got to hang out</u>
  <u t="1104160">with some people. Prague is cool. I'm by</u>
  <u t="1106080">myself, but I'm only here for a day and</u>
  <u t="1107620">[music] it's actually kind of cool here.</u>
  <u t="1109039">And I'm going to Munich tomorrow for</u>
  <u t="1110400">only a day. And then after that, I'm I</u>
  <u t="1112559">said, "Fuck it. I'm going back into the</u>
  <u t="1114000">mountains. I'm going back to Austria and</u>
  <u t="1116080">then Switzerland and then uh Shamani."</u>
  <u t="1118880">&gt;&gt; Yeah. I don't know. I don't know how to</u>
  <u t="1120320">describe it. I'm I'm I'm definitely</u>
  <u t="1122320">looking forward to going home, but I</u>
  <u t="1124080">know damn well I'm going to miss every</u>
  <u t="1125760">sec. Even the even the moments in</u>
  <u t="1127520">Budapest when I was [ __ ] miserable.</u>
  <u t="1129840">Like I'm going to miss that when I get</u>
  <u t="1131679">there. I'm trying to remind myself that.</u>
  <u t="1133520">Like no matter how much my feet ache and</u>
  <u t="1136000">no matter how much my shoulders hurt and</u>
  <u t="1138720">no matter how much I want to strangle</u>
  <u t="1140720">the snoring old man across the [ __ ]</u>
  <u t="1143440">bunks from me, I'm going to miss all of</u>
  <u t="1145280">it. Trying to keep that in mind and</u>
  <u t="1146960">pushing forward. So, [music] but I can't</u>
  <u t="1149039">wait to get back to the mountains.</u>
  <u t="1150320">Honestly, I don't think I'll have</u>
  <u t="1151360">another chance to make one of these</u>
  <u t="1152559">before then. So, I'll see [music] you in</u>
  <u t="1155039">the Alps.</u>
  <u t="1161328">&gt;&gt; [music]</u>
  <u t="1169188">[music]</u>
  <u t="1192768">[music]</u>
  <u t="1200628">[music]</u>
  <u t="1207360">&gt;&gt; Heat. Heat. [music]</u>
  <u t="1224209">[music]</u>
  <u t="1229760">Heat. Heat.</u>
  <u t="1232069">[music]</u>
  <u t="1247789">[music]</u>
  <u t="1253684">&gt;&gt; [music]</u>
  <u t="1262854">[music]</u>
  <u t="1267679">&gt;&gt; Okay, it's October 18th. I have [music]</u>
  <u t="1270960">13 days left in my trip. If I look</u>
  <u t="1273200">miserable, it's because I kind of am.</u>
  <u t="1275600">Yeah, I I I kind of had a a little bit</u>
  <u t="1277679">of a [ __ ] up with like scheduling my</u>
  <u t="1280080">stays and everything because the trains</u>
  <u t="1283120">yesterday to go to Shaman from where I</u>
  <u t="1286080">am just like didn't exist basically. So,</u>
  <u t="1288880">which means that I've been in Schwitz,</u>
  <u t="1290640">Switzerland for three full days. And</u>
  <u t="1293039">this place is the most unremarkable</u>
  <u t="1295520">place I have been in this entire trip.</u>
  <u t="1298240">I'm not even kidding. This might be</u>
  <u t="1300320">worse than Budapest. on top of</u>
  <u t="1302400">everything from like there being nothing</u>
  <u t="1304720">in this town, the weather being [ __ ]</u>
  <u t="1307039">there's no one in this hostel. There's</u>
  <u t="1309200">nobody. The cherry on top of all that is</u>
  <u t="1311440">it's expensive as [ __ ] for no reason.</u>
  <u t="1315255">[sighs]</u>
  <u t="1315919">Yeah, the past 3 days have sucked. I'm</u>
  <u t="1317840">not going to lie. I uh I actually called</u>
  <u t="1319440">it quits on a hike today, which I've</u>
  <u t="1321039">never done. This is the first day the</u>
  <u t="1323440">sun has been out the entire time I' I've</u>
  <u t="1325760">been in Schwitz. And I went to go do the</u>
  <u t="1328799">only hike that I even came to this town</u>
  <u t="1330880">for. And yeah, there's [ __ ] a ton of</u>
  <u t="1333440">people on that hike. Extremely popular</u>
  <u t="1335840">hike. I mean, it was Yeah, it wasn't</u>
  <u t="1338080">there. I was not able to get any shots</u>
  <u t="1340080">with just me in it. I didn't even try to</u>
  <u t="1342080">be honest cuz it was that bad.</u>
  <u t="1343679">Definitely thinking about home a lot,</u>
  <u t="1345760">especially in the hard moments. But um I</u>
  <u t="1349760">don't know. [snorts]</u>
  <u t="1350720">The next day, I was more than happy to</u>
  <u t="1353440">finally leave that place and head for</u>
  <u t="1355280">Shyaman, France.</u>
  <u t="1358080">I was a little concerned because the</u>
  <u t="1360240">weather wasn't looking too good, but</u>
  <u t="1362960">this was another instance where it ended</u>
  <u t="1365600">up being some of the best days of the</u>
  <u t="1367840">trip, solely because of the people that</u>
  <u t="1369600">I met there.</u>
  <u t="1371520">The weather sucked for basically the</u>
  <u t="1373200">entire time I was in Shamani except for</u>
  <u t="1376480">legitimately a single hour of the second</u>
  <u t="1380240">day where the weather cleared up just</u>
  <u t="1382159">for us to go up to take a look at Mlancc</u>
  <u t="1385120">at around 12,000 ft.</u>
  <u t="1387961">[music]</u>
  <u t="1395166">[music]</u>
  <u t="1401061">&gt;&gt; [music]</u>
  <u t="1403760">&gt;&gt; This cameras</u>
  <u t="1406301">[music]</u>
  <u t="1414161">[music]</u>
  <u t="1420056">[music]</u>
  <u t="1426640">and And I'm really glad that it ended on</u>
  <u t="1428320">that note cuz this was my last</u>
  <u t="1431679">destination in the mountains. After</u>
  <u t="1433760">this, I would be heading for Geneva and</u>
  <u t="1436799">then Paris and then London and then that</u>
  <u t="1439280">was that. After what felt like a pretty</u>
  <u t="1441440">long trip from Paris to London, I</u>
  <u t="1444720">arrived at my nice hotel to give myself</u>
  <u t="1448159">a bit of a break from these hostiles.</u>
  <u t="1450720">And um yeah, my trip had come to an end.</u>
  <u t="1456720">Oh my god, dude. This is honestly like</u>
  <u t="1460559">such a weird This is such a strange</u>
  <u t="1462400">feeling. I'm like I never thought I</u>
  <u t="1464559">would see home in this light where I</u>
  <u t="1466880">miss it so much. Even though like just</u>
  <u t="1468720">over 2 months ago I was like losing my</u>
  <u t="1470480">mind and I hated it there. But I just I</u>
  <u t="1472960">can't believe I haven't been home in</u>
  <u t="1476240">basically 58 59 days at this point.</u>
  <u t="1479440">Yeah, this is this has been this has</u>
  <u t="1481120">been a crazy like 2 months. I've never</u>
  <u t="1484480">ever done anything even remotely like</u>
  <u t="1486559">this in my entire life.</u>
  <u t="1491200">One of the things I discovered about</u>
  <u t="1493120">myself is that I'm just kind of like</u>
  <u t="1495520">chill. I don't know. I always like I I</u>
  <u t="1498640">always saw myself as someone who kind of</u>
  <u t="1500480">[ __ ] up under pressure. But every</u>
  <u t="1502720">single instance in this entire trip</u>
  <u t="1504559">where it was like, "Oh [ __ ] I [music]</u>
  <u t="1506000">missed this train." Or, "Oh [ __ ] this</u>
  <u t="1508080">got cancelled."</u>
  <u t="1510400">The anxiety was there for like a couple</u>
  <u t="1512240">seconds and it was gone.</u>
  <u t="1514640">I was just completely confident in my</u>
  <u t="1517039">ability that like no matter what</u>
  <u t="1518640">happens, I'll figure it out. There was</u>
  <u t="1521039">never a moment where I I [music] started</u>
  <u t="1522400">to like panic. And I mean that's a</u>
  <u t="1524720">lesson that I've learned or lesson that</u>
  <u t="1526799">I've kind of already been aware of. And</u>
  <u t="1528640">so I guess a lesson that like people</u>
  <u t="1530960">sometimes don't really realize. It's</u>
  <u t="1532559">like there's no reason to freak out in</u>
  <u t="1534720">any case scenario.</u>
  <u t="1536647">&gt;&gt; [music]</u>
  <u t="1537360">&gt;&gt; You absolutely 100% underestimate your</u>
  <u t="1540880">ability to just figure it out.</u>
  <u t="1547520">&gt;&gt; I'm going up there.</u>
  <u t="1549200">&gt;&gt; I didn't think that I would be 22, I</u>
  <u t="1551600">think, when I would do something like</u>
  <u t="1553200">this crazy. Um, I thought that I would</u>
  <u t="1555279">need more real life experience before</u>
  <u t="1557200">doing it. I I wouldn't say I have all</u>
  <u t="1559360">that much life experience here at 22</u>
  <u t="1561520">years old. And I went out to Europe with</u>
  <u t="1563520">zero of plan and I figured it the [ __ ]</u>
  <u t="1565440">out and it everything was fine.</u>
  <u t="1570640">It sounds cliche cuz I'm sure you've</u>
  <u t="1572640">heard a million Tik Toks saying the same</u>
  <u t="1574400">dumb [ __ ] but everyone says it cuz it's</u>
  <u t="1576480">true. You are so much more capable than</u>
  <u t="1579440">you think you are. Trust me. Trust me,</u>
  <u t="1582080">you can.</u>
  <u t="1585118">[music]</u>
  <u t="1589600">I just I never I never thought I [music]</u>
  <u t="1591760">couldn't have a YouTube channel, a</u>
  <u t="1593279">successful YouTube channel. I never</u>
  <u t="1594400">thought I couldn't travel to Europe by</u>
  <u t="1596159">myself. [music]</u>
  <u t="1599679">&gt;&gt; It was just a matter of whether I</u>
  <u t="1601440">actually pursued it or not.</u>
  <u t="1606078">[music]</u>
  </text>
