<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="41l5uU7EDUA" uploader="Project Happiness " channel="Project Happiness " likes="91777" title="VACANZE DI NATALE IN COREA DEL NORD 🇰🇵 (Episodio 3)" year="2020" month="2" day="2" date="20200202" date_ts="1580666400" is_ac="false">
  <u t="3080">Third day in North Korea</u>
  <u t="4520">I have almost nothing visited because of yesterday's accident</u>
  <u t="8960">But the guides/guardians</u>
  <u t="9840">promised to let me forget the bad day</u>
  <u t="12420">by giving me an unforgettable tour of the capital</u>
  <u t="16240">They requested in particular to be as elegant as possible</u>
  <u t="19180">in order to visit the Kumsusan Memorial Palace</u>
  <u t="22960">I have nothing but a wrinkled shirt in my backpack, I hope it will be fine</u>
  <u t="26920">Here they are!</u>
  <u t="32360">Good morning!</u>
  <u t="34420">What do you think?</u>
  <u t="36700">elegant enough?</u>
  <u t="38260">Yes!</u>
  <u t="39700">What...?</u>
  <u t="42020">don't worry</u>
  <u t="43600">I am sorry that I am filming everything</u>
  <u t="45820">but it's a memory for me</u>
  <u t="47820">everything is new</u>
  <u t="50740">so it's like if you go...you know what's Disneyland?</u>
  <u t="53880">No !?!</u>
  <u t="55200">Dis...what?</u>
  <u t="56400">Dis...</u>
  <u t="57440">And this is me giving stupid examples</u>
  <u t="59620">forgetting that they have never left the country</u>
  <u t="62040">and they have no idea what is outside the borders of their country</u>
  <u t="65280">Wow! look!</u>
  <u t="70360">nice!</u>
  <u t="72700">They just come to the street and do some kind of activities</u>
  <u t="77100">to activate the people to do more work</u>
  <u t="82740">yes</u>
  <u t="83340">Nice!</u>
  <u t="85340">To give energy to the people</u>
  <u t="86760">Yes, yes..</u>
  <u t="88340">To encourage people to do more work</u>
  <u t="92060">also they wish them good success in their work</u>
  <u t="95240">in our country soldiers do all kind of work</u>
  <u t="99420">they also defend the country, but not only defend the country</u>
  <u t="103400">they also do some construction and..</u>
  <u t="106180">they play a very big role in the social construction</u>
  <u t="112140">so, for example</u>
  <u t="112900">they build many high buildings</u>
  <u t="118620">like you just saw some high building in the Mirae Scientists Street</u>
  <u t="124040">Yes...</u>
  <u t="125260">Like this, for example...</u>
  <u t="126660">They just built that kind of high building</u>
  <u t="129840">in 20 days or 30 days</u>
  <u t="132940">Ok stop!</u>
  <u t="133880">For the record, she is referring to these buildings</u>
  <u t="136840">All these couloured buildings have been built in less than 30 days</u>
  <u t="141660">but let's go on</u>
  <u t="142720">What do you know about Korea exactly?</u>
  <u t="147460">Mmmm...</u>
  <u t="148320">Little Peppe, don't forget that you have to go home</u>
  <u t="152460">It's...</u>
  <u t="153540">it's a very complicated question</u>
  <u t="155500">I know that you are very closed</u>
  <u t="158120">of course</u>
  <u t="158920">Yes...</u>
  <u t="159420">And you are developing</u>
  <u t="162480">Yes..</u>
  <u t="163040">you are developing</u>
  <u t="163680">but I don't know much because</u>
  <u t="165680">we do not receive so many news about you</u>
  <u t="170420">as I think you do not receive so many news about us</u>
  <u t="173840">Right?</u>
  <u t="174580">Yes</u>
  <u t="175100">So...</u>
  <u t="175980">I am ready to discover everything about your country</u>
  <u t="179100">I did not know that you can build buildings in one month</u>
  <u t="184120">Stupid question:</u>
  <u t="185840">is it possible to meet the Leader?</u>
  <u t="189780">Hahah...Impossible!</u>
  <u t="190800">Impossible!</u>
  <u t="191720">Yeah...</u>
  <u t="192460">For North Koreans it's the most glorious thing to meet our Leader</u>
  <u t="199040">The best day of your life!</u>
  <u t="200660">Of course!</u>
  <u t="201160">I noticed that there are always the pictures of his grand-father</u>
  <u t="205300">and his father</u>
  <u t="206200">but there are no pictures of him</u>
  <u t="208200">around</u>
  <u t="209220">Even though this supreme leader...current leader Kim-Jong Un, he's the Leader</u>
  <u t="218540">he does't allow us to have his portrait already, or badge..</u>
  <u t="224760">Why?</u>
  <u t="226260">Because President Kim-Il Sung and Chairman Kim-Jong Il</u>
  <u t="232780">are the eternal President and the eternal Chairman</u>
  <u t="234880">Ok, let me explain you more in detail</u>
  <u t="236860">you should know that North Korea is the only "necrocrazy" in the world</u>
  <u t="240660">what does this mean?</u>
  <u t="242100">it means that in this country the current President is a dead person</u>
  <u t="245460">namely the founder of the nation Kim Il-Sung</u>
  <u t="248520">at his death, the reins of the country passed to his son, Kim Jong-il</u>
  <u t="252100">who became the country Chairman</u>
  <u t="254340">and he still is, although he passed away in 2011</u>
  <u t="256660">so making the whole country cry</u>
  <u t="260260">his son Kim Jong-Un, that we all know today</u>
  <u t="263040">is the ultimate leader of the country and the only chef of the party</u>
  <u t="269120">Here the Kim dynasty</u>
  <u t="275080">What's this one, Choe?</u>
  <u t="276600">That one?</u>
  <u t="277480">Yeah</u>
  <u t="278100">International Exhibition Hall</u>
  <u t="280880">Ah...here is where there all the gifts?</u>
  <u t="283060">Yes!</u>
  <u t="283680">presented to the great leaders of our country</u>
  <u t="290840">Wow</u>
  <u t="294020">How many gifts inside?</u>
  <u t="304200">If you go inside you can see with your own eyes</u>
  <u t="306760">Ok!</u>
  <u t="310020">There are over 140 rooms inside</u>
  <u t="313360">wow...140 rooms..</u>
  <u t="315060">Yes!</u>
  <u t="315620">So from now on I cannot film anymore</u>
  <u t="318100">yes</u>
  <u t="318980">To bring you with me inside the palace</u>
  <u t="320500">I found this very old video which will help me to describe</u>
  <u t="323700">what I've seen with my eyes</u>
  <u t="325940">The huge entrance door leads to a bright marble corridor</u>
  <u t="328920">which leads to the mean room</u>
  <u t="330780">where there are the gifts of the most important authorities in the world</u>
  <u t="335120">in front of every gift there is a plate with the delivery date</u>
  <u t="338060">and the name of the person bringing the present</u>
  <u t="342280">the guide immediately emphasises the great number of gifts</u>
  <u t="345840">received by all the political leaders of the world</u>
  <u t="349980">As to highlight the world's admiration and support for North Korea</u>
  <u t="359180">Actually, I learned that the Protocol of North Korea</u>
  <u t="362400">imposes and determines a gift exchange for every institutional visit</u>
  <u t="368300">So if you are visiting North Korea you are obliged to bring a gift to the leader</u>
  <u t="373160">Just to let you understand the grandness of the palace</u>
  <u t="375600">in a room there are the bulletproof train cars</u>
  <u t="378880">that Stalin and Mao Zedong offered to Kim Il-sung at his take-over</u>
  <u t="389660">the Italians chose a big classic: Murano glass and that's it</u>
  <u t="393840">The gifts that impressed me the most are those of Dennis Rodman</u>
  <u t="397380">un former NBA champion who surprisingly became Kim Jong-un's best friend</u>
  <u t="402840">such a close friend to perform for him at his birthday</u>
  <u t="414440">Among the thousands of gifts, the guide insisted on this one in particular</u>
  <u t="419360">and seeing my skeptical face, she asked for my opinion</u>
  <u t="422100">don't ask me why but, in a moment of pure honesty, I said that</u>
  <u t="425520">I don't like stuffed animal and I would not put it in my closet either</u>
  <u t="431080">let's say that...they didn't take it really well</u>
  <u t="433720">There is a crocodile who brings a plate with glasses</u>
  <u t="438160">it's a real crocodile</u>
  <u t="440500">and everyone likes it but..not me</u>
  <u t="443460">no, not that much</u>
  <u t="445580">Next stop?</u>
  <u t="446640">Next stop is Pohyon temple</u>
  <u t="449860">Close to the International Friendship Exhibition there is also a Buddhist temple</u>
  <u t="452840">dating back to 1000 years ago</u>
  <u t="455480">actually, with the dictatorship it became more a touristic attraction than a place of worship</u>
  <u t="461000">every religion is a threat to the regime</u>
  <u t="463960">which represses with violence every kind of devotion</u>
  <u t="467460">except one</u>
  <u t="469220">So usually Korean people don't believe in anything?</u>
  <u t="473740">We believe in JUCHE</u>
  <u t="475900">I know, my friends, I never heard about this before either</u>
  <u t="478340">but in North Korea everything turns around the idea of JUCHE</u>
  <u t="481720">a kind of anthropocentric philosophy created by the founder of the nation Kim Il-sung</u>
  <u t="486940">JUCHE is a true religion for North Korean people</u>
  <u t="490540">to summarise in a sentence which is applicable to any domain of their life, it means:</u>
  <u t="495940">"every man is the creator of his own destiny"</u>
  <u t="499800">I am leaving some links in the description because it is a very interesting subject</u>
  <u t="507280">THE MOST LUXURIOUS HOTEL IN NORTH KOREA</u>
  <u t="520200">Thank you!</u>
  <u t="523800">Ok, this is super weird, the restaurant is empty</u>
  <u t="527440">completely empty, no one is there</u>
  <u t="531280">and I am eating alone here, because my guides and driver</u>
  <u t="534040">went to eat in another room</u>
  <u t="537480">This is the starter</u>
  <u t="540900">with all the guests</u>
  <u t="543920">keeping me company</u>
  <u t="546840">unbelievable!</u>
  <u t="547860">I asked why and they told me that starting from tonight we are going to eat together</u>
  <u t="551000">so...I didn't understand why!</u>
  <u t="553980">this is a pork soup</u>
  <u t="555460">some eggs and seaweed</u>
  <u t="556900">here I am eating some vegetables seasoned with something...</u>
  <u t="561900">fried fish</u>
  <u t="563900">and boiled vegetables with bread</u>
  <u t="567980">Oh my God, I have such a performance anxiety!</u>
  <u t="570060">There is a waitress, let's call her that</u>
  <u t="572840">who keeps controlling every movement I do</u>
  <u t="577700">if she doesn't look at me directly, she does it through the mirror</u>
  <u t="581840">I am eating with such an anxiety that...</u>
  <u t="584420">Watch out what's going to happen now</u>
  <u t="587260">Potatoes</u>
  <u t="588940">Wow..that's it?</u>
  <u t="591660">I'm full</u>
  <u t="594440">after this...</u>
  <u t="596440">Yes</u>
  <u t="596940">...finished?</u>
  <u t="597440">Yes, yes</u>
  <u t="599440">Ok, perfect</u>
  <u t="600560">thank you!</u>
  <u t="601660">What's your name?</u>
  <u t="603080">Giuseppe</u>
  <u t="604220">Giuseppe?!</u>
  <u t="604720">Yes!</u>
  <u t="605880">[says her name]</u>
  <u t="607280">Yes</u>
  <u t="607980">Nice to meet you</u>
  <u t="609640">Yeah, nice to meet you</u>
  <u t="612800">I am learning English</u>
  <u t="616080">Can you teach me English?</u>
  <u t="618500">Can you...?</u>
  <u t="620100">teach me...</u>
  <u t="622100">Yes...</u>
  <u t="622780">...English?</u>
  <u t="623520">English?</u>
  <u t="624620">Yes!</u>
  <u t="625260">What do you want to learn?</u>
  <u t="627260">Everything!</u>
  <u t="627860">for example...</u>
  <u t="631860">what is this?</u>
  <u t="634100">Flower!</u>
  <u t="635460">Flower...</u>
  <u t="637920">What is this?</u>
  <u t="639120">Plate!</u>
  <u t="639900">Plate...</u>
  <u t="640940">Plate</u>
  <u t="641720">Plate...</u>
  <u t="643480">Yes...</u>
  <u t="644380">What is this?</u>
  <u t="645280">GoPro</u>
  <u t="646660">camera!</u>
  <u t="647680">Camera...</u>
  <u t="648720">Oh yes...</u>
  <u t="650560">Thank you!</u>
  <u t="651820">You're welcome!</u>
  <u t="661740">This was quite unbelievable</u>
  <u t="665160">she asked me to teach her some English</u>
  <u t="668020">and she asked me to pronounce the names of everything that was on the table</u>
  <u t="673900">to get to...my GoPro!</u>
  <u t="677100">and when I said that it was a camera she left</u>
  <u t="681640">Wow</u>
  <u t="683860">I mean...she wanted to know what it was but she didn't dare asking directly</u>
  <u t="688080">she made me say the names of all the things that were on the table</u>
  <u t="695720">I am going to clean the plate with some bread even in North Korea</u>
  <u t="702260">The most chemical thing I've ever eaten in my life</u>
  <u t="707640">Of course, today the driver was different after yesterday's accident</u>
  <u t="710540">we were running at 2 km/h</u>
  <u t="712740">we're are about to go into the Kumsusan -Palace of the Sun</u>
  <u t="714880">which is the mausoleum where they keep the bodies of past leaders</u>
  <u t="720820">Kim Jong-Un's father and grand-father</u>
  <u t="724380">it's a very particular moment because even my guides became more serious</u>
  <u t="730860">I can't wait to see what's inside</u>
  <u t="733320">How many times did you come here already?</u>
  <u t="736140">already tens of times</u>
  <u t="738140">Yeah?</u>
  <u t="738860">Always a great emotion?</u>
  <u t="741600">For the Korean people meeting their great leaders is the most glorious thing</u>
  <u t="748100">and today I am meeting my great leaders</u>
  <u t="751060">so I made up my mind to work harder and harder in the future</u>
  <u t="759240">What are they doing?</u>
  <u t="760560">Taking a picture</u>
  <u t="763080">Like a group picture?</u>
  <u t="764280">Yeah</u>
  <u t="773460">Here too it was forbidden to take pictures or videos</u>
  <u t="775700">so I am going to explain what I saw through some archive images</u>
  <u t="779200">To get inside the mausoleum we had to be led</u>
  <u t="782020">by an escalator for 15 minutes</u>
  <u t="784820">All the necessary time for guides</u>
  <u t="786500">to explain to me how to behave inside the mausoleum</u>
  <u t="790160">The rules were very easy:</u>
  <u t="791860">never put your hands in your pockets</u>
  <u t="793840">never cross your arms</u>
  <u t="795580">bend down 45 degrees in front of the statues of the leaders</u>
  <u t="800760">and most importantly in front of their bodies</u>
  <u t="804300">impressive guys, they were perfectly preserved</u>
  <u t="807740">like if they were sleeping</u>
  <u t="811160">in addition to the bodies, inside the mausoleum there were as well</u>
  <u t="813800">all the most valuable belongings of the two leaders</u>
  <u t="817300">some of the very small objects were:</u>
  <u t="819860">a collection of cars</u>
  <u t="822600">two trains</u>
  <u t="824120">and a yacht!</u>
  <u t="826020">when I asked my guides/gardians how they managed</u>
  <u t="828820">to bring a yacht inside the mausoleum</u>
  <u t="830920">the answer was very easy::</u>
  <u t="832420">"Korean people can do everything"</u>
  <u t="835280">Wow, we've just visited the palace in which the bodies are preserved</u>
  <u t="839780">the Kumsusan Palace of the Sun is the most majestic palace I've ever seen in my life</u>
  <u t="845240">I'm like...I'm really really impressed</u>
  <u t="847580">Inside the palace there was a yacht</u>
  <u t="850320">There was a....</u>
  <u t="852320">who was the owner of the yacht?</u>
  <u t="853660">Kim-Jong...Il?</u>
  <u t="855660">Yeah!</u>
  <u t="856520">Yeah...wow!</u>
  <u t="857660">I saw so many people crying when they saw the body of the leaders</u>
  <u t="863520">what was your feeling?</u>
  <u t="865520">We, the Koreans, we just respect our leaders</u>
  <u t="868680">so we also follow them as fathers</u>
  <u t="873060">not only the President or the leader of the country</u>
  <u t="878120">real fathers, we just follow them as real fathers</u>
  <u t="881960">so...</u>
  <u t="883360">how do you feel when your father died?</u>
  <u t="886000">You told me something that is very interesting</u>
  <u t="889220">Not everybody can go there</u>
  <u t="891220">Like, you go there only if you work hard, if you really deserve it</u>
  <u t="894940">so, for instance, you can go there with me because you worked hard in the past, and you can come with me</u>
  <u t="901740">that's correct</u>
  <u t="903120">Yes</u>
  <u t="903620">for example...</u>
  <u t="906520">if I am a farmer...</u>
  <u t="908340">if I did lot of work for the country</u>
  <u t="912960">especially in autumn...</u>
  <u t="916100">if I harvest lots of grains</u>
  <u t="921660">in comparaison with the others</u>
  <u t="923960">then we have the special honour to visit the Kumsusan Palais of the Sun</u>
  <u t="932320">So...</u>
  <u t="933840">those who are very good at their job</u>
  <u t="935840">and make a good contribution to the country</u>
  <u t="938480">they have a chance to visit the palace</u>
  <u t="941960">Kim, what do you think about death?</u>
  <u t="946020">what do you think there is after death?</u>
  <u t="948720">I don't think that our President and our General passed away</u>
  <u t="953420">we always bring their smile in our minds</u>
  <u t="959220">whenever we feel very tired we always think of them</u>
  <u t="963560">and we try very hard to...</u>
  <u t="968840">realise their ideas</u>
  <u t="980760">And here we are</u>
  <u t="981700">this is the moment when my relation with the guides/gardians starts to crack inexorably</u>
  <u t="987640">maybe they cared too much about that stuffed crocodile</u>
  <u t="990100">or maybe I went too far with all my questions</u>
  <u t="994040">anyway, everything changed starting from here</u>
  <u t="999100">In the next episode</u>
  <u t="1017760">Choe, is this a restaurant?</u>
  <u t="1019680">Yeah!</u>
  <u t="1020340">Why there are....?</u>
  <u t="1025580">Now or never, let's see if I can make it because yesterday</u>
  <u t="1028780">they were they were a little bit annoyed with all my filming</u>
  <u t="1031620">so...</u>
  <u t="1034520">ok...</u>
  <u t="1035840">what is happiness for you?</u>
  </text>
