<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="VI-h2tKG_iQ" uploader="Kurt Caz" channel="Kurt Caz" likes="28865" title="Venezuela's Most Isolated Place 🇻🇪" year="2024" month="7" day="1" date="20240701" date_ts="1719812334" is_ac="true">
  <u t="1079">Good morning right now we're at the base</u>
  <u t="3280">at the bottom of Lake marakaibo the</u>
  <u t="4920">biggest Lake in the whole country in</u>
  <u t="6759">Puerto kancha That's the name of this</u>
  <u t="8360">Little Town they got Blue crab factories</u>
  <u t="10759">over there there's two there's One over</u>
  <u t="12639">there so It's a little fishing Town</u>
  <u t="14599">and right now aland And I who's hiding</u>
  <u t="16520">In The Car Because it's so damn Hot</u>
  <u t="18240">we're about to embark On A tour a</u>
  <u t="20760">private tour up the Lake to go and spend</u>
  <u t="23720">two Nights three days no internet no</u>
  <u t="26640">WiFi Nothing we're going to go and sleep</u>
  <u t="28279">on hams and go see how the</u>
  <u t="34000">Let's go</u>
  <u t="36360">preped the sandflies already messed me</u>
  <u t="39079">up before but they're Not Going To get</u>
  <u t="40480">Me Again I came prepared with What is it</u>
  <u t="43719">where's the spray I got It</u>
  <u t="49640">somewhere</u>
  <u t="53320">Vamoso is be Captain for today his Roger</u>
  <u t="60400">[Laughs]</u>
  <u t="69040">Alejandrita here you're very hot no longer I'm</u>
  <u t="72640">sweating a little bit</u>
  <u t="75400">I'm sweating yoo</u>
  <u t="86140">[Music]</u>
  <u t="90280">you first</u>
  <u t="94439">Well</u>
  <u t="103070">[Music]</u>
  <u t="107719">here put that on you don't know how to</u>
  <u t="113200">swim It's not that it's the more professional</u>
  <u t="116200">but</u>
  <u t="120640">for exit and daal good Ah</u>
  <u t="124060">[Music]</u>
  <u t="126360">Well, quick</u>
  <u t="129119">selfies. Why so</u>
  <u t="132400">quiet? I feel bad, I feel bad.</u>
  <u t="137560">Okay. See you later. Let's go, you guys. Ready? Three-day journey, two nights, the palit sleep. H and stuff.</u>
  <u t="144280">Let's go, Che.</u>
  <u t="149239">This is. Do</u>
  <u t="154840">n't be shy if you want to explain</u>
  <u t="157599">something. Perfect, bring it out from</u>
  <u t="165920">within. So where are we now?</u>
  <u t="168760">We're on the Concha River.</u>
  <u t="171200">Concha is a canal that was created to allow</u>
  <u t="173599">ships to enter, to give</u>
  <u t="177080">Mérida access to ships. Okay, and it</u>
  <u t="180720">was the main canal where</u>
  <u t="182760">coffee produced in Mérida was exported</u>
  <u t="186159">and taken to Germany. It was taken by</u>
  <u t="188560">the Huancayo Company. They trafficked</u>
  <u t="192920">cocoa, coffee, and some other products.</u>
  <u t="196480">That was a long time ago, back in</u>
  <u t="198560">colonial times. Now it's</u>
  <u t="201040">only dedicated to fishing.</u>
  <u t="203959">The deltas that fill Lake</u>
  <u t="206159">Maracaibo filled</u>
  <u t="208640">most of the canals with sediment. This is</u>
  <u t="213680">a national park,</u>
  <u t="215560">Juan</u>
  <u t="217480">Manuel</u>
  <u t="223640">26 National Park.</u>
  <u t="226159">Wow, a family of howler monkeys in</u>
  <u t="229080">front. Monkeys, guys,</u>
  <u t="240040">you see</u>
  <u t="241159">it? Look how he jumped. Ah, look at him, he's got a</u>
  <u t="245760">big sack on his chin. This is a Box of</u>
  <u t="250720">bone a Box of bone yeah it works as a</u>
  <u t="253840">resonance Box for the</u>
  <u t="259639">voice Look at</u>
  <u t="263440">that How nice you speak</u>
  <u t="267720">clearly how they do</u>
  <u t="271120">Wow</u>
  <u t="276800">uel Juan Manuel Juan Manuel Was the</u>
  <u t="279520">Owner of exens Land in</u>
  <u t="284759">nobody</u>
  <u t="286400">and was of mysterious Us the and longest</u>
  <u t="307639">and</u>
  <u t="314039">naal</u>
  <u t="320039">andoni son fisherman dej</u>
  <u t="329919">s and</u>
  <u t="330919">Everything</u>
  <u t="332479">yeah I mean The Only way to get in here</u>
  <u t="335360">is with a private tour there's no way</u>
  <u t="338360">you guys know me I don't really Go with</u>
  <u t="340160">tours and the only way to get in here is</u>
  <u t="342080">with One so I decided Hey it's Worth it</u>
  <u t="345680">Let take a tour um with a guide and</u>
  <u t="348440">Everything Because I mean How the hell</u>
  <u t="351720">Are you going to come and Explore this</u>
  <u t="354240">Place by yourself I mean check it out</u>
  <u t="361919">incredible katum ling phenomeno with</u>
  <u t="366319">the you</u>
  <u t="368120">know work with an</u>
  <u t="370759">electrical impulse yeah This is called</u>
  <u t="374720">nodul sinal inish I don't remember the</u>
  <u t="378560">name in English but This is an organ</u>
  <u t="381080">that produces an Electricity and this</u>
  <u t="383599">Electricity Keep the Heart beating Wow</u>
  <u t="386440">That's a phenomenon that only happens</u>
  <u t="388080">here and only happens here If We compare</u>
  <u t="390919">the entire air with the human Body we</u>
  <u t="395880">can Say that We are in the Heart of the</u>
  <u t="398000">world Wow Because this</u>
  <u t="401520">is Electricity interesting and Helping</u>
  <u t="406440">to protect the the whole world</u>
  <u t="410639">Because recovering the ozono layer Every</u>
  <u t="414960">Time the catatumbo lining is strong the</u>
  <u t="418280">layer get</u>
  <u t="421479">Wow Oh</u>
  <u t="423639">yeah thick lilies</u>
  <u t="426599">here so hopefully Tonight When we sleep</u>
  <u t="429080">in the hammars we're going to see the</u>
  <u t="431160">Lightning phenomenon in the sky Go off</u>
  <u t="434360">It's a Lightning show that only happens</u>
  <u t="436280">here in this part of the world and</u>
  <u t="439199">happens constantly Pretty much so</u>
  <u t="442080">we'll see it</u>
  <u t="448290">[Music]</u>
  <u t="451120">That's a New name I got a nickname for</u>
  <u t="453000">aleandra</u>
  <u t="456360">malandra so these palitos that you see</u>
  <u t="458879">in front of you used to be the park</u>
  <u t="461160">guards the National guards the National</u>
  <u t="463560">guards right National guards National</u>
  <u t="466280">Park National Park guard so they Used To</u>
  <u t="468800">That's Where they were based but now the</u>
  <u t="471159">fishermen have taken over</u>
  <u t="475560">and yeah</u>
  <u t="483000">W guys take a Look at this here you can</u>
  <u t="486000">see the two col the Lake changes Why is</u>
  <u t="491360">that Because the catatumbo river is</u>
  <u t="495159">coming into the Lake in this Place the</u>
  <u t="497720">beginning of the Rain and the catatumbo</u>
  <u t="500440">is coming from a very Dry Area bring All</u>
  <u t="502960">the thirst and This is</u>
  <u t="505479">theat and here is Together</u>
  <u t="509800">Look at</u>
  <u t="510919">this So You can see literally the B</u>
  <u t="515839">here Look at the change of color</u>
  <u t="518839">incredible so over there It's like a</u>
  <u t="520479">Dark Green and over here your muddy</u>
  <u t="524080">Brown insane so we right on the</u>
  <u t="527480">Border so we Made It To One of the</u>
  <u t="530120">communities here that he was Talking</u>
  <u t="533560">About earlier on they moved so they</u>
  <u t="535880">moved All of the materials and boats</u>
  <u t="538640">they transported</u>
  <u t="547440">ol</u>
  <u t="550959">ol</u>
  <u t="554920">topitos This is Our refuge</u>
  <u t="569600">right guys so we Made It To Our First</u>
  <u t="571760">stop over here in the Community of</u>
  <u t="574880">ologa we're going to have lunch over</u>
  <u t="577399">here check it out Let's go take a quick</u>
  <u t="581040">look Our Guy Junior and the Captain is</u>
  <u t="585360">offloading the Goodies so we stocked up</u>
  <u t="588839">on supplies for these next two Nights we</u>
  <u t="591920">got fruit veg</u>
  <u t="594920">food almar</u>
  <u t="599480">Kit The</u>
  <u t="601120">kitchen Very nice they got Everything got</u>
  <u t="604240">Everything yeah have</u>
  <u t="607120">Electricity solar with a solar sometimes</u>
  <u t="610440">it works sometimes it works If not We</u>
  <u t="612640">are We have a generator that is going to</u>
  <u t="614959">be all right some in the Oh nice</u>
  <u t="618880">depending on How You Feel Oh very good</u>
  <u t="621160">at least we got some</u>
  <u t="623880">Electricity Ah check it out they Got the</u>
  <u t="626160">solar panels</u>
  <u t="627880">here so</u>
  <u t="641880">through sol</u>
  <u t="655560">as to see yes curs</u>
  <u t="659639">and</u>
  <u t="660720">s</u>
  <u t="663560">tasty yú there Clearly, when I was</u>
  <u t="667279">little, I</u>
  <u t="668680">loved, I saw, and</u>
  <u t="674800">barely everybody here sleeps, sleep.</u>
  <u t="678920">H don't have a bed, bed. And</u>
  <u t="689519">here, how do they get water? And that has to be</u>
  <u t="691920">brought from somewhere else. People bring water from</u>
  <u t="694480">there, and from the rain, from the rain, from the... fill it up.</u>
  <u t="697600">And how does that fill up? It fills the</u>
  <u t="700639">pipe there. Ah, okay, good, get fresh rainwater.</u>
  <u t="704120">That's what people drink. No,</u>
  <u t="706200">you drink rainwater. There are some who boil it,</u>
  <u t="708320">and there are some who drink it like that.</u>
  <u t="711560">Very, very</u>
  <u t="715240">nice. Love. Oh, what is that? It has</u>
  <u t="721360">many... what do I need?</u>
  <u t="723480">What do I</u>
  <u t="727200">need? The</u>
  <u t="731000">weeder. Today, talking about the weeder by</u>
  <u t="735600">Manscaped, today's sponsor. So if you guys don't want to look</u>
  <u t="739680">like some type of</u>
  <u t="741199">Wall Street, you want to keep those noses and</u>
  <u t="744639">use the</u>
  <u t="746560">weeder, I would trust this product. Up</u>
  <u t="749800">my nose like I do with</u>
  <u t="753279">Manscaped because Manscaped is the</u>
  <u t="755959">world's best men's grooming</u>
  <u t="758160">company. I've had this exact product for</u>
  <u t="760920">over a year. Now the battery is amazing. I do</u>
  <u t="763800">n't think I've ever charged it. Never</u>
  <u t="765639">replace the blades; they are extremely</u>
  <u t="767480">sharp and... Safe, not like those other</u>
  <u t="771560">companies. Not only is the Weed Whacker a</u>
  <u t="774360">very good product, but Manscaped has a</u>
  <u t="776399">whole bunch of cool stuff on their</u>
  <u t="777600">website, from boxes to ball colones to</u>
  <u t="781079">different types of beard shavers. You can</u>
  <u t="782839">just click the link in the description, it will</u>
  <u t="784480">lead you to mcap.com, and you</u>
  <u t="787320">can use my code Kurt cas, and with that</u>
  <u t="790040">you can get 20% off any Manscaped purchase. So thank you, manate, for sponsoring this video. Speaking of which, let's get some lunch. Right, we're over here.</u>
  <u t="807000">Try it, yeah, yeah, okay. Well, let's try it, but I'm</u>
  <u t="810680">going to bring you mine too</u>
  <u t="812560">so you can try it. Do you have another one, a stronger one?</u>
  <u t="816920">Ah, well, let's try that one</u>
  <u t="820279">then.</u>
  <u t="824399">Petare,</u>
  <u t="831120">the little poison, no</u>
  <u t="832880">poison,</u>
  <u t="835759">that's like oil, I don't</u>
  <u t="853720">peel them. But they don't make that in Colombia, right? Of course,</u>
  <u t="859040">on the</u>
  <u t="861440">coast, of course. The Llanos, the</u>
  <u t="865120">Llanos, it's</u>
  <u t="866639">a little milder than that one, that's the</u>
  <u t="871440">strongest, this one is more concentrated. Like</u>
  <u t="874279">chacaro, chacaro, and that Andean one, I think</u>
  <u t="879160">the chacaros are from...</u>
  <u t="881480">What's the difference, like the potency,</u>
  <u t="884160">or how this one is stronger? A little bit, no,</u>
  <u t="887440">but in Bo Once like a piece</u>
  <u t="889600">of</u>
  <u t="890959">gum, look here I have another one, that's it, I</u>
  <u t="893920">have it for testing, people, like this, don't swallow it,</u>
  <u t="896560">because, yes, of course, I</u>
  <u t="899399">also do it like this, you take it like this, down with your</u>
  <u t="906279">tongue, no? Or I put it</u>
  <u t="910160">up,</u>
  <u t="911600">down with your tongue, then it gives more</u>
  <u t="921160">saliva because if you swallow, well, if you</u>
  <u t="923839">swallow a little bit but gently, you scratch your</u>
  <u t="926800">[ __ ],</u>
  <u t="930680">and the paella of chingo, the p is drunk,</u>
  <u t="934759">when you get drunk on chingo you have to</u>
  <u t="936480">go to the</u>
  <u t="939399">bathroom, you sweat, you feel like</u>
  <u t="950120">pooping, chunca</u>
  <u t="955639">chico, fried boico,</u>
  <u t="966079">that's what they catch</u>
  <u t="968440">here, that</u>
  <u t="970920">fero, the</u>
  <u t="975480">pesero is called</u>
  <u t="991120">catfish.</u>
  <u t="1001030">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1002319">Plantain, Christmas, Christmas.</u>
  <u t="1006600">What do we have over</u>
  <u t="1016240">here? While</u>
  <u t="1021279">Mr. Polar Bear, I've missed</u>
  <u t="1040439">you, lunch has been served, check it out,</u>
  <u t="1042919">we got the fried bachiko, bachiko rice salad, fresh fruit</u>
  <u t="1049360">juice with</u>
  <u t="1051520">ice and fried</u>
  <u t="1055960">plantain. Very nice, you guys, know me, I'm not</u>
  <u t="1058679">the biggest fan of fish, but we're</u>
  <u t="1060120">going to give it a go. I mean, there's</u>
  <u t="1062480">nothing else,</u>
  <u t="1064200">so this is</u>
  <u t="1068679">it, poc</u>
  <u t="1072160">chico, because it has the little mouth</u>
  <u t="1077039">no you can see</u>
  <u t="1086880">little mouth No what do they eat like</u>
  <u t="1091960">little fish insect something that's in the</u>
  <u t="1096960">water but the branches on the branch Ah like</u>
  <u t="1100600">algae they fall too are vegetables</u>
  <u t="1106840">vegetarians let's eat</u>
  <u t="1110679">vegetarians little mouth has a little mouth</u>
  <u t="1114320">let's eat</u>
  <u t="1117679">Nero t isn't hungry yes I'm hungry yes yes</u>
  <u t="1122440">acc acc</u>
  <u t="1125559">let's eat little mouth and I eat everything</u>
  <u t="1129799">even the</u>
  <u t="1135799">old lady wow</u>
  <u t="1138880">Look at the</u>
  <u t="1140000">little mouth No I don't want that one I want the</u>
  <u t="1142400">little mouth it looks more it looks</u>
  <u t="1146080">more little mouth please Thank you little mouth Give</u>
  <u t="1153799">me how give me the eyes How so</u>
  <u t="1158320">from the fish How did you give me the</u>
  <u t="1161480">eyes What eyes to eat to</u>
  <u t="1165559">see the eye came out no to see</u>
  <u t="1168080">better it showed the no no no no no no</u>
  <u t="1170520">for protein for protein I always</u>
  <u t="1173880">loved what eyes to eat the</u>
  <u t="1176400">eyes and the brain is what has the most</u>
  <u t="1178600">protein of a foot no no no You're going to eat</u>
  <u t="1181440">the eye of</u>
  <u t="1183720">course I thought I was the</u>
  <u t="1187080">wild gringo No I swear to you I have</u>
  <u t="1190600">a wild Caracas woman I used to fight with My</u>
  <u t="1193360">dad so he'd let me have the eyes, me, Daddy, watch out for</u>
  <u t="1195600">that, eh, watch out for that, watch out for that, I</u>
  <u t="1198760">swear it's divine, I love it,</u>
  <u t="1201400">pass me a fork, a tenor please, kid.</u>
  <u t="1204840">No, you don't like it, no, but friend, but</u>
  <u t="1208320">you're not going to eat it, but you, but</u>
  <u t="1211039">you already will. Let's go, like</u>
  <u t="1212919">little mouths. But you, Teo, with that, with coming, don't mess</u>
  <u t="1218320">with me. I'm from here, no, you</u>
  <u t="1220600">'re not from here, I'm from here. You can</u>
  <u t="1222240">talk as fast as they talk here,</u>
  <u t="1223760">I'm going to talk super fast, however you want, no little</u>
  <u t="1226799">mouth, little mouth, nothing, little</u>
  <u t="1230280">fried, San</u>
  <u t="1236000">chicoo. Now if you want me,</u>
  <u t="1239760">abuser. Now if Maria, the</u>
  <u t="1244760">kitten, the</u>
  <u t="1247760">annoying kitten, kitten waiting for the sin,</u>
  <u t="1256400">you want it delicious,</u>
  <u t="1259320">oh, with the eye too, of course, it's divine, the</u>
  <u t="1263799">eye and the tail and the</u>
  <u t="1266000">shell. I always, I don't want you anymore, it's</u>
  <u t="1272480">not going to eat, no,</u>
  <u t="1276039">enjoy, you grab a little tail here and</u>
  <u t="1279440">the spine is here, here</u>
  <u t="1281720">with your hands. Of course, my love, very</u>
  <u t="1285760">bloody, very delicious, very delicious. It's good, it's good, it's</u>
  <u t="1325880">a</u>
  <u t="1331360">simple</u>
  <u t="1332880">and delicious.</u>
  <u t="1348880">I don't like fish.</u>
  <u t="1352279">Allish's buttery</u>
  <u t="1363880">tender, are you going to</u>
  <u t="1371240">give me a taste? No, no, no, no. Thank you. Another</u>
  <u t="1375679">day for another day.</u>
  <u t="1381240">Well, enjoy your meal. That's what</u>
  <u t="1383960">most people think. Boca chico fish.</u>
  <u t="1409630">[Applause]</u>
  <u t="1420960">Those who understand,</u>
  <u t="1422679">understand. Was that an</u>
  <u t="1425799">alien language or is that English? Those who</u>
  <u t="1428279">know, know, and those who don't are silent. No</u>
  <u t="1431559">one knows anything, and those who know are</u>
  <u t="1434679">silent. But I'm telling you,</u>
  <u t="1440159">so check it out, guys. This is how the</u>
  <u t="1442039">fishermen over here fish. All of this</u>
  <u t="1444360">is net. This is one massive net, and you</u>
  <u t="1447320">can see them pulling in the fish, they're</u>
  <u t="1449240">even jumping by themselves. Look at that! Look at that, they've got</u>
  <u t="1454840">two different types of fish</u>
  <u t="1458320">in there. Man, hard working guys, huh? They</u>
  <u t="1461360">do this in the sun all</u>
  <u t="1464159">day. And how much does a kilo of fish cost?</u>
  <u t="1477039">One kilo is a good day's</u>
  <u t="1480840">work. And some mermaids</u>
  <u t="1484200">over there, some mermaids too.</u>
  <u t="1488730">[Laughter]</u>
  <u t="1496279">Mermaids. But come loaded with</u>
  <u t="1503080">boca chico. What happened,</u>
  <u t="1505799">friend? Good, what's up? Wow, but</u>
  <u t="1510120">quite a lot. Not that they catch</u>
  <u t="1514840">2,000, but that's sold around town. They sell that.</u>
  <u t="1518640">The canes were with</u>
  <u t="1521240">the coolers. They were taped. They have</u>
  <u t="1523080">ice and they sell it. They throw ice.</u>
  <u t="1526559">Three days. What they eat, they go where to?</u>
  <u t="1528840">To the Puos, Santa Bárbara, Puerto</u>
  <u t="1531000">Concha.</u>
  <u t="1541039">No, no,</u>
  <u t="1551279">tomorrow, everybody. Now, now, it's</u>
  <u t="1567080">true.</u>
  <u t="1581880">People here,</u>
  <u t="1589679">even the Venezuelans don't understand</u>
  <u t="1593320">them. These are the crab fishman, the Blue crab</u>
  <u t="1595880">fishman. This is how they collect</u>
  <u t="1598399">the</u>
  <u t="1599559">crabs. Ah, check it out. You can see the crabs there. They have the</u>
  <u t="1609039">chicken</u>
  <u t="1611360">heads on the rope. There, the crab holds on to the</u>
  <u t="1614720">chicken heads. They don't let</u>
  <u t="1617159">go when they pull the line up. How much do you sell it for?</u>
  <u t="1634000">1 kilo? No, no, no, I don't want it.</u>
  <u t="1636799">But just one</u>
  <u t="1639559">question: how much do you sell it for? 0.60 to 1 kilo? A</u>
  <u t="1648600">petroleum extractor or</u>
  <u t="1651919">plant. A massive pump goes down into the</u>
  <u t="1655279">ground, deep below the lake surface, and extracts the petroleum.</u>
  <u t="1664679">Lake Maracaibo is a</u>
  <u t="1668360">massive petroleum</u>
  <u t="1673640">deposit, just like the rest of Venezuela.</u>
  <u t="1676360">All over the country, it</u>
  <u t="1693000">has...</u>
  <u t="1698330">[Laughter]</u>
  <u t="1703080">ID macaón macaón</u>
  <u t="1706320">es macaón. Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus</u>
  <u t="1710880">of theology, not</u>
  <u t="1712919">Nazareth from here, from here. Jesus of the wave, Jesus</u>
  <u t="1716760">from wave is p on the table there</u>
  <u t="1720159">from the incredible</u>
  <u t="1725320">ruto he is from the from the community he is</u>
  <u t="1728279">from Congo</u>
  <u t="1736360">too Agar see Wow the going hold on</u>
  <u t="1741039">to theal</u>
  <u t="1742519">B get absolutely</u>
  <u t="1763039">electrocuted got slowly All of This is</u>
  <u t="1765559">covered Up</u>
  <u t="1768200">to It is Almost Impossible to get to</u>
  <u t="1769880">That's why a lot of The People fled from</u>
  <u t="1772640">there right so Now we B brought some 12</u>
  <u t="1776200">timers that used to live there that Now</u>
  <u t="1778919">live in that Community wave to come and</u>
  <u t="1781720">show</u>
  <u t="1785760">Us and there's a big Storm coming Oh Wow</u>
  <u t="1789519">Look at this have to get through</u>
  <u t="1793360">here dam</u>
  <u t="1798070">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1799240">so he used to live here he knows the</u>
  <u t="1803200">way so this whole</u>
  <u t="1805720">town used to be flourishing with</u>
  <u t="1810519">Life Shops</u>
  <u t="1813480">here night</u>
  <u t="1815110">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1818519">clubs um Everything churches but</u>
  <u t="1822720">now everybody has left [</u>
  <u t="1827010">Music]</u>
  <u t="1833600">sck</u>
  <u t="1874799">see some</u>
  <u t="1880080">houses an old</u>
  <u t="1886120">mattress It's a</u>
  <u t="1889679">Oh Mango tree, look at that wild</u>
  <u t="1891919">mango tree. So you can just imagine this</u>
  <u t="1894960">would have been the neighbor's mango tree.</u>
  <u t="1896919">The children would have gone there and</u>
  <u t="1898200">picked their mango, and</u>
  <u t="1901639">now they all</u>
  <u t="1909559">left</u>
  <u t="1913480">asting. There are people living</u>
  <u t="1916120">there, yes there are.</u>
  <u t="1920400">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1935519">You see? Yes, today, yes.</u>
  <u t="1949190">[Music] [Music]</u>
  <u t="1959320">Ah yes, good. [Music]</u>
  <u t="1972730">[Music]</u>
  <u t="1974200">idea. How people move, I</u>
  <u t="1995679">had, but good. [Music</u>
  <u t="2009380">]</u>
  <u t="2016120">control. Venezuela.</u>
  <u t="2024160">[Music]</u>
  <u t="2027960">crazy, you know, there</u>
  <u t="2033039">are many types of water lilies here, they</u>
  <u t="2038080">are not very poisonous. Guayacán too, if they</u>
  <u t="2041760">sting you, hospital,</u>
  <u t="2044880">or they have stung you. Yes, and it hurts.</u>
  <u t="2050070">[Music]</u>
  <u t="2051399">like, well. Where, where are we now?</u>
  <u t="2054800">Can you explain a little bit? Congo Mirador,</u>
  <u t="2056639">Congo Mirador, okay. And what was that?</u>
  <u t="2061399">What is this? This is a fishing village, a</u>
  <u t="2063800">fishing village. Many years ago,</u>
  <u t="2065560">like 200 years old, this village is more or</u>
  <u t="2067119">less. Okay, it was 200 years old. Wow, more or</u>
  <u t="2070440">less quite a lot. This village, at least,</u>
  <u t="2072639">had even a</u>
  <u t="2075119">cemetery, you know where, and they buried the</u>
  <u t="2078679">dead there. Okay, in a part that is over there. Because</u>
  <u t="2081119">of that, this is a This town,</u>
  <u t="2084359">which was very, very beautiful, still is. It's</u>
  <u t="2088000">alive now, but the sediment from Catatumbo</u>
  <u t="2092040">passed through here and fed all of this</u>
  <u t="2095599">green vegetation you see. It was all water,</u>
  <u t="2098079">water, lagoon, everything was water. But now you can't get through, there's</u>
  <u t="2104000">not much sediment. Because of that, people</u>
  <u t="2107320">migrated to other places, wave by wave.</u>
  <u t="2110880">Not many others went to Barranquita, Santa</u>
  <u t="2113960">Bárbara, and found</u>
  <u t="2115800">work in many</u>
  <u t="2118240">places. This town was very beautiful and there were many people, many people, many people,</u>
  <u t="2125320">almost all taken away. How many</u>
  <u t="2128000">people were there? About</u>
  <u t="2129720">700, more or less,</u>
  <u t="2133040">100, 700 approximately. Wow, there were already</u>
  <u t="2138200">shops, there was a medical clinic</u>
  <u t="2141160">there, there were businesses, a</u>
  <u t="2144040">school, a disco, well, there was a little</u>
  <u t="2147800">bar, no, there was a little bar with a little pool</u>
  <u t="2149839">for playing. There was</u>
  <u t="2152760">also a fire station. Oh, also. Wow,</u>
  <u t="2156359">how crazy,</u>
  <u t="2158480">why is there so much water? Well, but for</u>
  <u t="2161480">emergencies, like pregnancy, Ah, okay,</u>
  <u t="2168640">emergency. It's a very well-known town.</u>
  <u t="2170680">This town may be more well-known than</u>
  <u t="2172079">any other part of Venezuela. Wow, because</u>
  <u t="2174359">many foreigners, as well as</u>
  <u t="2176520">Venezuelans, come to this place to</u>
  <u t="2178240">observe the lightning.</u>
  <u t="2179800">Many people from outside, but Yeah, yeah, nothing,</u>
  <u t="2185000">what do you guys do? You fish, you live</u>
  <u t="2188280">fishing. Wow, it's raining hard now,</u>
  <u t="2191119">eh? Thank goodness we arrived on time, yeah,</u>
  <u t="2193920">what? It was beautiful, and that was a church,</u>
  <u t="2207240">right? You live here, okay? And you live off</u>
  <u t="2211960">fish too, right? Uh-huh, everyone fishes. That's</u>
  <u t="2215240">great, wow.</u>
  <u t="2217990">[Applause]</u>
  <u t="2219280">Great, yeah, great. You're all</u>
  <u t="2223400">family, brothers or cousins. Cousin, cousin is the</u>
  <u t="2228119">only family here, or? Oh,</u>
  <u t="2230319">two more. Ah, there's another one.</u>
  <u t="2233070">[Music]</u>
  <u t="2236000">family, oh no, but there's quite a few in the little</u>
  <u t="2239440">ranch, another family. How many, how many</u>
  <u t="2241920">people are there now? Right now there are about 30</u>
  <u t="2246000">by 30 families,</u>
  <u t="2252079">but look, before there were about 700,</u>
  <u t="2254520">now there are only 30 left. You were born here,</u>
  <u t="2258599">everyone was born here, most of them.</u>
  <u t="2261560">Today we're going to see, today we're going to see, little dog, doggy,</u>
  <u t="2270240">doggy,</u>
  <u t="2278040">calmly. It's a little dog, it's a little</u>
  <u t="2280319">dog, yes, oh no, how cute,</u>
  <u t="2286000">what's its</u>
  <u t="2287880">name? Ah, no, they haven't named it, it's</u>
  <u t="2295200">chubby, it's</u>
  <u t="2300520">chubby. There's another one, there's another one.</u>
  <u t="2306400">[Music]</u>
  <u t="2313000">It's a male, a male, a</u>
  <u t="2314280">male. Ah, that explains why it's so in</u>
  <u t="2318160">love. Oh, how</u>
  <u t="2321000">cute,</u>
  <u t="2322440">there's the other one. That one's blacker. that</u>
  <u t="2326880">too Ah no That's female I think that's</u>
  <u t="2333480">female qu ternito</u>
  <u t="2336440">no bu do Come</u>
  <u t="2341160">here you are also</u>
  <u t="2345960">sorry that we say one two</u>
  <u t="2349079">TR cheesecake they say that 1 two TR</u>
  <u t="2358440">chees about ag us</u>
  <u t="2363920">toit hous</u>
  <u t="2368000">but then When the canals dried up and</u>
  <u t="2370200">filled up with sediments that The River</u>
  <u t="2372960">brought in people Had to move Because</u>
  <u t="2375960">they couldn't Get In and out of the</u>
  <u t="2377240">Community Anymore so a lot of them</u>
  <u t="2380520">packed up these houses they put All the</u>
  <u t="2382839">material on boats and they moved to</u>
  <u t="2385200">other towns like ologa Where we're</u>
  <u t="2386920">staying and they built New homes over</u>
  <u t="2389480">there and Back then there used to be</u>
  <u t="2392760">over 700 people they used to live here</u>
  <u t="2395119">and Now only about 30 people remain so</u>
  <u t="2398960">just a couple</u>
  <u t="2400119">families and yeah This is very common in</u>
  <u t="2402640">these Parts um this Place used to be</u>
  <u t="2405160">very Famous you know like he was</u>
  <u t="2406880">explaining to Us earlier on have a night</u>
  <u t="2409200">club Church As you</u>
  <u t="2411680">Saw sharps there was Life here and Now</u>
  <u t="2414839">Just The People Getting</u>
  <u t="2417119">by by fishing crab Blue crab and</u>
  <u t="2421599">Fish Oh Wow</u>
  <u t="2429760">lo V just to</u>
  <u t="2433680">consume you lived here years ago How many</u>
  <u t="2437960">years you lived</u>
  <u t="2440440">here</u>
  <u t="2445060">[Music]</u>
  <u t="2453640">years with</u>
  <u t="2457480">your Life here, yes, 9 years ago you moved</u>
  <u t="2463040">there, did you like it here more than there? I like it</u>
  <u t="2466359">more here than there because one is forced to go</u>
  <u t="2468640">there. Here it has a lot of history, it's</u>
  <u t="2473599">beautiful here.</u>
  <u t="2475359">Here there was an old man who used to go out, he</u>
  <u t="2478480">knew a lot of history. Yes, I imagine</u>
  <u t="2481280">200</u>
  <u t="2484880">years, there was a lot of Victoria, I imagine</u>
  <u t="2488079">when you were younger you went out partying</u>
  <u t="2490839">here all the time. No, I used to go to</u>
  <u t="2495359">Santa</u>
  <u t="2498280">Bárbara every 15th birthday party and you had girlfriends here too, there too,</u>
  <u t="2504640">and here</u>
  <u t="2506680">too, they arrived from</u>
  <u t="2512000">all over. On the</u>
  <u t="2518680">other hand, I feel like I'm from here</u>
  <u t="2520240">too. Yes, because it's my job. And of course you</u>
  <u t="2522960">were always here, my parents were born</u>
  <u t="2525000">in Palito too, your parents, my</u>
  <u t="2527280">grandparents too, but not here, no, another</u>
  <u t="2529560">part that was called La Boyera, La Boyera,</u>
  <u t="2531880">La Boera, but it doesn't exist anymore, it went to</u>
  <u t="2533680">Puerto. Ah, it's been many years, it</u>
  <u t="2537000">ended. I imagine that before there were many</u>
  <u t="2540200">communities in Palito, not leaving there, there was</u>
  <u t="2542839">a part called Chamita,</u>
  <u t="2544559">in the Chamita part there was La Boyera, there</u>
  <u t="2546440">was Boca de Zulia, Boca del Río Congo,</u>
  <u t="2550359">Mirador Ologá and Santa Ala and everything was</u>
  <u t="2554680">much more crowded. No little palace, much more</u>
  <u t="2556800">palatial, many comforts, how many people in</u>
  <u t="2559599">total, you can</u>
  <u t="2561520">say thousands,</u>
  <u t="2565559">thousands, and now they've all gone to the towns,</u>
  <u t="2568520">to the</u>
  <u t="2569520">cities, what a crazy place, there was a school too,</u>
  <u t="2572960">back there, a big, big</u>
  <u t="2574640">school,</u>
  <u t="2578119">you studied there for a few</u>
  <u t="2580800">months and the water was splashing me and my</u>
  <u t="2584319">mom tried the</u>
  <u t="2587359">school and this school, I was there too,</u>
  <u t="2591160">I was also a little one,</u>
  <u t="2596040">ah,</u>
  <u t="2608559">this was</u>
  <u t="2610280">beautiful,</u>
  <u t="2612440">10, so all that was water, no, all that</u>
  <u t="2615839">was water, and how did people get to</u>
  <u t="2617319">the church by boat and go up by</u>
  <u t="2621079">the</u>
  <u t="2622680">church, everything you see,</u>
  <u t="2625359">vegetation was water, like Venice,</u>
  <u t="2630880">so to go to the house you had to arrive</u>
  <u t="2633559">by boat and go up,</u>
  <u t="2635440">wow,</u>
  <u t="2637800">and now all</u>
  <u t="2639400">vegetation, those houses, houses there, you can't</u>
  <u t="2642040">go for a walk, all watery, right,</u>
  <u t="2645280">watery, we call</u>
  <u t="2647570">[Music]</u>
  <u t="2649440">radio, people never go to the</u>
  <u t="2652600">[Music]</u>
  <u t="2654599">church, we come at least around there,</u>
  <u t="2658359">boy, around there or around here, there, there, jump, there, jump, go to</u>
  <u t="2679119">church. Yeah, it's kind of</u>
  <u t="2683800">hard, apparently there are venous snakes in, trying to snake, you see, my</u>
  <u t="2702359">plan made</u>
  <u t="2707960">there, we go. So this is the old</u>
  <u t="2710839">church, got my mouth, this used to be the</u>
  <u t="2714520">church where the locals Used To</u>
  <u t="2718359">Come and</u>
  <u t="2724240">pray out</u>
  <u t="2731440">I don't think anybody's been in here in</u>
  <u t="2733119">many years there's some</u>
  <u t="2739920">bats It's the Virgin baby</u>
  <u t="2744920">J esus</u>
  <u t="2747280">Man It's completely</u>
  <u t="2751000">abandoned Imagine 5 years ago they were</u>
  <u t="2753720">to come here Every Sunday</u>
  <u t="2759480">for Mass</u>
  <u t="2761599">etc different types of events</u>
  <u t="2764800">all Catholic events that come here and</u>
  <u t="2769079">participate right here in this Little</u>
  <u t="2770760">Church This is the Community</u>
  <u t="2772599">Church which is now just a b</u>
  <u t="2797760">Bugs are biting</u>
  <u t="2799520">me</u>
  <u t="2802599">right full of</u>
  <u t="2808160">bats What a place and over here We have</u>
  <u t="2811079">San Benito Who was a Black Saint</u>
  <u t="2817680">from this area and also over here</u>
  <u t="2822319">they How Would you say they Praise no</u>
  <u t="2826760">yeah they take Great importance to</u>
  <u t="2829280">the Saints chinera or la chinita [ __ ]</u>
  <u t="2833599">I'm butchering that name but la chinita</u>
  <u t="2836280">the Virgin chinita was a very important</u>
  <u t="2839359">Saint or is a very important Saint here</u>
  <u t="2841359">in the State of suia So apparently The</u>
  <u t="2844280">Story goes there was an indigenous lady</u>
  <u t="2846920">washing clothes in the Lake marakaibo</u>
  <u t="2849400">and On A tablet appeared the image of</u>
  <u t="2853960">the Saint chinita so That's why they</u>
  <u t="2857119">celebrate her she's a very important</u>
  <u t="2859880">Saint here in the State of</u>
  <u t="2862040">sulia and apparently She was even</u>
  <u t="2864240">Colombian I don't know If That's true Or</u>
  <u t="2866319">Not but yeah That's That's The Story and</u>
  <u t="2868880">this Plaza used to be full of Life</u>
  <u t="2871480">people would come here youth would come</u>
  <u t="2873680">Here hang around</u>
  <u t="2879400">Church arriving is easy but coming back</u>
  <u t="2882440">is another</u>
  <u t="2892359">thing damn that was a warehouse there</u>
  <u t="2900440">the wild gringo</u>
  <u t="2924800">English saying speaking English</u>
  <u t="2937319">learning English</u>
  <u t="2940319">throwing English throwing</u>
  <u t="2942760">hard the little black</u>
  <u t="2944880">boy learning</u>
  <u t="2952200">English the little bad girl what do you say</u>
  <u t="2956559">we're active Alejandra the</u>
  <u t="2960079">bad girl chamao</u>
  <u t="2989720">that's it and a lot of the houses here</u>
  <u t="2993720">that you see from cone some some</u>
  <u t="2999040">Yes not all yes</u>
  <u t="3004640">some you know everyone</u>
  <u t="3009520">Nero but that's good no It's cool</u>
  <u t="3012760">but go further there there's</u>
  <u t="3014160">nothing just</u>
  <u t="3022599">drool no I don't like it like that much but</u>
  <u t="3026319">sometimes washing if it gets in no no no no Come on help me we'll leave</u>
  <u t="3028799">no Come on then let's go then</u>
  <u t="3032400">no please</u>
  <u t="3037440">cha No seriously well nothing before</u>
  <u t="3041599">the drool comes there it</u>
  <u t="3043440">comes from nothing nothing nothing I cry that</u>
  <u t="3055000">work works exercise No love okay well Let's</u>
  <u t="3059520">go then it's coming</u>
  <u t="3062520">the Lake</u>
  <u t="3073599">sea the sin Now yes Let's go now bye now</u>
  <u t="3079920">who is now who is the</u>
  <u t="3083160">victim you're not going to do that to me I'm</u>
  <u t="3086200">fast</u>
  <u t="3087839">Yes how was</u>
  <u t="3090559">elegant pretty the</u>
  <u t="3094359">little girl Melo caramel</u>
  <u t="3101040">Melo Give me that the</u>
  <u t="3104319">Little troublemaker with her little bag,</u>
  <u t="3108240">Alejandra the troublemaker, it's</u>
  <u t="3111119">harder to put on wet things, always, always</u>
  <u t="3113720">slow, I always have to</u>
  <u t="3115799">wait for her, an hour, three hours. Listen to this</u>
  <u t="3119000">little chili, I live my life waiting for her,</u>
  <u t="3121799">Alejandra the troublemaker. Give me your hand</u>
  <u t="3124920">then. And that,</u>
  <u t="3129520">my God, your little</u>
  <u t="3132000">bag. Ah, you see the flow, the flow, the flow,</u>
  <u t="3137280">and the flow, Caracas girl, no, the dogs</u>
  <u t="3140359">aren't calm, no, but he looks at me like he's in</u>
  <u t="3143079">love, no, good, good, how's</u>
  <u t="3147119">everything? Good, black,</u>
  <u t="3150280">what's up? Today, yes, today, today, yes, or</u>
  <u t="3155220">[Laughter]</u>
  <u t="3159319">what? What do we have here, Chelo, the beach,</u>
  <u t="3164240">here the</u>
  <u t="3167359">beach, we're at the lagoon behind, and here's</u>
  <u t="3169720">the lake, the lake. Ah, so that's right, the lake, a real</u>
  <u t="3173440">lake, right? All</u>
  <u t="3177400">along the coast here on the shores you can find petroleum blotches like this</u>
  <u t="3183319">because Lake Maracaibo is</u>
  <u t="3187040">or has one of the largest oil deposits</u>
  <u t="3195440">in the world. I think the second largest here in the country, and Venezuela has the most oil in the world, which you guys probably</u>
  <u t="3199799">never imagined, right? Because</u>
  <u t="3202040">you always think when you think of oil</u>
  <u t="3203240">you think of Saudi Arabia, etc., but not</u>
  <u t="3205559">Venezuela.</u>
  <u t="3213599">What's your</u>
  <u t="3219119">name? And</u>
  <u t="3223920">no, and</u>
  <u t="3228680">Toror</u>
  <u t="3234040">yú yú</u>
  <u t="3239240">silence. It looks like my cousins.</u>
  <u t="3265359">We use this for work, for</u>
  <u t="3268079">fishing. At least one fisherman</u>
  <u t="3269640">carries a radio and stays put. If his</u>
  <u t="3272400">motor breaks down, he communicates. Look, I'm in such and such a place. My</u>
  <u t="3277599">motor broke down for work. There's</u>
  <u t="3280240">no WhatsApp here. There's radio. There used to be</u>
  <u t="3283400">communication,</u>
  <u t="3286480">like,</u>
  <u t="3290559">8 years ago, that ended. So, since</u>
  <u t="3297440">cell phone communication ended, well,</u>
  <u t="3301520">we had to resort to this to</u>
  <u t="3303319">communicate with family, with the</u>
  <u t="3306520">worker, with transportation. If</u>
  <u t="3310520">possible, I call him, not directly on</u>
  <u t="3313040">his radio, but I call another one and the</u>
  <u t="3314960">other one connects me. And what? I don't know, all</u>
  <u t="3317720">the radios communicate. They all hear each other.</u>
  <u t="3319920">No, they don't hear each other, but you can't</u>
  <u t="3323000">talk to him. He can't. No, I can't talk to him, I mean,</u>
  <u t="3326920">with the radio. I can't talk</u>
  <u t="3328720">with this radio. You hear me? No. Who</u>
  <u t="3333400">is that? A</u>
  <u t="3337920">tourist? A tourist who always comes</u>
  <u t="3340359">here? Doesn't sleep? You dirty, sleeping [ __ ]!</u>
  <u t="3342640">You're always sleeping! Bravo eh</u>
  <u t="3352640">Now yes</u>
  <u t="3362610">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3362880">[Laughter]</u>
  <u t="3372280">quick what do you say the camera out what do you</u>
  <u t="3376880">say say hello well what</u>
  <u t="3386559">She is my sister your sister right</u>
  <u t="3389319">but she is my sister she looks like her she is</u>
  <u t="3392359">dark-skinned like</u>
  <u t="3395570">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3401280">I let's see let's see that damn it I</u>
  <u t="3407960">always we carry the nursery on us Where to over there over there</u>
  <u t="3419359">what do we have</u>
  <u t="3424880">here Ah acc sticking let's go well let's go Well</u>
  <u t="3432880">ah you know you say hello in English it's</u>
  <u t="3437359">or Hello you</u>
  <u t="3440559">knew well</u>
  <u t="3443319">she does know and How are you it's said How How how what did you</u>
  <u t="3456119">say what how</u>
  <u t="3461160">well come let's</u>
  <u t="3466000">see if she's okay So The Kids no let me</u>
  <u t="3469799">go</u>
  <u t="3471559">first to see if she's sure</u>
  <u t="3478520">I can go in Go ahead</u>
  <u t="3479480">you go</u>
  <u t="3482680">first but if I ca</u>
  <u t="3486640">ca Ah well good</u>
  <u t="3492960">they are intelligent</u>
  <u t="3502250">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3513630">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3516319">making a</u>
  <u t="3518960">heat well d d d</u>
  <u t="3523079">what you told me you</u>
  <u t="3531640">told me</u>
  <u t="3534280">more esem</u>
  <u t="3540079">Her name is Alejandra the</u>
  <u t="3543440">bad girl it's not a lie that's a name</u>
  <u t="3546119">Alejandra the</u>
  <u t="3547520">bad girl Do you know English</u>
  <u t="3550720">tell me</u>
  <u t="3553880">English</u>
  <u t="3555400">in</u>
  <u t="3560319">English here comes Chelo</u>
  <u t="3566160">that's her house no That It's my</u>
  <u t="3568640">mom's house. Oh, but you live here, I don't live over there</u>
  <u t="3571920">in the house of all. Oh, we're</u>
  <u t="3574319">staying there</u>
  <u t="3576480">where that is, that's close, I'm the</u>
  <u t="3580319">last one over there in the house. Oh, the last one.</u>
  <u t="3589810">[Music]</u>
  <u t="3595039">G That's</u>
  <u t="3597680">because, yeah,</u>
  <u t="3600799">Germans, the Germans found their way over</u>
  <u t="3603119">here some back in the days, and they</u>
  <u t="3605160">mixed up, and then, yeah, through the</u>
  <u t="3607640">generations, the genetics come through, and</u>
  <u t="3610359">that's why you see a lot of kids</u>
  <u t="3611520">with blond blue eyes, really, really</u>
  <u t="3615480">interesting. What do you bathe with here?</u>
  <u t="3618400">Blue soap, with the prehistoric blue soap.</u>
  <u t="3623079">That's very Venezuelan. No,</u>
  <u t="3625680">yes, the</u>
  <u t="3644920">LL live to see how it's done, part of</u>
  <u t="3651400">rural life. But there's a little cup,</u>
  <u t="3661920">sticks,</u>
  <u t="3665400">sea,</u>
  <u t="3667640">blue soap, good, and it falls,</u>
  <u t="3671000">but below, the water, the water goes over</u>
  <u t="3674880">there, of course, that's why, if I eat</u>
  <u t="3681319">fried water, it's not good, it's good, good,</u>
  <u t="3690440">round,</u>
  <u t="3702960">eh, there, over here, over there, no,</u>
  <u t="3707400">but the</u>
  <u t="3709960">Maracuchos think they own the</u>
  <u t="3712520">world. I've seen the Maracuchos say, "</u>
  <u t="3716760">We don't want to be like God,</u>
  <u t="3719079">God, and we are</u>
  <u t="3721799">equal," look at the technique very</u>
  <u t="3742760">round I think and G buo I love you</u>
  <u t="3747720">sometimes qui</u>
  <u t="3748920">dicea the thing got going the thing is going to</u>
  <u t="3757279">win and</u>
  <u t="3761079">how much do</u>
  <u t="3768640">we lend well 50 well thanks for</u>
  <u t="3772920">me I who am your country</u>
  <u t="3776680">Yes thank you He's going to be the judge Okay there's</u>
  <u t="3780520">no favorite here it's what you see</u>
  <u t="3783799">best you guys are going to work and I'm going to leave</u>
  <u t="3786359">and you're going to put for each qui so we don't</u>
  <u t="3788760">know who it is so we do that so hac</u>
  <u t="3792039">game on game on let's see</u>
  <u t="3795160">the gringo is going to beat you okay you'll see</u>
  <u t="3800279">Girl</u>
  <u t="3802200">we're active you know you</u>
  <u t="3805279">first then</u>
  <u t="3809079">me watching so nobody</u>
  <u t="3813960">cheats he's going to</u>
  <u t="3819319">leave Alejandra the</u>
  <u t="3832160">badass is slapping</u>
  <u t="3837039">Well then Ah look how how is he</u>
  <u t="3840680">thin There thick Ah that's not</u>
  <u t="3845200">fair Come on then let's go to the harassment that</u>
  <u t="3850279">we're going to see let's see let's see what he</u>
  <u t="3852119">says no but also not an hour</u>
  <u t="3854640">here with a repa put it in well stopwatch stopwatch</u>
  <u t="3856720">aha There's no life my</u>
  <u t="3862119">love and it was in the middle of time like</u>
  <u t="3865000">you did</u>
  <u t="3866599">Well then let's</u>
  <u t="3868119">wait for the judge let's go Let's see, it</u>
  <u t="3873839">stays.</u>
  <u t="3896079">Okay, my</u>
  <u t="3897400">friend,</u>
  <u t="3899240">well,</u>
  <u t="3905240">uh-huh, who</u>
  <u t="3907559">won? Well, that doesn't count.</u>
  <u t="3911000">Which ones count? Well,</u>
  <u t="3913240">these three. Which one is the</u>
  <u t="3917000">best of these three? Well,</u>
  <u t="3921559">this one is okay. Uh-huh, but which one is the best?</u>
  <u t="3924799">Well, it's okay because this one is</u>
  <u t="3926400">very thin. We make it like this, but</u>
  <u t="3929240">these two are the ones that are the best. And this one</u>
  <u t="3931480">is chubby, very pretty too. But</u>
  <u t="3934000">which one</u>
  <u t="3934799">wins?</u>
  <u t="3936960">I'm looking for a</u>
  <u t="3939279">texture. That's the best. What do you</u>
  <u t="3947039">say? What do you say? I</u>
  <u t="3949760">lost. Well, thank goodness. I didn't</u>
  <u t="3953039">bet anything. For a chubby one, a little more</u>
  <u t="3956760">chubby. I like it thin, of course. I</u>
  <u t="3959960">saw</u>
  <u t="3961440">Cos</u>
  <u t="3964720">gent. The German does it</u>
  <u t="3968240">better, but in a way. Which one is better? You're</u>
  <u t="3972720">watching that part. I'm not going to put it.</u>
  <u t="3985680">Admit it. Of course, I</u>
  <u t="3987640">admit it, but admit it well. Who makes</u>
  <u t="3991240">the best arepa? Look, Adal, Adal, admit it.</u>
  <u t="3995880">Junior said each one. He says it the way he does.</u>
  <u t="4002000">And</u>
  <u t="4004160">G F for yours,</u>
  <u t="4026960">[ __ ]. You've never eaten</u>
  <u t="4038760">crab.</u>
  <u t="4041240">Time, neveren cb.</u>
  <u t="4050599">Ah, what bad luck,</u>
  <u t="4055599">okay.</u>
  <u t="4060960">Dale,</u>
  <u t="4063359">right to try</u>
  <u t="4071440">this. It smells like sm Like Popcorn</u>
  <u t="4079160">Kat, crunchy, smells a little bit like</u>
  <u t="4091119">shell, yeah. It's sweet, kind of sweet. The</u>
  <u t="4093319">meat is soft and</u>
  <u t="4101120">tender. Suck it out, but the grilled shell</u>
  <u t="4104880">doesn't really.</u>
  <u t="4116960">If you want to chop it with a knife, you</u>
  <u t="4119239">can do this, and you can. Normally,</u>
  <u t="4121759">we do it with our own</u>
  <u t="4122759">teeth. We do</u>
  <u t="4126040">this without going too far down; it comes out.</u>
  <u t="4128400">And if you want, with the</u>
  <u t="4131799">knife you do this. Ah, and take out the C.</u>
  <u t="4136159">Oh man, it feels like a storm's coming,</u>
  <u t="4143520">Jesus, like.</u>
  <u t="4145910">[Applause]</u>
  <u t="4149480">Crazy, the</u>
  <u t="4160159">adventure, if you got something to cover.</u>
  <u t="4162600">You sleeping outside,</u>
  <u t="4165600">nice and cozy. Be sleeping out there. The</u>
  <u t="4168839">wind is horrible.</u>
  <u t="4173810">[Applause]</u>
  </text>
