<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="IgiIkW17ckM" uploader="Taylor Bell" channel="Taylor Bell" likes="11902" title="Vietnam VLOG: Exploring Hanoi, Street Food, Hạ Long Bay, Hidden Cafes, Train Street, &amp; bein' silly" year="2025" month="5" day="29" date="20250529" date_ts="1748523572" is_ac="true">
  <u t="2540">[Music]</u>
  <u t="26720">Hello Ramona.</u>
  <u t="34000">First morning in Hanoi. We are going to</u>
  <u t="37440">this coffee shop recommendation I got.</u>
  <u t="39360">So far, we're just enjoying the sights</u>
  <u t="41520">and the smells and the sounds. We're</u>
  <u t="43840">kind of in the thick of it. We're in the</u>
  <u t="45440">old corner and yeah, just a lot of</u>
  <u t="47200">motorbikes, a lot of amazing looking</u>
  <u t="49280">food.</u>
  <u t="52000">[Music]</u>
  <u t="55680">Okay, a lovely subscriber told me that</u>
  <u t="57760">this coffee shop is a hidden gem and I</u>
  <u t="60640">love me some hidden gems. So, naturally,</u>
  <u t="62719">I had to start strong for my first</u>
  <u t="64320">coffee in Vietnam.</u>
  <u t="66880">Oh, that's great. Thank you so much. The</u>
  <u t="68560">coffee is at the bottom. You can try the</u>
  <u t="70479">cream first and then just scoop the</u>
  <u t="72240">coffee with the cream.</u>
  <u t="74960">Thank you. Beautiful. Looks great.</u>
  <u t="78000">Oh my god. And then I do it with the</u>
  <u t="80880">coffee.</u>
  <u t="84840">Wow, it's insanely</u>
  <u t="89920">[Music]</u>
  <u t="95240">good. So, I realized I didn't even</u>
  <u t="97520">explain what I got. I got an egg cream</u>
  <u t="99680">coffee. They take egg yolk and whip it</u>
  <u t="102479">up with sweetened condensed milk and add</u>
  <u t="104159">it to espresso. A little mocha chocolate</u>
  <u t="106560">powder on top. Probably one of the best</u>
  <u t="108240">things I've ever tasted.</u>
  <u t="110220">[Music]</u>
  <u t="111600">Get out.</u>
  <u t="114799">And here we are.</u>
  <u t="117759">Not my My chicken thigh. Now I'm</u>
  <u t="120479">going to dress it up with all the garlic</u>
  <u t="122079">in the world. Do you want some? No,</u>
  <u t="124640">thank you. All right. I swear it's</u>
  <u t="126399">cooler on the inside, but that's what</u>
  <u t="128239">we're saying. Actually, it's cool on the</u>
  <u t="129920">outside. It has its own charm.</u>
  <u t="134400">All right. We are out walking around</u>
  <u t="135920">again after going back to the Airbnb to</u>
  <u t="138080">rest for a little bit after the fur and</u>
  <u t="140959">the walking around and the chaos. We're</u>
  <u t="142800">just meandering until we get to the</u>
  <u t="144239">Hanoi Hilton which is the P prison or it</u>
  <u t="146800">was a P prison during the Vietnam War.</u>
  <u t="148959">But for now, we got little ice cream</u>
  <u t="151120">cones which converted to what? 80 cents</u>
  <u t="152879">each. Yes. Everything here is very</u>
  <u t="155440">cheap. That's awesome.</u>
  <u t="159610">[Music]</u>
  <u t="161920">All right. All right. And about the</u>
  <u t="162720">amount of time it took us to eat those</u>
  <u t="163920">teeny tiny little ice cream cones, we</u>
  <u t="166160">got another dessert or another dessert</u>
  <u t="168879">station popped up. And anyway, I've</u>
  <u t="170640">never ever had these. I've seen them all</u>
  <u t="172879">over social media. I don't know where</u>
  <u t="175120">they originate from. TBH. They're</u>
  <u t="176720">strawberries crystallized in like a a</u>
  <u t="180000">hot sugar mold. Really? Yeah. Wow.</u>
  <u t="186959">I mean, obviously really good. The</u>
  <u t="189040">strawberries themselves are really good,</u>
  <u t="190319">too. Mhm.</u>
  <u t="196620">[Music]</u>
  <u t="204400">Hey there. A lot of sanding. My back</u>
  <u t="206000">kind of hurt. And we need a little</u>
  <u t="208080">refreshment. I like to try weird things.</u>
  <u t="210319">So, I got this melon milk soda. It is so</u>
  <u t="214319">good. If you like key lime laqua or</u>
  <u t="216959">lemon cello laqua, which kind of has</u>
  <u t="218799">that creamy flavor, you would love this.</u>
  <u t="221120">And it's zero calorie,</u>
  <u t="223320">[Music]</u>
  <u t="224840">too. We just got a drink, hung out with</u>
  <u t="228560">some friends for a couple hours, and now</u>
  <u t="231280">probably meander and find a food spot.</u>
  <u t="233120">Well, we'll see.</u>
  <u t="236680">Deciding. Chicken udon. Cucumber in my</u>
  <u t="239680">belly. Edamame in my belly. Fantastic.</u>
  <u t="246480">It's a wet</u>
  <u t="259560">wipe. What's up vlog? We're going to get</u>
  <u t="262360">bonies since we've done fa. We're going</u>
  <u t="265440">to do buncha um later today. Hang on.</u>
  <u t="268240">Let me cross the road here. But for now,</u>
  <u t="269759">we're going to do boni street bomb. It's</u>
  <u t="272080">going to be awesome. What's up, vlog? We</u>
  <u t="273919">got our Bonese. This one mysteriously</u>
  <u t="276160">has a bite taken out of it already. Not</u>
  <u t="278720">very cool of the people who made them.</u>
  <u t="280560">It was me. I took the bite. Soaking it</u>
  <u t="282880">in. Life on a stick. Life on a bon.</u>
  <u t="287120">Cheers.</u>
  <u t="295580">[Music]</u>
  <u t="297040">All right, we just walked down this cute</u>
  <u t="298960">little alleyway. The crowded area is</u>
  <u t="300800">right over there, but it's actually kind</u>
  <u t="301840">of wide over here. Anyways, we're going</u>
  <u t="303840">to another hidden coffee spot. Go</u>
  <u t="306240">straight and turn left. Okay, we didn't</u>
  <u t="308880">actually end up getting a coffee here</u>
  <u t="310320">because somehow they didn't have the</u>
  <u t="312080">classic Vietnamese style coffee we were</u>
  <u t="314080">wanting, but I'm just so into these</u>
  <u t="316800">hidden nook and cranny coffee shops and</u>
  <u t="319280">still wanted to show you.</u>
  <u t="323740">[Music]</u>
  <u t="329680">walked into a little ceramic shop and</u>
  <u t="332080">everything here is hand</u>
  <u t="334199">painted. Like everything. And then I</u>
  <u t="337120">thought this was funny. I can't get</u>
  <u t="339360">away. We're at the train street where a</u>
  <u t="341759">train sometimes comes directly through.</u>
  <u t="344000">You know, I'm not sure going to come by</u>
  <u t="345759">given that they're putting seating</u>
  <u t="347039">directly on the truck. I say no one's</u>
  <u t="348960">not scheduled now. Let's go. But it's</u>
  <u t="351039">pretty cool.</u>
  <u t="358140">[Music]</u>
  <u t="367280">All right. This is B-52 Lake. That's a</u>
  <u t="370039">B-52 bomber that was shot down during</u>
  <u t="373680">the Vietnam</u>
  <u t="375060">[Music]</u>
  <u t="378120">War. The chaos leading up to the train</u>
  <u t="382960">Everyone getting their orders.</u>
  <u t="385000">[Music]</u>
  <u t="390080">Okay, the train is coming in like 2 - 2</u>
  <u t="392240">minutes and she just asked us to angle</u>
  <u t="394479">our legs this way because it comes this</u>
  <u t="396880">close to us. Okay, I heard the rumble. I</u>
  <u t="400160">don't see it before I think 2 minutes.</u>
  <u t="403120">It's getting smushed. Yeah, it's Korean.</u>
  <u t="404960">Okay. All right. We used to do that as a</u>
  <u t="407360">kid or me and my brother.</u>
  <u t="412800">Oh my god.</u>
  <u t="415890">[Music]</u>
  <u t="441680">Oh my god.</u>
  <u t="445170">[Music]</u>
  <u t="448000">What's your reaction?</u>
  <u t="451639">Wa. It's still hot. Look at that. We got</u>
  <u t="455520">the coin in Korea and we smashed it in</u>
  <u t="458280">Vietnam. That's really cool. Okay, it</u>
  <u t="461120">was hard to tell in the video, but I'm</u>
  <u t="462720">not kidding. It probably came to like</u>
  <u t="464400">what? Here. probably about a foot away.</u>
  <u t="467120">Yeah. Wow.</u>
  <u t="470720">Crazy. Crazy. Okay. So, after the train,</u>
  <u t="474879">we walked back down cuz we were here</u>
  <u t="476400">earlier and I found him. I went store to</u>
  <u t="480319">store and asked if if you've seen this</u>
  <u t="482720">puppy and he said, "Yes, he's sleeping</u>
  <u t="484319">right here." So, I we literally just</u>
  <u t="487039">came to find the most wanted puppy. Hey,</u>
  <u t="490080">puppy. Lua. Lua. Puppy teeth. Puppy</u>
  <u t="493199">teeth. Puppy's teeth. Puppy belly. Puppy</u>
  <u t="496639">belly. A 20 months old. Hi little one.</u>
  <u t="500960">Okay. We were having a very hospitable</u>
  <u t="502639">experience. We came looking for Lua and</u>
  <u t="505440">we found her. I thought she was a he and</u>
  <u t="507680">then I investigated further. She is a</u>
  <u t="510919">she. She wants to play. And then the</u>
  <u t="514000">shop owner came and brought us some</u>
  <u t="515919">black bean sprouts just to munch on</u>
  <u t="518080">while we play with his</u>
  <u t="519560">trophy. I'm</u>
  <u t="521399">happy. Oh, lua</u>
  <u t="525399">lua puppy on. It was about in this</u>
  <u t="528959">moment after the train rushing by and</u>
  <u t="531519">playing with the puppy and crossing</u>
  <u t="533200">these chaotic streets that I realized</u>
  <u t="535680">Hanoi reminded me of why I love New</u>
  <u t="537920">York. And I thought jaywalking in New</u>
  <u t="539760">York was bad. It's got that same wild</u>
  <u t="542399">energy that keeps you on your toes, but</u>
  <u t="544399">set against a completely different</u>
  <u t="546720">cultural background. In some ways, I</u>
  <u t="548560">felt right at home, and in other ways, I</u>
  <u t="550720">couldn't have felt further from home.</u>
  <u t="552800">All right, after that very exhilarating</u>
  <u t="556080">experience, which woke me up because I</u>
  <u t="558560">think my jet lag was hitting kind of bad</u>
  <u t="560399">like an hour ago. Now, we're going to Oh</u>
  <u t="562480">my god, I hope we get in. It's But it's</u>
  <u t="565760">where Anthony Bourdain and Obama ate</u>
  <u t="567600">together. And I have no sense of if</u>
  <u t="570480">we'll be able to get in or it's going to</u>
  <u t="572320">be an insane line or you need to get a</u>
  <u t="574240">reservation 3 months in advance. I don't</u>
  <u t="575839">know. Guess we'll find out. Here we are.</u>
  <u t="577839">Oh my god. It looks not that</u>
  <u t="582760">crazy. That was Obama. All right, guys.</u>
  <u t="587279">Just walk right in. No problem. New York</u>
  <u t="589440">can never. So, we got the traditional</u>
  <u t="592560">chowo. This is what Obama got, but uh</u>
  <u t="595600">I'm not quite as hungry as he was. So,</u>
  <u t="598240">take a look. My mom, while I was in the</u>
  <u t="600160">bathroom, just read that I guess you</u>
  <u t="601600">take noodles, dip it into the sauce. I'm</u>
  <u t="603760">gonna add</u>
  <u t="605160">obviously a lot of this garlic to it.</u>
  <u t="607920">Let's see what it's all about.</u>
  <u t="611200">Start small. I'm trying it just for the</u>
  <u t="613120">flavor.</u>
  <u t="614640">Flavorful. Here's when Anthony Boude and</u>
  <u t="617120">Obama were here.</u>
  <u t="619360">And now</u>
  <u t="621090">[Music]</u>
  <u t="626620">[Music]</u>
  <u t="637000">me. Okay. On the right. Uh, this is the</u>
  <u t="641200">Lia Bridge. Lia Bridge is the oldest</u>
  <u t="644480">bridge in Hanoi. All right. We are in</u>
  <u t="646160">the bus on the way to Hong Bay. Got some</u>
  <u t="650000">coffee. Got a little hotel breakfast</u>
  <u t="652000">this morning. Normally I'm against hotel</u>
  <u t="653600">breakfast. Like I like to go out in the</u>
  <u t="655120">city and not waste one of my meals on</u>
  <u t="657360">not getting kind of authentic city</u>
  <u t="659519">thing. But it was really good. Included</u>
  <u t="662079">like unlimited perfectly ripe cut</u>
  <u t="665240">mango. Incredible.</u>
  <u t="670400">[Music]</u>
  <u t="683920">What's up, vlog? Here we are in Hong</u>
  <u t="686320">Bay. Here is</u>
  <u t="688760">mother. All right, we're in the caves. I</u>
  <u t="691440">haven't really thought to film because</u>
  <u t="692880">it is so touristy. Like, we're basically</u>
  <u t="695839">waiting in line, but this is a little</u>
  <u t="697200">bit more open and it is really, really</u>
  <u t="699279">cool what it is. This is huge cave</u>
  <u t="702000">system on one of the</u>
  <u t="706680">islands.</u>
  <u t="711830">[Music]</u>
  <u t="715720">Yeah. What is it? Hey,</u>
  <u t="719560">Taylor. I'm</u>
  <u t="725320">relaxing. Mother enjoying a Vietnamese</u>
  <u t="727760">beer.</u>
  <u t="729600">Living life pretty good. I have myself</u>
  <u t="732320">some club soda.</u>
  <u t="736340">[Music]</u>
  <u t="741680">That is the turtle of the long bay. This</u>
  <u t="744560">is the other one.</u>
  <u t="755200">[Music]</u>
  <u t="764750">[Music]</u>
  <u t="767360">All right, I'm about to go climb one of</u>
  <u t="769600">these tall mountains in Hong Bay to get</u>
  <u t="772959">a panoramic view at the top. I know it's</u>
  <u t="775440">a lot of steps up and very very steep,</u>
  <u t="777680">but I hope and I think there's going to</u>
  <u t="779680">be enough people in line where it just</u>
  <u t="780959">kind of moves slow and won't be too</u>
  <u t="782560">hard. Anyways, let's do</u>
  <u t="784560">[Music]</u>
  <u t="796440">this. And there's my</u>
  <u t="799399">mom. She didn't join me for this one,</u>
  <u t="801760">but it was awesome. Let's get back on</u>
  <u t="804000">the boat. We're at the end of our</u>
  <u t="805440">cruise. This is the sunset party. We got</u>
  <u t="808240">some snacks. These are really, really</u>
  <u t="810240">good. And then about a 3-hour drive back</u>
  <u t="812160">to Hanoi once we dock. It's been really,</u>
  <u t="815760">really nice. Would highly recommend</u>
  <u t="817360">coming to Halong Bay if you're in Hanoi.</u>
  <u t="820320">It's like a dayong thing. You can make</u>
  <u t="822000">it longer, but we did the dayong thing.</u>
  <u t="823519">I don't know what else to say. They kind</u>
  <u t="824800">of they kind of did it all with me.</u>
  <u t="828240">Well, I didn't really get a good outro</u>
  <u t="830800">for Vietnam video, but here we are in</u>
  <u t="833680">the airport bright and early heading to</u>
  <u t="836120">Taipei. Any final thoughts, mother? It's</u>
  <u t="839680">been a wonderful trip so far. I hope</u>
  <u t="841440">Taipei is just as good. Over and out.</u>
  <u t="844560">It's kind of giving iceberg a Titanic.</u>
  <u t="849600">Hopefully</u>
  <u t="850600">not. It's a cucumber. It's a cucumber.</u>
  <u t="854970">[Music]</u>
  <u t="856150">[Applause]</u>
  <u t="858640">[Music]</u>
  <u t="858970">[Applause]</u>
  <u t="860050">[Music]</u>
  </text>
