<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="pDB8a389rdg" uploader="Sol Life" channel="Sol Life" likes="69281" title="Visiting the Ghibli village in Japan| Yufuin Floral village, Hells of Beppu Oita | Japan travel vlog" year="2021" month="12" day="8" date="20211208" is_ac="false">
  <u t="38654">Saturday</u>
  <u t="42803">good morning from Oita</u>
  <u t="45550">today we're heading to Yufuin floral village</u>
  <u t="51200">it's a place I've always wanted to visit in Japan!</u>
  <u t="54299">it's meant to look like a Ghibli movie</u>
  <u t="57317">and off we go</u>
  <u t="61812">so glad the weather looks perfect as well</u>
  <u t="66022">got a coffee for the ride</u>
  <u t="73833">the place is about 1 hr from Beppu</u>
  <u t="81317">the view was so scenic, it didn't feel long at all</u>
  <u t="91593">looks like a scene from 'Howl's moving castle'</u>
  <u t="98116">there's the town of Yufuin</u>
  <u t="104197">the old lady told us to look at the nice view&lt;3</u>
  <u t="109550">a very picturesque ride</u>
  <u t="114668">we've arrived</u>
  <u t="122152">heading to the cafe first for some breakfast</u>
  <u t="129550">Cafe la ruche</u>
  <u t="144776">this cafe has a fantastic view of Lake Kinrin</u>
  <u t="150000">and the autumn leaves have just started</u>
  <u t="158056">second coffee with a view</u>
  <u t="162916">breakfast time</u>
  <u t="167150">I ordered the breakfast set</u>
  <u t="173412">I think this cafe has the best view</u>
  <u t="178298">and the weather is just about perfect with the early autumn breeze</u>
  <u t="185911">and the food is good too</u>
  <u t="194875">so great to just sit outside and enjoy a cup of coffee</u>
  <u t="217834">I found this little temple next to the lake</u>
  <u t="230681">the reflections of the sky in the water are so pretty</u>
  <u t="243150">on our way to the floral village now</u>
  <u t="253400">enjoying the autumn scenery on the way</u>
  <u t="269401">we're here</u>
  <u t="274751">this village is meant to be based on the streets of Cotswolds in England</u>
  <u t="279800">which is said to be the filming location for Harry Potter</u>
  <u t="285266">the whole place looks like a fairytale</u>
  <u t="291840">and here is Kiki's bakery!</u>
  <u t="297245">let's go in</u>
  <u t="301534">the shop was full of Kiki goodies</u>
  <u t="310151">there was a mix of everything</u>
  <u t="316000">and each store had a different theme</u>
  <u t="331663">they even had an outdoor footbath, but it was closed on this day</u>
  <u t="347539">don't know if this is a real apple crumble store but looks do cute</u>
  <u t="364434">time for some souvenir shopping</u>
  <u t="380751">ended up getting this candle holder</u>
  <u t="385377">you can use it with tea leaves</u>
  <u t="392317">so happy with my purchase</u>
  <u t="396535">the street outside of the village was really cute too</u>
  <u t="409067">snack time</u>
  <u t="414117">getting this meat bun</u>
  <u t="417034">I got the curry flavour</u>
  <u t="423321">of course, need some dessert</u>
  <u t="428200">got the mont blanc ice cream</u>
  <u t="432866">now we're heading back to Beppu station</u>
  <u t="441117">I think Yufuin is one of my favourite spots in Oita!</u>
  <u t="447626">I would definitely want to come again one day</u>
  <u t="454917">time to explore a bit of Beppu city</u>
  <u t="464545">little library</u>
  <u t="469662">found this cute alleyway with some unusual shops</u>
  <u t="481753">this cafe looks so interesting</u>
  <u t="486809">but I think it's closed</u>
  <u t="491539">heading down to the beach to see the sunset</u>
  <u t="503331">love that the city is surrounded by so much nature</u>
  <u t="521210">a great way to end the day</u>
  <u t="525633">Sunday</u>
  <u t="531717">it's our last day in Oita!</u>
  <u t="534667">we're visiting the Hells of Beppu this morning</u>
  <u t="540617">getting a quick coffee while we wait for the bus</u>
  <u t="551467">our flight back to Tokyo is at 5 so we have all morning to look around</u>
  <u t="557585">the coffee was pretty good</u>
  <u t="564550">there is a hand bath at the station</u>
  <u t="572638">this would be great for cold days</u>
  <u t="577234">finally on the bud</u>
  <u t="583288">the Hells of Beppu are hot springs for viewing rather than bathing</u>
  <u t="590317">we're at the most famous blue onsen! Umi jigoku</u>
  <u t="621916">the water is such a vivid blue</u>
  <u t="629444">it's naturally this colour because of the iron sulphate</u>
  <u t="641150">although you can't bath in the hot spring you can take a bit of it back home</u>
  <u t="648035">time for some lunch</u>
  <u t="653000">we're trying the famous jigokumushi</u>
  <u t="657391">got the meat and veggie et</u>
  <u t="670513">it's 'hell-steamed' food</u>
  <u t="674200">you can cook the food yourself over these thermal springs</u>
  <u t="689574">got this steamed rice too</u>
  <u t="694267">all the food was so fresh</u>
  <u t="703544">they give you some salt and ponzu to dip</u>
  <u t="710405">a good meal</u>
  <u t="712317">lastly heading to an onsen before leaving</u>
  <u t="726167">Ebisu onsen</u>
  <u t="734550">the onsen had a nice view of the ocean and the mountains</u>
  <u t="739460">there's this cute cafe in the onsen as well</u>
  <u t="752467">wanted something sweet after the bath</u>
  <u t="759673">got this black sesame pudding</u>
  <u t="771991">so rich</u>
  <u t="783898">having some time to relax</u>
  <u t="791823">so sleepy and warm after the onsen</u>
  <u t="803101">the pudding was also made with the steamers</u>
  <u t="817446">heading to the airport</u>
  <u t="824904">enjoying the last view of Oita</u>
  <u t="849877">Tokyo skytree</u>
  <u t="857317">finally arrived in Tokyo!</u>
  <u t="862795">really enjoyed the trip to Oita, but feels good to be back home!</u>
  <u t="876030">time to use my souvenir</u>
  <u t="921523">I'm using my favourite essence 'green citus blend'</u>
  </text>
