<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="aA-48GJMAwY" uploader="Project Happiness " channel="Project Happiness " likes="43162" title="VIVERE CON GLI ULTIMI CACCIATORI CON LE AQUILE DELLA MONGOLIA 🇲🇳" year="2024" month="11" day="11" date="20241111" date_ts="1731328207" is_ac="false">
  <u t="81666">An adventure is about to begin that is one of a kind because the men behind me</u>
  <u t="85766">are the last eagle hunters in the world.</u>
  <u t="88066">Sit back and relax because you are about to embark on an adventure to discover how the concept of happiness changes</u>
  <u t="93666">at the edges of the world.</u>
  <u t="99400">My name is Giuseppe and I have a mission to travel the world</u>
  <u t="102466">to meet the most extraordinary people on the planet and ask them a simple question: What is happiness to you?</u>
  <u t="109733">Welcome to the “Happiness Project”.</u>
  <u t="116600">In the heart of the vast steppes of Western Mongolia live the Kazakhs,</u>
  <u t="120900">a group of legendary hunters. These nomads are descendants of ancient tribes of Central Asia.</u>
  <u t="126666">For over 2000 years, they have perfected the art of hunting with one of the most majestic and powerful birds of prey in the world,</u>
  <u t="133966">the golden eagles.</u>
  <u t="135400">These eagle hunters, called “berkutchi”, train the eagle chicks from their early months of life,</u>
  <u t="140400">establishing a deep bond with their loyal companions.</u>
  <u t="143766">The eagles, trained to hunt foxes and other small animals, become inseparable companions,</u>
  <u t="149566">capable of executing complex hunting maneuvers under the expert guidance of their trainers.</u>
  <u t="154900">However, this ancient tradition is in danger.</u>
  <u t="158400">The berkutchi are disappearing, as the younger generation prefers the promises of the city over eagle hunting</u>
  <u t="164233">and the reduction of natural prey caused by climate change further threatens this practice.</u>
  <u t="170766">Batu and his son Rinat are among the last eagle hunters of the Altai region of Mongolia</u>
  <u t="175733">they welcomed us into their family to show the world their culture, making it immortal so it will never disappear.</u>
  <u t="184033">To become a true hunter one must capture their own eagle with bare hands.</u>
  <u t="189266">The rite of passage that requires courage and skill. The steep peaks of the Altai are full of dangers.</u>
  <u t="195900">The berkutchi risk their lives to reach the nest.</u>
  <u t="205266">There is a nest up there.</u>
  <u t="208766">It is from that nest that Rinat took his chick. We climbed that peak with a rope. It is very, very dangerous!</u>
  <u t="223900">But the harder it is to reach, the more powerful the eagle will be. That's how we decide. When the eggs hatch in the spring, the best hunters capture the best eagles.</u>
  <u t="235033">And a chick taken directly from the nest can be trained more quickly, that's why we take such risks.</u>
  <u t="246900">Batu passionately tells me about the techniques they use to create a bond with the chick from its earliest days.</u>
  <u t="252766">It must be immediately exposed to the sounds and smells of humans, learning to recognize them as part of its new habitat.</u>
  <u t="258900">Trust is fundamental.</u>
  <u t="260400">The eagle must learn to trust its trainer to feel safe and willing to help him hunt.</u>
  <u t="265966">For this reason, they dedicate hours every day to feeding, caring for, and even talking to the eagle,</u>
  <u t="271533">which becomes, in all respects, part of the family.</u>
  <u t="275233">You must take care of your eagle as you would your own child.</u>
  <u t="281533">And I see these birds as my children.</u>
  <u t="285066">My husband mainly takes care of them, but I am always happy to help when he is not around.</u>
  <u t="293800">It's nice to follow and honor our tradition.</u>
  <u t="296300">In my home village, we never had eagles, but the elders here have been training them for centuries.</u>
  <u t="305800">My husband was his grandfather’s disciple. He learned from one of the best.</u>
  <u t="314266">And now he is among the best hunters.</u>
  <u t="319233">Our children admire him a lot, especially Rinat who wants to follow in his father's footsteps and is learning about the eagles.</u>
  <u t="329966">I like the idea of having an eagle in our house.</u>
  <u t="334566">Are you worried when your husband and son go hunting?</u>
  <u t="338766">Of course, I worry. What if they encounter some fierce animal?</u>
  <u t="343566">And if they lose their eagles? What if they get bitten when capturing an animal? I worry a lot about my son, but then I think this is the life of a hunter.</u>
  <u t="353466">In the autumn months, the chick begins a long training process that requires patience and dedication.</u>
  <u t="359533">This process is essential to teach one of the planet's deadliest predators to hunt</u>
  <u t="364900">and then to return trustingly to the trainer's arm.</u>
  <u t="368666">They are saddling the horses to go hunting.</u>
  <u t="371666">This is the... typical Kazakh saddle.</u>
  <u t="374900">They are very narrow, very small, and very uncomfortable,</u>
  <u t="378666">but the peculiarity of these is that they have an armrest where</u>
  <u t="384066">the hunter can rest his arm when holding the eagle, because the eagle weighs dozens of kilos,</u>
  <u t="389966">so he can't always hold it like this,</u>
  <u t="391400">it would be unthinkable, but it is almost invisible because when you see him, you see him proud,</u>
  <u t="397600">with his arm extended forward, but it is resting, relaxed, ready for action, to release the eagle into the air.</u>
  <u t="404666">Now they are... they are putting it on.</u>
  <u t="417666">Cho, cho, cho, cho.</u>
  <u t="420000">We can do it.</u>
  <u t="420700">But before we start this great adventure, I want to give you some advice on how to avoid being spied on online.</u>
  <u t="426166">If you're not using a VPN while watching this video,</u>
  <u t="429400">then your IP address, browsing history, location, and other sensitive personal data</u>
  <u t="434566">are, at best, visible to advertisers</u>
  <u t="437600">who will bombard you with ads</u>
  <u t="439666">or, unfortunately, to cybercriminals.</u>
  <u t="441766">To protect yourself, I’ve left a link below this video</u>
  <u t="444600">to try NordVPN’s new "Threat Protection Pro,"</u>
  <u t="447666">which allows you to protect up to 10 devices with a single subscription</u>
  <u t="451766">and make your connection and your family’s connection invisible,</u>
  <u t="454766">hiding your IP and all your personal information from malicious entities.</u>
  <u t="458900">For example, I always keep it active on my phone and PC</u>
  <u t="462266">because it not only protects all my passwords but also checks the files I download</u>
  <u t="465566">and alerts me if they contain malware.</u>
  <u t="467400">It even blocks me in time if I try to access harmful websites</u>
  <u t="470766">that could steal my data and infect my device with viruses.</u>
  <u t="474466">I recommend taking advantage of the exclusive "Black Friday" discount</u>
  <u t="478166">plus 4 extra months on the two-year plans,</u>
  <u t="480466">and as if that weren't enough, you can try NordVPN for 30 days</u>
  <u t="484066">and get a refund if you’re not satisfied.</u>
  <u t="486466">As always, I’m leaving a link in the description to try NordVPN</u>
  <u t="489366">with the best offer on the market, and now we can get started.</u>
  <u t="494166">The training requires entire days, they climb the highest peaks on horseback</u>
  <u t="498600">to allow the eagle to reach the right altitude and then dive down on the prey.</u>
  <u t="504066">These two chicks are about a year old, and to teach them to hunt, they start using a lure,</u>
  <u t="509566">usually a piece of meat tied to a rope, and every time the eagle grabs the lure</u>
  <u t="514300">it is rewarded with a piece of meat.</u>
  <u t="516166">As the eagle becomes more confident, the hunter gradually increases the distance between the eagle and the lure.</u>
  <u t="521933">This repetitive exercise helps the eagle develop strength and endurance in its wings,</u>
  <u t="527233">improving its flight capability.</u>
  <u t="530300">It is truly majestic.</u>
  <u t="532033">Imagine that depending on the year these eagles were born, they are given a name, so this eagle is one year old and is called Balapan</u>
  <u t="540933">and every hunter's eagle around here that is one year old has the same name.</u>
  <u t="545866">This one, for example, however,</u>
  <u t="547100">has a peculiarity that it is missing some, some feathers here below, the lower plumage...</u>
  <u t="553766">because it was attacked by a red fox during a confrontation, when it was trying to hunt a... a red fox.</u>
  <u t="560100">It is missing some feathers here and also a claw.</u>
  <u t="563433">It is said that each claw of an eagle is equivalent to the strength of a man, so</u>
  <u t="568766">it has a very strong grip when it grabs the prey.</u>
  <u t="572100">This is the eagle's hood,</u>
  <u t="573233">it is called “Tomaga” in Kazakh and it is custom-made for each eagle.</u>
  <u t="578233">It is used to keep them calm during trips, during the journey,</u>
  <u t="582600">the journey to find the perfect spot, and then release it, once the hood is removed,</u>
  <u t="587733">the eagle can see up to two kilometers away and be able to spot if there are any prey to hunt.</u>
  <u t="594600">See? As soon as I take off the hood, it wants to fly.</u>
  <u t="599933">See how it moves?</u>
  <u t="602166">It is the greatest, the most sacred, it is the most powerful bird in nature.</u>
  <u t="606233">It is an infallible predator and does not suffer from our winter's cold.</u>
  <u t="613233">That's why for us the eagle is the queen of the skies.</u>
  <u t="617933">Moreover, it is very determined.</u>
  <u t="620300">The fact that it can tolerate living with a hat on its head is proof of that.</u>
  <u t="626433">I admire it for its strength and patience.</u>
  <u t="630933">Look how proud it is.</u>
  <u t="635233">It can hunt anything it sets its eyes on.</u>
  <u t="639733">Any animal, including a fox, would be hunted mercilessly by an eagle.</u>
  <u t="644600">What do you hunt with your eagle?</u>
  <u t="647100">The largest animal I can capture with an eagle is a fox.</u>
  <u t="650933">Rusty-spotted cats, corsac foxes, and rabbits. Animals like these.</u>
  <u t="658533">Have you ever been injured by your eagles?</u>
  <u t="662800">The eagle is a hunting bird. If you don't train it well with meat, it can easily harm you.</u>
  <u t="669300">It can grab your face, leg, or arm. There was only one time it grabbed my arm.</u>
  <u t="676166">It was a wild eagle; I was feeding it, and that’s when it pierced my arm with its talon. I was lucky not to lose my arm.</u>
  <u t="685266">According to tradition, I release them when they become mothers, when they can lay eggs.</u>
  <u t="690733">I will release her in five years. Only when it is warm, preferably in May, when there is plenty of food around.</u>
  <u t="700266">I will give her the last meal, tie a white handkerchief on her leg, and release her from the mountain top.</u>
  <u t="704933">Of course, it is always difficult to let them go. After spending 5 or 6 years together all the time.</u>
  <u t="711066">But it is nature that decides, and I have to do it. She must reproduce and be free. It will be really hard to let her go.</u>
  <u t="725600">Shout! Call her!</u>
  <u t="733733">Okay, then, catch her!</u>
  <u t="745233">Now!</u>
  <u t="764833">Okay... you must always be careful</u>
  <u t="767633">of the eagle's wingspan because, it doesn't seem like it, but it's a couple of meters.</u>
  <u t="773700">Now it's Rinat's turn</u>
  <u t="775900">he has to release the eagle so that it lands on his father's arm.</u>
  <u t="782566">Now we will see him in action, it is one of his first times, so he is a bit excited, but...</u>
  <u t="788500">we are happy to be here to see him.</u>
  <u t="791066">Today we are learning to call a chick, my father is right there trying to call it.</u>
  <u t="797833">I love walking in the mountains with an eagle. It excites me, and I enjoy watching it hunt animals.</u>
  <u t="803966">What do you like most about hunting with the eagle?</u>
  <u t="807633">When my eagle flies in the sky, I feel free too. I feel like I am flying as well. It makes me very happy.</u>
  <u t="818700">Now I will remove the hood so my father can call her.</u>
  <u t="824266">Call her!</u>
  <u t="832066">He did it, he did it</u>
  <u t="835966">Great!</u>
  <u t="838300">She landed exactly on his father's arm,</u>
  <u t="841133">and now his father is giving her a piece of meat to reward her.</u>
  <u t="845266">For doing a good job.</u>
  <u t="849400">It feels a bit like when we used to play football as kids, right?</u>
  <u t="852600">where you had a goal, but the goal had no nets, so every time you scored you had to go get the ball.</u>
  <u t="857633">Now it is the same, he released the eagle, and every time he has to go get it, bring it back up, and try again.</u>
  <u t="863433">This is the training.</u>
  <u t="867766">I don't know how they got into this situation, but... the adrenaline is high.</u>
  <u t="876266">Let's go</u>
  <u t="883066">Go, go, go!</u>
  <u t="888266">First attempt failed. Because I held</u>
  <u t="891600">I held the... the string attached to the legs too tightly, so... it didn't take off.</u>
  <u t="898700">Let's try again.</u>
  <u t="900900">Second attempt.</u>
  <u t="904333">Fly, fly.</u>
  <u t="976500">I did it! My heart is pounding... Beautiful!... Wow!.</u>
  <u t="983566">It's extraordinary, the power of the talons can be felt</u>
  <u t="986400">almost even through this special glove made of yak leather, which is actually very tough.</u>
  <u t="992466">It feels almost... almost like wood, but I could feel the might of the talons' power even through it.</u>
  <u t="998466">That's why my heart was pounding because when I released her, she looked into my eyes</u>
  <u t="1003333">and I thought, now instead of flying down, she will attack me. Clearly she is a predator,</u>
  <u t="1008133">if she ever attacked a man it wouldn't end well.</u>
  <u t="1012833">It's impossible not to be enchanted by the grace and power of the eagles in flight, but also by the mastery of the hunters</u>
  <u t="1018966">who guide them with pride.</u>
  <u t="1020833">The ancient bond between the berkutchi and their eagles evokes images of past generations of hunters.</u>
  <u t="1026766">Every gesture, every rite, seems suspended in a timeless era, which, however, might vanish after Rinat.</u>
  <u t="1034466">It is a tradition that has been passed down to us by our ancestors.</u>
  <u t="1038266">My grandfather trained eagles, and I had the honor of learning from him.</u>
  <u t="1043566">My father was also a hunter. We all hunted together.</u>
  <u t="1047566">But now I am the only one left, and I hunt alone or with my son.</u>
  <u t="1051333">My only purpose is to pass on the tradition of our ancestors.</u>
  <u t="1055566">Among my children, he is the most skilled with the eagles. When he was born, I already knew he would be the chosen one to become a hunter.</u>
  <u t="1064066">The proof was when he managed to capture his chick and became a true hunter.</u>
  <u t="1071633">It makes me so proud to have him by my side and that one day he will pass on our traditions.</u>
  <u t="1075766">Our responsibility in this life is to live in symbiosis with the eagles.</u>
  <u t="1079700">I had to teach my son how to stroke her, how to talk to her, how to calm her.</u>
  <u t="1084833">The first year he was very scared, but then they became friends, and now the eagle trusts him. They are like brothers.</u>
  <u t="1093066">Then I had to teach him how to ride a horse. For us, it is very important.</u>
  <u t="1098766">We are united by a bond of brotherhood with our horse as well.</u>
  <u t="1103633">And the biggest challenge is to teach your eagle to land on your arm while you are riding.</u>
  <u t="1108900">You must know the eagle and the horse so well that you become together a great sacred animal.</u>
  <u t="1115766">This is how you become a true hunter.</u>
  <u t="1119566">I am teaching all this to Rinat so that he can carry on the traditions and not let them disappear.</u>
  <u t="1124966">Being an eagle hunter for us is like being connected to all the ancestors before us.</u>
  <u t="1131800">We have never been born and we have never died. We are a single hunter who has lived forever and will live forever through the ages.</u>
  <u t="1139900">And this for me is happiness: having a horse under me and an eagle on my arm.</u>
  <u t="1145833">Making my ancestors proud and being a fearless hunter.</u>
  <u t="1149133">You know, here it is said: "a man without a horse is like a bird without wings."</u>
  <u t="1156333">As long as I have a horse to ride and an eagle to hunt with, I will be the happiest person in the world!</u>
  <u t="1164833">Batu's happiness</u>
  <u t="1166066">is so natural, so pure, exactly like the flight of his eagles in the sky.</u>
  <u t="1171566">There is no conflict between his dreams and his reality, because as long as he is an eagle hunter,</u>
  <u t="1176200">like his ancestors were, as his son is destined to be, he will have his happiness.</u>
  <u t="1181766">Every day lived in this way for him is a tribute to his ancestors in his millennial heritage,</u>
  <u t="1187400">which I hope Rinat can protect and pass on to future generations</u>
  <u t="1192300">with a testament of eternal happiness.</u>
  </text>
