<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<text id="KO1s1uMqgeM" uploader="Luisito Comunica" channel="Luisito Comunica" likes="413465" title="¿En verdad COREA DEL SUR es tan increíble como pensamos? | Seúl 🇰🇷" year="2022" month="7" day="11" date="20220711" is_ac="false">
  <u t="0">Look at this, it's beautiful and how crazy as everybody look at the world on their phones.</u>
  <u t="4803">A lot of people, many stores, trade of all kinds, colors, signs, I'm liking this.</u>
  <u t="12810">[Music]</u>
  <u t="27085">Friends, friends! (Speaks korean) that was Korean for "hello friends, welcome to South Korea"</u>
  <u t="37865">That's right, that's right, this is an adventure I've been looking forward to do</u>
  <u t="42900">for several years now- When I found out that South Korea was open again to receive tourists</u>
  <u t="48734">I bought my ticket at that very moment and here we are in Seoul capital of South Korea</u>
  <u t="55050">Known for being the technology capital of the world</u>
  <u t="59034">South Korea as of the date I record this, has a population of just over 51 million people</u>
  <u t="64427">Its official language is Korean , its currency is the Korean Won which the conversion is a little bit complicated</u>
  <u t="72435">But it would be something like 10,000 won is 7.50 DLLS</u>
  <u t="77049">A very famous country for its music, for its not so recent boom in the K-Pop</u>
  <u t="83117">For its television series the K-Drama,</u>
  <u t="85703">Its cinema has also for some time now has also made a lot of noise</u>
  <u t="89456">South Korea is also known for its makeup</u>
  <u t="92165">For their fashion</u>
  <u t="93025">For their technology, for their their gastronomy</u>
  <u t="95252">It goes without saying this is going to be a great epic adventure</u>
  <u t="99974">We start this trip in Seoul the capital city, in the area of Dongdaemun which is this beauty that is at my backs</u>
  <u t="107725">The correct pronunciation is... (Speaks korean) Did I say it right?</u>
  <u t="111989">Today we are going to give an overview, let's let us be surprised by the first impressions we get from this beautiful territory</u>
  <u t="119645">Normally I would say "let's hit it" but we're in Korea so we're saying (Speaks korean)</u>
  <u t="123950">[Music]</u>
  <u t="130047">So let's hit it, let's hit it. Let's get to know the subway, sounds good? Sounds like a good idea?</u>
  <u t="135048">Something tells me that the subway here is sure to be really awesome.</u>
  <u t="139247">I really like that the signs are lights</u>
  <u t="142869">We are going to cover up the sign, oh no! Where's the sign?</u>
  <u t="145690">Was erased? What happened? No... It's a reflector</u>
  <u t="149153">Well, let's go, let's go, let's meet</u>
  <u t="151125">This is very cool!</u>
  <u t="154033">Most of the subway stations in fact are not just that</u>
  <u t="157615">They're also some kind of small shopping malls</u>
  <u t="160741">Actually, they're not that small</u>
  <u t="163175">Threre's a few that look like real massive shopping malls, there are from three floors down</u>
  <u t="169332">You can really found every brand you can think of, cheap or expensive, every kind</u>
  <u t="173026">It's a really impressive trade happening here</u>
  <u t="177401">Here we're seeing an example, we found a coffee shop, convenience store, storage areas for luggage, etc. etc.</u>
  <u t="188866">But here, this goes on all the way there, and really you'll find everything</u>
  <u t="193837">From a portable electric fan to Gucci shoes</u>
  <u t="197117">You can find a lot of things</u>
  <u t="198461">In the subways of seoul</u>
  <u t="200229">By the way, since we're here, let's quickly see what's there in a convenience store</u>
  <u t="204851">Obviously, lots and lots of energy drinks</u>
  <u t="207248">See the variaty of energy drinks</u>
  <u t="209172">It's real common on East Asia, they really like energy drinks</u>
  <u t="214124">Here there are delicacies of all kinds</u>
  <u t="216350">Some little coffee</u>
  <u t="218552">Look, here we're also buying the subway cards</u>
  <u t="222267">How do you say "thank you"? (Speaks korean)</u>
  <u t="225876">Is difficult, Korean is difficult</u>
  <u t="227401">See I picked the casanova bear one</u>
  <u t="230092">OMG! Check how many instant soups</u>
  <u t="233859">Yum! Like this video if you would like a video tasting only of instant korean soups</u>
  <u t="239603">It will make a grat video and pleasing too</u>
  <u t="242375">I can't wait</u>
  <u t="243038">Oh here, there's an oreo fever, they have different flavors look</u>
  <u t="247376">A blue one, triple chocolate, the classic ones, red velvet cake,</u>
  <u t="252464">With more chocolate, a complete fever and that this one only a little shop</u>
  <u t="256058">Look at these Cheetos, I already want to try this, uff!</u>
  <u t="259929">I have to make a special video about convenience stores, right?</u>
  <u t="262008">Yes, we agree, a convenience store video is coming soon</u>
  <u t="266006">This is how the card is recharged at South Korea</u>
  <u t="269323">By the way, meet Jeks, she's our guide. Say hi, my dear Jeks</u>
  <u t="273974">Yeah! Our dear Jeks</u>
  <u t="275551">An we're with Arisita, also</u>
  <u t="277318">- Here's my subway card</u>
  <u t="278476">This cards have animals, little animals</u>
  <u t="280601">So check this, we put the card in here, right? It goes there</u>
  <u t="285303">And you recharge it, how much you want? 10</u>
  <u t="288151">I remembered how to say it</u>
  <u t="290826">Then I stuck my hand</u>
  <u t="292295">By the way, this how money looks like</u>
  <u t="293194">This guy's name is Sejong, who is one of the creators of korean language, ok?</u>
  <u t="298751">We put this in here</u>
  <u t="299651">Here you go</u>
  <u t="300616">There it is!</u>
  <u t="301209">So here's recharging, gluck, gluck, gluck</u>
  <u t="304028">One moment please, your card is recharging</u>
  <u t="306742">And there you go</u>
  <u t="308626">So now we'll go deep inside the city</u>
  <u t="311531">Check this, we trake our card and put it on top</u>
  <u t="314436">Ohhh...</u>
  <u t="316890">And look at this, the doors on the subway get completly closed</u>
  <u t="321676">Wow! This, of course, is to prevent many things, to prevent accidents, to prevent people from going on the tracks</u>
  <u t="329951">Very unfortunate things that sadly do happen</u>
  <u t="332647">We have here some of the little beverage machines just like the ones in Japan</u>
  <u t="336506">See this reminds me a lot a lot a lot of Japan</u>
  <u t="338416">And, it's a very curious fact that I love, I've told it many times in the channel</u>
  <u t="343007">Most of the garbage cans that we go to see will be transparent this is because many years ago</u>
  <u t="350245">In Japan there were a terrorist attack in which some gas bombs were placed in the garbage dumps and many people died</u>
  <u t="357382">So that's why the garbage cans are transparent in many in many east asian countries</u>
  <u t="361041">What do you think? Uh?</u>
  <u t="361860">Maybe you already seen it in the channel, I have told it many times but it's very interesting and above all, it's a very disturbed data</u>
  <u t="368004">The wagon has arrived, the wagon has arrived,</u>
  <u t="370579">Let's go up!</u>
  <u t="372056">Wow! Hey it's like a very wide wagon</u>
  <u t="376067">How can I show it to you? How can I make an example?</u>
  <u t="378672">Maybe with steps, let's check, from here to there is one, two, three, oh!</u>
  <u t="383624">Four, five,</u>
  <u t="385021">There's eight steps, about 2,50 meters, approx.</u>
  <u t="389545">Around 2.50 meters wide, yeah, it's a very wide wagon, very clean, very pretty</u>
  <u t="394796">And above all, it's really quiet</u>
  <u t="397417">I even feel bad speaking this loud</u>
  <u t="399297">It's a calm, relaxed, wagon and very very clean</u>
  <u t="403511">It's important to mention that you won't always find it like this clean, everyone sittng</u>
  <u t="410189">How do I open this? Like this?</u>
  <u t="412148">I'm told that at rush hour, you get to find a lot of people standing around, it's not this quiet all the time cubans how many lines how</u>
  <u t="419564">But, I think still is a great example of how this works</u>
  <u t="421987">Hey! Check this out! How nice and how crazy that everybody is on their phones</u>
  <u t="426572">Wich means there's goog signal down here on the subway</u>
  <u t="431845">We even have open Wi-Fi down here for free use</u>
  <u t="435739">You pay around 1,200 wons for every subway ticket</u>
  <u t="440838">Wich is around .85 cents of a dollar</u>
  <u t="443058">Around 19 mexican pesos</u>
  <u t="445559">The subway actually covers most of South Korean capital surface</u>
  <u t="449262">Check this</u>
  <u t="450577">Look how many lines, how many stations</u>
  <u t="453963">What do you think, uh? Take a look</u>
  <u t="455963">Very pretty</u>
  <u t="457142">Very tidy</u>
  <u t="458067">Very nice</u>
  <u t="458709">Seoul's subway, South Korea's capital</u>
  <u t="461912">(MUSIC)</u>
  <u t="472575">And see, in this subway station you can better appreciate what I was telling you, check this!</u>
  <u t="477720">Ok, so the subway is over there, ok? We're coming from over there, we walk nothing, and see here, right here</u>
  <u t="483300">The subway turns into a whole shopping mall, a whole big mall, take a look</u>
  <u t="488700">Wow! Do you want a french bread? Some discount shoes or you want a dress or a blouse?</u>
  <u t="497048">Do you want? Well, whatever you want, really this one it's huge, goes way beyond there</u>
  <u t="502470">There and there. It's massive and it's not a one time thing, really</u>
  <u t="507120">This happens in many stations, near from where we're staying</u>
  <u t="511650">There's like two, right? Two that are very huge. It's really impressive and you get to see a lot of this</u>
  <u t="516810">In Japan and in China then I guess it's something like East Asian countries</u>
  <u t="521820">The developed countries in this part of the world</u>
  <u t="524150">Wow! Just look at it! The beauty shops</u>
  <u t="527517">It's very interesting, you know, like to be walking in an eternal japanese store, I feel like that</u>
  <u t="535415">Every store looks pretty much the same for my very occidental eyes</u>
  <u t="538787">Anothe beauty store over here</u>
  <u t="540972">Some clothes, looks very pretty</u>
  <u t="542972">Baby clothes</u>
  <u t="544009">Wow!</u>
  <u t="544915">It seems to go on and on and on and on and on and on</u>
  <u t="548255">[Music]</u>
  <u t="559238">Here's a couple of fun facts about South Korea</u>
  <u t="562981">Fact number 1: People here are one year older</u>
  <u t="567073">Because when they are born they are already born being 1 year old, so if you have a friend in South Korea</u>
  <u t="574520">Who is exactly the same age as you are, if you are 17 he's going to be 18</u>
  <u t="577989">If you're 34 he's going to be 35</u>
  <u t="580304">This is so confusing, they're about to take it down</u>
  <u t="583590">They're about to revoke</u>
  <u t="585337">Maybe for next year it can change</u>
  <u t="587682">Fun fact number 2: did you know that p*rn is illegal in South Korea</u>
  <u t="593593">It's a true fact, completely true and real, see here we try to open a website</u>
  <u t="599834">And it comes up an ad that says this is illegal, is forbidden because the site is improper</u>
  <u t="605532">The principle for this is that it is believed that the young people should focus on their studies one hundred</u>
  <u t="611950">And not be distracted by watching p*rn on a screen</u>
  <u t="615178">I think it's very curious and a little bit hilarious</u>
  <u t="617928">I would imagine that the young people here just use a vpn on their phone and just like that, problem solved! It's not complicated at all</u>
  <u t="625153">Well, come over here, now we come to Gangnam</u>
  <u t="630105">There it is, Gangnam style the little dance, of course</u>
  <u t="634775">Remember you guys the Gangnam Style? This super macro trend, like a real world trend of about 10 years ago Opppa gangnam style</u>
  <u t="643174">And the guy danced this way, it was so popular he has his own monument in the Gangnam neighborhood</u>
  <u t="649959">In fact, the song is done for the district of Gangnam in Seoul</u>
  <u t="654275">Which is like one of the most wealthy districts here, the most fancy.</u>
  <u t="659836">And wow! Gangnam district is divine, a lot of people, a lot of stores, trade of all kinds, colorful signs</u>
  <u t="669092">I am liking here! Look at this! Look at this streets, see these buildings</u>
  <u t="673746">I think still my favorite area of the ones we've seen if I ever get too crazy and want to move to South Korea, Gangnam is where I want to live, we'll be here</u>
  <u t="682402">Here I will be an outsider in South Korea</u>
  <u t="684757">Something I have to mention, people in South Korea smoke a lot, really</u>
  <u t="689804">In the convenience stores you see a lot of variety of cigarettes, they smoke a lot, but you can't smoke anywhere in the streets but only in designated areas</u>
  <u t="696384">See, this is one of them, we are going to enter</u>
  <u t="699790">So check this, here people come have a little smoke, the vaporizer, whatever and off you go</u>
  <u t="705000">But only in these designated spaces</u>
  <u t="707959">No, no, really I declare myself a fan of the Gangnam area.</u>
  <u t="711506">Check this, it's full of bars and restaurants,</u>
  <u t="714397">They say that here at night is where the fun's at, here are the bars here are the nightclubs here is the life</u>
  <u t="720485">Yes yes this is my area, this is my environment I want to take pictures in every corner</u>
  <u t="725610">Gangnam is my zone, ok? So far, Gangnam is gaining a space in my heart in Seoul</u>
  <u t="731970">(Music)</u>
  <u t="736390">Oh my god! Check this tremendous structure, this is Seoul's digital plaza</u>
  <u t="743470">It's arquitechture is impressive, they always have very interesting exhibits, but above all I find it fascinating</u>
  <u t="748900">Because it tells us an interesting part of the history of South Korea. You will see:</u>
  <u t="754360">South Korea, although it doesn't look like it at all, is a relatively relatively a very new country. We are talking about</u>
  <u t="760540">They gained their independence in 1945 when the armed forces of the</u>
  <u t="767260">Japan surrendered in 1945. Wow! less than 100 years of being fully independent and the reason</u>
  <u t="775450">This place tells us an important part of that history, as you will see, this used to be a stadium a very very symbolic baseball stadium</u>
  <u t="783623">Since many, many, many years ago.</u>
  <u t="785543">It used to have a Japanese name, and after the Japanese retired</u>
  <u t="789951">It was renamed to the Seoul stadium, then to the Dongdaemun stadium, which is the area</u>
  <u t="794706">And now it has became a public square, for that people come here to hang out and be amazed with the Digital Square displays</u>
  <u t="803027">One of the architects in charge of the design of this Square was Zaha Hadid, a super famous Iraqi architect, who lost her life a few years ago</u>
  <u t="810653">And is now one of the great icons of Seoul</u>
  <u t="814861">Hey, folks who are watching this video, maybe you think you have seen big shopping malls, well I can assure you that they are not as big as those in South Korea</u>
  <u t="822778">Check this out!</u>
  <u t="826155">Wow! How many floors are those? Filled with just stores. Check this style and design</u>
  <u t="833800">Not even Dubai dared to so much</u>
  <u t="835952">I have gone to the supposedly world's largest mall in Dubai</u>
  <u t="838427">I think this is more shocking, I don't know, I don't know</u>
  <u t="841501">[Music]</u>
  <u t="850757">Uff! So, we had a few drinks, we had a delicious dinner. Everything is really fascinating, even going to the bar is a very interesting experience</u>
  <u t="859853">How they interact, wow! I'm fascinated by it all</u>
  <u t="863080">I'm stunned, I really want to record everything, really</u>
  <u t="867022">So stay tuned because there are a lot of super interesting videos coming of this journey, that I'm sure it's going to fascinate all of us equally</u>
  <u t="876662">Let me know anyway if you have any suggestions of something I should see here in South Korea, I'm going to be a while</u>
  <u t="882400">I'm going to be a little over a month here</u>
  <u t="884119">So if you have any suggestions, video ideas, whatever, leave them below at comments and I will do my best to make them</u>
  <u t="891385">Thanks for joining me, it was an excellent first day in South Korea, in the beautiful city of Seoul</u>
  <u t="897123">I'm really tired, I have to go to rest to make the most of tomorrow</u>
  <u t="901563">Of course we will see each other, as usual, in a few days with a new video. I proceed to try to say goodbye in Korean</u>
  <u t="908680">[Music]</u>
  </text>
